<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-18T00:53:04.537Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-18T00:53:04.537Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing MC²: Securely perform analytics and machine learning on confidential data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chester/announcing-mc-securely-perform-analytics-and-machine-learning-on-confidential-data-3i7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chester/announcing-mc-securely-perform-analytics-and-machine-learning-on-confidential-data-3i7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T00:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the initial release of the open source MC2 Project, a collection of tools for computing and collaborating on confidential data. Developed by our team in the UC Berkeley RISELab, MC2 (Multi-Party Collaboration and Coopetition) enables rich analytics and machine learning on encrypted data, ensuring that data remains concealed even when it’s being processed. The data in use remains hidden from the server running the job, allowing confidential workloads to be offloaded to untrusted third parties or cloud providers. This not only protects confidential data from intrusions, but also enables secure collaboration -- multiple data owners can jointly run analytics or ML on their collective data, without explicitly revealing their individual data to anyone else: not even a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chester Leung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protected Routes (Next js & CRA) simple but efficient]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atapg/protected-routes-next-js-cra-simple-but-efficient-2f7o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atapg/protected-routes-next-js-cra-simple-but-efficient-2f7o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T00:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes we need to hide pages/routes from the user and disabling their accessibility to those pages. 
1.I will start with create-react-app
// Create a new app
npx create-react-app route-app react-router-dom

// Run the created app
cd route-app
yarn start

// http://localhost:3000

2.In our main component(App.js) we will define our routes
import ProtectedRoute from './ProtectedRoute'
import { BrowserRouter, Switch, Route } from 'react-router-dom'

export default App = () => {
   return(
      <BrowserRouter>
        <Switch>
          <Route exact path='/posts' component={Home} />
          <ProtectedRoute exact path='/login' component={Login} />
          <Route path='/' component={NotFound} /> 
          //this is 404 page btw - no "exact" prop
        </Switch>
      </BrowserRouter>
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ata Parvin Ghods</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Disable a Repository in Azure DevOps (Azure Repos)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/how-to-disable-a-repository-in-azure-devops-azure-repos-3i65</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/how-to-disable-a-repository-in-azure-devops-azure-repos-3i65"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T00:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I'm going to show you how to disable a repository in Azure DevOps and prevent users from accessing its contents.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/G_um1mm7LiM
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
Before we talk about how to disable a repo, why would you want to do it?
Well, for example you may want to disable a repository because you found a secret in it. Or a third-party scanning tool found the repository to be out of compliance.
In such cases, you may want to temporarily disable the repository while you work to resolve the issue.
Let's see now how to disable a repo. It is very easy.
Just go to the Project Settings, scroll down to the Repositories section and enter it, then click on the specific repo you want to Disable. In the settings, you have the Disable Repo switch

When a repo is disabled, it still shows up in the list of repos, however no one can access or update its content.
And you would also see a message saying that the repo has been disabled when they try to access it in the Azure Repos UI.

And of course after the necessary mitigation steps have been taken, disabled repositories can be re-enabled using the same setting.
Final note: you can disable a repository only if you are either admin or owner, or you have the Delete repository permissions.
Let me know in the comment section below if you think this is useful and if you've ever been in a situation in which you could have disabled a repo.
Like, share and follow me 🚀 for more content:
📽 YouTube
Buy me a coffee
Patreon
CoderDave.io Website
Merch
Facebook page
GitHub
Twitter
LinkedIn
Podcast]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Virtual DOM work? (Build your own)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aidenybai/how-does-virtual-dom-work-b74</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aidenybai/how-does-virtual-dom-work-b74"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T23:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plug: I help develop million: <1kb virtual DOM - it's fast!
The virtual DOM is a tree of virtual nodes that represents what the DOM looks like. virtual nodes are light, stateless, and are JavaScript objects that only contain necessary fields. virtual nodes can be assembled into trees, and "diffed" to make pinpoint changes to the DOM.
The reasoning behind this is because modification and access of DOM nodes is computationally expensive. A diff between virtual nodes, accessing the DOM only for modification, is the premise of virtual DOM. It avoids the DOM as much as possible, favoring plain JavaScript objects instead, making reading and writing much cheaper.
The Million virtual DOM contains three main functions: m, createElement, patch. To completely understand how virtual DOM works, let's t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aiden Bai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Mock Data for an Angular list view component]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michaelahoffman/making-mock-data-for-an-angular-list-view-component-41op</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michaelahoffman/making-mock-data-for-an-angular-list-view-component-41op"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T23:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I’m going to start the process of making a prototype using mock data. My goal at the end of the series is to have quickly mocked data for a prototype while binding it to the UI. As a result, the data can be used across the app and there is only one point of maintenance. 
When I’m done with the series, I will have one data set that I can use to create demo components of my application.
If you are a front-end developer or designer who codes and working without the back-end API for a proof of concept or prototype in the browser, this is for you. In order to complete this tutorial, you’ll need to have a good understanding of HTML. And how to start an Angular application.
The skills in this series allow you to create demo content in your prototype. This is really useful for ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michaela Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Mock Data for an Angular list view component]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michaelahoffman/making-mock-data-for-an-angular-list-view-component-41op</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michaelahoffman/making-mock-data-for-an-angular-list-view-component-41op"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T23:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I’m going to start the process of making a prototype using mock data. My goal at the end of the series is to have quickly mocked data for a prototype while binding it to the UI. As a result, the data can be used across the app and there is only one point of maintenance. 
When I’m done with the series, I will have one data set that I can use to create demo components of my application.
If you are a front-end developer or designer who codes and working without the back-end API for a proof of concept or prototype in the browser, this is for you. In order to complete this tutorial, you’ll need to have a good understanding of HTML. And how to start an Angular application.
The skills in this series allow you to create demo content in your prototype. This is really useful for ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michaela Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures in Typescript - Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-stack-1h35</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-stack-1h35"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T22:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A stack uses LIFO (last-in-first-out) ordering, the most recent item added is the first item to be removed, just like a real stack.

A stack can be implemented using an array or a linked list, can be either fixed or dynamic size.
Push - Add an item to the top of the stack
Pop - Remove the top item from the stack
Peek - Return the top of the stack, without removing it.
isEmpty - Return true if the stack is empty.
isFull - Return true if the stack is full, used when the stack is fixed size.
Here's an implementation of a stack using an array, in Typescript an array doesn't have a fixed length, so the operation isFull is not required, however you can implement a stack with a fixed length and use that operation.
class Stack<T> {
  private array: T[] = [];

  pop(): T | undefined {
    if (this.isEmpty()) throw new EmptyStackException();

    return this.array.pop();
  }

  push(data: T): void {
    this.array.push(data);
  }

  peek(): T {
    if (this.isEmpty()) throw new EmptyStackException();

    return this.array[this.array.length - 1];
  }

  isEmpty(): boolean {
    return this.array.length === 0;
  }
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Borges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functional Programming Notes:]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rthefounding/functional-programming-notes-19j6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rthefounding/functional-programming-notes-19j6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T21:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Functional Programming, code is organized into smaller, basic functions that can be combined to build complex programs.
In these upcoming posts, you'll learn the core concepts of Functional Programming including pure functions, how to avoid mutations, and how to write cleaner code with methods like .map() and .filter().
Functional programming is a style of programming where solutions are simple, isolated functions, without any side effects outside of the function scope: INPUT -> PROCESS -> OUTPUT

Functional programming is about:
Isolated functions - there is no dependence on the state of the program, which includes global variables that are subject to change


Pure functions - the same input always gives the same output


Functions with limited side effects - any changes, or mutations,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an Instagram downloader API with Nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-an-instagram-downloader-api-with-nodejs-254p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-an-instagram-downloader-api-with-nodejs-254p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T20:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm Hossein, In this article, I'll show you how to create your Nodejs Instagram photo and image downloader.
npm init

After installation dependencies have done, Create an index.js file and put the codes below into it:
const axios = require('axios');
const { parse } = require("node-html-parser");

const instagramPostLink = "https://www.instagram.com/p/CD5um-vHA33/";

async function getPostLink(url) {

  url = url + 'embed' + '/captioned';


  let res = axios.get(url).then(async (response) => {
    const root = parse(response.data);

    let link = "";
    if (response.data.search("video_url") != -1)
      link = getVideoLinkFromHtml(response.data);
    else
      link = root.querySelector('img.EmbeddedMediaImage').getAttribute("src");





    while (link.search("&amp;") != -1) {
      link = link.replace("&amp;", "&");
    }
    let caption =await getCaptionFromHtml(response.data);

    return {link,caption};

  });

  return res;

}

async function getCaption(url) {


  url = url + 'embed' + '/captioned';

  let res = axios.get(url).then((response) => {

    let caption= getCaptionFromHtml(response.data);

    return caption;

  });

  return res;

}

async function getCaptionFromHtml(html) {


  const root = parse(html);

  let caption=root.querySelector('.Caption')?.text;
  if(caption == undefined)
      caption="No caption";

  caption=caption.replace("view all comments","");
  return caption;

}

function getVideoLinkFromHtml(html) {
  let crop = "{\"" + html.substring(html.search("video_url"), html.search("video_url") + 1000);

  crop = crop.substring(0, crop.search(",")) + "}";

  return JSON.parse(crop).video_url;
}

(async ()=>{
    await getPostLink(instagramPostLink);
})();


Some trouble with download the Instagram app is it needs a login, So we are use the embed Instagram posts to download that. 
Do you like to create animated emojis for your website? Click this link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>h_mobarakian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird rants of a new Devops + Backend engineer 😤 [18 June 21]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uds5501/weird-rants-of-a-new-devops-backend-engineer-18-june-21-4on</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uds5501/weird-rants-of-a-new-devops-backend-engineer-18-june-21-4on"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T18:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the weird notes of a new DevOps and Backend engineer. This is my (quite open) notebook on what was all the stuff I read and learnt. Not necessarily tech, you can just read on and understand what I am rambling on about.
I finally created my own Docker image of a gin-app and deployed it in a kubernetes pod.
The biggest challenge? Connecting the 2 pods, our otlp-example and the opentelemetry-collector. 
I needed to connect from pod A to port 4317 of pod B. Ofcourse, i had exposed the port in pod B using NodePort yet it didn't seem to work.
What finally worked? Instead of using 0.0.0.0:4317, I just needed to use otel-collector.observability.svc.cluster.local:4317 psst, it's the port name (or deployment name? not sure) , then namespace, then service and so on, which is exposed by a Node Port in this other service.
MAN ELASTIC APM IS AMAZING. LIKE. SO AMAZING TO LOOK AT THE TRACING <3





  
  
  Stuff I need to check out tomorrow? 📅



Plan on figuring out how to collect logs from a pod using fluentD and exporting it to our dear openetelemetry-collector. 
Use env vars to toggle the GRPC connection port.
Nothing today
Thanks for listening to the rant.
Uddeshya Singh,
Signing off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uddeshya Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🛒 Shopping for obscure libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adam_cyclones/shopping-for-obscure-libraries-188p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adam_cyclones/shopping-for-obscure-libraries-188p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T17:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to convert Java into Typescript...
Wired but true, I'm looking for a way to generate type definitions from Java, both the stdlib and custom stuff in .jar archives for use in Rhino 🦏😬
Its a long shot, but do you have any ideas or old code that does this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Crockett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular on Azure — Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/angular-on-azure-part-i-gng</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/angular-on-azure-part-i-gng"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T17:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pankaj Parker | ng-conf | May 2019
Using Azure Pipeline
Developers test software in a local environment using servers such as LAMP, WAMP, node, IIS, and Apache. Local deployment is good in terms of fast development and debugging, but we can’t ship our physical machines to the client in order to access to the application 😂. We have to deploy an application to a web server/cloud in order to make it accessible to the end user on their preferred platform (mobile, desktop, etc).
A variety of cloud providers exist in the current market, the most popular being Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, AWS. These providers offer an unbeatable combination of ease, speed, and automation, so if you have not deployed using such a platform, then this is the article for you! This article focuses on deplo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular on Azure — Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/angular-on-azure-part-i-gng</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/angular-on-azure-part-i-gng"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T17:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pankaj Parker | ng-conf | May 2019
Using Azure Pipeline
Developers test software in a local environment using servers such as LAMP, WAMP, node, IIS, and Apache. Local deployment is good in terms of fast development and debugging, but we can’t ship our physical machines to the client in order to access to the application 😂. We have to deploy an application to a web server/cloud in order to make it accessible to the end user on their preferred platform (mobile, desktop, etc).
A variety of cloud providers exist in the current market, the most popular being Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, AWS. These providers offer an unbeatable combination of ease, speed, and automation, so if you have not deployed using such a platform, then this is the article for you! This article focuses on deplo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LightDM Web Greeter updated!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jezerm/lightdm-web-greeter-updated-50lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jezerm/lightdm-web-greeter-updated-50lj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T17:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LightDM is a light display manager for Linux, which have lots of different greeters/themes to choose. One of these greeters is the previously known as lightdm webkit2 greeter, then named lightdm web greeter, a greeter that allows theming with web technologies like HTML and JavaScript.
Sadly, this greeter was abandoned as Antergos team didn’t have time to develop their distro. The latest version, 2.2.5 uses an outdated WebKit engine, which could cause some new web technologies to not work in the greeter. Also, the Debian package is not working, a shame.
Luckily, Antergos team were developing a 3.0.0 version, getting rid of WebKit and using the QtWebEngine, based on Chromium, with Python. So, I decided to update some things about this greeter based on this pre-release.
Whither is the “new” tool that 3.0.0 would be using, developed by Antergos, allows to create web applications in a similar way to Electron.js, but in Python.
So, I’m here to introduce a new pre-release. You can install it from the GitHub Repository. Though, you need to install the whither sdk to run it.
Command line arguments support, such as —-help, —-theme, —-debug and others
Some fixes with the LightDM API, as power functions didn’t work
Man pages updated
Every local request is made through web-greeter:/ url scheme
WebKit no longer here. Replaced with Chromium
Some API changes. 2.2.5 deprecated functions and globals were removed
If you are using LightDM, I recommend you to use this greeter, try some themes and create your own!
Use the Glorious theme by Manilarome~ It’s glorious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jezer Mejía</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This $1 billion startup spent 18 months rewriting its entire codebase from JavaScript to TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kyliebytes/this-1-billion-startup-spent-18-months-rewriting-its-entire-codebase-from-javascript-to-typescript-mei</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kyliebytes/this-1-billion-startup-spent-18-months-rewriting-its-entire-codebase-from-javascript-to-typescript-mei"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T16:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.businessinsider.com/javascript-typescript-codebase-sentry-frontend-devs-2021-5]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Robison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cody Ko explains how his 5 years as an app developer helped prepare him for a career as a YouTuber with 5.5 million subscribers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kyliebytes/cody-ko-explains-how-his-5-years-as-an-app-developer-helped-prepare-him-for-a-career-as-a-youtuber-with-5-5-million-subscribers-2mf6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kyliebytes/cody-ko-explains-how-his-5-years-as-an-app-developer-helped-prepare-him-for-a-career-as-a-youtuber-with-5-5-million-subscribers-2mf6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T16:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.businessinsider.com/cody-ko-youtuber-vine-creator-computer-science-engineering-iphone-apps-2021-4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Robison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building End-to-End Pipeline in Sagemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-end-to-end-pipeline-in-sagemaker-2g03</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/building-end-to-end-pipeline-in-sagemaker-2g03"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T16:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this part, we will see how we can make an end-to-end pipeline of an entire machine learning process. We can use a combination of AWS services to automate the entire process of machine learning.
AWS Step Functions is the service provided by Amazon that you can use to create workflows and automate them. These workflows consist of AWS resources, algorithms,
Each component in a step function is called a state machine. In this part, we will be creating multiple state machines, as follows:
State machine for training a model
State machine for saving the model


State machine for configuring endpoints


State machine for model deployment



Then we will combine all the state machines in a sequential format so that the entire process can be automated. 

Let’s start the process of creating the pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 10 most popular programming languages, according to Microsoft-owned GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kyliebytes/the-10-most-popular-programming-languages-according-to-microsoft-owned-github-22ka</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kyliebytes/the-10-most-popular-programming-languages-according-to-microsoft-owned-github-22ka"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T16:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.businessinsider.com/10-most-popular-programming-languages-2020-according-to-github-2021-1#4-typescript-7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Robison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking KubeMQ Build & Deploy for a Test Drive: My Thoughts and Impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mbogan/taking-kubemq-build-deploy-for-a-test-drive-my-thoughts-and-impressions-1djg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mbogan/taking-kubemq-build-deploy-for-a-test-drive-my-thoughts-and-impressions-1djg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T15:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


As a full-stack developer who often takes on DevOps and infrastructure responsibilities, the following happens all too frequently. 
Problem: I need to set up a backend server for my app!
Solution: Google it!
Google result #1: How to set up tech 1, tech 2, and tech 3 in just five minutes, for free!
(skip the prereqs because who needs those, follow the instructions, hit an error)
Hmm, let’s try that again…
(install all the prereqs, follow the instructions, hit another error)
Okay, maybe it’s just this article. Let’s try a different one.
Google result #2: Make your own tech 2 and tech 3 server using Docker and Kubernetes.
(follow the instructions, hit an error)
Well...maybe the third time’s the charm?
(day passes)
Guess I’ll try again in the morning…
While every tool promises t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Bogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom, Spotify and others slashed their cloud costs by millions - how did they do it?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/castai/zoom-spotify-and-others-slashed-their-cloud-costs-by-millions-how-did-they-do-it-38b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/castai/zoom-spotify-and-others-slashed-their-cloud-costs-by-millions-how-did-they-do-it-38b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Q1 2021, Zoom reported that its gross margin widened to 73.9% from 69.4% in the previous quarter - primarily thanks to the optimization of public cloud resources.
And Zoom is certainly not the only company that realized the value of optimizing the cloud infrastructure.
As businesses migrate their workloads to the cloud and build cloud-native applications, they’re starting to realize that overprovisioning and cloud sprawl aren’t just urban legends. 
For startups, the cloud is an essential technology because of its unparalleled support for scalability. But the cloud may quickly turn into a struggle because of growing costs.
Here's what a16z wrote in a recent analysis:
“[...] across 50 of the top public software companies currently utilizing cloud infrastructure, an estimated $100B of mark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CAST AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Easiest Way to Monitor Ruby: Automatic Instrumentation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appsignal/the-easiest-way-to-monitor-ruby-automatic-instrumentation-44af</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appsignal/the-easiest-way-to-monitor-ruby-automatic-instrumentation-44af"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a proper monitoring overview over your application's performance is a complex task. Normally, you'd first need to figure out what you need to monitor, then instrument your code, and finally make sense of all the data that has been emitted.
However, with a few things set in place, and an APM that natively supports Ruby, it's easier than ever to take this step. In this post, we'll show you how you can do it too.
To discover which pieces of your code are causing your performance issues, you’ll need to add instrumentation to it. That way, you can break down all the actions and measure which ones are the slowest.
With AppSignal’s automatic instrumentation, we take away as much manual work as we can. Just run a few commands through the CLI, and you’ll be set.
Our monitoring agent dete…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Milica Maksimovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make Vim your text editor and customizable IDE]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrdestructive/how-to-make-vim-your-text-editor-and-customizable-ide-42p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrdestructive/how-to-make-vim-your-text-editor-and-customizable-ide-42p4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all are asked to use visual studio code and other rich looking editors as a beginners text editor or an IDE but that makes a habit of a rich and pleasing interface of running and debugging programs, and that is the reason we don't feel good to use command line or the terminal. Terminal or Command line are quite important to learn and are powerful as well.  
Vim is a text editor, not any text editor but a special and one of the fastest out there, if you use it wisely. Vim can be used in the terminal which means it can run terminal commands inside the editor interface. That makes it quite a great option to improve your terminal command skills and also for enhancing your Linux knowledge. You can run program files from vim itself just by a few keystrokes. This text editor is preinstalled in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meet Gor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Port]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adiladvani/open-port-40mk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adiladvani/open-port-40mk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In security parlance, the term "open ports" are used to refer to a TCP or UDP port number that accepts packets. In contrast, closed ports reject connections and ignore all packets directed at them.
Three types of ports are:
Open Port: A port is open, and someone has left the door unlocked.
Closed Port: A closed port is a black hole that's open to attack. Administrators should block ports at the firewall level, and this could be exploited if an attacker has compromised another system. This can cause problems for networks because they'll have no way of knowing what kind of traffic will come in or out on these vulnerable holes across their firewalls
Filtered Port: Filtered Port: It's no small feat to filter all requests. This is likely due to a filtering device, so be careful!
Are you concern…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adiladvani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 12 factor app best practices for microservices]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ankit01oss/the-12-factor-app-best-practices-for-microservices-5cdg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ankit01oss/the-12-factor-app-best-practices-for-microservices-5cdg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I want to talk about the powerful 12 factor app methodology, which is an essential framework for both developers and ops engineers!
The 12 factor app methodology was first published in 2011 by Heroku engineers, who witnessed hundreds of apps being developed and deployed and came out with a method for building web applications at scale.
This methodology, when followed, enables companies to:
🔸 develop software quickly 
Now, let's take a look at the 12 factors in brief:
One codebase tracked in revision control, many deploys
There is only one codebase for a 12 factor app that is shared across development, production, staging, and QA. One codebase does not mean you can't have different deployments; the difference between deployments is taken care of by a version control system like Git.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Anand ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypress How to Configure HTML Results with Screenshot Step by Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ganeshsirsi/cypress-how-to-configure-html-results-with-screenshot-step-by-step-guide-55n7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ganeshsirsi/cypress-how-to-configure-html-results-with-screenshot-step-by-step-guide-55n7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might have written thousands of test cases but what makes you proud of it is, when you visualize the test results to stakeholders in an understandable way. There is a lot of articles over the internet to Integrate HTML reports into Cypress but when it comes to screenshot integration it's very difficult and time-consuming. The complexity is more.
This plugin is built on top of the mocha awesome report just to make life easy, so some of the options available in the mocha awesome reports are available here too.
Let's start
Assumptions:
In Visual Studio Code, Navigate to Terminal (Ensure present working directory is your Project root level directory) type below command.
npm i --save-dev cypress-mochawesome-reporter

Open, cypress.json file which is located in your project root directory, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh H</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🛠  Authorization for ASP.NET Web APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/authorization-for-asp-net-web-apis-3o73</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/authorization-for-asp-net-web-apis-3o73"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📘 Learn how to secure an ASP.NET Web API by granting access only to authorized users through Auth0 authentication and authorization services.


Having control over who can access your API is a necessary requirement to make your application secure. This article will show you how to restrict access to your ASP.NET Web API to authorized users only.
Let's start by setting up the ASP.NET Web API application to be protected. You can download a glossary Web API from this GitHub repository by running the following command in a terminal window:
git clone --branch starter --single-branch https://github.com/auth0-blog/glossary-web-api-aspnet.git


This ASP.NET application provides you with a CRUD Web API to manage a glossary of terms. You can learn the details of its implementation by reading this article.
Once you download the application, move to the glossary-web-api-aspnet folder and launch it by typing dotnet run in a terminal window. By pointing your browser to https://localhost:5001/swagger, you should see a page like the following to interactively test the APIs:

The Web API application allows you to get a list of term definitions or a single term definition. It also lets you create a new definition and modify or delete an existing one.
The current implementation of this glossary Web API allows anyone to perform all the available operations on the glossary. Most probably, you want to allow everyone to get a single glossary item or the full glossary. Still, only authorized users should be enabled to create, update, and delete glossary items.
Let's go and see how to protect these three actions by integrating your ASP.NET Core Web API with Auth0 services.
Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure AI Fundamentals Certification (AI-900) – Pass the Exam With This Free 4 Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60c2aa56d3126007592d6226</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/azure-data-fundamentals-certification-ai-900-pass-the-exam-with-this-free-4-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Azure AI Fundamentals Certification?The Azure AI Fundamentals Certification is for those seeking a Machine Learning role such as AI Engineer or Data Scientist. In the last decade companies have been collecting vast amount of data surrounding their service and product offerings. The successful companies of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0 Levels Up Analytics Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/auth0-levels-up-analytics-experience-8k6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/auth0-levels-up-analytics-experience-8k6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T11:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the refresh, customers have access to actionable insights that give them a high-level understanding of their tenant data without the overhead of third-party tools.


We’re excited to announce the first availability of the new Activity page in Auth0’s dashboard. With the refresh, customers have access to actionable insights that give them a high-level understanding of their tenant data without the overhead of third-party tools.
With Activity analytics, developers can ensure that their Auth0 implementation is working and report back usage and utility. Security engineers can quickly gauge failed logins and monitor security events for potential audit. And product owners can easily understand usage and relay that information to relevant stakeholders.
The new Activity page drives more data-driven outcomes by enabling customers to:
Visualize metrics such as active users and failed logins
Compare data across previous time periods
Filter data by specific timeframes
Segment active users across connections and applications (Coming Soon)
Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assess your networking and security Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/limonsafayet/assess-your-networking-and-security-skills-44cn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/limonsafayet/assess-your-networking-and-security-skills-44cn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T11:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network security is the practice of preventing and protecting against unauthorized intrusion into corporate networks. As a philosophy, it complements endpoint security, which focuses on individual devices; network security instead focuses on how those devices interact, and on the connective tissue between them. 
According to the SANS institute Network security is the process of taking physical and software preventative measures to protect the underlying networking infrastructure from unauthorized access, misuse, malfunction, modification, destruction, or improper disclosure, thereby creating a secure platform for computers, users, and programs to perform their permitted critical functions within a secure environment. 
A brief network security consists of Three layers, Protection, Detection, and Reaction. This is a kind of defense-in-depth strategy. But a system should not rely on a single line of the defense system, rather it should have multiple defense strategies lined up. 
So how can you test your network and security skills, there is a perfect website to validate your skills and prove yourself as a network and security expert. You can visit Free Tech Exams website and attend CompTIA, A+, Network+, and Security+ Practice Test and Exam. They also provide certification on completion of your test. Each segment is consisting of 10 tests you can practice to. Good luck with becoming a network expert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Limon Safayet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to threading and multiprocessing: Concurrency and Parallelism in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adarshpunj/introduction-to-threading-and-multiprocessing-concurrency-and-parallelism-in-python-2m81</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adarshpunj/introduction-to-threading-and-multiprocessing-concurrency-and-parallelism-in-python-2m81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T11:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topics covered:
Concurrency 
Parallelism
threading module in Python
multiprocessing module in Python
 Real world examples (Downloading images from the web concurrently)
How processes and threads are managed at OS level
Topics not covered:
AsyncIO
GIL
👉🏻 Read now
Published at Pythongasm on 16/06/2021]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adarsh Punj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS Basics: Fixing Dependency Security Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smarthomedan/nodejs-basics-fixing-dependency-security-issues-3jdg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smarthomedan/nodejs-basics-fixing-dependency-security-issues-3jdg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T11:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When hitting an issue with nodejs modules having security vunerabilties, I follow the below process. Assume the problematic module is sharp version 0.22.1
Updating the module
Check out the repository
npm ci
npm ls sharp
npm i sharp@0.28.2
npm ls sharp
npm uninstall sharp
Make sure we now commit this package.lock to the repository, and our CI pipeline should have been sorted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smart Home Dan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS Basics: Fixing Dependency Security Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smarthomedan/nodejs-basics-fixing-dependency-security-issues-3jdg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smarthomedan/nodejs-basics-fixing-dependency-security-issues-3jdg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T11:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When hitting an issue with nodejs modules having security vunerabilties, I follow the below process. Assume the problematic module is sharp version 0.22.1
Updating the module
Check out the repository
npm ci
npm ls sharp
npm i sharp@0.28.2
npm ls sharp
npm uninstall sharp
Make sure we now commit this package.lock to the repository, and our CI pipeline should have been sorted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smart Home Dan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.JS Basics: Handling Cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smarthomedan/node-js-basics-handling-cookies-24n1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smarthomedan/node-js-basics-handling-cookies-24n1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below is the test code I have for checking if my method for sending cookies is working.
Example Cookie Parsing Server
const express = require("express");
const app = express();
const cookieParser = require("cookie-parser");

app.use(cookieParser());

app.get("/test-cookie", (req, res) => {
    console.log(req.cookies);
    // Here we should have access to the Cookies sent.
    res.status(204);
});

app.post("/login", (req, res) => {
    res.writeHead(200, 
        {
            "Set-Cookie": "token=encryptedstring; HttpOnly",
            "Access-Control-Allow-Credentials": "true"
        }
    ).send();
});

app.listen(8080, () => {
    console.log("listening on port 8080 for Cookies...");
});]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Smart Home Dan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[😡 Agonies, Despair and self hosted Redash BI server on Microsoft Azure cloud platform 😋 part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alxizr/agonies-despair-and-self-hosted-redash-bi-server-on-microsoft-azure-cloud-platform-4e73</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alxizr/agonies-despair-and-self-hosted-redash-bi-server-on-microsoft-azure-cloud-platform-4e73"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone,
Thank you for joining in today to talk about the open source BI tool named Redash. We will focus today mainly on how to set up a self hosted Redash server in the cloud starting from a local environment setup. We will see the nuances hidden in the process and try to 'debug' on the fly.
You may wonder about the article's title to be a bit... maybe negative ?! Well i *** you not but the amount of energy and time wasted on solving simple issues is tremendous. I am writing this article so you potentially and hopefully won't go into the rabbit hole as a public service.
Let's hit the road!
Before we begin, as always we want to know what is the minimum for us to be able to start and be efficient and productive.
Visual Studio Code
Azure Account
Docker - You do need to be famalier wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alxizr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript cast is a type breaker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ylerjen/typescript-cast-is-a-type-breaker-1jbh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ylerjen/typescript-cast-is-a-type-breaker-1jbh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover image by Pankaj Patel on Unsplash
Everyone is aware that the any type is a bad thing because it would basically be like coming back to Javascript where there's no strong type check and anything is allowed.
But even if we respect this rule, we can fall into another pitfal where we break Typescript's type-check by casting types. Following chapter will describe you why and how to avoid it.
Type creation can be done in several ways in typescript. It can be anonymous, interface/class declarations, type aliases, duck-typings, etc. (See everything in the doc)
But when it comes about typing a variable, there's one syntax only which is with colon :.
const mystring: string = 'hello'; // this example could be duck-typed, but yeah, focus on the colon

By typing a variable, TS will know what type…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yann L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vue Vs Angular- A 2021 Comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ltdsolace/vue-vs-angular-a-2021-comparison-14hm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ltdsolace/vue-vs-angular-a-2021-comparison-14hm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past decade, frontend frameworks have dramatically evolved and some of them are game changers. These frameworks not just create cross-platform apps easily but are better for future development too. But when it comes to choosing popular Javascript frameworks in 2021, Vue and angular stand out. With lots of benefits, you might be confused to choose the best framework for business, so here we will discuss both Javascript frameworks on the basis of various parameters. But before digging to the comparison, let’s see an overview of each Vue and Angular.
Vue is an open-source framework that can deal with challenges related to Angular and React. It is popular to build single-page web apps. Vue 3 is the latest version of Vue.js that includes production of standalone reactive objects, templat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solace Infotech Pvt. Ltd.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best structure for connected apps?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bgrgndzz/best-structure-for-connected-apps-1n12</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bgrgndzz/best-structure-for-connected-apps-1n12"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a product that we're expanding upon. We want to build satellite products that have a completely different functionality and interface than the main product. Users will be able to create accounts on both products separately but will also be able to sign up with the main account's details.
What is the best way to do this? I've tried building them out as separate apps and creating a connection endpoint that moves the satellite account to the main database, but that seems really hacky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Buğra Gündüz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best structure for connected apps?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bgrgndzz/best-structure-for-connected-apps-1n12</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bgrgndzz/best-structure-for-connected-apps-1n12"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a product that we're expanding upon. We want to build satellite products that have a completely different functionality and interface than the main product. Users will be able to create accounts on both products separately but will also be able to sign up with the main account's details.
What is the best way to do this? I've tried building them out as separate apps and creating a connection endpoint that moves the satellite account to the main database, but that seems really hacky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Buğra Gündüz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Command Line tool with Node.js and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kayfortune/building-a-command-line-tool-with-node-js-and-fauna-nmk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kayfortune/building-a-command-line-tool-with-node-js-and-fauna-nmk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T09:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a command line tool with Nodejs and Fauna


Written in connection with the Write With Fauna program. 
Command line tools are one of the most popular applications we have today, in fact we use command line tools everyday, they range from git, npm or yarn. Command line tools are very fast and useful for automating applications and workflows
In this post, we will be building a command line tool with Node.js and Fauna for our database. We will be building a random qoutes application using Node.js, we will add permission and a keyword for our app. 
To take full advantage of this tutorial, make sure you have the following installed on your local development environment:
Node.js version >= 16.x.x installed.
Have access to one package manager such as [npm](https://www.npmjs.com/) or [yarn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fortune Kelechi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the DevOps lifecycle and the Best Practices Followed?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/weblineindia/what-is-the-devops-lifecycle-and-the-best-practices-followed-4efd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/weblineindia/what-is-the-devops-lifecycle-and-the-best-practices-followed-4efd"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T09:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is referred to as a methodology in which software development is combined with information technology operations. These two worlds are blended in the entire service lifecycle, from the initial phase of designing products through the whole development process and production support. To explain DevOps precisely, it is a practice that enables one team to manage the complete development phase, which comprises the development, testing, deployment, and operations. 
This approach enables the development of superior quality software rapidly and reliably. It means that various phases constitute an entire lifecycle, like continuous development, continuous integration, continuous testing, deployment, and the monitoring of applications. Let us know more about each phase and how DevOps consultin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikrant Bhalodia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting The Type Of An Interface Property In Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/simondosda/getting-the-type-of-an-interface-property-in-typescript-5bl5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/simondosda/getting-the-type-of-an-interface-property-in-typescript-5bl5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T09:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem


The problem is quite simple, but its solution is not obvious. 
Imagine that we are working on a Typescript project and we have defined an interface with several fields using different types. 
interface BlogPost {
  title: string,
  content: string
  publishDate: Date | null,
  isDraft: boolean
}

Let's say now that we would like to provide a simple setter that will allow us to update a blog post while running some custom logic. For instance, let's consider that our setter will allow updating a post only if it is a draft. 
In Typescript, we would write something like this.
function updatePost(post: BlogPost, property: keyof BlogPost, value): boolean {
    if (!post.isDraft) {
        return false;
    }
    post[property] = value;  // error: Type 'any' is not assignable to type 'n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You need to build a collaborative text editor RIGHT NOW!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abhishekraj272/you-need-to-build-a-collaborative-text-editor-right-now-5fcj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abhishekraj272/you-need-to-build-a-collaborative-text-editor-right-now-5fcj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T08:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By building a collaborative text editor you will get to learn
Send data from server to client - Polling/Sockets
Algo/DS to use for efficient data transfer - Text Compare
Update editor in such way, user's cursor doesn't move.
There are way too many things it will teach you, read the below post to learn more or Try out the live project here -> Live URL




  
  
  Intro


Recently, I started working on this cool project, a Web Based Code Editor. So, in this post I will talk about how I implemented this project and what will be the further features I will be adding. 😃
As we all know there are thousands of AWESOMEEE code editors out there like repl.it, codepen, codesandbox, etc. So most you must be wondering why I decided to write my own code editors.
 
What I think is, if you build a system then you will get to know how that thing really works, so my curiosity made me do it. 🙂
Lets talk about the features this web app currently has,
Separate tabs for HTML/CSS/JS for better coding style.
Code Output Display, shows the output by merging all codes and creating a Virtual DOM.
Fully Mobile Responsive.
Download merged code as text file.
Night Mode
Code auto save in browser
Code Sharing Link (Planned)
Code Collaboration (Planned)
In this project, I have used,
React - For UI
Material UI - Design/Animation
Redux - For State Management
Redux Saga - For Side Effects
Redux Persist - For Auto Save
Socket IO (Planned) - For socket connection
JsDiff - For Calculating Difference

Github
Try out the live project here -> Live URL
Connect Me @ Linkedin Github Twitter Youtube
Instagram 😇
Ping Me Anytime with doubts related to Full Stack / Pen Testing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Raj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a TODO List App with React + Node.js  | MERN Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jahangeer/how-to-build-a-todo-list-app-with-react-node-js-mern-stack-3ban</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jahangeer/how-to-build-a-todo-list-app-with-react-node-js-mern-stack-3ban"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys in this video, you learn how to build todo application with react, node.js, express and mongodb (MERN stack). We gonna cover all crud(create, read, update, delete) operations in this video. even if you are beginner feel free watch and build project. I hope you will learn something new from this video.




Please subscribe and support my channel.
Thank You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jahangeer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Region KMS Key and its use cases]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chathra222/multi-region-kms-key-and-its-use-cases-35jl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chathra222/multi-region-kms-key-and-its-use-cases-35jl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Folks, AWS announced that a new capability in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) called multi-Region keys, where it lets you replicate keys from one Amazon Web Services (AWS) Region into another. 
So today I am going to show how multi-Region keys can be used and its usefulness with few examples.
Multi-Region keys are a set of interoperable KMS keys that have the same key ID and key material, and that you can replicate to different Regions within the same partition. With symmetric multi-Region keys, you can encrypt data in one Region and decrypt it in a different Region.
AWS services also let you configure multi-Region keys for server-side encryption in case you want the same key to protect data in multiple regions. Also multi-region key will be useful for Client-side encryption where …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chathra Serasinghe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to call a external API from Angular Application while executing ng serve]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surya_n/how-to-call-a-external-api-from-angular-application-while-executing-ng-serve-p99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surya_n/how-to-call-a-external-api-from-angular-application-while-executing-ng-serve-p99"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to call a external API from Angular Application after executing ng serve ? (not with browser loading)
I have to register my Angular Application in one service registry (Eureka) by calling a external POST API before the application loads. I have tried with APP_INITIALIZER but it is calling the API once we are loading the application in browser. I want to execute the API before loading the app in browser (browser will not be open while the api call).
Something like when I start the app with "ng serve" I want to execute API. Is there any way?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surya N</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to call a external API from Angular Application while executing ng serve]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surya_n/how-to-call-a-external-api-from-angular-application-while-executing-ng-serve-p99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surya_n/how-to-call-a-external-api-from-angular-application-while-executing-ng-serve-p99"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to call a external API from Angular Application after executing ng serve ? (not with browser loading)
I have to register my Angular Application in one service registry (Eureka) by calling a external POST API before the application loads. I have tried with APP_INITIALIZER but it is calling the API once we are loading the application in browser. I want to execute the API before loading the app in browser (browser will not be open while the api call).
Something like when I start the app with "ng serve" I want to execute API. Is there any way?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surya N</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongo and Node.js on local instance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/areatomic/mongo-and-node-js-on-local-instance-528e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/areatomic/mongo-and-node-js-on-local-instance-528e"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use MongoDB locally



  
  
  To do


For the MERN stack it can be great to use MongoDB locally. Mainly if your company proxy does not accept to run on cloud. To install MongoDB on local there is three main steps :
Download the installer
Install on local without services
Create databases for test
First step, the easiest one but it can be confusious. The server installer can be found at the following link https://www.mongodb.com/try/download/community. It will allow you to install mongo.exe (the mongo shell), mongod.exe (the mongo server), mongos.exe.
This one can be various following your needed. I will explain you how to install on Windows without services.

Click next, and choose to install MongoDB Compass to have graphical tool for your databases.
For this step we will use MongoDB Comp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AreAtomic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an RSS Scully Plugin - Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/building-an-rss-scully-plugin-angular-1lg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/building-an-rss-scully-plugin-angular-1lg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will learn how to extend Scully functionality through plugins. We will do this by building an RSS Plugin. This plugin will generate an RSS feed for our blog web app build using Angular and Scully.
For an RSS plugin, we will build a routeDiscoveryDone plugin, which is usually called when all routes have been discovered. This is going to use data discovered during the route discovery process to create an RSS feed. The route discovery process is done by a router plugin, which you can learn more about here.
Scully provides 9 types of plugins which are called at during different stages of Scully build. For more information about different types of plugins, please visit the official documentation here.
Setup Scully for Your Angular Project - Link.
If you used schematics to se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an RSS Scully Plugin - Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/building-an-rss-scully-plugin-angular-1lg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/building-an-rss-scully-plugin-angular-1lg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T07:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will learn how to extend Scully functionality through plugins. We will do this by building an RSS Plugin. This plugin will generate an RSS feed for our blog web app build using Angular and Scully.
For an RSS plugin, we will build a routeDiscoveryDone plugin, which is usually called when all routes have been discovered. This is going to use data discovered during the route discovery process to create an RSS feed. The route discovery process is done by a router plugin, which you can learn more about here.
Scully provides 9 types of plugins which are called at during different stages of Scully build. For more information about different types of plugins, please visit the official documentation here.
Setup Scully for Your Angular Project - Link.
If you used schematics to se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any way I can change a file header in Linux like how I'd change a file extension in Windows (10).]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baenencalin/is-there-any-way-i-can-change-a-file-header-in-linux-like-how-i-d-change-a-file-extension-in-windows-10-5257</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baenencalin/is-there-any-way-i-can-change-a-file-header-in-linux-like-how-i-d-change-a-file-extension-in-windows-10-5257"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T06:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know in Windows, "file extensions", the part of a file name after the final period in the file name, are more than just part of the file name, they also act as metadata to tell Windows what kind of file the document should be treated as, and what apps to open them in (i.e. what apps are associated with those file types).
However, I want to start moving to Linux (Ubuntu) which I installed on my PC a while back, so, I recently tried making a new file ("extensionless"), and I wanted to make it a different type, so I tested to see if that would work by testing by renaming it .go, so I could try to open it in VSCode like I normally would on WIndows.
I look up multiple searches, involving how to change the file extension (only getting results using command line), and eventually coming over to a horrifying S.O. answer that horrified me, it gave me the info that "extensions" (file types) are determined by header.
There doesn't seem to be any way in the "Files" file manager for Ubuntu to change the header type.

What I want is a program that can give me a simple GUI to edit the file type of a file so I can easily go between one or the other as needed/wanted.
Info:
OS: Ubuntu 20.04.2 LTS
WindowingSystem: X11
GNOME: 3.36.8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Calin Baenen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish Websites Using Sanity CMS With 21YunBox]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/21yunbox/publish-websites-using-sanity-cms-with-21yunbox-431p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/21yunbox/publish-websites-using-sanity-cms-with-21yunbox-431p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T03:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will walk through the steps of publishing websites using Sanity CMS with 21YunBox. 
 


  
  
  Steps to deploy websites with Sanity CMS and 21YunBox:



Sign up on 21YunBox

Create or use existing Sanity project
Fork Sanity CMS Starter on Github
Use the following values during creation:
...
To read the full content of this post, go to: https://launch-in-china.21yunbox.com/cms/publish-websites-using-sanity-cms-with-21yunbox.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>21YunBox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Sanity CMS Work in China?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/21yunbox/does-sanity-cms-work-in-china-5c7c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/21yunbox/does-sanity-cms-work-in-china-5c7c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T03:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Sanity CMS?


Sanity is one of many headless CMS (content management systems) for structured content. Headless CMS helps content editors, marketers, and developers work together to deliver a better content experience to their users.
 


  
  
  Does Sanity CMS work in China?


The short answer is No. 
Why? Sanity is built and hosted on top of the Google Cloud Platform which is blocked completely in China. 
 

Here is the long answer:
We reached out to the Sanity team to see if their service works in China, and here is what we got:
 


 

So simply put, if the Sanity team doesn't have experience with China, you are unlikely to get good support from them. If you are just testing Sanity out, and don't need your site to be highly available in China. It doesn't hurt to try.
Since the Sanity CMS is based on GCP (Google Cloud Platform), if GCP has good support in China, we probably can still use it in production, but what we found was this: 
" Google does not offer and has not offered cloud platform services inside China and Google Cloud is not weighing options to offer the Google Cloud Platform (GCP) in China."
Google's Media Statement
So this looks like Sanity CMS doesn't work in China by "words" and it is also not in the coverage area of the Sanity and GCP. The next thing we want to know is: if a website is published with Sanity CMS, whether the site can be loaded in China or not. More specifically, how fast the site loads in China. Here are the speed test results:
...
To read the full content of this post, go to: https://launch-in-china.21cloudbox.com/solutions/does-sanity-cms-work-in-china.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>21YunBox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.Net + Angular + PoUi : FullStackPlayGroung]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/silverio27/net-angular-poui-fullstackplaygroung-4f1d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/silverio27/net-angular-poui-fullstackplaygroung-4f1d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T01:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oi Pessoal!
Nesse post vou mostrar como criar um crud com .net e angular utilizando po-ui, uma biblioteca de componentes para angular de alta produtividade.
O código completo está no meu github, clique aqui para acessar.
.Net5 SDK
VsCode
Windows Terminal
NodeJs
Angular - CLI
Abra uma pasta de sua preferencia no terminal.
src.
Abra o terminal e navegue até esta pasta e digite o comando abaixo para abrir o vscode.
code .

A partir de agora vamos utilizar o terminal integrado do vscode. Aperte ctrl + ' para abrir o terminal integrado.
Crie o projeto com o comando abaixo:
dotnet new webapi -o api

Apague as classes WeatherForecast.cs e Controllers/WeatherForecastController.cs
Navegue até a pasta do projeto
cd api

Crie um arquivo de gitignore
dotnet new gitignore

Crie a pasta Models e crie a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Silvério</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement an Event Bus in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/how-to-implement-an-event-bus-in-typescript-f1d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/how-to-implement-an-event-bus-in-typescript-f1d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T00:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're building a Single Page Application using Web Components only. You have several pages, have configured the routes, and need to be able to handle general events or actions.
Here's when you start to think about potential solutions as well: Maybe it's time to add state management to the application?  Is it a good time to build a "custom" solution? What about using some design patterns in this case?
The answers to these questions will depend on the complexity of the current scenario, the experience of the developers, or on the opinions of the team. It is clear that there is no absolute answer!
In this article, we'll go over how to communicate between components using a custom Event Bus implementation.
The Event Bus idea is generally associated with the Publish-subscribe pattern:
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Aviles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Bookmarklets? How to Use JavaScript to Make a Bookmarklet in Chromium and Firefox]]></title>
        <id>60c88bbc4dc1a607ed7b2ffa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T00:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bookmarklets are browser bookmarks that execute JavaScript instead of opening a webpage. They're also known as bookmark applets, favlets, or JavaScript bookmarks. Bookmarklets are natively available in all major browsers, including Mozilla Firefox and Chromium-based browsers like Chrome or Brave. Scripting with JavaScriptLearning how to write scripts provides many benefits,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring 2FA on your Linux Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended Setup


Update your server to the latest packages.
sudo apt update && apt upgrade && reboot

Add a non-root user with sudo privileges.
adduser username
usermod -aG sudo username
su username

First, install the Google Authenticator PAM module.
sudo apt install libpam-google-authenticator

Run the google-authenticator binary to create a new secret key (keep this one safe).
google-authenticator

After completing the process, you can scan/enter the code in an Authenticator App.
I've chosen the following settings for this example.
Do you want authentication tokens to be time-based (y/n) y

Do you want me to update your "/home/username/.google_authenticator" file? (y/n) y

Do you want to disallow multiple uses of the same authentication
token? This restricts you to one login about ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florentin / 珞辰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring 2FA on your Linux Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended Setup


Update your server to the latest packages.
sudo apt update && apt upgrade && reboot

Add a non-root user with sudo privileges.
adduser username
usermod -aG sudo username
su username

First, install the Google Authenticator PAM module.
sudo apt install libpam-google-authenticator

Run the google-authenticator binary to create a new secret key (keep this one safe).
google-authenticator

After completing the process, you can scan/enter the code in an Authenticator App.
I've chosen the following settings for this example.
Do you want authentication tokens to be time-based (y/n) y

Do you want me to update your "/home/username/.google_authenticator" file? (y/n) y

Do you want to disallow multiple uses of the same authentication
token? This restricts you to one login about ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florentin / 珞辰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Split – How to Split a String into an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>60c088e5d3126007592d56f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-split-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In general, a string represents a sequence of characters in a programming language.  Let's look at an example of a string created using a sequence of characters, "Yes, You Can DO It!". In JavaScript, we can create a string in a couple of ways: Using the string literal as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comandos básicos que debes conocer para dominar LINUX. ​💻​]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gdcodev/comandos-basicos-que-debes-conocer-para-dominar-linux-1emi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gdcodev/comandos-basicos-que-debes-conocer-para-dominar-linux-1emi"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En la informática saber usar la consola de comandos Linux es fundamental, es por eso que les comparto una serie de comandos básicos para que aprendas y logres dominar el terminal.
A continuación vamos a ver algunos de los comandos con los que se puede empezar.
Sirve para encontrar la ruta del directorio (carpeta) de trabajo actual en el que te encuentras
pwd

Crear un nuevo directorio
mkdir <nombre-directorio>

Sirve para navegar por los archivos y directorios
cd Fotos/  entrar en el directorio Fotos 
cd .. (con dos puntos) retroceder un nivel
cd ../.. retroceder dos niveles
cd para ir directamente a la carpeta de inicio (raíz)
cd - (con un guión) para ir al directorio anterior

Crear ficheros
touch index.html

Si necesitas eliminar un directorio, pero solo te permite eliminar directorios …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gastón Danielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skewness and Kurtosis – Positively Skewed and Negatively Skewed Distributions in Statistics Explained]]></title>
        <id>60b8cb0aacb62507dd1d82ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/skewness-and-kurtosis-in-statistics-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain two important concepts in statistics: skewness and kurtosis. And don't worry – you won't need to know very much math to understand these concepts and learn how to apply them. What are Density Curves?Let's first talk a bit about density curves, as skewness and kurtosis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Better React Apps with These Simple Tricks]]></title>
        <id>60ca25704dc1a607ed7b408c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-better-react-apps-with-these-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a list of amazing tricks that you can use to improve your React applications instantly. These tips will not only make your code cleaner and more reliable, but they also aim to make your development experience easier and overall more enjoyable.  Give these techniques a try in your React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla Use Reducer with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fangoh/vanilla-use-reducer-with-typescript-4f9p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fangoh/vanilla-use-reducer-with-typescript-4f9p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I was recently doing a project for my portfolio, a React Project with a slightly complex state. Personally, I really love TypeScript and the Redux/Reducer patterns, because they give me a great Developer Experience with TypeScript and a lot of autocompletion available, quite useful in order to not get bit by a bug caused by a typo, and really convenient as I don't have to explore files constantly in order to know what are the properties that a certain object should have.
I always prefer to use TS over vanilla JS, so, it makes a lot of sense to try to make use of strict typing, even in a concept app. Also, while vanilla useReducer might not be what most projects use, I still want to share how I found it to be pretty useful in this context.
My application is a Social Media-like platform,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hector Osuna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ngModel - Type 'Event' is not assignable to type 'string'.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mateuszto/ngmodel-type-event-is-not-assignable-to-type-string-f2n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mateuszto/ngmodel-type-event-is-not-assignable-to-type-string-f2n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T18:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://stackblitz.com/edit/angular-ivy-ws1lhp?file=src%2Fapp%2Fapp.component.ts What am I doing wrong? Somebody help?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mateusz Tomczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach Yourself Data Analytics in 30 Days]]></title>
        <id>60ca30af4dc1a607ed7b4197</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/teach-yourself-data-analytics-in-30-days/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T17:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn the basics of Data Analytics with 30 days of practice.  We just released a Data Analytics course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. The course includes a 40-minute video, as well as a website and Jupyter notebooks. If you follow the plan laid out in these course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Most Interactive Shell On A Linux Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nirupamvas/how-to-install-most-interactive-shell-on-a-linux-machine-36ko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nirupamvas/how-to-install-most-interactive-shell-on-a-linux-machine-36ko"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T16:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Guys, I am Nirupamvas and I am back again with an other awesome Linux tutorial. So let's get started.
Before getting into it, let's understand some of the things 
A shell is an interface to the underlying operating system. It allows you to execute operations using text and commands, and it provides users with advanced features like being able to create scripts.
So, everytime you want to execute a command you need to type entire command, I think this is one messy thing we need to do each and every time. To boost productivity and to save time for our lazy squad we have something called Fish. So let's see what is it all about.
Fish, or the “Friendly Interactive Shell,” is the most user-friendly and interactive shell, in my opinion.
Let's start our installation,
Step 1 : Download Fish


…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nirupamvas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342353</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-used-the-waapi-to-build-an-animation-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Animations API lets us construct animations and control their playback with JavaScript. The API opens the browser’s animation engine to developers and was designed to underlie implementations of both CSS animations and transitions, leaving the door open to …
The post How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okiki Ojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize Angular Webpack config]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dontry/customize-angular-webpack-config-4be6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dontry/customize-angular-webpack-config-4be6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[add customWebpackConfig to angular.json
{
    "projects": {
        "architect": {
            "build": {
                "options": {
                  "customWebpackConfig": {
          "path": "./custom-webpack.config.js",
          "replaceDuplicatePlugins": true
        },
                }
            }
        }
    }
}

add the extra webpack plugin config in the custom-webpack.config.js
module.exports = {
    module: {
        rules: [
            {
                test: /\.js$/,
                loader: 'babel-loader',
                query: {
                    presets: ['@babel/preset-env'
                    ]
                }
            }
        ]
    }
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build quality forms with React 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alarid/build-quality-forms-with-react-9nk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alarid/build-quality-forms-with-react-9nk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by  Kelly Sikkema
☕️ Read this article on my blog
When it comes to building forms with React, there are tons of possibilities out there in the React Ecosystem. Many libraries have emerged to answer specific needs, and it can be a little bit overwhelming at first: which one to choose? what strategy to adopt? 
Even without using a library, just using pure React, you can basically go two ways: controlled or uncontrolled. We will briefly discuss this, so if you're new to React, you might want to start there. 
If you already know all about controlled VS uncontrolled forms, you can skip the first part and jump right to the second one, where I will show you how I like to build my forms today: using react-hook-form, yup and TypeScript. Those tools allow me to quickly build any type of form w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yohann Legrand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What JS frameworks fail at that makes the new ones being developed so often?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrisczopp/what-js-frameworks-fail-at-that-makes-the-new-ones-being-developed-so-often-2o73</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrisczopp/what-js-frameworks-fail-at-that-makes-the-new-ones-being-developed-so-often-2o73"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any thoughts? Aren't we in some sort of limbo?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chris-czopp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como ter janelas em seu terminal usando tmux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itexto/como-ter-janelas-em-seu-terminal-usando-tmux-g46</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itexto/como-ter-janelas-em-seu-terminal-usando-tmux-g46"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Muitas vezes você lida com ambientes que possuem apenas uma interface de linha de comandos e precisa executar mais de uma ação ao mesmo tempo. Como resolver esta necessidade tendo uma única sessão/janela? Nesta receita apresentamos o tmux. 
Esta receita lhe fornecerá o essencial para que possa dar os primeiros passos com esta super ferramenta de produtividade que não é tão conhecida como deveria por usuários Linux. 
Ingredientes

Linux (mas você pode substituir pelo WSL no Windows ou mesmo pelo macOS).
tmux.
Habilidade e memória manual mínima.
Um pouco de paciência e persistência pois o primeiro contato pode não ser tão fácil assim.
Ingrediente principal: tmux

A melhor maneira de entender o problema é vendo-o em ação, sendo assim vamos a um caso real. Preciso iniciar dois processos, acomp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henrique Lobo Weissmann (Kico)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go from Zero to Cypherpunk]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blahblahman9/go-from-zero-to-cypherpunk-3h5a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blahblahman9/go-from-zero-to-cypherpunk-3h5a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We live in a post-Snowden world. For many, that means assuming none of your digital assets are safe from surveillance.
There are ways, however, to use the internet with insane mathematics in your favor to ensure that no one can see whatever it is that you’re sending to someone else.
Cryptography is an ancient mathematical science that was originally used for military communications, and designed to conceal the contents of a message should it fall into the hands of the enemy. Recent developments in cryptography have added additional uses, including mechanisms for authenticating users on a network, ensuring the integrity of transmitted information and preventing users from repudiating (i.e. rejecting ownership of) their transmitted messages.
Today, encryption is an integral part of many of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blahblahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PrimeNG v12.0.0 is here!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/primeng-v12-0-0-is-here-5cge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/primeng-v12-0-0-is-here-5cge"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PrimeTek is thrilled to announce the PrimeNG 12.0.0 release to bring first class Angular 12 support with new gray scheme along with numerous improvements and responsive updates to the components.
Angular 12
PrimeNG v12.0.0 depends on Angular 12 and is fully compatible with it. As it is always suggested, use the PrimeNG whose major version matches your Angular version e.g. PrimeNG 12 with Angular 12.
Responsive Updates
PrimeNG v12.0.0 focuses on improving the responsiveness of components so that they can be used within a responsive layout seamlessly. Latest additions to the set are:
Responsive Toast
Responsive TabMenu
Responsive BreadCrumb
Changelog
changelog for more details.
Download
PrimeNG is licensed under MIT and free to download at NPM.
Roadmap
Always Bet On Prime!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Rogue]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daveclarke/going-rogue-5fc4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daveclarke/going-rogue-5fc4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T07:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time I was at University doing a maths and computer science degree (and presumably provided subject matter for the BOFH but that's a different story). The University had a shiny DEC VAX 11/780 running VMS. The computer lab was an underground bunker with a bunch of physical terminals. Second year students were allowed a key to access it after hours. Yes a physical key. What did comp-sci students do after hours back in 1984? We played Rogue on a VAX 11/780. 
While Rogue was not the first dungeon-crawling game with procedural generation features, it introduced the subgenre of roguelike RPG procedurally generated dungeon crawlers with Dungeons-and-Dragons-like items (armor, weapons, potions, and magic scrolls) that also had permadeath (permanent death) and an overhead graphical vie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daveclarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you wanted to know about the Security+ SY0-601 but were afraid to ask]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kiarasmith/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-the-security-sy0-601-but-were-afraid-to-ask-4p7j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kiarasmith/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-the-security-sy0-601-but-were-afraid-to-ask-4p7j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T04:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CompTIA Security+ is the pinnacle cyber protection certification. Security+ certification is in high demand and maintains to serve as a fundamental certification for experts beginning an IT career or others looking to construct a profession in cybersecurity. On top of that, Security+ certification is also authorized using the Department of Defense (DoD) to satisfy Directive 8570.01 -M requirements.

If you’re looking for employment within the government, then it's far a required certification. CompTIA Security+ SY0-501 is the present-day Security+ examination and maybe to be had to take till the Spring of 2021. However, the Security+ SY0-601 is scheduled to be launched in October of 2020. If you’re an IT security professional and you’re seeking to decide which certification is nice for you or if you’re simply trying to research extra about every examination, check out the statistics under:
The SY0-501 examination specializes in these talent regions:
• Threats, attacks, and vulnerabilities
The SY0-601 Exam will cover the equal talent regions pondered within the SY0-501. However, some of these areas will consist of extra information. Expect to see changes in the following regions:
• Threats, assaults, and vulnerabilities
• Cloud assist
Also, expect to peer extra overall performance-based questions (PBQs) on SY0-601.
Professionals need to determine to take every examination based on their man or woman's needs and timeline. Both assessments will train you on how to recognize and manipulate security threats, but if you’re equipped properly now SY0-501 is the most effective examination to be had until October.
If you can wait till October, the SY0-601 will include updates based totally on the nature of the current cyber protection environment and troubles that cyber protection specialists are combating these days. If you decide to put together for SY0-601 make certain that your examination education is appropriate to that exam!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiara Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Custom Form Validators In Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karvel/exploring-custom-form-validators-in-angular-52fb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karvel/exploring-custom-form-validators-in-angular-52fb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T04:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that the reactive form library in Angular is one of the most powerful tools in the framework. Developers can create performant and reactive forms that provide great UI/UX. One part of the reactive form toolkit that I think people often overlook is creating custom validators. In this article I show how to create a custom password field validator and how to use it.
Reactive forms create objects that all inherit from the same AbstractControl. The AbstractControl has an errors object property, which is where I can get or set validation errors for the form or particular control. This errors object contains key value pairs. When using the default built-in validation, these key value pairs are predefined with specific (often boolean) values. That means that I would need to evaluate the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elanna Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Luxarg" Text Editor ! liberty + pure python3 !]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-text-editor-liberty-pure-python3-5754</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-text-editor-liberty-pure-python3-5754"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T02:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/ 
        luxarg
      
    
LUXARG is another keyboard friendly text editor.
This project started at August 2019 and restarted at 2021 TODAY!
Easy to use and userfriendly !
LUXARG support :
Fedora, CENTOS and RedHat,
Debian and Ubuntu,
OpenSUSE,
Arch and Manjaro, ...


INSERT MODE : <F1>
SAVE   MODE : <F2>
OPEN   MODE : <F3>



INSTALLATION
$ python<3X> installer.py



dependencies
$ pip3 install -r requirements.txt



update method
$ cd ~/.luxarg
$ python<3X> update.py



Install pip
pip.txt








  
View on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amzy 0 |  محمد امین عظیمی</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Unused Classes in… HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342198</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/detect-unused-classes-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T23:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when “unused” comes up in conversation regarding CSS, it’s about removing chunks of CSS that are not used in your site or, at least, the styles not currently in use on a specific page. The minimal amount of CSS …
The post Detect Unused Classes in… HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Engineering Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60c91b2b4dc1a607ed7b389a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/devops-engineering-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is one of the highest-paying roles you can get at a software company. And even if you aren't working as a DevOps, knowing how it works will make you a more productive developer. We just published a DevOps Engineering course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Learn all about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does &#x27;this&#x27; Mean in JavaScript? The this Keyword Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c72a0ad3126007592d7e2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-this-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand what this truly means in JavaScript, let's take a look at a very similar concept in the English Language: Polysemy. Let's consider the word "run". Run is a single word which could mean many different things depending on the context. “I will run home” – means to move quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Charge as a Freelance Developer – and Why You Should Avoid Being the Cheapest]]></title>
        <id>60c8912c4dc1a607ed7b2fff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-to-charge-as-a-freelance-developer-dont-be-the-cheapest/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a freelance developer, knowing how much to charge for a project can often feel like a gamble. It's easy to wonder "Am I setting my price too high?" This is normally the first question that comes to mind. And your brain will probably meet this question with a resounding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Fraudulent POS ~cybersafety]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/beware-of-fraudulent-pos-cybersafety-4cnh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/beware-of-fraudulent-pos-cybersafety-4cnh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[so dear friends, 
Please share any experiences you may have so others can learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Queries in Times of @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342519</id>
        <link href="https://mxb.dev/blog/media-queries-in-times-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T19:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Böck took me up on my challenge to look through a codebase and see how many of the @media queries could ultimately become @container queries.
I took the bait and had a look at some of my projects – 
…
The post Media Queries in Times of @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need an SSH Access Manager - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before diving into this article I recommend you take 5 minutes to have a read of part 1 of our 2 part, "Why you need an SSH Access Manager" blog series.
Part 1 of our article featured more information on the security aspects for why to use one but in this article, I want to talk more about the "managing" of SSH keys as a reason to use one.
To define which SSH keys have access to your server, each server user has its own directory and within, a folder called .ssh. This folder should have a file called authorized_keys and the purpose of this file is to hold the public key for each SSH key that should have access.
It's a very simple system that works great, as it's a simple case of adding a new public key on a new line in the file and saving it, (or deleting a line to remove access).
This how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Decorators – How to Create and Use Decorators in Python With Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c3dcb3d3126007592d6c6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-decorators-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python decorators allow you to change the behavior of a function without modifying the function itself. In this article I will show you how to create and use decorators. You will see how easy it is to use this advanced Python feature. In this article I will discuss the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just How Niche is Headless WordPress?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342248</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/just-how-niche-is-headless-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder where headless WordPress will land. And by “headless” I mean only using the WordPress admin and building out the user-facing site through the WordPress REST API rather than the traditional WordPress theme structure.
Is it… big? The future …
The post Just How Niche is Headless WordPress? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE CAT COMMAND IN LINUX]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bazeng/the-cat-command-in-linux-1fl0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bazeng/the-cat-command-in-linux-1fl0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T11:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cat(concatenate) command reads data from the file and gives their content as output.
Here are some of the use cases of the command :
$ cat >newfile


Creates a new file called newfile
You may have run into this while checking your os type.
$ cat /etc/os-release

On my Os this outputs:
PRETTY_NAME="Debian GNU/Linux 10 (buster)"
NAME="Debian GNU/Linux"
VERSION_ID="10"
VERSION="10 (buster)"
VERSION_CODENAME=buster
ID=debian
HOME_URL="https://www.debian.org/"
SUPPORT_URL="https://www.debian.org/support"
BUG_REPORT_URL="https://bugs.debian.org/"


$cat [filename-whose-contents-is-to-be-copied] > [destination-filename]


$ cat file1 file2


Outputs contents in file1 and file2 .
$cat file1 >> file2


Will append contents of file1 to file 2
$cat -- "-dashfile"


Will display the content of -dashfile
$cat "filename" | more

$cat "filename1" "filename2" "filename3" > "merged_filename"


Will merge the contents of file in respective order and will insert that content in "merged_filename".
$cat *.html

Will show the content of all html files present in the folder.
$cat >> geeks.txt
The newly added text.

Will append the text "The newly added text." to the end of the file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bazeng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-tables-with-sticky-header-and-footers-got-a-bit-easier/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago when I looked at sticky headers and footers in HTML <table>s in the blog post A table with both a sticky header and a sticky first column. In it, I never used position: sticky on …
The post Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-chronicle-xxxx/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a little link roundup of some off-site stuff I’ve done recently. As I’m wont to do from time to time. 
DevJourney Podcast
#151 Chris Coyier from ceramics to CSS-Tricks and CodePen‘
Chris took us from playing on 
…
The post CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/securing-your-website-with-subresource-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you load a file from an external server, you’re trusting that the content you request is what you expect it to be. Since you don’t manage the server yourself, you’re relying on the security of yet another third party …
The post Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari McMillian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342429</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-new-ui-theme-colors-and-a-css-tricks-cameo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a 33-minute video (and resources) over on apple.com covering the upcoming Safari changes we saw in the WWDC keynote this year in much more detail. Look who’s got a little cameo in there:
Perhaps the most noticeable thing there …
The post Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Possibilities of Syndication]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-possibilities-of-syndication/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the one word that isn’t an adjective in the acronym RSS. 
Really Simple Syndication.
Update: Lol there are literally two mistakes there. RSS is an initialism not an acronym, and “Really” is an adverb not an adjective. 
RSS …
The post The Possibilities of Syndication appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342164</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-shadows-to-svg-icons-with-css-and-svg-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T14:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would we need to apply shadows to SVG?
Shadows are a common design feature that can help elements, like icons, stand out. They could be persistent, or applied in different states (e.g. :hover, :focus, or :active) 
…
The post Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put a Background on Open Details Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/put-a-background-on-open-details-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that can be just a smidge funky about the <details> element is that, when open, it’s not always 100% clear what is inside that element and what isn’t. I’m not saying that always matters or that it’s a …
The post Put a Background on Open Details Elements appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>