<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-16T01:03:46.132Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-16T01:03:46.133Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the most of our startup’s on-call rotation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koan/making-the-most-of-our-startups-on-call-rotation-3mnh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koan/making-the-most-of-our-startups-on-call-rotation-3mnh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T00:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will I have to be on call?
In the last hour of Koan’s on-site interview we turn the tables and invite candidates to interview our hiring team. At face value it’s a chance to answer any open questions we haven’t answered earlier in the process. It’s also a subtle way to introspect on our own hiring process — after three rounds of interviews and side-channel conversations with the hiring manager, what have we missed? What’s on candidates’ minds? Can we address it earlier in the process?
So, you asked, will I have to be on call?
The middle of the night pager rings? The panicked investigations? Remediation, write-ups, post-mortems?
Patrick Collison’s been there, too:
And that's how I ruined ducks for myself.
    
“Don’t ruin the duck.” There are worse guiding principles for an on-call process …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RJ Zaworski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parse your escaped JSON jq and fromjson]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lucassha/parse-your-escaped-json-jq-and-fromjson-4cpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lucassha/parse-your-escaped-json-jq-and-fromjson-4cpn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T23:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was looking at secrets manager in AWS and used the AWS CLI in order to read a secret in my terminal, such as: aws secretsmanager get-secret-value --secret-id arn:aws:secretsmanager:us-west-2:[acct-id]:secret:testing/slack/slack_api_key-y8FHjv --profile [profile] --region us-west-2
This gives the following response:
{
    "ARN": "arn:aws:secretsmanager:us-west-2:[account-id]:secret:testing/slack/slack_api_key-y8FHjv",
    "Name": "testing/slack/slack_api_key",
    "VersionId": "a9a1fc45-80d5-45d0-8884-27d359b55ebd",
    "SecretString": "{\"SLACK_API_KEY\":\"itsasecret\"}",
    "VersionStages": [
        "AWSCURRENT"
    ],
    "CreatedDate": "2021-11-15T15:32:59.737000-08:00"
}

As you can see, the response gave me escaped JSON with \ in front of every " character for the actual…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Props in React]]></title>
        <id>619140bc11d3cb08287a60d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-props-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T23:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll talk about an important concept in React – props. I'll show you how to use them to keep the flow of data in your app dynamic. PrerequisitesIn other to follow along with this tutorial, you will need: A React app.Additionally, I assume that you already understand:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitar o acesso ao serviço de metadados de instâncias EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rafaelonline/limitar-o-acesso-ao-servico-de-metadados-de-instancias-ec2-44kh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rafaelonline/limitar-o-acesso-ao-servico-de-metadados-de-instancias-ec2-44kh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivação


Limitar o acesso aos metadados de uma instância faz parte de uma estratégia de segurança em camadas, que tem como objetivo impedir o acesso aos metadados por usuários/aplicações não autorizadas. 
Essa ação soma-se à utilização do IMDSv2.
Podemos utilizar regras de iptables para limitar o acesso, permitindo acesso a usuários ou grupos específicos.
O exemplo a seguir libera o acesso ao serviço de metadados da instância por todos os processos em execução na conta do usuário "app".
sudo iptables -I OUTPUT 1 --proto tcp --destination 169.254.169.254 --match owner --uid-owner app--jump ACCEPT

O exemplo a seguir impede o acesso ao serviço de metadados da instância por todos os processos, exceto os processos em execução na conta do usuário root.
sudo iptables --append OUTPUT --proto tcp --destination 169.254.169.254 --match owner ! --uid-owner root --jump REJECT

A ordem é fundamental, a regra de bloqueio deverá ser a última.
Obs.: O módulo owner do iptables só corresponderá à associação do grupo se o grupo for o grupo primário de um determinado usuário local. Outros grupos não são correspondidos.
Criei uma role Ansile para ser utilizada na configuração das instancias ou no processo de criação de AMIs
Repositório: EC2 Metadata Service restrict access
A configuração o acesso ao metadata está sendo limitado somente ao usuário root e/ou aqueles usuários que realizam sudo
As configurações foram feitas seguindo as seguintes documentações:
Documentação oficial da AWS
Apresentação sobre EC2 instance metadata
PDF da Apresentação sobre EC2 instance metadata
Documentação oficial do Ansible - Módulo Iptables]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Conceição</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitar o acesso ao serviço de metadados de instâncias EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rafaelonline/limitar-o-acesso-ao-servico-de-metadados-de-instancias-ec2-44kh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rafaelonline/limitar-o-acesso-ao-servico-de-metadados-de-instancias-ec2-44kh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivação


Limitar o acesso aos metadados de uma instância faz parte de uma estratégia de segurança em camadas, que tem como objetivo impedir o acesso aos metadados por usuários/aplicações não autorizadas. 
Essa ação soma-se à utilização do IMDSv2.
Podemos utilizar regras de iptables para limitar o acesso, permitindo acesso a usuários ou grupos específicos.
O exemplo a seguir libera o acesso ao serviço de metadados da instância por todos os processos em execução na conta do usuário "app".
sudo iptables -I OUTPUT 1 --proto tcp --destination 169.254.169.254 --match owner --uid-owner app--jump ACCEPT

O exemplo a seguir impede o acesso ao serviço de metadados da instância por todos os processos, exceto os processos em execução na conta do usuário root.
sudo iptables --append OUTPUT --proto tcp --destination 169.254.169.254 --match owner ! --uid-owner root --jump REJECT

A ordem é fundamental, a regra de bloqueio deverá ser a última.
Obs.: O módulo owner do iptables só corresponderá à associação do grupo se o grupo for o grupo primário de um determinado usuário local. Outros grupos não são correspondidos.
Criei uma role Ansile para ser utilizada na configuração das instancias ou no processo de criação de AMIs
Repositório: EC2 Metadata Service restrict access
A configuração o acesso ao metadata está sendo limitado somente ao usuário root e/ou aqueles usuários que realizam sudo
As configurações foram feitas seguindo as seguintes documentações:
Documentação oficial da AWS
Apresentação sobre EC2 instance metadata
PDF da Apresentação sobre EC2 instance metadata
Documentação oficial do Ansible - Módulo Iptables]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Conceição</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to generate a TypeScript client from a Swagger documented API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/po5i/how-to-generate-a-typescript-client-from-a-swagger-documented-api-14d8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/po5i/how-to-generate-a-typescript-client-from-a-swagger-documented-api-14d8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous tutorial, I built a simple REST API with Swagger documentation. Check it out:
How to set up a REST API in Flask in 5 steps
Carlos Villavicencio ・ Nov 5 ・ 4 min read
#python
        #rest
        #api
        #flask
      
In this tutorial, I will generate a TypeScript client code based on the Swagger documentation and use it on a simple React application (it can be any front-end application).
Why we want to do something like this? First of all, it's better to have one a single source of truth for the contracts in our server-client architecture. Otherwise, one change can break all our consumers.
For this process, I'm gonna use swagger-typescript-api. I've seen this tool constantly evolving throughout the last year, its maintainers are doing an awesome job.
First of all, I boo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Villavicencio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Node.js/Express app + MongoDB with jest and supertest]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shyamajp/testing-nodejsexpress-app-mongodb-with-jest-and-supertest-56ce</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shyamajp/testing-nodejsexpress-app-mongodb-with-jest-and-supertest-56ce"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


I find it quite hard to find the right steps when you already have a set of technologies in your project, and as the title goes, my target audience are those who already know how to develop a backend application in Express + MongoDB but not how to write tests for it. If you are still with me, let's get started. 
Node.js
JavaScript runtime environment outside of browser
Express
Backend application framework for Node.js
MongoDB
NoSQL database like JSON.
Jest
JavsScript testing framework maintained by Facebook
supertest
npm package that helps test HTTP
Prepare a mongodb in memory server for testing
Write tests with jest and supertest
(Optional) Set up NODE_ENV to test




  
  
  Prepare a mongodb in memory server for testing


First, install the in-memory-mongodb-server with t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shyamajp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate WebVTT and SRT Captions Automatically with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepgram/generate-webvtt-and-srt-captions-automatically-with-nodejs-3jkp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepgram/generate-webvtt-and-srt-captions-automatically-with-nodejs-3jkp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Providing captions for audio and video isn't just a nice-to-have - it's critical for accessibility. While this isn't specifically an accessibility post, I wanted to start by sharing Microsoft's Inclusive Toolkit. Something I hadn't considered before reading this was the impact of situational limitations. To learn more, jump to Section 3 of the toolkit - "Solve for one, extend to many". Having a young (read "loud") child, I've become even more aware of where captions are available, and if they aren't, I simply can't watch something with her around.
There are two common and similar caption formats we are going to generate today - WebVTT and SRT. A WebVTT file looks like this:
WEBVTT

1
00:00:00.219 --> 00:00:03.512
- yeah, as much as it's worth celebrating

2
00:00:04.569 --> 00:00:06.226
- …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transcribe Videos With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepgram/transcribe-videos-with-nodejs-38ia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepgram/transcribe-videos-with-nodejs-38ia"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether your video is hosted online or on your machine, for accessibility or analysis, Deepgram can provide accurate transcriptions in just a few lines of code.
I'm glad you're here, but I must confess that I am leading you down a path slightly different to what you would expect. Instead of transcribing video directly, this post will cover converting video files to audio files and then sending them to Deepgram. First, we will transcribe local files, and then we will download files programatically before transcribing them.
You will need:
Node.js installed on your machine - download it here.
A Deepgram project API key - get one here.
A video file to transcribe - here's one you can download and place in your new project directory.
A link to a hosted video file - here is the same video's direc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML FormData para JSON]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/guiseek/html-formdata-para-json-1i6i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/guiseek/html-formdata-para-json-1i6i"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[É possível converter os dados de um formulário HTML para JSON de forma muito prática.
Primeiro selecionamos nosso elemento form
Então criamos uma instância de FormData usando nosso form
Então podemos usando Object.fromEntries usando o método entries da instância FormData




const form = document.querySelector('form')
const data = new FormData(form)
const values = Object.fromEntries(data.entries())
console.log(values)

Desta forma temos todos elementos do formulário mapeados num objeto JSON, como esperado.
Espero ter ajudado, valeeeeu
[]s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guilherme Siquinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Censor Profanity with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepgram/automatically-censor-profanity-with-nodejs-21jp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepgram/automatically-censor-profanity-with-nodejs-21jp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Deepgram we run GRAM JAM - a series of internal hackathons to have Deepgrammers build cool projects using our own API. Sometimes the projects lead to product improvements, sometimes they get a laugh, and other times they are just super useful. This blog post is based on one of those projects - Bleepgram - built by the very interdisciplinary team of Faye Donnelley, Mike Stivaletti , Conner Goodrum, Claudia Ring, and Anthony Deschamps.
Sometimes we all let "unprovoked or unintended utterances" slip out of our mouth, and often it's the job of an editor to go through recordings and overlay a bleep so no one has to hear the original word. Historically this has been a manual process, but with Deepgram's Speech Recognition API we can work to censor them automatically.
If you want to look …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transcribe YouTube Videos with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepgram/transcribe-youtube-videos-with-nodejs-47bh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepgram/transcribe-youtube-videos-with-nodejs-47bh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T21:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post we will be creating transcripts for YouTube videos using Deepgram's Speech Recognition API. First, we will download videos and convert them to mp3 audio files. Then, we will use Deepgram to generate a transcript. Finally, we will store the transcript in a text file and delete the media file.
We need a sample video, so I am using a Shang-Chi and The Legend of The Ten Rings teaser trailer - if that is a spoiler for you please go ahead and grab another video link.





  
  
  Before We Start


You will need:
Node.js installed on your machine - download it here.
A Deepgram project API key - get one here.
A YouTube Video ID which is part of the URL of a video. The one we will be using is ir-mWUYH_uo.
Create a new directory and navigate to it with your terminal. Run npm init -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Começando um projeto Web com TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/guiseek/comecando-um-projeto-web-com-typescript-588f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/guiseek/comecando-um-projeto-web-com-typescript-588f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Para começar um projeto do zero, simples, usando HTML, CSS, TypeScript e ESBuild.
Precisa fazer as seguintes etapas:
Criar o diretório com o nome do seu projeto
Criar o package.json
Criar o tsconfig.json
Instalar as dependências


esbuild
esbuild-serve
typescript
prettier
Criar o diretório src
Escrever o TypeScript inicial dentro de src

Criar o diretório public/styles
Escrever o HTML inicial dentro de public

Escrever o CSS inicial dentro de public/styles

Criar a configuração do ESBuild
Criar a configuração do prettier
Adicionar "type": "module" ao package.json

Adicionar o script de build ao package.json

Adicionar o script de start ao package.json

Executar o npm start



Ou então compactar tudo isso em um script bash e usa-lo da seguinte forma
./create-project.sh meu-projeto

Segue o código do script
Ele é extremamente simples e resolve o propósito com excelência.
Espero ter ajudado, até a próxima.
[]s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guilherme Siquinelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is IPTV? IPTV Service Guide]]></title>
        <id>618216148bcfae07ca4e072f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-iptv-ip-tv-service-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IPTV stands for Internet Protocol Television. It's a service you can use to watch your favorite TV shows without needing to sign up for cable. But how does it work exactly? In this article, I will break down the different types of IPTV services including free and paid services.  What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing environment variables to GitHub Actions using dotenv]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shyamajp/passing-environment-variables-to-github-actions-using-dotenv-hlb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shyamajp/passing-environment-variables-to-github-actions-using-dotenv-hlb"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR - Create .env file using GitHub Secrets before running tests in your workflow file
My backend project, written in TypeScript/Express, uses dotenv for environment variables. dotenv package takes variables in from .env file, but when I looked for a solution, everyone had env or with inside workflow file, which never worked for me. So I had to figure out something else.
Add secrets to your repository
Add a step to create .env file inside your workflow
Go to repository's Settings page



Go to Secrets from the sidebar menu



Click New repository secret to add secrets
GITHUB_.




  
  
  Add a step to create .env file in your GitHub workflow


Now that you have all secrets set up, you can access to them by ${{ secrets.YOUR_SECRET_NAME }}. Below is a working example workflow file.
/.gith…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shyamajp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[External Hard Drive Not Showing Up? Disk Management in Windows 10 Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>61923fda11d3cb08287a65ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/external-hard-drive-not-showing-up-disk-management-in-windows-10-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[External hard drives let you back up your files. With external drives, you can also easily move files from one computer to another - especially when you get a new computer.  But sometimes when you're trying to back up or retrieve files from an external hard drive, the drive might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding TypeScript & Using it in Your Node Environment.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giwajossy/understanding-typescript-using-it-in-your-node-environment-3355</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giwajossy/understanding-typescript-using-it-in-your-node-environment-3355"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T19:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I struggled with this concept a lot, but let me save you the stress, and explain as simply as I can.
Typescript is just a secure way of writing JavaScript code. Do not get confused by the fancy terminologies people throw around it.
The good news is, if you know JavaScript, you already know ~90% of Typescript. The additional layer only forces you to be a lot more intentional about your variables and data types.
...
Simple answer? To catch errors early in your editor. 
...
let id = 1
let company = "GYRO Design Lab"
let isPublished = true
let mandem = ["Dexter", "Mide", "Emmy"]


But the unfortunate thing here is that, at some point later in your code, the variable company - for instance, could be re-assigned to a value of an entirely different data type, which would be unexpected behavior. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giwa Jossy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding TypeScript & Using it in Your Node Environment.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giwajossy/understanding-typescript-using-it-in-your-node-environment-3355</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giwajossy/understanding-typescript-using-it-in-your-node-environment-3355"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T19:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I struggled with this concept a lot, but let me save you the stress, and explain as simply as I can.
Typescript is just a secure way of writing JavaScript code. Do not get confused by the fancy terminologies people throw around it.
The good news is, if you know JavaScript, you already know ~90% of Typescript. The additional layer only forces you to be a lot more intentional about your variables and data types.
...
Simple answer? To catch errors early in your editor. 
...
let id = 1
let company = "GYRO Design Lab"
let isPublished = true
let mandem = ["Dexter", "Mide", "Emmy"]


But the unfortunate thing here is that, at some point later in your code, the variable company - for instance, could be re-assigned to a value of an entirely different data type, which would be unexpected behavior. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giwa Jossy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing OpenShift Container
Platform 4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedshendy/introducing-openshift-containerplatform-4-16mc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedshendy/introducing-openshift-containerplatform-4-16mc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T18:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Container Platform 4 Architecture


Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform 4 (RHOCP 4) is a set of modular components and services built on top of Red Hat CoreOS and Kubernetes.
The following diagram illustrates the high-level logical overview of the OpenShift Container Platform 4 architecture.

The following diagram illustrates the OpenShift Container Platform stack.

From bottom to top, and from left to right, this shows the basic container infrastructure, integrated and enhanced by Red Hat:
Red Hat CoreOS is the base OS on top which OpenShift runs. Red Hat CoreOS is a Linux distribution focused on providing an immutable operating system for container execution.
CRI-O is an implementation of the Kubernetes Container Runtime Interface (CRI) to enable using Open Container Initiativ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Shendy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Arccticy™?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arccticy/what-is-arccticy-8hc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arccticy/what-is-arccticy-8hc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T18:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arccticy™ Chat



  
  
  What is it?


Arccticy™ Chat is an open-source, simple, (for now), chat platform.
Product Manager: (1 person)@dudeactualdev
Head Developer: (2 ppl)(Taken - @Lankdev @StringentDev)(Advantages: Team Admin)
Designer: (2 people)(Open - @ch1ck3n)) 
Back-end development: (3 people)(Available - @natethemaker, @zplusfour)
Marketing Assistant: (1 person)(Taken - @natethemaker)
Developer: (2 people)(Available)
Design
User Interface
Landing Page
Components
Templates
Desktop app with Electron.JS (All devs)
Mobile app with Flutter? (Optional)
Skeleton shimmers (better than using a circular indicator as it tells the user what type of content to expect)
Implement
SPA routing (No reloading for moving channels/servers and to all pages)
Video Chat (P2P?)
Custom Database module (Stringent)
API server (Stringent)
Clusters module (standard nodejs module)
Subscription service using API (NOT POSSIBLE ON REPL)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>masspopcorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speeding Up Docker Builds with Remote Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/martinheinz/speeding-up-docker-builds-with-remote-cache-4890</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/martinheinz/speeding-up-docker-builds-with-remote-cache-4890"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T18:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building images in CI/CD pipeline can be quite different from builds on local machine. One major difference is availability of cache. In the local environment you most likely have all the resources, dependencies and image layers cached from previous builds and therefore your builds might take just a few seconds. In the CI pipeline on the other hand, there's no local cache, which can cause the builds to take several minutes. There's solution to this though, and in this article we will look at how we can solve it both with and without Docker and for any CI/CD platform you might be using.
The idea for the generic solution that would work in any environment is pretty simple - we need to somehow create or bring the cache to the pipeline. We have 2 options here - either we point the builder tool…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Heinz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is .gitkeep? How to Track and Push Empty Folders in Git]]></title>
        <id>6171abc8d48e1707b6d79990</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-gitkeep/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T18:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you need to completely restructure the directories of your codebase. You need to move some folders higher, move some other folders lower, and move lots of files into some new folders you're going to create. You start shifting the code around, checking that everything works, and adding some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[📈 Introducing Cost Savings for Nonprofits on All Auth0 Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/introducing-cost-savings-for-nonprofits-on-all-auth0-plans-3nai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/introducing-cost-savings-for-nonprofits-on-all-auth0-plans-3nai"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T18:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👤 Continuing our Pledge to create SAFEr Social Impact Organizations.



  
  
  
As a former business owner, nonprofit board member, developer, and volunteer; I know of one consistent, daunting, universal expenditure all modern organizations face - their tech stack. While some items, such as hardware, have a front-loaded cost that can be justified and managed through a lifetime; taking an uncertain “digital leap” for philanthropic entities can be challenging. Even when it's known and agreed that improvements to legacy systems and tools are needed, or that building something completely custom from the ground up to meet the demands of a digital-first economy is in order, there is always trepidation when it comes to modernization and understandably so.
All these issues are even more challeng…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future Javascript: Javascript Pipeline Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smpnjn/future-javascript-javascript-pipeline-operators-5jj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smpnjn/future-javascript-javascript-pipeline-operators-5jj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pipeline operators are an upcoming feature to Javascript which gives us another way to pass values through a series of transformations. It gives more context to what developers were trying to achieve when they wrote their code, and allow us to do some cool things to boot. Here, we'll take a quick look at pipeline operators, how they work, and how you can use them today.
Currently, no browser or server side ECMAScript implementation (like Node.JS) support pipeline operators. You can, however, get them to work using Babel 7.15. You can learn more about installing Babel here, but suffice to say this will allow you to add pipeline operators into your code.
Pipeline operators are simply another way to manipulate values in Javascript. The pipeline operator is |>. Suppose we have 3 mathematical f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johnny Simpson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run the freeCodeCamp Backend Challenges Locally]]></title>
        <id>6190f0c811d3cb08287a5f96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-the-freecodecamp-backend-challenges-locally/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the freeCodeCamp Back End Development and APIs certification, you can do all of the challenges locally and submit the local server link. But how does that work exactly? In this article, I will walk you through step by step how to setup the backend challenges on your local computer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barcode Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fkkarakurt/barcode-generator-45id</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fkkarakurt/barcode-generator-45id"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This repo is designed to convert any data, number and text into barcode. The barcode you produce is valid everywhere and when you read it with a barcode reader, it shows the data you entered. It is a very practical and fast way to encrypt or organize products.
Any data you convert to barcode will be valid everywhere. You can scan and save them with the barcode reader and organize the products in a shop.
In addition, you can use your passwords or data that you do not want anyone to see by converting them to barcodes.
It is not risky to make this conversion on the website. Because it is completely coded with vanilla JS. Since there is no database or registration network, you can use it with peace of mind. 
Also, your comments and interest are very important to me. I look forward to your feedback.
Take care and don't forget to fork :)
Github
Preview]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatih Küçükkarakurt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Popular ES6 Interview Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/priteshbhoi/most-popular-es6-interview-questions-4nf9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/priteshbhoi/most-popular-es6-interview-questions-4nf9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FULL Article Is Here https://bhylu.com/interview-questions/es6-interview-questions-and-answers/
Some of the common ES6 features are:
Supports constants/immutable variables.
The object-oriented features supported in ES6 are:
Classes: We can create classes in ES6. The class function essentially builds a template from which we may later create objects. When a new instance of the class is created, the constructor method is invoked.
ES5 ES6
What is the difference between let and const? What distinguishes both from var?
When declaring any variable in JavaScript, we used the var keyword. Var is a function scoped keyword. Within a function, we can access the variable. When we need to create a new scope, we wrap the code in a function.
Both let and const have block scope. If you use these keywords to declare a variable, it will only exist within the innermost block that surrounds them. If you declare a variable with let inside a block (for example, if a condition or a for-loop), it can only be accessed within that block.
The variables declared with the let keyword are mutable, which means that their values can be changed. It's akin to the var keyword, but with the added benefit of block scoping. The variables declared with the const keyword are block-scoped and immutable. When variables are declared with the const keyword, their value cannot be modified or reassigned.
In ES6, arrow functions are introduced. The shorthand syntax for writing ES6 functions is arrow functions. The arrow function's definition consists of parameters, followed by an arrow (=>), and the function's body.
The 'fat arrow' function is another name for the Arrow function. We won't be able to employ them as constructors.
const function_name = (arg_1, arg_2, arg_3, ...) => {

    //body of the function

} 
It reduces the size of the code.
https://bhylu.com/interview-questions/es6-interview-questions-and-answers/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pritesh Bhoi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Questions New Developers Ask When Learning How to Code]]></title>
        <id>61870b688bcfae07ca4e31f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/questions-new-developers-ask-when-learning-how-to-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're relatively new to coding, you surely have some questions – how should you get started, what should you learn first, what does "front-end development" really mean...? In this article, I've shared 7 questions I had when I first started learning to code about 20 years ago (man, now I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing the JFrog Xray “Summary View” in Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jfrog/implementing-the-jfrog-xray-summary-view-in-slack-o3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jfrog/implementing-the-jfrog-xray-summary-view-in-slack-o3j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to get your engineering teams real-time information about security issues happening during software development? As you may know, JFrog Xray already allows you to scan the entire composition of your binaries and enables you to send alerts to your teams using webhooks, but now with our new Slack integration we make it quite easy for entire channels to be updated in real time. The integration further allows teams to discuss new CVE's with developers on other teams as well. In order to make the JFrog Xray notifications super digestible in Slack, we built a whole new way to view your vulnerabilities and license compliance issues.
The integration with Slack uses Jfrog Xray’s security and license compliance policies to trigger webhook events whenever a new violation is detec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Hung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Secrets in GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/officialcookj/azure-key-vault-secrets-in-github-actions-1naf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/officialcookj/azure-key-vault-secrets-in-github-actions-1naf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental rule to a secret is to not share a secret. Once shared it's more likely going to be shared again and in an unsecure format, but how do we keep a secret a secret?
When it comes to Cloud technology we can use resources that store our sensitive information in a secure environment. For example, Azure Key Vault allows us to store secrets, certificates and keys where we can set access control using authentication methods like Azure AD.
But when we add secrets into a secure resource like Key Vault, how do we access them when running deployments?
In this blog post I will be covering how we get the secrets from an Azure Key Vault for a deployment in GitHub Actions.
We will need login to Azure using the Azure CLI. The first workflow step will be the following:
      - name: Azure CLI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Key Vault Secrets in GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/officialcookj/azure-key-vault-secrets-in-github-actions-1naf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/officialcookj/azure-key-vault-secrets-in-github-actions-1naf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental rule to a secret is to not share a secret. Once shared it's more likely going to be shared again and in an unsecure format, but how do we keep a secret a secret?
When it comes to Cloud technology we can use resources that store our sensitive information in a secure environment. For example, Azure Key Vault allows us to store secrets, certificates and keys where we can set access control using authentication methods like Azure AD.
But when we add secrets into a secure resource like Key Vault, how do we access them when running deployments?
In this blog post I will be covering how we get the secrets from an Azure Key Vault for a deployment in GitHub Actions.
We will need login to Azure using the Azure CLI. The first workflow step will be the following:
      - name: Azure CLI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful Software Development in a Hybrid Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/trustacks1/successful-software-development-in-a-hybrid-environment-5ck</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/trustacks1/successful-software-development-in-a-hybrid-environment-5ck"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remote work, especially for software development teams, is continuing to increase as digital transformation continues to evolve. We have learned that many people prefer working from home due to less time spent commuting, more productivity, and flexibility. Hybrid environments and emerging technologies are making it possible to meet customer demands while remaining effective in organizational expectations.
https://devops.com/successful-software-development-in-a-hybrid-environment/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TruStacks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consistency vs flexibility when building components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/consistency-vs-flexibility-when-building-components-i34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/consistency-vs-flexibility-when-building-components-i34"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago I asked Twitter how would one solve the task of implementing a button component that can also display an icon. Is it by adding an icon property to the button component or by having a separate icon component nested inside the button? I also asked why would one choose one approach over the other.

Quite a few people replied with their pros and cons for both options. In this post I’m going to try and summarize the points mentioned there. I think that’s quite valuable to have as a reference in the future.
icon property on a button component



  
  
  Pros



Convention - only one way to display an icon
Consistency - all buttons with an icon will look the same across the app/product
Simpler syntax to remember
Simple at first but might become complex later on when more requiremen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dzhavat Ushev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔐 Structure of a single-page Vue 3 (TypeScript) app using JWT authorization requests to the backend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koddr/structure-of-a-single-page-vue-3-typescript-app-using-jwt-authorization-requests-to-the-backend-2lm0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koddr/structure-of-a-single-page-vue-3-typescript-app-using-jwt-authorization-requests-to-the-backend-2lm0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello, DEV World! 👋
This weekend I had time to refactor my old projects, where I found an interesting case of working with JWT in a Vue.js web application, which I'll tell you about now.
🔥 Disclaimer: The article is intended primarily for advanced frontend developers, because it does not contain a beginner's description of technologies in use. You should already understand how the Vue 3.x framework and Vuex 4.x works, and the basics of JWT.
OK, let's go! 😉

A lyrical digression about the backend
The main component of the Vue app


The structure of the business logic
Function for updating tokens
Function for calling the background update tokens
The result we got

I believe that without a description of the backend scheme, it is impossible to understand my implementation in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vic Shóstak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Angular, React, Vue, and Vanilla-JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/comparing-angular-react-vue-and-vanilla-js-37o9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/comparing-angular-react-vue-and-vanilla-js-37o9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's take an analytical look at several of the key library / frameworks and compare them to Vanilla JavaScript.
Basically, I want to explore these tools in various ways:
Installation Processes
Setup Processes
Code Management
Routing
Binding Props
Binding Events
Services (API Access, etc.)
Referencing Assets
Unit Testing
Code Execution (Build Process and Size)
To do this, four separate builds of the same project were implemented. There were three "frameworks":
Angular
React
Vue
And, the fourth build was Vanilla JS.
The core logic was complex enough to use several parts of the frameworks, but simple enough I could build this in a reasonable time frame.



Category
Angular
React
Vue
Vanilla-JavaScript




Code (assets 4.2M)
19k
28k
21k
232k


Build (assets 4.2M)
273k + assets
760k + assets
1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.ts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Swipe Animations to a CardView in an Android App]]></title>
        <id>618e548011d3cb08287a4e09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-swipe-animations-to-a-card-view-in-android-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building an Android app, you should consider adding animations. They can improve your app's user experience and increase retention.  These days, if you see an app that has no animation, it can feel odd and out-dated. And since interactive experiences are kind of the new norm, you'll want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My first Hacktoberfest experience 2021!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codemastersk/my-first-hacktoberfest-experience-2021-20ia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codemastersk/my-first-hacktoberfest-experience-2021-20ia"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a great experience.I learned a lot of new things about open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saurav kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy your package documentation on GitHub Pages in the RTD style: preview PRs, and more!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/epassaro/deploy-your-package-documentation-on-github-pages-in-the-rtd-style-preview-prs-and-more-ogf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/epassaro/deploy-your-package-documentation-on-github-pages-in-the-rtd-style-preview-prs-and-more-ogf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was published during the GitHub Actions Hackathon 2021
In the recent years, a lot of Python package developers moved their documentation pipelines from third party services like ReadTheDocs to GitHub Pages, but some useful features were missing in the process.
In this post, I'm going to describe how to write an -almost- complete RTD pipeline for GitHub Actions.
Support of pip and conda dependency files.
Build and deploy branches under /branches/<branch>.
Build and deploy tags under /tags/<tag>

Secure build and preview of pull requests under /pull/<number> via labels.
Manual trigger for branches.
Select branch to deploy the site (default: gh-pages).
Redirect the main domain to /latest or /stable (default: /latest).
Redirect the /stable subdomain to the latest SemVer tag, or the s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>epassaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Masonry Layout with TailwindCSS in 2 Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kdrbek06/responsive-masonry-layout-with-tailwindcss-in-2-steps-4kkj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kdrbek06/responsive-masonry-layout-with-tailwindcss-in-2-steps-4kkj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Masonry views on a website are visually appealing. Let's quickly create a carousel with you using TailwindCSS. This article assumes basic knowledge of Tailwind.
First of all, let's add @layer to your index.css file in src folder. We create masonry layout class for 3 different screen;
.masonry         (1 column)
@tailwind base;
@tailwind components;
@tailwind utilities;

@layer utilities {
    @variants responsive {
        .masonry {
            column-gap: 1.5em;
            column-count: 1;
        }
        .masonry-sm {
            column-gap: 1.5em;
            column-count: 2;
        }
        .masonry-md {
            column-gap: 1.5em;
            column-count: 3;
        }
        .break-inside {
            break-inside: avoid;
        }

    }
}

Now you can use these classes as standard TailwindCSS feature. You should use them inside parent div.
<div className="masonry sm:masonry-sm md:masonry-md">

  <div className="rounded-lg bg-gray-500 p-4 break-inside">
    <p> lorem100 </p>
  </div>
  <div className="rounded-lg bg-gray-500 p-4 break-inside">
    <p> lorem150 </p>
  </div>
  <div className="rounded-lg bg-gray-500 p-4 break-inside">
    <p> lorem50 </p>
  </div>
  <div className="rounded-lg bg-gray-500 p-4 break- inside">
    <p> lorem200 </p>
  </div>

</div>

That is all. You now have a masonry layout that is simple to use and looks good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kdrbek06</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/defining-and-applying-ui-themes-using-the-mimcss-css-in-js-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Theming UI refers to the ability to perform a change in visual styles in a consistent manner that defines the “look and feel” of a site. Swapping color palettes, à la dark mode or some other means, is a good …
The post Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Michlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ใช้ SSH config ช่วยจำ option เวลาจะ remote ด้วย SSH]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iporsut/aich-ssh-config-chwyccham-option-ewlaaccha-remote-dwy-ssh-3f1d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iporsut/aich-ssh-config-chwyccham-option-ewlaaccha-remote-dwy-ssh-3f1d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SSH config ช่วยให้เรา config option ของแต่ละ host เอาไว้หลายๆอันได้ ทำให้ตอนเรียก ssh ใส่แค่ชื่อ hostname ใน config ก็พอแล้ว
เวลาใช้ ssh เพื่อ remote เครื่องอื่น ปกติแล้วจะสั่งประมาณนี้
ssh user@hostname

หรือถ้ามี port ที่ต่างจาก ssh ปกติ (22) ก็ใส่ option สำหรับ port เพิ่มคือ
ssh -p 2222 user@hostname

หรือถ้ามี IdentityFile ด้วย ก็ต้องเพิ่ม option ไปอีกแบบนี้
ssh -i identity.key -p 2222 user@hostname

ตัวอย่างเช่นผมจะ ssh เข้า Ubuntu ที่ลงไว้ใน Virtual Box โดยใช้ vagrant ปกติแล้วจะสั่ง vagrant ssh ก็ได้ แต่ถ้าจะสั่งด้วย ssh เองโดยตรงจะต้องสั่งประมาณนี้
ssh -i ~/vagrants/ubuntu/.vagrant/machines/default/virtualbox/private_key -p 2222 vagrant@127.0.0.1

ทีนี้ถ้าเราจะใช้ SSH config ช่วยเราก็สร้างไฟล์ config ที่ $HOME/.ssh/config
จากนั้นกำหนดค่าแบบนี้
Host ubuntu-vagrant
  HostName 127.0.0.1
  IdentityFile ~/vagrants/ubuntu/.vagrant/machines/default/virtualbox/private_key
  Port 2222
  User vagrant

ลักษณะ config file ของ SSH ก็มี key เช่น Host, HostName, IdentityFile, Port และ User แล้วเว้นวรรคด้วย 1 ช่องว่าง ตามด้วยค่าที่กำหนดให้ key นั้นๆ 
แล้วก็มีการใช้ indentation เพื่อบอกว่าค่านั้นเป็น key/value ย่อยๆของ key หลักอีกที
จากตัวอย่างผมกำหนด Host คือ ubuntu-vagrant แล้วก็กำหนดค่า HostName เป็น IP หรือ Domain name ของ Host ที่เราต้องการต่อ แล้วก็ค่า IdentityFile ไปที่ path ของ private key ของ vagrant ที่กำหนดให้กับ VM ที่ต้องการ remote ตามด้วยค่า Port 2222 แล้วก็​ User คือ username ในทีนี้คือ vagrant
เสร็จแล้วหลังจากนั้นเวลาเราต้องการ connect ไปที่ Ubuntu ใน VM ก็แค่สั่ง
ssh ubuntu-vagrant

เท่านี้ก็ได้แล้ว]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Weerasak Chongnguluam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplest way to compile all TypeScript into one single Js file by SilvenLEAF]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/silvenleaf/simplest-way-to-compile-all-typescript-into-one-single-js-file-19bj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/silvenleaf/simplest-way-to-compile-all-typescript-into-one-single-js-file-19bj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahoy there! It's I, SilvenLEAF!! Have you ever faced an issue where you have many TypeScript files but want them all to convert into one Single JavaScript file so that you can reference it from your HTML? Then fear you not! Let's get it done in the simplest way!! 
We'll be using Webpack with TypeScript. Let's start!
Create a folder and open it in your favorite editor (mine VS Code). Then type this command on your project terminal
npm init -y

(It'll create a package.json file to track all the packages that you'd download and so on)
For those who are a bit lost on how to set up the environment and run the TypeScript files, check this one out TypeScript SETUP by SilvenLEAF
Well anyway, in short (for details, checkout the above link)
install typescript




npm i typescript 

init our tsconfig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SilvenLEAF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is DevOps a legacy practice?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/peibolsang/is-devops-a-legacy-practice-4g66</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/peibolsang/is-devops-a-legacy-practice-4g66"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Cover picture credits: Sigmund @sigmund via Unsplash)
The idea of this article is expalined in detail in the book Building Software Platforms. A Guide to SaaS Transition with AWS available on Leanpub and Amazon
The commoditization of cloud compute and the proliferation (and adoption) of managed cloud services during the first years of the past decade enabled the co-evolution of other software engineering practices that helped teams build and release software faster. This progression eventually led to DevOps, a technique that has helped reduce the dependency on a centralized operations team during the software development lifecycle.
But things have changed. We just don't do cloud anymore. I mean, this is what we do 10 years ago when we spun up virtual machines on the cloud and installed We…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Bermejo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is free memory in Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yugabyte/what-is-free-memory-in-linux-18km</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yugabyte/what-is-free-memory-in-linux-18km"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blogpost is about linux memory management, and specifically about the question that has been asked about probably any operating system throughout history: how much free memory do I need to consider it to be healthy?
To start off, a reference to a starwars quote: 'This is not the free memory you're looking for'. 
What this quote means to say is that whilst the free memory statistic obviously shows free memory, what you are actually looking for is the amount of memory that can be used for memory allocations on the system. On linux, this is not the same as free memory.
Of course free memory is directly available, actually free memory, which can be directly used by a process that needs free memory (a free page). A free page is produced by the kernel page daemon (commonly named 'swapper'),…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frits Hoogland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Query in Apache CouchDB: Clouseau]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-clouseau-41ll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-clouseau-41ll"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles, we have talk about how to query with CouchDB Views and Mango Query. Both methods are working very well and able to cover a lot of use cases. Why Clouseau?
There are still very limited for CouchDB Views and Mango Query when we talk about search, there are a lot of complex searching required which makes the Views function and Mango Index more complex and harder to build, at the same time need to have a great search performance. You are still able to build your own search engine from scratch with Mango and Views. However it is very tough and you have to put a lot of resources to build a good search engine, ton of work like text preprocessing, tokenization, algorithm, ranking and etc...😰

Start from CouchDB v3, CouchDB can build and query full-text search indexes using a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Soo Yen Yih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Key Management Service Best Practices | AWS White Paper Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/aws-key-management-service-best-practices-aws-white-paper-summary-3ci3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/aws-key-management-service-best-practices-aws-white-paper-summary-3ci3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T11:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) is a managed service that allows you to concentrate on the cryptographic needs of your applications while Amazon Web Services (AWS) manages availability, physical security, logical access control, and maintenance of the underlying infrastructure. 
Further, AWS KMS allows you to audit usage of your keys by providing logs of all API calls made on them to help you meet compliance and regulatory requirements.
Customers want to know how to effectively implement AWS KMS in their environment. 
This whitepaper discusses how to use AWS KMS for each capability described in the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework Security Perspective whitepaper, including the differences between the different types of customer master keys, using AWS KMS key policies to ensure least privi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding TypeScript-support to your Node.js project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhaeussermann/adding-typescript-support-to-your-nodejs-project-3bfm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhaeussermann/adding-typescript-support-to-your-nodejs-project-3bfm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T11:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Node.js projects will reach a level of complexity where we'll often find ourselves wondering what a certain object's structure looks like. We'll also have the need for early warnings about errors due to trying to access fields that don't exist or assuming different types from what they really are. These are good indications that you would derive a lot of benefit from using a type-checking system such as TypeScript. This article will look into how to make the transition from JavaScript to TypeScript in an existing project.
TypeScript-support for Node.js is provided by the typescript NPM package. The best way to implement this package will depend on your project's build tooling. If you have webpack set up, then the easiest way will be by using the ts-loader package (see the "Setting up …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernhard Häussermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding TypeScript-support to your Node.js project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhaeussermann/adding-typescript-support-to-your-nodejs-project-3bfm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhaeussermann/adding-typescript-support-to-your-nodejs-project-3bfm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T11:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Node.js projects will reach a level of complexity where we'll often find ourselves wondering what a certain object's structure looks like. We'll also have the need for early warnings about errors due to trying to access fields that don't exist or assuming different types from what they really are. These are good indications that you would derive a lot of benefit from using a type-checking system such as TypeScript. This article will look into how to make the transition from JavaScript to TypeScript in an existing project.
TypeScript-support for Node.js is provided by the typescript NPM package. The best way to implement this package will depend on your project's build tooling. If you have webpack set up, then the easiest way will be by using the ts-loader package (see the "Setting up …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernhard Häussermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My frequently bugs using Firebase & Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davidmimay/my-frequently-bugs-using-angular-firebase-3hbe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davidmimay/my-frequently-bugs-using-angular-firebase-3hbe"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T10:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attempt to Login using firebase authentication:





…
"{"error":{
"code":403,
"message":"Requests to this API identitytoolkit method google.cloud.identitytoolkit.v1.ProjectConfigService.GetProjectConfig are blocked.",
"errors":[{"message":"Requests to this API identitytoolkit method google.cloud.identitytoolkit.v1.ProjectConfigService.GetProjectConfig are blocked.",
"domain":"global",
"reason":"forbidden"}],
"status":"PERMISSION_DENIED",
"details":[{"@type":"type.googleapis.com/google.rpc.ErrorInfo",
"reason":"API_KEY_SERVICE_BLOCKED",
"domain":"googleapis.com",
"metadata":{"service":"identitytoolkit.googleapis.com"}}]}}"
…

Check your Google Cloud APIs Credentials look for the same apiKey given in the project settings of Firebase, click ✏️ edit API scroll down to API restrictions and add Identity Toolkit API to the list of allowed APIs, or just select Don't restrict key, then Save.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>david mimay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Build Express Server. Beginners Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shreyanshsheth/lets-build-express-server-beginners-guide-3od1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shreyanshsheth/lets-build-express-server-beginners-guide-3od1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T09:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Express Js?


Express Js Is Web Framework For Node.js
Most Popular Use Of Express Js In the Current Time Is To Create Web Apis.
Also Some People Are Using To Create Full-stack Web App With using Pug, Ejs, Or Basic HTML
here we are going to create a simple API to understand concepts of express
You need Node.js Installed In Your System. You can download node.js from Node.js


Open New Directory And Write This command to initialize a new project.
npm init -y



-Now install express as dependencies for your project
npm install express
Create index.js file and import express js & initialize the app

Create an endpoint 
in simple term endpoint is a path where you are getting expected data
/users return all users
/products returns all products

/ where we are sending hello world as a response.
3 Open a port for connections

Run application
> write node index.js to start the application

open localhost:3000 on browser





  
  
  hooray you made it 🥳



  
  
  what now


now try to render Html. try to create forms & process data using any database.
find material online and create your own express apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shreyansh sheth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to Hire Perfect Dedicated AngularJS Developers in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itsmekrishlee/steps-to-hire-perfect-dedicated-angularjs-developers-in-2021-4ji2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itsmekrishlee/steps-to-hire-perfect-dedicated-angularjs-developers-in-2021-4ji2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T08:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to Follow While Hiring Skilled AngularJS Developers
Moreover, here’s the complete step-by-step guide to hire AngularJS developers who would prove to be the perfect fit for your project.
Prepare the project description:
The first and foremost step is preparing the project description. Without a clear description, it’s difficult to find the right talents.  Also, make sure you have not missed any important details about your project. If you already have an existing developer team, you can get their assistance in this. This helps you determine what developer expertise you need. Besides, this will also assist the candidate to know whether they possess the necessary expertise to participate in your project.
Determine the hiring model:
Based on the complexity of your project, you may select…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krishlee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create protected route using keycloak and React JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ramnirmal0/how-to-create-protected-route-using-keycloak-and-react-js-2ckc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ramnirmal0/how-to-create-protected-route-using-keycloak-and-react-js-2ckc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T08:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you done configure keycloak with react using keycloak adapter you can use keycloak default functions to create protected routes based on realm roles , client roles , user privileges , resource type.
below i share react code to demonstrate the inbuilt functions in keycloak-js library
to use library
npm i keycloak-js@12.0.1

import './App.css';
import {
  BrowserRouter as Router,
  Switch,
  Route,
  Link
} from "react-router-dom";
import ClientAdmin from './component/ClientAdmin';
import ClientUser from './component/ClientUser';
import RealmAdmin from './component/RealmAdmin';
import SuperAdmin from './component/SuperAdmin';
import Unprotected from './component/Unprotected';
import Protected from './component/Protected';
import NoPermission from './component/NoPermission';

function Ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nirmal Ram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I created a terminal style website.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/m4tt72/i-created-a-terminal-style-website-1jb2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/m4tt72/i-created-a-terminal-style-website-1jb2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T08:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://m4tt72.com
https://github.com/m4tt72/terminal
I'm a Linux enthusiast, and I tried creating something that will allow 'normal' people to have a glimpse at my world.
It's still work in progress, I will open-source it soon. 
Feedback is welcomed 🙏]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yassine Fathi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to change default title in client login screen using Keycloak?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ramnirmal0/how-to-change-default-title-in-client-login-screen-using-keycloak-p6n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ramnirmal0/how-to-change-default-title-in-client-login-screen-using-keycloak-p6n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T08:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your realm settings > HTML Display name
replace:
<div class="kc-logo-text"><span>Keycloak</span></div>

with your Application name that you wish to show on your login screen. you can also provide HTML code for using image instead of title
use
<img alt="..ALT-TEXT.." src="../../SOURCE" width="400"/> 

to insert your logo instead
Happy Hacking..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nirmal Ram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BotMeNot performs its first test!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/botmenot/botmenot-performs-its-first-test-4ab6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/botmenot/botmenot-performs-its-first-test-4ab6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T08:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are very proud to announce that BotMeNot has successfully performed its very first test!
And guess what website did we choose? BotMeNot’s own https://botmenot.com/ :-)
Not only we have tested how BotMeNot works, but we also tested how our bot is seen in raw HTTP log files (in our case - Apache’s .access log).
As you can see - BotMeNot protection score is 40%
Here’s what the results look like!

Let us know what you think!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BotMeNot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stream in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cretus_mukiza/stream-in-nodejs-16mn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cretus_mukiza/stream-in-nodejs-16mn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T07:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by cretus mukiza]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cretus mukiza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AdonisJs - Introduction to database migrations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tngeene/adonisjs-introduction-to-database-migrations-i03</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tngeene/adonisjs-introduction-to-database-migrations-i03"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T06:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Database Migrations



This article will introduce you to the concept of migrations in AdonisJs.
In the previous articles, we learned 2 approaches to working with events in AdonisJs. In this fifth installment of the everything you need to know about adonisJs series, we will familiarize ourselves with the concept of migrations. The aim is to have a broader understanding of how our database state will look like.
Source code for this tutorial can be found here
I will link the resources at the end of the article.
Let's get started.
Just to remind you how our database should look like, we'll reference this diagram.

Database migrations and modeling can sometimes be a pain point for many devs to fully understand. It's important to plan your database in the most optimal way that m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ted Ngeene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gerenciando processos no Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mdcg/gerenciando-processos-no-linux-5m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mdcg/gerenciando-processos-no-linux-5m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T22:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução


Provavelmente você já deve ter ouvido sobre "processos" enquanto estava mexendo em seu computador. A maioria de nós talvez só nos damos conta da existência deles em "momentos ruins", por exemplo, quando alguma aplicação está travada e temos que "finalizar o processo dela". Contudo, fora o conhecimento em saber como finalizar o "bendito" para você continuar exercendo suas atividades, algo importantíssimo também é entender qual é a real importância de um processo.
Quando estamos trabalhando em um ambiente multiprogramado/multitarefa, o Sistema Operacional (SO) é responsável por gerenciar diversos programas executados "concorrentemente", controlando o compartilhamento dos recursos para cada um deles. Para que isso seja possível, todo programa executado deve sempre estar associado…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauro de Carvalho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript ANY vs UNKNOWN—A Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomdohnal/typescript-any-vs-unknown-a-deep-dive-3iem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomdohnal/typescript-any-vs-unknown-a-deep-dive-3iem"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we'll dive deep into what any and unknown types are, what are their similarities and differences, and when (not) to use them.
(You can find a video version of this article on YouTube! 📺)





  
  
  TLDR;





// ANY
const anyValue: any = 'whatever'

// OK in TypeScript (error in runtime!) 👇
anyValue.do.something.stupid() 


// UNKNOWN
const unknownValue: unknown = 'whatever, too'

// Fails TypeScript check (prevents runtime error) 👇
unknownValue.do.something.stupid() 

Mnemonics to help you remember the difference 👇
any -> first letter is an "A" -> Avoid TypeScript
unknown -> first letter is a "U" -> Use TypeScript
The any Type
The unknown Type
Use Cases

any Type


The any type is something like an escape hatch from TypeScript. 
What does that mean?
If your variab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Dohnal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criando um pendrive bootável live com Kali Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mdcg/criando-um-pendrive-bootavel-live-com-kali-linux-3j5l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mdcg/criando-um-pendrive-bootavel-live-com-kali-linux-3j5l"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T20:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução


Se você já faz parte ou tem interesse de entrar no mundo do hackvismo, provavelmente já deve ter ouvido falar do Kali Linux. Nessa postagem, eu pretendo falar um pouco sobre essa distribuição, e também, ensiná-lo como você pode estar criando um pendrive bootável no modo live com o mesmo, utilizando apenas a linha de comando do seu terminal. Sem mais delongas, vamos começar!
PS: Caso você não saiba o que é "bootável no modo live", significa que você poderá inicializar o sistema operacional direto do seu pendrive, com isso, você não precisará necessariamente fazer a instalação do Kali Linux em sua própria máquina.
O Kali Linux é uma distribuição GNU/Linux baseada no Debian, totalmente open source, que é mantido e financiado pela Offensive Security. Ele é usado para pentesting, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauro de Carvalho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criando um pendrive bootável live com Kali Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mdcg/criando-um-pendrive-bootavel-live-com-kali-linux-3j5l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mdcg/criando-um-pendrive-bootavel-live-com-kali-linux-3j5l"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T20:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução


Se você já faz parte ou tem interesse de entrar no mundo do hackvismo, provavelmente já deve ter ouvido falar do Kali Linux. Nessa postagem, eu pretendo falar um pouco sobre essa distribuição, e também, ensiná-lo como você pode estar criando um pendrive bootável no modo live com o mesmo, utilizando apenas a linha de comando do seu terminal. Sem mais delongas, vamos começar!
PS: Caso você não saiba o que é "bootável no modo live", significa que você poderá inicializar o sistema operacional direto do seu pendrive, com isso, você não precisará necessariamente fazer a instalação do Kali Linux em sua própria máquina.
O Kali Linux é uma distribuição GNU/Linux baseada no Debian, totalmente open source, que é mantido e financiado pela Offensive Security. Ele é usado para pentesting, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauro de Carvalho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary/Hex Conversion in Linux Shell with xxd [RE#13]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/binaryhex-conversion-in-linux-shell-with-xxd-re13-2cjd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/binaryhex-conversion-in-linux-shell-with-xxd-re13-2cjd"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not that unusual to need to see/check/verify the binary output of a shell command in HEX format. Clearly, I mean without picking up a HEX editor or something like that. Last time, it happened to me a few days ago when I was to inspect the content of a base64-encoded string. The tool to the rescue is (of course not limited to) xxd. 🏅
Using xxd, to get the HEX representation for some binary content you just need to call it with no argument:
echo -n 'Computer says: "Hello World!"' | xxd

Depending on the case it could be more insightful to also have the ASCII values column. That’s simply done by calling xxd with -C option:
echo -n 'Computer says: "Hello World!"' | xxd -C

Which results in such a neat output:
00000000: 436f 6d70 7574 6572 2073 6179 733a 2022 Computer says: "
00000010: 4865 6c6c 6f20 576f 726c 6421 22 Hello World!"

Also, xxd can do things the other way. For instance, may you need to turn a HEX string into a binary content, just call xxd with -r option, like this:
echo -n "0x48656c6c6f20576f726c6421" | xxd -r

Which would result in:
Hello World!

There are more xxd options which you can find by checking:
xxd --help

or
man xxd

About Regular Encounters

I’ve decided to record my daily encounters with professional issues on a somewhat regular basis. Not all of them are equally important/unique/intricate, but are indeed practical, real, and of course, textually minimal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[C3.js][TypeScript] Draw line charts 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masanori_msl/c3jstypescript-draw-line-charts-1-1g0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masanori_msl/c3jstypescript-draw-line-charts-1-1g0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T17:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


This time, I will try drawing line charts with specific design.
I have tried drawing line charts with Chart.js.
【TypeScript】Try Chart.js
[TypeScript][Chart.js] Play my own voice 3
But because I couldn't find how to draw additional lines with specific format like dashed lines.
C3.js | D3-based reusable chart library
Node.js ver.17.0.1
TypeScript ver.4.4.4
C3 ver.0.7.20
PostCSS ver.8.3.11
Webpack ver.5.61.0
@types/c3 ver.0.7.6
postcss-cli ver.9.0.2
postcss-import ver.14.0.2
ts-loader ver.9.2.6
ts-node ver.10.4.0
webpack-cli ver.4.9.1
First, I will try drawing line charts with sample data.
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
    <head>
        <title>chart sample</title>
        <meta charset="utf-8">
        <link href="css/chart.page.css" rel="stylesheet" />
    </head>
    <body>
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masui Masanori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made a neovim plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/waylonwalker/i-made-a-neovim-plugin-k2j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/waylonwalker/i-made-a-neovim-plugin-k2j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T16:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've slowly adding more and more lua functions into my neovim configuration, and recently I noticed a pattern for a class of functions that reach out to run shell commands that can be abstracted away.





  
  
  Telegraph.nvim


Check out the project readme for the most up to date details on the plugin itself.
I want a simple way to make remaps into shell commands that can open new tmux windows, popups, or just run a command with context from the editor.
For example I want to make remaps to do things like open the current file in lookatme.
# vim :terminal
nnoremap <leader>s <cmd>Telegraph pipx run lookatme {filepath} --live-reload --style gruvbox-dark<cmd>

# tmux session
nnoremap <leader><leader>s <cmd>lua require'telegraph'.telegraph({cmd='pipx run lookatme {filepath} --live-reload --s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a single-node Hadoop cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/donaldsebleung/setting-up-a-single-node-hadoop-cluster-p0a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/donaldsebleung/setting-up-a-single-node-hadoop-cluster-p0a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T15:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will see Hadoop in action by configuring a single-node cluster on Ubuntu 20.04.
Before we start, it is assumed that you are:
Familiar with basic Linux commands and operation
Aware of what Hadoop is and how it works




  
  
  Initial setup


Set up a virtual machine (VM) or cloud instance (or physical machine, if you wish) with a fresh installation of Ubuntu 20.04. Ensure that the VM or cloud instance is reachable from the host (with ping or otherwise), and that the appropriate ports are open if a firewall is enabled. For the purposes of this tutorial, you may wish to disable the firewall (the default in Ubuntu 20.04) and / or enable all inbound traffic for the security group (or equivalent) associated with the cloud instance if you are using one, though note that you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donald Sebastian Leung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS Marble tests in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/rxjs-marble-tests-in-angular-5fjl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/rxjs-marble-tests-in-angular-5fjl"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T14:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description


There is an excellent feature called Marble tests from RxJS to test asynchronous code synchronously. We could easily use it in Angular unit tests. I have made a few basic examples about testing code by Marble tests in Angular.
My project is using Angular, so I have created a new project (using Angular CLI) by typing in console:
ng new marble-tests

My demo project is quite simple, so I answered no on
I have made a simple dummy service for getting data. All of its methods return observables using of operator, which returns the stream from given arguments. The complete code is below.
import { Injectable } from '@angular/core';
import { Observable, of } from 'rxjs';

@Injectable({
  providedIn: 'root',
})
export class DataService {
  constructor() {}

  getList$(): Observable<st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomasz Flis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add toastr module to Angular project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mightytechno/how-to-add-toastr-module-to-angular-project-34ki</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mightytechno/how-to-add-toastr-module-to-angular-project-34ki"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T13:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In any web application showing the alert or message to indicate the different status is required functionality to have which help to understand the users what is happening under the hood.
First, open the terminal and run the following command inside your project to install the ngx-toastr plugin
npm install ngx-toastr --save

Next, you need to install animation package which is required to toastr plugin.
npm install @angular/animations --save

Next open angular.json and add the following style which is required for toastr.
"styles": [
       "src/styles.scss",
       "node_modules/ngx-toastr/toastr.css"
  ],

Next open app.module.js file and import BrowserAnimationsModule and ToastrModule.
import { BrowserAnimationsModule } from '@angular/platform-browser/animations';

import { ToastrModule…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mighty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InterSystems Security Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/intersystemsdev/intersystems-security-contest-1fe2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/intersystemsdev/intersystems-security-contest-1fe2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T12:49:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security wanted!
Welcome to the next InterSystems online programming competition: 
🏆 InterSystems Security Contest 🏆
Duration: November 15 - December 05, 2021
Prizes: $9,450 in prizes!

Prizes
1. Experts Nomination - a specially selected jury will determine winners:
1st place - $4,000 



  🥈 2nd place - $2,000 



  🥉 3rd place - $1,000



  🌟 4-10th places - $100


2. Community winners - applications that will receive the most votes in total:
1st place - $1,000 



  🥈 2nd place - $500 



  🥉 3rd place - $250


If several participants score the same amount of votes, they all are considered winners, and the money prize is shared among the winners.  
Who can participate?
Any Developer Community member, except for InterSystems employees (ISC contractors allowed). Create an account!
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>InterSystems Developer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure static IP Address in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-configure-static-ip-address-in-linux-3670</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-configure-static-ip-address-in-linux-3670"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T12:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use Ubuntu server or other Linux server, you need configures IP Address using CLI interactive. Now i can show you how to configures IP Address in Ubuntu and Debian. Let's start
Ubuntu
first, you should know where is the interface when you assign an IP. Type this command on your terminal:
$ ifconfig   
or
$ ip address

after that, so we can assign an IP to interface 'ens33' by type this command:
$ sudo nano /etc/netplan/01-netcfg.yaml

then type this:
network:
  ethernets:
    ens33:
      addresses: [172.16.238.20/24]
      gateway4: 172.16.238.2
      nameservers:
        addresses: [8.8.8.8]
  version: 2


after all, you must apply or enable the configure:
$ sudo netplan apply
$ ifconfig

2: ens33: <BROADCAST,MULTICAST,UP,LOWER_UP> mtu 1500 qdisc fq_codel state UP group default qlen 1000
    link/ether 00:0c:29:77:41:f0 brd ff:ff:ff:ff:ff:ff
    inet 172.16.238.20/24 brd 172.16.238.255 scope global ens33
       valid_lft forever preferred_lft forever
    inet6 fe80::20c:29ff:fe77:41f0/64 scope link 
       valid_lft forever preferred_lft forever

Debian
Okay, after that i think you should configure too in Debian side. First thing, type this command on your Debian terminal:
$ nano /etc/network/interfaces

after that, add this command to assign an IP:
auto ens33
iface ens33 inet static
address 172.16.238.10/24
gateway 172.16.238.2
nameservers 8.8.8.8

finally, save it by type ctrl+s to save then ctrl+x to exit. Let's apply:
$ /ete/init.d/networking restart

[ ok ] Restarting networking (via systemctl): networking.service.

then check your IP configure:
$ ip address

2: ens33: <BROADCAST,MULTICAST,UP,LOWER_UP> mtu 1500 qdisc pfifo_fast state UP group default qlen 1000
    link/ether 00:0c:29:a0:41:4e brd ff:ff:ff:ff:ff:ff
    inet 172.16.238.10/24 brd 172.16.238.255 scope global ens33
       valid_lft forever preferred_lft forever
    inet6 fe80::20c:29ff:fea0:414e/64 scope link 
       valid_lft forever preferred_lft forever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Pepuho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hangi Sunucu İşletim Sistemini tercih etmeliyim?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aciklab/hangi-sunucu-isletim-sistemini-tercih-etmeliyim-am7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aciklab/hangi-sunucu-isletim-sistemini-tercih-etmeliyim-am7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T10:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Çeşitli proje ve durumlarda ilk karşımıza çıkan önemli bir sorunun "hangi sunucu işletim sistemini tercih etmeliyim?" olduğunu düşünüyorum. Çünkü en basitinden üzerine kurulacak uygulamanın bağımlılıklarının belirlenmesi, güncelleme süreçlerinin yönetilme süreçleri için ortaya çıkacak cevap oldukça önemli. 
Her ne kadar bu soru "konteynır" mimarileriyle birlikte önemini biraz yitirse de sanal makine (VM) kullanımının hala ciddi oranda kullanıldığı alanlarda bu yapı devam etmektedir. Bu yazımda genel olarak konteynır sistemlerle ilgili bir yorum içermemektedir. Bu konu hakkında ayrıca bir yazı yazma düşüncem var.
Tercih etmeden önce elimizde neler olduğu ve tabi ki sonrasında bu seçeneklerin neler sunduklarına bakmak gerekir. Tabi ki bu yazıyı yazarken yani 2021 yılı sonu ve Türkiye piyasas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Orhun Akkirman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when you type “ls -l *.c” in the shell?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hamicch/what-happens-when-you-type-ls-l-c-in-the-shell-522e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hamicch/what-happens-when-you-type-ls-l-c-in-the-shell-522e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T10:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have to understand what a shell is in relation to the kernel to understand what really happens when you run a command.

The Kernel is the most fundamental part of a computer operating system. It’s a program itself and it controls all other programs on the computer. It talks to hardware and software and is highly involved in resource management.
The Shell is an application that executes programs called commands through an interactive user interface with an operating system. It is the layer of programming that understands and executes the commands a user enters. In some systems, the shell is called a command interpreter.
Use the syntax below to write a command with an argument.
command [arg1] [arg2] .. [argn]

ls?


ls is a shell command that lists files and directories within a director…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayatu Sanusi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Azure Service Bus SAS tokens with Github]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-azure-service-bus-sas-tokens-with-github-37ok</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-azure-service-bus-sas-tokens-with-github-37ok"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T10:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview


In todays tutorial I will demonstrate how to use powerShell in Github Actions to automate Azure Service Bus SAS tokens to generate short lived usable tokens with a validity period of 10 minutes and securely store the newly generated SAS tokens inside of an Azure Key Vault ready for consumption.
We will create an Azure Service Bus and Key Vault and a single reusable github workflow to handle our SAS token requests as well as a service principal / Azure identity to fully automate everything. For the purpose of this demonstration we will also have a main workflow that is triggered manually. Our main workflow, when triggered, will first call our reusable github workflow that will generate our temporary SAS token that will only be valid for 10 minutes and store the SAS token inside o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[conexión segura ssh para la RaspberryPi(FreeBSD,Linux)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gloriousmusketeer/conexion-segura-ssh-para-la-raspberrypifreebsdlinux-4ci0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gloriousmusketeer/conexion-segura-ssh-para-la-raspberrypifreebsdlinux-4ci0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T03:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH SSH client(SSH) es un protocolo de administración remota que le permite a los usuarios controlar y modificar sus servidores remotos a través de Internet a través de un mecanismo de autenticación.
La conexión SSH está cifrada de extremo a extremo además de necesitar una autenticación para poder conectar al servidor. SSH funciona de manera similar a Telnet, pero al contrario que este, con SSH todos los datos que se envían desde el cliente al servidor, y los que se reciban desde el servidor al cliente viajan cifrados para que nadie pueda interceptar la información dotando de una capa extra de seguridad con respecto a Telnet.
Este tutorial de SSH cubrirá los conceptos básicos de cómo funciona, junto con las tecnologías subyacentes utilizadas por el protocolo SSH para ofrecer un método …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glorious Musketeer™</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uptime of macOS system via terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stankukucka/uptime-of-macos-system-via-terminal-4jip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stankukucka/uptime-of-macos-system-via-terminal-4jip"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T20:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are logged into your system. In this case, it's macOS. You are facing just a simple question. Are you the only one who is logged in? I would like to give you an answer to this simple question with a bit of explanation. Here in upcoming lines, there will be a bit of theory background behind it.
In case your system is healthy (understand as an official system with applied updates), you are the only physical user logged in. You can check this logged in information with a simple command you will enter into the terminal. But there is a trick in that, will explain in next lines hereunder. Open your Terminal.app you'll find out in Finder in the section Applications and Utilities. For more informations check official Terminal User Guide.
By entering uptime command you'll be informed in one line output about the current time, number of days your system is up, number of logged-in users etc.
uptime

If you'll enter this very same command into the terminal in capital form as UPTIME, you'll receive a more readable summary of the logged-in sessions by the user.
UPTIME

The same output can be given by entering w command into the terminal.
w

Do remember you will always have a minimum of 2 logged-in users. By default when you open another terminal session it will be counted as another active user logged in. In other words, if you open four-terminal sessions, you will see 4 users logged in +1 as the default logged-in user I have written about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stan ku2ck4</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's build a list of real and alive open-source Angular projects.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ovidiu141/lets-build-a-list-of-real-and-alive-open-source-angular-projects-1en6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ovidiu141/lets-build-a-list-of-real-and-alive-open-source-angular-projects-1en6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T19:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only found lists polluted with dead/toy/component-library OSS projects. (or even containing AngularJS projects)
I want to find some real and alive open source projects which are using Angular. I'm sure some of us want to dive deeper and read some Angular code used in real life.
Feel free to mention projects in the comments and I will try to keep the list up to date.
List:
PeerTube (Angular 13 | 9.9k Github stars) 
https://github.com/Chocobozzz/PeerTube


Openproject (Angular 12 | 5.3k Github stars)
https://github.com/opf/openproject


Oppia (Angular 11 | 4.3k Github stars)
https://github.com/oppia/oppia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ovidiu Miu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Angular know about (click)?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ovidiu141/how-does-angular-know-about-click-3poc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ovidiu141/how-does-angular-know-about-click-3poc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T18:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<button (click)="doSomething()">Do it</button>
But how does Angular know how to deal with this (click) thing? 
It works because of the so called Event Biding. Basically it binds the target event name (click) to a method from the component (doSomething).
As explained in this nice article , Angular doesn't have a list of it's own event names, but it actually uses the names of the underlying DOM events.
So the event binding part of the <button (click)="doSomething()">Do it</button> snippet is the equivalent of this vanilla snippet:
element.addEventListener('click', () => { doSomething() });


This means the if I want to know which events I can bind to in Angular I can search them here: https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/Events
What about the $event?
If the event is a DOM event, like click, mouseenter, keyup etc then the $event is the event itself. For example in the case of click, the $event is a MouseEvent.
EventEmitter) the $event is actually the emitted data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ovidiu Miu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to display a navbar component after logging in without reloading the page in angular 12]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-display-a-navbar-component-after-logging-in-without-reloading-the-page-in-angular-12-2kfi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-display-a-navbar-component-after-logging-in-without-reloading-the-page-in-angular-12-2kfi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T16:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My landing page does not show a navbar, but I want to display a navbar after logging in successfully.  Currently, I'm able to show navbar if I do a full page reload after logging in successfully. I'm very sure that there is a better way than this approach.
app.component.html
<app-navbar></app-navbar>
<router-outlet></router-outlet>

login.component.ts
login(){
    this.credentials = this.myForm.value;
    if(this.credentials){
      this.loginService.authenticate(this.credentials)
      .subscribe(data => {
        this.storageService.setLocalStorageItem('auth', JSON.stringify(data));
        this.dataService.global.showNav = true;
        this.sharedService.getProjectMetadata()
        .subscribe(metadata => {
          this.storageService.setLocalStorageItem('projectMetaData', JSON.strin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Murthy Kota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cplayer and Its application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/crajbanshi/cplayer-and-its-application-2eap</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/crajbanshi/cplayer-and-its-application-2eap"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T15:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have created a web based music player using javascript. I kept its name as CPlayer.
Github link
https://github.com/crajbanshi/cplayer
And also created one website using this. Application name is MSound. Now it is deployed in stage trying to move it to production. I hope th MSound app will be in fly very soon.
Visit the application stage url: http://tune.rf.gd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chanchal Rajbanshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular app in Github pages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davidmimay/angular-app-in-github-pages-2a56</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davidmimay/angular-app-in-github-pages-2a56"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T12:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy and angular app to GitHub pages and get it running under your own domain: username.github.io. Also you can use the GitHub API to get access to your repositories data as I did on my personal portfolio:
Live demo
Source code
Git
GitHub account
Angular CLI
Create a new public repository using your GitHub username and this form:
username.github.io

First, clone the newly created repository to a local folder:
$ git clone https://github.com/username/username.github.io.git
Navigate to the repository root folder:
$ cd username.github.io
Create a new angular project in the root directory of the repo:
$ ng new myApp --directory ./
Open angular.json file and change the buildOutput path to “docs”:
angular.json
…
"architect": {
        "build": {
          "builder": "@angular-devkit/build-angular:browser",
          "options": {
            "outputPath": "docs",
…

Build the angular application in production mode:
$ ng build --prod
You can push the /docs folder only, or you can push the whole application /myApp (recommended):
$ git add .
$ git commit -m "Init app"
$ git push
Now navigate to your repository settings https://github.com/username/username.github.io/settings

scroll down to the GitHub pages section to change the build source to /docs. Few seconds later your site will be built and published and you should see the message “Your site is published at…”. If don’t, try refreshing the site.

Then you can view the deployments at the right side of the repository, under environments, pressing github-pages or at https://github.com/username/username.github.io/deployments

You can make changes locally, test them using $ ng serve and then build for production using $ ng build --prod and push your updated code to GitHub. The page will automatically re-build.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>david mimay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Other Looks at the Conditional Border Radius Trick]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356304</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/other-looks-at-the-conditional-border-radius-trick/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T23:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when Ahmad Shadeed wrote about that border-radius “toggle” he found in Facebook’s CSS? It was interesting! I covered it. A few weeks after that surge of linkage, a couple of articles came out digging into it a little deeper. …
The post Other Looks at the Conditional Border Radius Trick appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Good Commit Messages with Commitlint]]></title>
        <id>618deac811d3cb08287a4ba3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-commitlint-to-write-good-commit-messages/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T20:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are often in a hurry to commit our changes in Git and so we write something random in our commit messages. In fact, I have seen people putting the date and time or even something like commit 1, commit 2 in their messages.  This is not a good practice,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does my WiFi Keep Disconnecting? [Solved on Windows 10 PC]]]></title>
        <id>618e136011d3cb08287a4c71</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-does-my-wifi-keep-disconnecting-solved-on-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're using your Windows machine, your WiFi might unexpectedly disconnect.  This might be caused by various problems such as an outdated network adapter driver, outdated router software, and optimized power management in Windows 10.  If your WiFi keeps disconnecting and you're looking for a solution, you've come to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Rebase: Clean up your Commit History]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355658</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/interactive-rebase-clean-up-your-commit-history/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Rebase is the Swiss Army knife of Git commands: lots of use cases and lots of possibilities! It's really a great addition to any developer's tool chain, because it lets you revise your local commit history—before you share your work with the rest of the team. Let's see what you can do with an interactive rebase and then look at some practical examples.
The post Interactive Rebase: Clean up your Commit History appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying .net core, angular and sql server to ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxwelladn/deploying-net-core-angular-and-sql-server-to-ubuntu-2a6h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxwelladn/deploying-net-core-angular-and-sql-server-to-ubuntu-2a6h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will share with you how I deploy NGX.BILL a .net core/SQL Server and angular application to ubuntu using nginx
Prerequisites:  You must have an Ubuntu 16.04, 18.04, or 20.04 machine with at least 2 GB of memory.
Create your own private server and choose ubuntu  16.04, 18.04, or 20.04
link to get a free credit with digital ocean to start
Connect to the same server as the database using an ssh client.
Putty 
adduser USER

Enter new UNIX password:
Retype new UNIX password:
passwd: password updated successfully

Changing the user information for USER
Enter the new value, or press ENTER for the default
        Full Name []:
        Room Number []:
        Work Phone []:
        Home Phone []:
        Other []:
Is the information correct? [Y/n] y

Give admin rights to the user.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxwell ADANZOUNNON</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic menu context]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356652</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/semantic-menu-context/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott digs into the history of the <menu> element. He traced it as far back as HTML 2 (!) in a 1994 changelog. The vibe then, it seems, was to mark up a list. I would suspect the intention …
The post Semantic menu context appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Laravel 8 on Your Android Phone]]></title>
        <id>618b035411d3cb08287a3f7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-laravel-8-on-android-phone/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T16:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, how are you doing? In this article, I'm going to show you how you can install Laravel 8 on your phone.  To get the most out of this guide, you should have some knowledge of PHP and you should know what Laravel is. But if you don't, don't worry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy Dark Mode (and Multiple Color Themes!) in React]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355683</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/easy-dark-mode-and-multiple-color-themes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T15:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was working on a large React application for a startup, and aside from just wanting some good strategies to keep our styles organized, I wanted to give this whole “dark mode” thing a shot. With the huge ecosystem around …
The post Easy Dark Mode (and Multiple Color Themes!) in React appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abram Thau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly Get Alerted to Front-End Errors and Performance Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355516</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quickly-get-alerted-to-front-end-errors-and-performance-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T15:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Measuring things is great. They say what you only fix what you measure. Raygun is great at measuring websites. Measuring performance, measuring errors and crashes, measuring code problems. 
You know what’s even better than …
The post Quickly Get Alerted to Front-End Errors and Performance Issues appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Snore on CORS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356058</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dont-snore-on-cors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T22:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever, I just needed a title. Everyone’s favorite web security feature has crossed my desk a bunch of times lately and I always feel like that is a sign I should write something because that’s what blogging is. 
The main …
The post Don’t Snore on CORS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick and Dirty Bootstrap Overrides at Runtime]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355649</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-and-dirty-bootstrap-overrides-at-runtime/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, Bootstrap, that old standard web library that either you hate or you spend all your time defending as “it’s fine, it’s not that bad.” Regardless of what side you fall on, it’s a powerful UI framework that’s everywhere, …
The post Quick and Dirty Bootstrap Overrides at Runtime appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meredith Matthews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cleanup.pictures]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356208</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cleanup-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T14:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice domain, eh? Does just what it says on the tin: cleans up pictures. You draw over areas of the image you want cleaned up, and it does its best using weird science. It’s like Photoshop’s Spot Healing Brush…
The post cleanup.pictures appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Specific Text Input with HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356142</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/detecting-specific-text-input-with-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T22:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Lazaris breaks down some bonafide CSS trickery from Jane. The Pen shows off interactivity where:
You have to press a special combination of keys on a keyboard.
Then type a secret password.
From there, a special message pops …
The post Detecting Specific Text Input with HTML and CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VideoPress for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356370</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/videopress-for-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T22:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
The leade here is that VideoPress makes video on WordPress way better. VideoPress is a part of Jetpack. And now, if VideoPress is the only thing you care about from the Jetpack world, you …
The post VideoPress for WordPress appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Suspense: Lessons Learned While Loading Data]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356187</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/react-suspense-lessons-learned-while-loading-data/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T15:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suspense is React’s forthcoming feature that helps coordinate asynchronous actions—like data loading—allowing you to easily prevent inconsistent state in your UI. I’ll provide a better explanation of what exactly that means, along with a quick introduction of Suspense, and then …
The post React Suspense: Lessons Learned While Loading Data appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid Can Do Auto Height Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356204</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-can-do-auto-height-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T19:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bonafide CSS trick alert! Nelson Menezes figured out a new way (that only works in Firefox for now) that is awfully clever.
Perhaps you know that CSS cannot animate to auto dimensions, which is super unfortunate. Animating from …
The post CSS Grid Can Do Auto Height Transitions appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Icon Glassmorphism Effect in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=322098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/icon-glassmorphism-effect-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a cool effect known as glassmorphism in a Dribble shot. My first thought was I could quickly recreate it in a few minutes if I just use some emojis for the icons without wasting time …
The post Icon Glassmorphism Effect in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the Next Generation of Static Site Generators Make Building Sites Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356134</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/does-the-next-generation-of-static-site-generators-make-building-sites-better/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just ran across îles, a new static site generator mostly centered around Vue. The world has no particular shortage of static site generators, but it’s interesting to see what this “next generation” of SSGs seem to focus on or …
The post Does the Next Generation of Static Site Generators Make Building Sites Better? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Quasar Framework: Building Cross-Platform Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar is an open-source Vue.js-based cross-platform framework that allows you, as a developer, to easily build apps for both desktop and mobile using technologies such as Cordova and Electron and writing your code once. The app we’ll build will store and get its data from Firebase, meaning that we will also be seeing how to use Firebase in Quasar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joel Olawanle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The SSG I’ve Always Wanted: An 11ty, Vite And JAM Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, Ben Holmes set out to do what just about every web developer does each year: rebuild his personal site. In this article, he shares his story of how he set out to build his own build pipeline from absolute ground zero and created “Slinkity”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Holmes)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An API With Gatsby Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Paul Scanlon explains how to build an API by using Gatsby Functions and what you need to keep in mind when deploying it to Gatsby Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 42 With Jeff Smith: What Is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about DevOps. What is it, and is it a string to add to your web development bow? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeff Smith to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving CLS Issues In A Next.js-Powered E-Commerce Website (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cumulative Layout Shift is one of the hardest core web vital to debug. In this article, we go through different tools to investigate CLS, when to use them(and when not), and solutions to some of the CLS issues we faced in our Next.js-based e-commerce website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arijit Mondal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>