<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-24T01:03:08.566Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-24T01:03:08.566Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Math You Need to Know in Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>6197c7ce11d3cb08287a9271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-the-math-you-need-in-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an AI researcher, and I’ve received quite a few emails asking me just how much math is required in Artificial Intelligence. I won’t lie: it’s a lot of math. And this is one of the reasons AI puts off many beginners. After much research and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criando e configurando projeto Node.Js com TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Requisitos necessários


Para iniciarmos a criação de nosso  projeto, precisaremos desses componentes instalados:
Node.js
yarn
Em algum lugar de sua preferência, crie uma pasta e a abra em seu editor de código. No terminal, navegue até a pasta e rode o comando:
$ yarn init -y

Podemos observar que o arquivo packge.json foi criado na raiz de seu projeto, onde estão contidos dados como o nome de seu projeto, a versão, o arquivo principal, a licença e futuramente conterá as dependências. 
No terminal, baixe a dependência de desenvolvimento do TypeScript:
$ yarn add typescript -D

Podemos observar que uma pasta chamada node_modules foi criada, ela é responsável por armazenar os módulos de dependências de seu projeto.
No terminal, inicie o TypeScript:
yarn tsc --init

Podemos observar que o arq…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Ferrari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criando e configurando projeto Node.Js com TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Requisitos necessários


Para iniciarmos a criação de nosso  projeto, precisaremos desses componentes instalados:
Node.js
yarn
Em algum lugar de sua preferência, crie uma pasta e a abra em seu editor de código. No terminal, navegue até a pasta e rode o comando:
$ yarn init -y

Podemos observar que o arquivo packge.json foi criado na raiz de seu projeto, onde estão contidos dados como o nome de seu projeto, a versão, o arquivo principal, a licença e futuramente conterá as dependências. 
No terminal, baixe a dependência de desenvolvimento do TypeScript:
$ yarn add typescript -D

Podemos observar que uma pasta chamada node_modules foi criada, ela é responsável por armazenar os módulos de dependências de seu projeto.
No terminal, inicie o TypeScript:
yarn tsc --init

Podemos observar que o arq…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Ferrari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is GitOps? Principles, Best Practices, and Kubernetes Workflow]]></title>
        <id>619bb55911d3cb08287aa581</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitops-principles-kubernetes-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, CTO Cornelia Davis will teach you what GitOps is and what its four main principles are.  What is GitOps?The first thing you need to know is that GitOps is a set of modern best practises for deploying and managing cloud native infrastructure and applications.  And it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Facebook system design interview questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/top-10-facebook-system-design-interview-questions-57m7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/top-10-facebook-system-design-interview-questions-57m7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The system design interview is a necessary hurdle as you advance in your career as a software engineer. System design interviews assess your design skills by asking you to build a scalable system. Even seasoned engineers can struggle with this interview round, but you’re already ahead of the game if you’re here for interview preparation.
Today we’ll discuss the top system design interview questions asked at Facebook. These questions are also common fare for system design interviews at all top tech companies, including FAANG (Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix, and Google). 
We’ll cover:
Facebook’s interview process
How to answer system design interview questions
Top 10 Facebook system design interview questions
1. Design Facebook Newsfeed 
2. Design Messenger 
3. Design Instagram
4. Design T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ericaeducative</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Stacks and Stages on AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tinystacks/a-guide-to-stacks-and-stages-on-aws-44fh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tinystacks/a-guide-to-stacks-and-stages-on-aws-44fh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article by Jay Allen
Learning AWS is complicated enough. But learning AWS is made more challenging when you're also still grappling with some of the major concepts of DevOps software deployments. In this article, I discuss two key concepts: stacks and stages. I also address how you can manage stacks and stages in AWS, along with other factors you need to consider when managing them in practice. 
In simplest terms, a stack is a unit of application deployment. Using stacks, developers can organize all of the resources required by an application or an application component as a single unit. This enables devs to deploy, tear down, and re-deploy their applications at will. 
Stacks can be stood up manually. However, it's better on cloud platforms to program the creation of your stack - e.g., usi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Ciulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎄 Render in Vue, 16+ ways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/render-in-vue-16-ways-d50</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/render-in-vue-16-ways-d50"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post I will show you 16 ways how to render something in Vue
Talk is cheap. Show me the code.
Here is full example that you can play around 
https://github.com/iamandrewluca/vue-render-everywhere
I'm using Vite with this configuration
import { defineConfig } from 'vite'
import vue from '@vitejs/plugin-vue'
import vueJsx from '@vitejs/plugin-vue-jsx'

export default defineConfig({
  plugins: [vue(), vueJsx()],
  resolve: { alias: { vue: 'vue/dist/vue.esm-bundler.js' } }
})

When refering to a DOM element, this is the HTML for every example
<script type="text/html" id="template-in-script">
  <li>The quick brown fox...</li>
</script>

I'm showing these methods only for learning purposes. Use at your own risk.
template option as string





import { defineComponent } from "vue"

ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Luca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: npm install throwing error in node-sass]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: npm install throwing error in node-sass
            
        
Mar  1 '20
        
Add manually in package.json :  "node-sass": "4.13.0"
and update package.json in terminal npm install
Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed how much time you waste on AWS-Logins and Account-Switching ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alex20465/simperate-4cop</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alex20465/simperate-4cop"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simperate is developed by developers for developers as a product software solution that aims to operate AWS services with a cross-platform application that can do more in a user-friendly desktop environment.
The beta version is just the beginning, our roadmap is long and has many features and ideas that are waiting to be implemented.
We are currently in the process of risk-analysis in order to invest more in the development. We are thankful for any kind of assistance with bug reports and feedback, If your are interested to support and accelerate the development of simperate, you can purchase a license key that gives you unrestricted access to all features for 3 years of support.
https://simperate.io]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandros Fotiadis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error
            
        
Feb 25 '21
        
I solved this issue by typing the following:
 npm install grpc --save
 npm install node-pre-gyp --save

Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning for Anomaly Detection: Decreasing Time to Find Root Cause by Automating Log Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxshash/machine-learning-for-anomaly-detection-decreasing-time-to-find-root-cause-by-automating-log-analysis-2ak2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxshash/machine-learning-for-anomaly-detection-decreasing-time-to-find-root-cause-by-automating-log-analysis-2ak2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T21:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a practical approach to using Machine Learning for Log Analysis and Anomaly Detection in the article below.
There are many articles on applying machine learning for log analysis. However, most of them are dated, academic in nature, or don’t focus on practical outcomes. On Dev.to, most of the articles cover ML courses or the difference between deep learning and machine learning.
In this article, we want to share our real-life experience on using ML/AI for log analysis and anomaly detection with the specific purpose of automatically uncovering the root cause of software issues.
We will also discuss the various approaches to ML-based log analysis, some of the existing challenges, and provide details of our approach to solving these problems.
Disclaimer: We are Zebrium and we work on a p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Shash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a MySQL database server in Kubernetes - Static]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/musolemasu/deploy-a-mysql-database-server-in-kubernetes-static-dpc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/musolemasu/deploy-a-mysql-database-server-in-kubernetes-static-dpc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T20:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you are going to learn how to deploy a MySQL database server in a Kubernetes Cluster set up in a local machine, this is one of many ways to persist data in Kubernetes.
Kubernetes is a tool for automating deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications.
Get familiar with some terminologies and kubernetes objects that will be used through this tutorial:
Docker Image: A collection of files that packs together all the necessities needed to set up a completely functional container,
Container: An instance of an image, a running image,
Node: A Kubernetes Object, a virtual machine that runs a container and provide resources,
Kubernetes Cluster: A collection of nodes and configurations to manage them,
Pod: A Kubernetes object, a running container, the smallest de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Musole Masu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IAM managed policies for Amazon DynamoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws/aws-iam-managed-policies-for-amazon-dynamodb-4g5n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws/aws-iam-managed-policies-for-amazon-dynamodb-4g5n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T20:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For application access, you should not use the managed AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies for Amazon DynamoDB. These IAM policies are designed for use with the AWS Web Console and therefore have more permissions to more services than most applications need access to. Instead, please create your own IAM policies for DynamoDB.
In order to follow least privilege security conventions, it is best practice to create your own custom IAM policy for DynamoDB access by an application. If this is something you have never done before, don't be intimidated. I got ya. To get you started, here are a few templates I created to use to enable full access to only Amazon DynamoDB table resources. 
Once you play with these templates, you should ultimately create a new policy that narrows access down to just the operations the app needs to do on the resources it needs to do it. If all you are doing is SELECT and INSERT with the PartiQL API for DynamoDB on one table, then the only actions you should allow are these two:
"dynamodb:PartiQLInsert"
"dynamodb:PartiQLSelect"
In summary, use security best practices when designing access to Amazon DynamoDB for your apps, create your own customer managed IAM policies and do not use the AWS managed IAM policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirk Kirkconnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/which-svg-technique-performs-best-for-way-too-many-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T19:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Sticka digs in here in the best possible way: by making a test page and literally measuring performance. Maybe 1,000 icons is a little bit of an edge case, but hey, 250 rows of data with four icons in …
The post Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a REST API to your Vite Server in 5 Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/xjamundx/adding-a-rest-api-to-your-vite-server-in-5-seconds-270g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/xjamundx/adding-a-rest-api-to-your-vite-server-in-5-seconds-270g"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T18:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many others I've been blown way by the incredible performance and capabilities of vite as a tool for rapidly building out React apps. In my role as an egghead educator and a Developer Advocate at PayPal I'm looking for tools that install quickly, have minimal setup costs and let me start building immediately. vite does all that and more, but in the past I often run into one limitation: I need some kind of API to complement my apps.

I've been using express to build out APIs pretty much since it first came out. Checkout my course on using express 5 if you want a quick tutorial. Express makes it easy to build out APIs and it's super easy to add express support to your vite app. You just need a single plugin: vite-plugin-mix.
I promised 5 seconds, so get ready to copy & paste!
npm install -D vite-plugin-mix

Then in your vite.config.js file add this to your plugins array
mix({
  handler: './api.js',
}),

And then in api.js type:
import express from 'express';

const app = express();

app.get("/api/hello", (req, res) => {
  res.json({ hello: "world" });
});

export const handler = app;

Once you do that you can startup vite with npm run dev and like magic you'll have the ability to reference /api/hello on your local dev server. Like everything else in vite, if you make any changes to your API they'll be available immediately without having to restart anything. Just edit the code and call the route again and you'll see the latest!
One little note: I have only used vite so far for local development and can't personally vouch for it for production apps. If you're looking for something a bit more production ready you might want to check out fastify-vite which combines another popular API server, fastify with vite for one powerful and fast full-stack development tool.
Happy hacking friends!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamund Ferguson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Modern Angular Tooling?


With the Angular CLI no longer including a complete out-of-the-box development solution, it is more important than ever to understand the tools at our disposal to improve the developer experience when building Angular applications.
Modern Angular Tooling is the term used to describe modern tools that will enable you and your team to build a comprehensive development environment. This development environment takes advantage of the latest improvements in the JavaScript ecosystem to improve productivity, consistency, reliability, scalability and developer experience when building Angular applications and libraries. 
We consider Modern Tools to be additional tools that can and should be used when building Angular applications and Angular libraries. These tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colum Ferry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 easy ways to install nodejs in linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing node in linux is quite challenging sometimes, especially if you are a beginner and don't have any idea on how to do that.
In this article, I will show you three different ways of installing Nodejs in linux. You can feel comfortable following the same process in any ubuntu-baseds distro you use.
Installation of Nodejs is insanely easy with apt package manager in linux. To install nodejs with apt package manager, just open up your terminal. Copy this command sudo apt update  && sudo apt upgrade and paste here, hit enter, and type your password. Then we use the command sudo apt install nodejs, press enter, wait few seconds and you find your nodejs is successfully installed. To check the version just type the command node —version and you get the version. 
To install linux binaries,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aashish Panthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 easy ways to install nodejs in linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing node in linux is quite challenging sometimes, especially if you are a beginner and don't have any idea on how to do that.
In this article, I will show you three different ways of installing Nodejs in linux. You can feel comfortable following the same process in any ubuntu-baseds distro you use.
Installation of Nodejs is insanely easy with apt package manager in linux. To install nodejs with apt package manager, just open up your terminal. Copy this command sudo apt update  && sudo apt upgrade and paste here, hit enter, and type your password. Then we use the command sudo apt install nodejs, press enter, wait few seconds and you find your nodejs is successfully installed. To check the version just type the command node —version and you get the version. 
To install linux binaries,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aashish Panthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356977</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/control-layout-in-a-multi-directional-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many business websites need a multilingual setup. As with anything development-related, implementing one in an easy, efficient, and maintainable way is desirable. Designing and developing to be ready for multiple languages, whether it happens right at launch or is expected …
The post Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alaa Abd El-Rahim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Serve Massive Computations Using Python Web Apps.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thuwarakesh/how-to-serve-massive-computations-using-python-web-apps-5ege</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thuwarakesh/how-to-serve-massive-computations-using-python-web-apps-5ege"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article, I wrote about the limitations of using Python web apps for analytics projects. Some of the points kindled readers' curiosity and inspired me to write another story to complement it.
The central question of this article is, "if Python has severe drawbacks because of its sync behavior, how do platforms such as Instagram and Spotify use it to serve millions around the world?"
While I have no official information from these platforms (or similar ones), I have insights into handling such massive requests from my experience.
Here in this article, I prepared a demo to show the basics. A real-life project might have several other technologies in the stack; I haven't included them all here. But I've hinted at some of my favorites in this story and links to resources whenever …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thuwarakesh Murallie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Not Recognizing Headphones – Windows 10 PC Headphone Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>619cb4e711d3cb08287ab00c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/computer-not-recognizing-headphones-windows-10-pc-headphone-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if you plug in your headphones to listen to your favorite music, watch a movie, or do something else and your computer fails to recognize the headphones? That's frustrating.  Your computer not recognizing your headphones is a fairly common issue in Windows 10 PCs.  It could be caused by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Commands Cheat Sheet – How to Learn SQL in 10 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>6197bcba11d3cb08287a90cc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-sql-in-10-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an AI researcher, so one of the main things I deal with is data. A lot of it.  With more than 2.5 exabytes of data generated every day, it comes as no surprise that this data needs to be stored somewhere where we can access it when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Customizable Table of Contents in Word]]></title>
        <id>6198c2d511d3cb08287a97e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-customizable-table-of-contents-in-microsoft-word/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's tricky to make a good-looking and functional table of contents in Microsoft Word. You might often encounter documents that have messy tables of contents along with navigation panes with links to missing headings, non harmonized styles, and badly structured sections.  This wouldn't be a big problem for smaller documents,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling Client-Side Data Securely]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transmitting Data Via the Client


Many applications leave themselves exposed because they transmit critical data such as product prices and discount rates via the client in an unsafe manner.
If possible, applications should avoid transmitting this kind of data via the client. In virtually any conceivable scenario, it is possible to hold such data on the server and reference it directly from server-side logic when needed. 
For example, an application that receives users’ orders for various products should allow users to submit a product code and quantity and look up the price of each requested product in a server-side database. There is no need for users to submit the prices of items back to the server. Even where an application offers different prices or discounts to different users, ther…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling Client-Side Data Securely]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transmitting Data Via the Client


Many applications leave themselves exposed because they transmit critical data such as product prices and discount rates via the client in an unsafe manner.
If possible, applications should avoid transmitting this kind of data via the client. In virtually any conceivable scenario, it is possible to hold such data on the server and reference it directly from server-side logic when needed. 
For example, an application that receives users’ orders for various products should allow users to submit a product code and quantity and look up the price of each requested product in a server-side database. There is no need for users to submit the prices of items back to the server. Even where an application offers different prices or discounts to different users, ther…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUT | Read Notebooks in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/waylonwalker/jut-read-notebooks-in-the-terminal-40hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/waylonwalker/jut-read-notebooks-in-the-terminal-40hp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to read a .ipynb file without starting a jupyter server?  jut has you covered.





watch the video version of this post on YouTube
jut is packaged and available on pypi so installing is as easy as pip installing it.
pip install jut

jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb
jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb --head 3
jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb --tail 2

Take a look at the help of the jut cli to explore all the options that it offers.
jut --help

There is some good information on the projects readme as well.
using pipx
Don't want jut cluttering up your venv, or want to save yourself from making a new one, pipx can manage a separate virual environment for you.  This is one …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello 👋]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preston_overton_72efbf406/hello-5gol</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preston_overton_72efbf406/hello-5gol"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good Morning To All of You Have A blessed Day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Overton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is infrastructure drift?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ukmadlz/what-is-infrastructure-drift-3c85</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ukmadlz/what-is-infrastructure-drift-3c85"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent most of my career as an application/web developer, so primarily glueing X to Y to do a thing that I love doing! And my exposure to operating through DevOps has been through the lens of an application developer.
I’ve recently joined CloudQuery, which is an open-source cloud asset inventory powered by SQL. What this means is that I’m learning more about infrastructure than I’ve ever done before. With that, I’m learning about things like infrastructure as code through Terraform and the concept of infrastructure drift.
Simply put, it’s when the state of your infrastructure is different from the state set by your IaC (Infrastructure-as-Code). For example, if you’ve deployed five lambdas via terraform with the default 128 MB of memory, but now three of them are using 256 MB then you h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Elsmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberpunk 2077 on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dyslexicjedi/cyberpunk-2077-on-linux-149e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dyslexicjedi/cyberpunk-2077-on-linux-149e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T13:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I picked up Cyberpunk 2077 on GOG at 50% off for black friday. I had a bit of trouble getting it to work on Linux (POP!_OS), here are my steps in case it helps someone else. 
First, I spun up Lutris and the game downloaded and installed fine. But when I tried to launch it, it first crashed, then on second launch it played but felt like I was watching a stop motion video. 
After googling, I found proton-tkg which is a patched version of Steam's proton. Downloaded:
wget https://github.com/Frogging-Family/wine-tkg-git/releases/download/6.17.r0.g5f19a815/proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release.tar.gz

Unpacked it
tar xf proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release.tar.gz

Then I linked it to the runners and restarted Lutris.
ln -s /home/<user>/Downloads/proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release/files/ /home/<user>/.local/share/lutris/runners/wine/proton

Selected the proton item under the Runner Options:

I've been playing for an hour now, it's smooth and hasn't crashed. YMMV
Good Luck Have Fun!
If you liked this post:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dyslexicjedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOing down the rabbit hole]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ujjavala/going-down-the-rabbit-hole-6cc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ujjavala/going-down-the-rabbit-hole-6cc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T13:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently upgraded a service written in golang which was deployed using Google's AppEngine and I have just one word for the experience. It was unpleasant. Just to be clear, I really am all in for golang and was also impressed with how easy it is to deploy any service using gcloud. Unfortunately the ride from go1.1 to go.1.2+ was more of a roller coaster for me. Let’s take a glimpse of this three-course meal together so that we can be well prepared for the next upgrade.
I had already run my code locally using dev_appserver.py --enable_host_checking=no --support_datastore_emulator=yes app.yaml , verified the entries in the datastore and was fairly satisfied with the code that I had written.
I was all set to deploy my service on go111 if I hadn’t seen the error on my console related to a pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ujjavala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons Why Developers are Shifting Towards ReactJS Instead of Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/reasons-why-developers-are-shifting-towards-reactjs-instead-of-angular-jnc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/reasons-why-developers-are-shifting-towards-reactjs-instead-of-angular-jnc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T11:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Reasons Why Everyone is Opting for ReactJS over Angular
1. Better Performance
React is mostly like a library than just a framework. Therefore, one does not has to work upfront with DOM or Data Object Model. Instead of that, it goes for a Virtual DOM layer. It updates only those parts of the actual DOM which is needed to update. This escalates the development speed in React instead of Angular. 
Moreover, the Virtual DOM is one of the best features to have as it resolves the issues associated with cross-browser.
The developers also get access to a unified API of cross-browser that runs even on old browser versions. Such excellent performance of React has made everyone not hire AngularJS developers and opt for ReactJS developers as it is becoming more and more popular than Angular.
2. JSX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic server side caching using Redis in nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/singhutkarshh/basic-server-side-caching-using-redis-4e1f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/singhutkarshh/basic-server-side-caching-using-redis-4e1f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T11:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caching is the process of storing copies of files in a cache, or temporary storage location, so that they can be accessed more quickly. 

There is commonly two types of caching :-
1) Server side caches are generally used to avoid making expensive database operations repeatedly to serve up the same content to lots of different clients. 
2) Client side caches are used to avoid transferring the same data over the network repeatedly.
Today we will learn basic server side caching using redis(a fast, open source, in-memory, key-value data store).
Installing Redis:-
Firstly we will need to install redis before using it in our project.
Installing redis on Mac using Homebrew -
brew install redis
brew services start redis
redis-server /usr/local/etc/redis.conf


Installing redis on Windows -
Enable-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Utkarsh Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Hacked Shuttl 🚎]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heykush/how-i-hacked-shuttl-5h1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heykush/how-i-hacked-shuttl-5h1h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How it started 🔥


I was in my 2nd-year @delhitechnicalcampus. College timing is 9 to 4 pm, and I have to rush to pick public transport at 7 pm. It took 2 hours to reach college in between route of Noida to Pari chowk. I used this new service Shuttl. 
Shuttl - They provide Transport service from Noida Sector 37 to Pari Chowk. I am inspired by this startup as they provide 30 rupee journey costs in 10 rupees and with AC minibus.

So, for the first ride, they provide a free Coupon Ride, which is one time applicable. BUT why so and why don't we apply again so? For this, I made a Dual app and login with my secondary number, but that code is not valid for the second number. What the Hackman!

I need to figure out how's this thing working and why can't I apply code in my secondary number account…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav kushwaha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Good Parts of AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/topitguy/the-good-parts-of-aws-3pk0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/topitguy/the-good-parts-of-aws-3pk0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This amazing Digital Book authored by Ex AWS engineers Daniel Vassallo and Josh Pshorr is available at Black Friday Price $15. Anyone who wants to learn from 15 years of combined experience of these ex AWS engineers should take this book.
Everything they know about AWS is shared in the book. It will be an asset for you. Consider grabbing a copy if it interests you.
Cheers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wes Bos Black Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/topitguy/wes-bos-black-friday-jj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/topitguy/wes-bos-black-friday-jj4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, Wes Bos, the popular full stack web developer from Ontario, Canada is offering Black Friday discount on all of his courses. For the next 7 days, you are eligible to get 50% discount for any Wes Bos’s course you buy. This is the only time of the year when Wes Bos slashes the price of his amazing courses.
You don’t want to let this opportunity go. Do take a look at the list of popular Wes Bos courses down below and sign up for your favorite with Black Friday offer. And, the best part is, Wes Bos supports Parity Purchasing Power, so on top of black friday discount, you get additional discount if you are from a country where the price may look expensive.
List of Wes Bos Popular Courses
Master Gatsby — Build modern websites with Gatsby, React and Friends – ReadMore 
Beginner JavaScript – Learn Javascript from scratch – Read More
Advanced React and GraphQL — Build Full Stack Applications with React and GraphQL – Read More
React For Beginners – The best way to learn React – Read More
ES6 for Everyone — The best way to learn modern ES6 JavaScript – Read More
Learn Node — The best way to learn Node.js, Express, MongoDB – Read More
For each of the above courses, you get 50% black friday discount.
You can also take a look at Wes Bos’s most popular course “JavaScript 30 — Build 30 things with vanilla JS in 30 days with 30 tutorials“. It is available for free at the moment until next notice.
If you have any questions about this offer, please feel free to reach out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Dyslexia-Friendly Mode To A Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little CSS, we can adapt our web designs to be more accommodating for people with dyslexia. In this article, we’ll explore those techniques by adding a dyslexia-friendly mode to an existing design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John C Barstow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structure and Endianness in Nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emmygozi/data-structure-and-endianess-in-nodejs-1jgp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emmygozi/data-structure-and-endianess-in-nodejs-1jgp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data structure is the collection of data values, the relationship among them and the functions or operations that can be applied to the data according to Wikipedia.
Memory in Data structure
For example:
1 represented as a byte is 0000 0001         
2 represented as a byte is 0000 0010
3 represented as a byte is 0000 0011
4 represented as a byte is 0000 0100

These are represented in base 2. And that gives us a finite amount of numbers we can store because base 2^8 = 256. So to save bigger numbers, we increase the bytes. 
In java for example, "int" is the equivalent of 4 bytes, 32 bits integer. Type "long" represents 8 bytes, a 64 bits integer.
Endianness in Data Structure
65,000 decimal number in base 2 is: 0b11111101 11101000.
0b here helps us know it is in base 2 and not 1,111,110,111,101,000

The answer above is in big-endian byte because the byte with the biggest 0b11111101 is written first reading from left to right. We can confirm this by converting the big-endian padded by another byte of zeros "0b1111110100000000 to base 10" on google. The result is 64,768 which is very close to our initial number of 65,000.
For networks, the standard is Big-endian and for most PCs, the standard is Little-endian. Check this code snippet online to find out what endian your machine runs. My machine runs on Little-endian.
Endianness has largely ceased to be a matter of concern because of modern computer languages removing this needless complexity and processors which are Bi-endian and can handle both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahaiwe Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Custom Structural Directives in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular comes with many built-in directives. Some of them (eg. NgIf, NgModel or FormControlDirective) are used daily by Angular developers. Those directives can be split into 2 categories:
Attribute directives
They can be used to modify the appearance of behavior of Angular components and DOM elements. For example:
RouterLink
NgModel
FormControlDirective
Structural directives
They can be used to manipulate the HTML structure in the DOM. Using them, we can change the structure of part of the DOM that they control. For example:
NgIf
NgForOf
NgSwitch
In this article, I will focus on the latter.
As I've mentioned above, there are a couple of built-in structural directives in Angular. However, we might come across a case that the ones provided with the framework don't solve. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Custom Structural Directives in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular comes with many built-in directives. Some of them (eg. NgIf, NgModel or FormControlDirective) are used daily by Angular developers. Those directives can be split into 2 categories:
Attribute directives
They can be used to modify the appearance of behavior of Angular components and DOM elements. For example:
RouterLink
NgModel
FormControlDirective
Structural directives
They can be used to manipulate the HTML structure in the DOM. Using them, we can change the structure of part of the DOM that they control. For example:
NgIf
NgForOf
NgSwitch
In this article, I will focus on the latter.
As I've mentioned above, there are a couple of built-in structural directives in Angular. However, we might come across a case that the ones provided with the framework don't solve. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to access your server anywhere without SSH]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mage1k99/how-to-access-your-server-anywhere-without-ssh-fdf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mage1k99/how-to-access-your-server-anywhere-without-ssh-fdf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T08:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to access your server anywhere without SSH.
You want to have temporary access of your server from a remote location


You don't want to authorize a key to connect via ssh






OK now lets get into the process.
root access
A Linux machine with ports 3023, 3024, 3025, and 443 open
A registered domain name
An SSH client like OpenSSH.
2FA App
visit Teleport website




Click getting started, and select the community edition

Select acconding your platform, for me its Ubuntu 18.04 LTS, so I select the Linux 64-bit DEB version 8.0

Now login to your server via ssh, and download teleport using wget by running wget https://get.gravitational.com/teleport_8.0.0_amd64.deb




Install the deb package by sudo apt install ./teleport_8.0.0_amd64.deb




Configure your domain for SSL certificate




sudo teleport configure --acme --acme-email=your-email@example.com --cluster-name=tele.example.com -o /etc/teleport.yaml

443 you needed to edit it and change the port (/etc/teleport.yaml) [Included at last step].




Now start the teleport sudo systemctl start teleport.service


Add user with




tctl users add teleport-admin --roles=editor,access --logins=root,ubuntu,ec2-user

It will give you a url to access the teleport


Follow the steps in the webpage to activate







  
  
  For users with port address being used by other process



Open the config file in /etc/teleport.yaml

Go to the line where




web_listen_addr: 0.0.0.0:443
public_addr: tele.example.com:443

Change the port address there


reload teleport service by sudo systemctl restart teleport.service






for more about installation documentation checkout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Magesh Babu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Java 17 features for improved security and serialization]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brianverm/new-java-17-features-for-improved-security-and-serialization-5h3f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brianverm/new-java-17-features-for-improved-security-and-serialization-5h3f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T08:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2020, I wrote the article Serialization and deserialization in Java: explaining the Java deserialize
 about the problems Java has with its custom serialization implementation. The serialization framework is so deeply embedded inside Java that knowing how dangerous some implementation can be is important. Insecure
Recently, Java 17 -- the new LTS version -- was released. But how do the new features impact this problem, and can we prevent deserialization vulnerabilities better using these features?
In the blog post, I will look at three main Java 17 features:
Records
Java Flight Recorder (JFR) improvements
JEP 415 (Java Enhancement Proposal) Context-Specific Deserialization Filters.
Records were introduced in Java 14 as a preview feature and became a fully released feature in Jav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Vermeer 🧑🏼‍🎓🧑🏼‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices to protect your smartphone with MobSF]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/best-practices-to-protect-your-smartphone-with-mobsf-17am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/best-practices-to-protect-your-smartphone-with-mobsf-17am"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this era of technology, we are completely relying on smartphones and yet most of us are unaware of its vulnerabilities. A smartphone is a new necessity in our day-to-day life and if intruders get access to our smartphones, it is like intruders have access to our life. This itself states how vital securing our smartphones is. Aviyel is coming with another great event to help you protect your smartphones and making it your top priority.
Why I should join this event?
You’ll learn how to secure your sensitive data.
Know how your digital life is at risk and how to protect it from intruders.
You'll learn how to make use of MobSF to protect your sensitive data from hackers.
Join Edem Gold where he will guide you with some of the most important steps to hack-proof your smartphones using MobSF and secure your digital information by preventing possible malicious activities on your smartphones.
Edem Gold is a teen Nigerian AI Engineer and content creator. He loves converting complex concepts into non-jargon stories. Gold has also experience in Blockchain development on the Ethereum system.
Join us to get hands-on experience with MobSF, open-source, and learn to tackle mobile security!
Date: November 28th, 2021
Time: 8.00 AM PST | 11:00 AM EST
Where 👉: https://bit.ly/3xddbD5
Impressed? Check out the rest of our events!
Let’s build open-source together! 🎉
Edem Gold Socials!
Twitter: Edem Gold
Edem Gold
Edem Gold]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sankalp Swami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EP14: Create Terraform Modules for Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/someoneelsescloud/ep14-create-terraform-modules-for-azure-nhc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/someoneelsescloud/ep14-create-terraform-modules-for-azure-nhc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the Episode on YouTube: https://youtu.be/o9KD7lLrQvg
In this Episode, I’ll show you how to create your first Terraform Module to use in Azure! We will walk-through, the standard terraform code and how to generalise it into a module. I’ll run through a demo to show you how to write code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going serverless with MongoDB Realm - Vue.js Version]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-vuejs-version-nld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-vuejs-version-nld"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture is a pattern of running and building applications and services without having to manage infrastructure. It involves the applications and services running on the server, but all the server management is done by a cloud provider.
This post will discuss building a fullstack user management application using MongoDB, MongoDB Realm, and Vue.js. At the end of this tutorial, we will learn how to create a database on MongoDB, serverless functions as our endpoints using MongoDB Realm and consume the endpoints in a Vue.js application.
MongoDB Realm is a development platform designed for building mobile, web, desktop, and IoT applications. It offers services like data synchronization, serverless functions, triggers, user authentication, e.t.c. We can build and maintain applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going serverless with MongoDB Realm - React.js Version]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-reactjs-version-jh6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-reactjs-version-jh6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture is a pattern of running and building applications and services without having to manage infrastructure. It involves the applications and services running on the server, but all the server management is done by a cloud provider.
This post will discuss building a fullstack user management application using MongoDB, MongoDB Realm, and React.js. At the end of this tutorial, we will learn how to create a database on MongoDB, serverless functions as our endpoints using MongoDB Realm and consume the endpoints in a React.js application.
MongoDB Realm is a development platform designed for building mobile, web, desktop, and IoT applications. It offers services like data synchronization, serverless functions, triggers, user authentication, e.t.c. We can build and maintain app…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Comprehensive Guide to Angular Performance Tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/the-comprehensive-guide-to-angular-performance-tuning-1l5n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/the-comprehensive-guide-to-angular-performance-tuning-1l5n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T06:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not uncommon to see Angular apps slow down over time. Angular is a performant platform, but if we don't know how to create performant Angular apps, our apps will become slower as they evolve. As a result, any serious Angular developer must be aware of what makes an Angular app slow in order to prevent it from being slow in the first place.
Change detection can be the most performance-intensive part of Angular apps, so it's important to understand how to render the templates efficiently so that we would just re-rendering a component if it has new changes to display.
When an asynchronous event occurs in the app, such as click, XMLHttpRequest, or setTimeout, the default change detection behavior for components is to re-render. This can be a matter of concern because it will result in a l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to store result from async pipe in angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codever/how-to-store-result-from-async-pipe-in-angular-a0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codever/how-to-store-result-from-async-pipe-in-angular-a0k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T05:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project: codever - File:  snippet-details.component.html
Use the async pipe and store it in variable for later use *ngIf="(snippet$ | async) as snippet". Below the complete snippet example with usage included:
<div *ngIf="(snippet$ | async) as snippet" class="card">
  <div class="card-body show-hide">
    <div class="header-wrapper">
      <div class="titles">
        <h4 *ngIf='inlist; else hyperLinkTitle' class="card-title">
             <span *ngIf="snippet.public; else linkToPrivateSnippet">
                <i class="fas fa-eye fa-xs mr-2" title="Public snippet"></i>
                <a routerLink="/snippets/{{snippet._id}}/details"
                   [innerHtml]="snippet.title | highlight: queryText"></a> </span>
          <ng-template #linkToPrivateSnippet>
                <span>
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Matei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building RESTful APIs with Node JS & Hoppscotch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/live-event-building-restful-apis-with-node-js-hoppscotch-1oll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/live-event-building-restful-apis-with-node-js-hoppscotch-1oll"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T05:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are planning to get into Backend Development, it is a must to understand what RESTful APIs are and how they work for building a robust, reliable, and scalable web application. Despite googling for hours, you are still chaotic about RESTful APIs? Time to relax as Aviyel is coming with an amazing event to answer all of your questions.
Why you should join this event?
You will learn how to make CRUD API endpoints with Node.js, and Express.js.
You will learn how to test your backend APIs with Hoppscotch.
You will learn how to set up your database using HarperDB



Ayodele Samuel Adebayo (unclebigbay) is coming live on Aviyel to clear all your doubts about RESTful APIs. Unclebigbay is a Nigerian software developer, technical writer, and content creator who writes about programming concepts and project-based articles on his blog. He graduated from Tiidelab's coding Bootcamp, and currently works as a freelancer, where he enjoys participating in open source projects and hackathons, with two of his projects making it to the winning list of hackathons on Hashnode. Unclebigbay can be seen playing volleyball with his sports team if he is not coding or writing.
Join us to get hands-on experience with APIs and open-source!
Date: November 28th, 2021
Time: 8.00 AM PST | 11:00 AM EST
Register Here 👉: https://bit.ly/3nHxPYL
Impressed? Check out the rest of our events!
Ayodele Samuel Adebayo Socials!
Twitter: unclebigbay
unclebigbay
Unclebigbay
Ayodele Samuel Adebayo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sankalp Swami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horrifying Vulnerabilities in the Death/Birth Certificate System]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/scriptautomate/horrifying-vulnerabilities-in-the-deathbirth-certificate-system-11mn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/scriptautomate/horrifying-vulnerabilities-in-the-deathbirth-certificate-system-11mn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T04:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premise: Death and birth certificates can be filed online, with practically no oversight.
DefCon Response: Let's show the world how easy it is to kill anyone, and/or profit from the birthing/killing of virtual…babies?
This is one of my DefCon 23 Debriefs, from the blog archives back in 2015! If you ever have the opportunity to get your work to ship you to Defcon, take it. If you ever get the opportunity to ship yourself, don't think: just go.
Presentation Title: I Will Kill You
The Presenter: Chris Rock
Published Book: The Baby Harvest



Chris Rock gave a crazy presentation about how terrifyingly vulnerable the systems are surrounding death certificates and birth certificates. It's incredibly vulnerable due to how easy it is to register yourself in the online systems currently available, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Ardolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 WordPress Plugins to Improve Your Website&#x27;s Performance]]></title>
        <id>6195174b11d3cb08287a7b96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/wordpress-plugins-to-improve-your-website-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T02:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I will show you which free WordPress plugins you should use and how to configure them to significantly improve your WordPress website's performance.  Web performance is an essential SEO factor, and you shouldn’t underestimate it. Each second your website takes to load can hurt your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to Hexo, an SSG powered by Node!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/belokond/contributing-to-hexo-an-ssg-powered-by-node-1lho</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/belokond/contributing-to-hexo-an-ssg-powered-by-node-1lho"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T01:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I was looking for a repository to contribute to. Looking for a repository to contribute is always the hardest step, because you need to adapt to the new project, get used to the code structure, and you have to learn a lot of things about the codebase before contributing something meaningful.🥵🥵
After searching for a while, I found Hexo, an SSG. I was interested on working on this one since I am working on an SSG myself. I thought, "maybe I can get some inspiration from them on how to approach the design of my SSG🕵️‍♀️🕵️‍♀️"
I skimmed through the issues list, until I found one that seemed manageable for my level, issue #4516: Only show line number when number of lines of code greater than a threshold! We can guess the feature requested just by reading a title: implement an opt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbelokon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding form validation to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-form-validation-to-an-angular-application-387a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-form-validation-to-an-angular-application-387a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T22:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 13 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
Form validation enables the quality, accuracy, and integrity of the user input data. It’s possible to validate a form in Angular in two ways, one with reactive (using functions in the component class) and the other with template-driven forms (using attributes in the HTML) and we will use the template-driven forms way.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the application with the Angular base structure using the @angular/cli with the route file and the SCSS style…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Directory-Scoped Variables with direnv in POSIX Systems]]></title>
        <id>619909b111d3cb08287a9bd9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-directory-scoped-envs-with-direnv-in-posix-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common practice in software projects is to keep certain information separated but accessible from the codebase which uses it. Developers usually do this with secrets such as passwords or private keys, or with user or context-specific info pieces.  But managing environment variables can be a pain. There are a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Design Thinking Process Explained]]></title>
        <id>613f3cad852f4307d372c7dc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-design-thinking-process-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Design Thinking Process is a way to come up with creative, user centric solutions to complex problems. But how does it work exactly? In this article, I will explain what the Design Thinking Process is and break down the five phases behind it. We will explore how this process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-user-tracking-and-industry-standards-on-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Eva PenzeyMoog’s new book, Jeremy highlights the widespread user tracking situation in this industry:
There was a line that really stood out to me: 
The idea that it’s alright to do whatever unethical thing is currently the 
…
The post On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My golden rules for Angular intercomponent data communication]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/polyterative/my-golden-rules-for-angular-intercomponent-data-communication-44g7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/polyterative/my-golden-rules-for-angular-intercomponent-data-communication-44g7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are some rules that I have lazily picked up over the past four years of professional development on angular.
I generally work on small to medium projects without the time to integrate a formal state management system.
It is for this reason that there are data services that try to solve the problem of carrying communication around. If anyone has any further questions or curiosities regarding these points feel free to leave a comment.
methods must be extracted into functions until nothing can be extracted anymore
the component logic shold refer only to local resources of the component as much as possible
dataservices deal with data I/O with the server
the business Logic must live within the dataservice and all components should be of assistance to the business Logic, visualization assistance and small local logics to visualize and modify data
components (internal to the feature internal to the root component) must implement the root dataservice or receive data as input (observables are strongly preferred)
avoid multi-level handovers through inputs, it slows you down and makes refactoring a hassle
if the data as input changed hands more than twice use a dataservice,
each feature must have its own module and declare components related only to that feature
putting the general dataservice next to the feature module is the best way to indicate the root from which to start exploring the code
the beginning of the end of the data flow must take place within the dataservice

the substrate cache-services for API calls must live in the provide of the feature module they belong to and refer to
components  can be interaction contexts between dataservices but services are preferred when possible
interaction services can be interaction contexts between dataservices]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladyslav Yakovenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; Base64 [LS#1]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-base64-ls1-42d4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-base64-ls1-42d4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encode inline





echo -n 'Hello World!' | base64

base64 ~/.bashrc > encoded-file.txt

cat ~/.bashrc | base64 > encoded-file.txt

echo -n "SGVsbG8gV29ybGQh" | base64 -d

base64 -d encoded-file.txt > decoded-file.txt

cat encoded-file.txt | base64 -d > decoded-file.txt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISO Roadmap: The First 90 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gitguardian/ciso-roadmap-the-first-90-days-efl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gitguardian/ciso-roadmap-the-first-90-days-efl"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


You may have found this article for several reasons. Maybe you just landed a big promotion to CISO/CSO or you’re looking to become one soon. You could have been a CISO or security lead for a while now and are looking for new ideas. Whatever brought you here, you will come away with a game plan for strengthening your information security program.
First and foremost, a CISO is an advocate for good information security practices within the business. Stating it like that makes it sound simple, but there are so many responsibilities and considerations that go into a complete information security program. Security considerations go far beyond just technical controls. The many domains of cyber security could be listed along with key components of each, but it’s much easier to provi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C.J. May</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheus and Grafana, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muckitymuck/prometheus-and-grafana-part-2-47bg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muckitymuck/prometheus-and-grafana-part-2-47bg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prometheus.yml:
# my global config
global:
  scrape_interval:     15s # Set the scrape interval to every 15 seconds. Default is every 1 minute.
  evaluation_interval: 15s # Evaluate rules every 15 seconds. The default is every 1 minute.

scrape_configs:
  # The job name is added as a label `job=<job_name>` to any timeseries scraped from this config.
  - job_name: 'prometheus'

    # metrics_path defaults to '/metrics'
    # scheme defaults to 'http'.

    static_configs:
      - targets: ['localhost:9090']

  - job_name: 'node-exporter'

    # Override the global default and scrape targets from this job every 5 seconds.
    scrape_interval: 5s
    metrics_path: /metrics

    static_configs:
      - targets:
        - <PUBLIC IP>:9100

This is a good starting place for a monitoring system for Linux boxes
Running the services in docker is also advised as it simplifies the rollout.
Docker node exporter:
sudo docker run --restart always -d --net="host" --pid="host"  -v "/:/host:ro,rslave"  prom/node-exporter:latest  --path.rootfs=/host

Docker prometheus:
sudo docker service create --replicas 1 --name dockerprometheus     --mount type=bind,source=/home/ubuntu/prometheus/prometheus.yml,destination=/etc/prometheus/prometheus.yml     --publish published=9090,target=9090,protocol=tcp     prom/prometheus

When you get around to making panels in Grafana, these queries are very useful:
100 - ((node_filesystem_avail_bytes{mountpoint="/",fstype!="rootfs"} * 100) /            node_filesystem_size_bytes{mountpoint="/",fstype!="rootfs"})

node_filesystem_avail_bytes


OR you could just setup a template for Node Exporter:

Enter 405 for the Grafana ID.

Pick up the name and choose a Data Source for the dashboard.

To make an alert, start a NEW dashboard and NEW panel. Template dashboards like above will not work. 
Enter the query for the item you want to track and press the Alert tab.
That should do it for a basic monitoring service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>muckitymuck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReactJS Project – Build a Rick and Morty Character Wiki]]></title>
        <id>619b998511d3cb08287aa257</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-js-project-build-a-rick-and-morty-character-wiki/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T19:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're gonna practice our React JS skills by building a Rick and Morty Character Wiki.  Here's what we'll build today:    Here's a [live demo of the project] 👇  https://react-projects-psi.vercel.app/.  And here's the GitHub Repository.  The topics we'll cover while building this project are:  React Hooks (useState, useEffect)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Bloggers/Technical Bloggers Wanted]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hitsubscribe/developer-bloggerstechnical-bloggers-wanted-m7c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hitsubscribe/developer-bloggerstechnical-bloggers-wanted-m7c"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T19:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hit Subscribe is a company that hires engineers to write content for technical blogs. So what we're looking for is quite straightforward: engineers interested in a side hustle writing technical content for companies that sell to engineers. Or, put more simply, we want you to write content (mostly blog posts) about technical topics like DevOps, automated testing, machine learning, security, and more.
https://www.hitsubscribe.com/apply-to-be-an-author/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angela C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monster 1.25.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schukai/monster-1250-released-ic1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schukai/monster-1250-released-ic1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we released the latest edition of our Monster project. Monster is a collection of javascript classes that we need for daily work in our web projects.
Besides small helper functions and classes it also provides useful functions to enable reactive programming.
Monster is available via jsdelivr and npm.
Only the changes are described here. The full functionality can be found in the documentation.
We have added a new class to handle resources. Resources are external content such as scripts, data, or stylesheets.
These classes are usually used by the ResourceManager.
The class takes care of creating the tags and monitors the load event.
With the new class RessourceManager scripts, styles and data can be included in an HTML page simply by specifying the URL.
// new Object
const manager = n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Volker Schukai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS “decorations”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357046</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-decorations/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reader wrote to me the other day asking about this bit of CSS they came across in Wikipedia’s Common.css:
.mw-collapsible-leftside-toggle .mw-collapsible-toggle {
  /* @noflip */
  float: left;
  /* @noflip */
  text-align: left;
}
What’s that @noflip business? That’s …
The post CSS “decorations” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[website to dextop App In six steps with electron]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kartiks26/website-to-dextop-app-in-six-steps-with-electron-3nnn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kartiks26/website-to-dextop-app-in-six-steps-with-electron-3nnn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Convert Url To Desktop App With Electron



  
  
  Perquisites



node JS - install





  
  
  Step-1




  
  
  Create Folder And in Terminal Run This Commands





npm init

just hit enter unless you end up .
{
    "name": "tutorial",
    "version": "1.0.0",
    "description": "",
    "main": "main.js",
    "scripts": {
        "start": "electron ."
    },
    "author": "",
    "license": "ISC"
}

"scripts": {

        "start": "electron ."
    },


tutorial
|package.json


npm install --save-dev electron

{
    "name": "tutorial",
    "version": "1.0.0",
    "description": "",
    "main": "main.js",
    "scripts": {
        "start": "electron ."
    },
    "author": "",
    "license": "ISC",
    "devDependencies": {
        "electron": "^16.0.1"
    }
}


tutorial
        |node modu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kartiks26</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[¿Cómo crear un juego Play to Earn?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/turupawn/como-crear-un-juego-play-to-earn-3g8j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/turupawn/como-crear-un-juego-play-to-earn-3g8j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proyectos como Plant vs Undead, Decentraland, Sandbox, Crypto Cars, Axie Infinity han sido el primer arcercamiento con el modelo Play to Earn. En este video vamos a ver que necesitas para crear tu juego que premie a los jugadores con tokens por jugar.





  
  
  Dependencias


Para este tutorial ocuparás NodeJs que recomiendo descargarlo en Linux via NVM , también necesitarás un URL de RPC te recomiendo usar INFURA, y finalmente Metamask con fondos de Rinkeby Testnet que puedes conseguir desde el Faucet.
Primero bajamos el proyecto Demo.
git clone https://github.com/FilosofiaCodigo/PlayToEarnDemo.git
cd PlayToEarnDemo/

Ahora instalamos las dependencias.
npm install

Antes de lanzar debemos agregar el archivo de configuración .env que puedes construir en base al arhivo de ejemplo .env.example.
Finalmente lanzamos.
npx truffle deploy --network rinkeby --reset

Primero ingresamos en la carpeta del backend e instalamos las dependencias.
cd backend
npm install

Luego crea un nuevo archivo .env pero esta vez en la carpeta /backend, este archivo contiene lo mismo que creamos en el paso 1.
También debes copypastear el archivo ./build/MyToken.json en ./backend/MyToken.json.
Finalmente edita acorde las variables CONTRACT_ADDRESS y BACKEND_WALLET_ADDRESS en ./backend/backend.js.
Ahora levantamos el servidor backend.
node backend.js

Para poder jugar en el frontend debemos lanzar la web del cliente. Para eso ingresamos en la carpeta del cliente e instalamos la única dependencia de manera global.
cd client
npm i -g lite-server

Igual como lo hicimos antes, debes copypastear el archivo ./build/MyToken.json esta vez en ./client/MyToken.json.
Una vez hecho esto lanzamos el juego.
lite-server

Recuerda agregar el contrato a metamask para observar cómo obtienes tokens por jugar.
¡Gracias por ver este tutorial!
Sígueme en dev.to y en Youtube para todo lo relacionado al desarrollo en Blockchain en Español.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Castro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scanning and Repairing Drive – How to Fix Stuck Windows 10 PC Hard Drive]]></title>
        <id>619bb03e11d3cb08287aa4c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/scanning-and-repairing-drive-how-to-fix-stuck-windows-10-pc-hard-drive/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T17:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a Windows 10 PC, you might occasionally see the notorious "scanning and repairing drive" message. This error can happen to the C drive, hard drive, and any other external drive.  This scanning and repairing can take several hours, or even cost you a whole workday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vuex With Class Components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/carrotfarmer/vuex-with-class-components-5fc1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/carrotfarmer/vuex-with-class-components-5fc1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helloooo, in this post I'll show you how you can use vuex with TypeScript and class-components.
In this tutorial I will be using:
Vue 2
Vuex ^3.6.2
TypeScript 4.5

Now let's start coding! First we have to create our Vue.js app. To do that run:
vue create vuex-counter

and make sure you include Vuex, TypeScript and Use class components in your options.




Let's now create the Vuex store. The store will consist of a singular state which will contain the main count from where we'll derive the incremented and decremented ones.
src/store/index.ts
import Vue from "vue";
import Vuex from "vuex";

Vue.use(Vuex);

export default new Vuex.Store({
  state: {
    count: 1,
  },
  getters: {},
  mutations: {},
  actions: {},
  modules: {},
});

Using the count variable in the state we will use getters…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dhruva Srinivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Workshops: Winter 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of CSS, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our [online workshops on UX, front-end and design](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357080</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-layouts-fewer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T15:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We cannot talk about web development without talking about Responsive Design. It’s just a given these days and has been for many years. Media queries are a part of Responsive Design and they aren’t going anywhere. Since the introduction of …
The post Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Week learning rust]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/enyelsequeira/first-week-learning-rust-4j7i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/enyelsequeira/first-week-learning-rust-4j7i"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My First week learning Rust using (The Rust Programming Language) "The Book"



  
  
  Why Rust?



As a Front-End developer, there is a lot you need to learn and keep up to date. One of the biggest changes coming to web development is  web3.0, if you are not living under a rock you have probably heard about it,  at least a little. With these changes coming to the web I decided to learn rust to make myself more valuable, this decision also comes after researching the kind of projects you could do. One of them is a compiler, which funny enough my favorite React framework Next uses. I am a big fan of Next and my goal is to understand how rust  made a framework that was already fast even faster.
Read The Rust Programming Language 
Try and read at least 1-2 hours each week
Practice solving co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enyel Sequeira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: How I Broke ngOnInit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-how-i-broke-ngoninit-4mkm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-how-i-broke-ngoninit-4mkm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T14:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, recently I ran into an issue where one of my functions was not being implemented "at the correct time." The solution was to trigger it in another component via ngOnInit.
Moving the code was simple, but in the process I ran into an issue that I've seen before but not dug into.
The issue is that I like to use fat-arrow functions in my code (() => {}) and somewhere along the way I converted an ngOnInit to fat-arrow. I unknowingly broke the OnInit lifecycle hook complete.
ngOnInit = async (): Promise<void> => {
  await this.init();
  ...
};

The fix was actually pretty simple, I converted the code back to a traditional function pattern ...
async ngOnInit(): Promise<void> {
  await this.init();
  ...
}

... and my function started working again.
Be careful (yes, I am telling myself this) as you may inadvertently write code that does not execute correctly. It was a simple mistake and one that was hidden by some layers of async behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.ts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add parameterized route in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/redthemer/how-to-add-parameterized-route-in-angular-1n5l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/redthemer/how-to-add-parameterized-route-in-angular-1n5l"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T13:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose you have the requirement that you want to show list of users if the url is /user, and you want to show user detail of a particular user when the URL is /user/useId.
To achieve this we can create a users component, then in its ngOnInit we could check if params are present.
/// Here route is ActivatedRoute

this.route.queryParams.subscribe(params => {

if(params.userId){
//// Do Something
console.log(params.userId);
}
});


You can get the params like this and then write your logic accordindly. If params are present then show userDetails if not then list of users.
Like So
const routes: Routes = [
  { path: '/user', component: UsersComponent },
  { path: '/user:userId', component : UserDetailsComponent}
];

Here we are explicitly stating that if url is /user then show UsersComponent or if it is like /users/xxxid then show userDetials page.
This is more Systematic & preferred way of doing the task.
If you are using only one parameter then use parameterized route. But if you have many parameters then use querry Params as stated above in solution 1.
<a *ngFor="let user of users"
  routerLink="/user/{{user.id}}">
  {{user.name}}
</a>

Assume we are having list users and clicking on a user name will open that particlular user details.
To get the value of ther parameter use ActivatedRoute
console.log(this.route.snapshot.paramMap.get('userId');

Points To remember
If you are getting any error remember to recheck the route you had written. sometimes you append extra / like user/:userId/ or prepend extra slash (/) like /user/:userId.
Although you can use more then two parameters
like  user/:userId/:id/:age 
I would suggest to avoid it and if it cannot be avoided atleast limit it to two parameters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A technical tale of NodeSecure - Chapter 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fraxken/a-technical-tale-of-nodesecure-chapter-1-2mm8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fraxken/a-technical-tale-of-nodesecure-chapter-1-2mm8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T13:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello 👋
I have been working on the NodeSecure project for almost three years now 😵. I have personally come a long way... At the beginning I didn't know much about the field in which I started 🐤.
That's why I thought that writing articles about "some" of the technical difficulties and the tools I used could be valuable 🚀.
I will try to make articles that focus on one aspect 🎯. Let's get started 💃.
One of the first challenges I had to solve was how to get the dependency tree and all the information attached to the packages.
My first instinct was to work with the public API of the npm registry.
What I wanted to do has already been implemented in the package named pacote.
Note: Arborist did not exist yet. I will come back to this in a future article. The first versions of NodeSecure did …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas.G</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hiding primary keys and database IDs using Hashids]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/romansorin/hiding-primary-keys-and-database-ids-using-hashids-2ida</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/romansorin/hiding-primary-keys-and-database-ids-using-hashids-2ida"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T13:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In most CRUD operations and REST APIs, primary keys are used to reference models that you want to access or modify. A majority of APIs will take an ID as a parameter in a route:
GET /api/v1/posts/:id

// Return the Post resource with an ID of 457
GET /api/v1/posts/457

While it's the simplest and most effective way of specifying the model to use, we often don't want to show these IDs to the user. By displaying primary keys, you give users the ability to estimate the number of rows in your tables. If authorization isn't effective or routes aren't protected, users could input random numbers to access information that they otherwise shouldn't have.
Using obfuscated IDs can be useful in social media or feed contexts, where the content isn't used in the URL, but you want something less signific…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Sorin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xplorer, a modern File Explorer that was written using TypeScript, has its performance improved on the recent release]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kimlimjustin/xplorer-a-modern-file-explorer-that-was-written-using-typescript-has-its-performance-improved-on-the-recent-release-4f99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kimlimjustin/xplorer-a-modern-file-explorer-that-was-written-using-typescript-has-its-performance-improved-on-the-recent-release-4f99"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T12:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello devs!
About two months ago, I released the first version of Xplorer and wrote a post about it which makes both of the blog and the repository went into trending 🚀. Thanks a lot for it. Please read this blog before continue reading
I wrote a fully-functioning File Explorer, using TypeScript.
Justin Maximillian Kimlim ・ Sep 25 ・ 2 min read
#typescript
        #showdev
        #node
        #xplorer
      
What is Xplorer?  (click to expand)
  
Xplorer is a file explorer built from ground-up to be fully customizable. And even without any customization, it already looks modern!
Xplorer is a cross-platform application built using Tauri, and you can run it on Windows, MacOS, or Linux without having much trouble. One of the key feature is Xplorer allows you to preview the files you have di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Maximillian Kimlim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS Library in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/rxjs-library-in-angular-2e3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/rxjs-library-in-angular-2e3d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T12:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is RxJs?


Reactive Extensions for JavaScriptis a library for reactive programming. RxJS uses observables which will make it easier to compose call back-based code or asynchronous code.
If you are working with Angular, you should at least be familiar with RxJs.The angular framework itself is build using RxJs and around some of the RxJs concepts. We can do much more by using RxJs and observable like better and more readable code and we can even reduce the number of lines of code
The component is a key part of the Angular App structure. Everything in Angular comes around the state of the component and how it will be projected in the UI. On many occasions, we can use streams that will help us to represent volatile pieces of our data inside the view.
RxJs provides an implementation that i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Transfer a Website to a Different Host (Without Downtime or Issues)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/derosaj/how-to-transfer-a-website-to-a-different-host-without-downtime-or-issues-3ph6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/derosaj/how-to-transfer-a-website-to-a-different-host-without-downtime-or-issues-3ph6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T11:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picking the best hosting provider for your website can be time-consuming as there are so many options available. Unfortunately, sometimes when you make your choice, the service doesn’t meet your expectations, making you feel stuck. 
In this case, the next suitable step might be to switch to another hosting company. Yet, this option also has its risks, such as downtime issues and complicated processes. 
This article will provide a step-by-step guide to help transfer your website to a different web host safely. You’ll learn all of the essential points, from choosing the best web host to canceling your current hosting service. 
It’s important to pick a new web hosting provider before canceling your existing hosting plan. Several aspects to consider when choosing a new provider are cost, resou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary J Derosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't panic when using CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elisboa/dont-panic-when-using-cli-3d99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elisboa/dont-panic-when-using-cli-3d99"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T11:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


When using the Command Line Interface, we often find a few long and / or confusing commands. And this post intends to ease the pain of getting along with that.
When things start to get complicated, there are some things that can be done. In this post, we are talking about three of them:
Aliases
Functions
Comments
An alias is exactly what it means: a nickname. It is very useful when running commands that take too much arguments. For example:
alias lah=ls -ltrah

Now, when running the lah command, it will be exactly like running ls -ltrah.
A function is probably the best way to run a group of commands. When adding a if or a for statement, it gets even more interesting. Let's suppose we want to connect to a server which is still being provisioned or rebooted:
function keeptrying() {
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduardo Lisboa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[change case sensitive setting in less command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/icy1900/change-case-sensitive-setting-in-less-command-3j57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/icy1900/change-case-sensitive-setting-in-less-command-3j57"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick guide in 2 steps: Do your search:
:/put search lowercase word here after slash
Then after all the case sensitive matches are highlighted:
:-i
This will highlight all matches regardless of case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Wix Websites (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a performance culture is very important. In this article, Dan Shappir shares which actions and processes the Wix team put in place in order to achieve dramatic improvements in the performance of websites built and hosted on their platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Advanced Types of TypeScript with type-challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shoki/learn-advanced-types-of-typescript-with-type-challenges-1l5h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shoki/learn-advanced-types-of-typescript-with-type-challenges-1l5h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T09:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One distinctive difference between TypeScript and JavaScript is the difference in typing: JavaScript is dynamically typed, where the data type is determined at runtime, while TypeScript is statically typed, where the type is defined in advance.
While being able to type makes it easier to notice errors at compile time, there are many times when typing does not work. So, let's practice typing!
What I use through this article is open source of type-challenges by Anthony Fu
Hello World (example)



  
  
  ✳️Problem





/* _____________ Your Code Here _____________ */
type HelloWorld = any // expected to be a string

/* _____________ Test Cases _____________ */
import { Equal, Expect, NotAny } from '@type-challenges/utils'

type cases = [
  Expect<NotAny<HelloWorld>>,
  Expect<Equal<HelloWorl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sho-ki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js + MUI v5 with TypeScript support]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/huydhoang/nextjs-mui-v5-with-typescript-support-b51</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/huydhoang/nextjs-mui-v5-with-typescript-support-b51"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since MUI v5 (Material UI) was released, I've started a new project with it. But as it's a brand new version with breaking changes, I couldn't find an example project that I'm fully satisfied with.
The one on the official MUI's Github repo featuring Next.js with TypeScript (my framework of choice) didn't follow standard Next.js folder structure, as of this writing.
So I felt inclined to create one with the most basic features that I would use myself. The result is on my Github (link below).
Here's a screenshot of the About page:

It features a standard folder structure as generated by create-next-app and the leanest usable ESLint + Prettier configs for linting/formatting.
View on Github
If you like my work, please give it a star to let me know it's useful to you :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Huy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty System Specs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skino2020/pretty-system-specs-ca1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skino2020/pretty-system-specs-ca1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


One thing i spotted when i started using Tech Twitter was people would post screenshots of there system specifications in terminals with pretty logos etc and i wanted to know how it was all done!...... its actually SUPER simple.
NeoFetch is a free, easy to install application which gathers system information and prints it to the terminal in a "pretty way". It pulls together all of your system information and strips out the crap and displays it in a way that doesnt hurt the brain....
Installing NeoFetch is as easy as typing the following two commands....
sudo add-apt-repository ppa:dawidd0811/neofetch


and
sudo apt update && sudo apt install neofetch


this add the official NeoFetch PPA to your ubuntu installation and means you will always get the most up to date version.
after that simply type neofetch in your terminal and you will get a screenshot like below.

Another app you can use is screenfetch which does near enough the exact same thing!.
Install it with the following command:
sudo apt install screenfetch


and then just type screenfetch in your terminal to get your system specs like below.

Well thats going to do it today hope this quick blog post will be of interest and help you out. as a side note you can also get Screenfetch for MacOS.
 
Raspada-Blog
  I post on my blog primarily and share the posts via API, please check out Raspada-Blog for more posts and information. If you have any questions please message me on twitter or use my website contact form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Primeros pasos en Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/analucygdl/primeros-pasos-en-docker-17e7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/analucygdl/primeros-pasos-en-docker-17e7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T07:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker es un software de código abierto que automatiza el despliegue de aplicaciones con el uso de contenedores. Esto hace que sea más fácil empaquetar y aislar el  software para que  pueda implementarse más tarde en otro entorno. Todo esto proporcionando una API muy fácil de usar.
Podrá surgir la duda "¿Qué es un contenedor?" en algunos. Un contenedor es la unidad  de software estándar que encapsula el código y todas sus dependencias para que una aplicación se ejecute de manera eficiente y sólida independientemente del entorno en el que se implemente.
Las instrucciones para crear el contenedor son llamadas "imagen". Esta imagen se puede compartir, y podrá replicar con totalidad el contenedor original en cualquier sitio donde se despliegue. Dentro de estas instrucciones se encuentra el cód…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Lucía Guzmán</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[ReactJS] From Javascript to Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alserembani/reactjs-from-javascript-to-typescript-9jj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alserembani/reactjs-from-javascript-to-typescript-9jj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T06:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salam and holla, amigos!
This article can be used other than React as well, but I will focused on React ecosystem, so just skip the React part if you do other than React. 😉
So, today I am discussing how you can move from the Javascript world to the Typescript wonderland. But before that, there is one question you need to ask yourself first, "Why do I need to use Typescript in the first place 🤔?"
Honestly, Typescript might introduce a little bit more learning curve, and maybe a little bit more on syntax, with a trade of shorter and verbose syntax. Of course, there are more to just shorter and verbose.
So, the good of Typescript:
Moving from type loosed to typed variables and functions. Imagine the reason you didn't get your desired output, just because of "1+1=11". Ridiculous, right?
Verb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atif Aiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Email From Cron Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cuu508/how-to-send-email-from-cron-jobs-48ho</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cuu508/how-to-send-email-from-cron-jobs-48ho"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T06:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you are writing a shell script for a systems housekeeping task. Perhaps the script is uploading backups to a remote server, or it is cleaning up old data, or it is making a measurement and submitting it to a somebody else’s HTTP API. What is the least cumbersome way for the script to contact you in case of problems? Let’s say you want to be contacted via email – how to make it work?
If you run the script from cron, you can look into using cron’s MAILTO= option. You put a MAILTO=you@example.org line in your crontab, and, when a job fails, cron will send a notification to the specified address using system’s MTA. OK, then, what MTA to use?
sSMTP is a send-only MTA which hands off messages to an external SMTP server that you configure in /etc/ssmtp/ssmtp.conf. For example, you can c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pēteris Caune</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prevent Unwanted File Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-prevent-unwanted-file-recovery-48lp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-prevent-unwanted-file-recovery-48lp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T05:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this article to find out how files are removed and why they can be recovered, how to recover deleted files – or remove them permanently.
While files are just deleted from the hard disk in a conventional way, they don’t actually disappear – the information about these files remains on the hard disk even after you empty the Recycle Bin. It is this peculiarity that lets these files to be recovered – by you, or by other people… If you are not cautious enough, the removed confidential files can be recovered by other people, and used for purposes you may not like.
Windows tracks file location on the hard disk with a sort of labels. Every file and folder have this label that helps the operating system determine the beginning and the end of file.
When you delete a file, Windows removes the la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infer in TypeScript, the Great and Powerful]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/artemmalko/infer-in-typescript-the-great-and-powerful-5cch</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/artemmalko/infer-in-typescript-the-great-and-powerful-5cch"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T04:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk about the infer keyword in TypeScript. I believe, there're a lot of developers, who've been confused about infer. When should I use it? How it works? What is the purpose?

Let's start with something easier. The next cases will help us to understand the concept of infer. Ok, look at the piece of code:
let a = 10;

TypeScript infers a type quite smoothly — it's a number. This fact allows developers to not write such types everywhere. TypeScript takes care of it. By the way, where will be another type in case of const usage. Try it by yourself. I'm waiting for your explanation in the comments. This is a small interactive with a reader)
Ok, we've just found out, TypeScript is pretty smart. If a value corresponds to a specific condition, TS can make a decision about its type. Somethi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Malko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I want to use Linux but I can't...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/archerallstars/i-want-to-use-linux-but-i-cant-4ck7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/archerallstars/i-want-to-use-linux-but-i-cant-4ck7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T03:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bet that everyone here has heard about Linux. However, only a few can use it because their hardware doesn't work with Linux.
In my case, I want to use Ubuntu 21.10 on my laptop, Acer Swift 5 - SF514-52T, but I can't because there's no sound coming out of the HDMI port. I have filed this issue here.
I also can't connect my Bluetooth headset, Sony WH-CH710N, at all. The headset paired successfully but it just won't connect. I believe that this could be solved using the method provided here but I didn't have a chance to try it yet.
In fact, I had tried to run Linux on this laptop since Ubuntu 19.04 came out but fail because the integrated mic didn't work at all. Fortunately, this issue is fixed on Ubuntu 21.10.
Nevertheless, the sound system on Linux is a mess...
Linux will not succeed in the desktop market unless it works on most laptops considering that laptops already sell nearly 3 times more than PCs.
Hey, Linux, see you again in Ubuntu 22.04 LTS, KDE neon, or SteamOS 3.0!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Archer Allstars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Docker container for kiterunner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/building-a-docker-container-for-kiterunner-56ca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/building-a-docker-container-for-kiterunner-56ca"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last few weeks, I've finally wrangled my head around Docker a bit. 
As a demo, I've built a docker container for kiterunner.
Kiterunner is an API-fuzzing tool, very useful for bug bounty hunters and pen-testers. Shoutouts to @insiderphd for introducing me to the tool. I should have watched that video sooner!
Like any good tool, it requires some installation stuff beforehand.
I realized this is a good opportunity to begin integrating Docker into my workflow in a potentially useful way.
To quickly get Docker installed on debian or ubuntu:
# Install Docker
sudo apt-get install \
    ca-certificates \
    curl \
    gnupg \
    lsb-release
curl -fsSL https://download.docker.com/linux/debian/gpg | sudo gpg --dearmor -o /usr/share/keyrings/docker-archive-keyring.gpg
echo \
  "deb [arch=$(…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>darkmage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Atomic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/reimagine-atomic-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T22:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not the biggest fan of Atomic CSS myself. I don’t like all the classes. I like to express my styles in CSS because I find CSS… good. But I appreciate that a lot of people seem to like it, …
The post Reimagine Atomic CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Font Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/coding-font-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tournament bracket UI where you pick your favorite between two coding fonts and your choices are whittled down all the way to a final winner. A clever way to suss out your own taste and arrive at a choice.…
The post Coding Font Game appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357192</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/parallax-powered-by-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good friend Kent C. Dodds has recently dropped his new website which had a lot of work go into it. I was fortunate enough that Kent reached out a while back and asked if I could come up with some …
The post Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting with a wildcard subdomain enables your users to visit your site on any subdomain of your domain (*.example.com), and as you can imagine, we can use this to create unique user experiences which we’ll be exploring in this article through a Next.js lens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry-Picking Commits in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356700</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cherry-picking-commits-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 5 of this series, we looked at rebasing and merging. Although there are a couple of differences between git merge and git rebase, both commands have the same goal: they integrate changes from one branch into another.
The post Cherry-Picking Commits in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gap (Design Engineering)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357023</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-gap-design-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egor Kloos describes a situation where a (purely visual) designer asks for some changes to a component. There is a misunderstanding where the (code monkey) developer implements the change exactly as requested—but really what was required was both a bug …
The post The Gap (Design Engineering) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clever Sticky Footer Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357053</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-clever-sticky-footer-technique/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T00:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upon hearing “sticky footer” these days, I would think most people imagine a position: sticky situation where a footer element appears fixed on the screen while in the scrolling context of some parent element.
That’s not quite what I’m talking …
The post A Clever Sticky Footer Technique appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting in early January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>