<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-08T00:52:07.569Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-08T00:52:07.569Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrolling to an Element Only After It Appears using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferfox1981/scrolling-to-an-element-only-after-it-appears-using-angular-1g6m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferfox1981/scrolling-to-an-element-only-after-it-appears-using-angular-1g6m"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T00:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an evolution of my previous article. Let's suppose you have the following requirement:
In a long page, wait for a specific HTML Element to appear, and only after its generation scroll to it.
It looks simple right? But imagine that this Element exibition could take some time, for instance, it could be a grid with some information provided from a web service, or some data from a slow SQL query. Nevertheless, there's no reason to scroll before the data is already shown. So how can we do it? My goals are:
Create a button that will generate a grid at the bottom of a long page;
After the button is clicked, some mechanism is needed to simulate random time;
Scroll to the grid only after it was added to the page.
comment: The table to be scrolled is not added to the page by default. This is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Raposo da Camara Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a JavaScript Object? Key Value Pairs and Dot Notation Explained]]></title>
        <id>60e521aa134ad707be00e41d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T22:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objects are one of the most valuable things you can learn in Javascript. You can use them to take your programs to the next level.  An object is a collection of data – or key value pairs – which consist of variables and functions that you can access using dot notation. Now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi I'm Waylon


I am currently a Masters's candidate studying computer science at Colorado State University. After I completed my bachelor's degree in Mathematics and Philosophy, I was employed as a cybersecurity intern by the academic computing and networking services at CSU. I quickly developed a deep passion for cybersecurity and computer science and decide to go back to school to learn more.
While studying for my master's, I have been employed as a Junior Systems Administrator for the Computer Science department, managing over 600 Unix machines. This summer I am also working for Hedera Hashgraph as a developer advocate intern providing educational content on how to leverage the Hashgraph distributed network.
I love python, Linux, rust, and cryptography. If you share any of these interests, don't hesitate to reach out. I look forward to sharing my technical experiences with all of you hear and learn from the community. Thanks for reading :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Jepsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi I'm Waylon


I am currently a Masters's candidate studying computer science at Colorado State University. After I completed my bachelor's degree in Mathematics and Philosophy, I was employed as a cybersecurity intern by the academic computing and networking services at CSU. I quickly developed a deep passion for cybersecurity and computer science and decide to go back to school to learn more.
While studying for my master's, I have been employed as a Junior Systems Administrator for the Computer Science department, managing over 600 Unix machines. This summer I am also working for Hedera Hashgraph as a developer advocate intern providing educational content on how to leverage the Hashgraph distributed network.
I love python, Linux, rust, and cryptography. If you share any of these interests, don't hesitate to reach out. I look forward to sharing my technical experiences with all of you hear and learn from the community. Thanks for reading :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Jepsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install multiple node versions on the same machine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-install-multiple-node-versions-on-the-same-machine-ofc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-install-multiple-node-versions-on-the-same-machine-ofc"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our headless CMS, Strapi requires node version <= 14.x.x and we had node version 15 installed in our development machine. So that brought a question to my mind, is there a way like python venv for node to install different versions in the same machine. After doing a quick investigation, I found nvm node version manager that lets you have different versions of node on the same machine and switching between them.
curl -o- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nvm-sh/nvm/v0.38.0/install.sh | bash


or
wget -qO- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nvm-sh/nvm/v0.38.0/install.sh | bash


To verify installation run nvm --version
To list available versions, you can run
nvm ls-remote

To install specific version you can use nvm install VERSION for example
nvm install 12.18.4

You can use nvm use to switch to a specific version. For example
nvm use 12.18.4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cubite Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Project Fonos with Cloud-Init]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/psanders/deploying-project-fonos-with-cloud-init-4a6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/psanders/deploying-project-fonos-with-cloud-init-4a6f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Fonoster, Inc, we want to help companies and individuals that wish to adopt Project Fonos(PF) as their Programmable Telecommunications solution. To help archive this goal, our team uses Cloud-Init for cloud instance initialization.
You can deploy PF to all major public cloud providers, private cloud infrastructure, and bare-metal installations with Cloud-Init.
In this tutorial, we will also use Multipass. 
Multipass is a Canonical project that offers a lightweight VM manager for Linux, Windows, and macOS. With Multipass, you can deploy Project Fonos on Ubuntu in a local environment in a single command. This deployment method is by far the fastest way to get started with PF.
Before you start this tutorial, you will need the following:
Multipass
NodeJS 14+ (Use nvm if possible)
Fonos comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Building with Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343495</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-look-at-building-with-astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astro is a brand new framework for building websites. To me, the big thing is that it allows you to build a site like you’re using a JavaScript framework (and you are), but the output is a zero-JavaScript static site. …
The post A Look at Building with Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need help with your npm audit?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naugtur/do-you-need-help-with-your-npm-audit-3olf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naugtur/do-you-need-help-with-your-npm-audit-3olf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok, I'm gonna try and surf the wave of publicity resulting from Dan Abramov's recent post and its discussions. 
Let me address the elephant in the room too. Or talk about how I'm working to address it.
I've encountered the npm audit fatigue just days after the audit feature was released. It was on a Node.js project. (ok, 20+ of them at once) 
It resulted with the first version of npm-audit-resolver
If you want to know how npm-audit-resolver came to life, I've told the story in this recording:
OpenJS World 2021 pkg vuln talk
apologies for the quality of my webcam
The video introduces Package Vulnerability Management & Reporting Collaboration Space.

Actually, I recommend you stop reading and watch a bit of it now. 
What I want to talk about here is the ideas for the future of npm-audit-reso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>naugtur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross site scripting(XSS) in 10 mins]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/avishkardalvi/cross-site-scripting-xss-in-10-mins-455d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/avishkardalvi/cross-site-scripting-xss-in-10-mins-455d"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if we have control over the JavaScript of another website? Let your imagination run wild on this one! What could be the possibilities in this case?
We know that JavaScript has access to the HTML documents via the DOM API's which are provided by the browser itself. This means we can manipulate the DOM and make it look different, like changing the styling or the HTML structure of the page or we can read some cookies using document.cookie and send it over to your website via Ajax request or form submission or some other way.
But I think you get the idea that I am trying to convey here, having access to JavaScript on another website in a different user's context can be very problematic.
Now the question is can we really inject some JavaScript into another web page? Well, the answer is yes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AvishkarDalvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Next-Generation ORM: Prisma]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/myfatemi04/use-prisma-s-powerful-javascript-client-generator-to-write-a-blog-app-18gj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/myfatemi04/use-prisma-s-powerful-javascript-client-generator-to-write-a-blog-app-18gj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T19:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Prisma?


Prisma is one of the best database libraries I've ever used. In a nutshell, you write a schema, and Prisma can apply the changes to your database, and generate a Typescript client library custom-tailored to your databases.
For this example, I'll use a simple blog app. It has a User table, and an Article table. Users can have many Articles, and each Article only has one author.
To install Prisma, run yarn add prisma -D.
In a folder called prisma at the root of your project, you can create a file called schema.prisma. This is where the descriptions (or "schemas") of your tables will be stored.
Prisma uses this file to apply changes to the database, and generate a custom client for us.

You can ignore the migrations folder for now.
To specify where your database will be, you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Fatemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ananya26vishnoi/what-is-devops-448i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ananya26vishnoi/what-is-devops-448i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T18:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a set of platform as a service (PaaS) products that use OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers.Containers are isolated from one another and bundle their own software, libraries and configuration files; they can communicate with each other through well-defined channels.Because all of the containers share the services of a single operating system kernel, they use fewer resources than virtual machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ananya Vishnoi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[JavaScript] Super dangerous, underrated vulnerability impacting JavaScript apps!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/javascript-super-dangerous-underrated-vulnerability-impacting-javascript-apps-4dgn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/javascript-super-dangerous-underrated-vulnerability-impacting-javascript-apps-4dgn"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, security researchers at Snyk disclosed details of a severe vulnerability in Lodash, a popular JavaScript library, which allowed hackers to attack multiple web applications.
The security hole was a prototype pollution bug – a type of vulnerability that allows attackers to exploit the rules of the JavaScript programming language and compromise applications in various ways.
JavaScript is prototype-based: when new objects are created, they carry over the properties and methods of the prototype “object”, which contains basic functionalities such as toString, constructor and hasOwnProperty.
Object-based inheritance gives JavaScript the flexibility and efficiency that web programmers have come to love – but it also makes it vulnerable to tampering.
Malicious actors can make application-w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuma-Tsushima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Machine Learning – Tips and Resources to Learn ML the Practical Way]]></title>
        <id>60ccd1794dc1a607ed7b4feb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-machine-learning-practical-tips-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people want to learn machine learning these days. But the daunting bottom-up curriculum that most ML teachers propose is enough discourage a lot of newcomers.  In this tutorial I flip the curriculum upside down and will outline what I think is the fastest and easiest way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Comprehension in Python Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60e25e17134ad707be00d947</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-comprehension-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List comprehension is an easy to read, compact, and elegant way of creating a list from any existing iterable object. Basically, it's a simpler way to create a new list from the values in a list you already have. It is generally a single line of code enclosed in square]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Node.js using Gitlab CI pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atdigitals/deploy-node-js-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2jod</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atdigitals/deploy-node-js-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2jod"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prerequisite



Repository in Gitlab with Node.js project
Production server for which you have SSH access
Configure a folder in the server for a production Node.js server using steps from this digitalocean guide




  
  
  Goal


Setup the Gitlab CI/CD pipeline to push the Node.js code to the server and deploy it whenever code is merged to master branch.
Using a deploy token ensures that we can pull the code without the need to enter the credentials manually or save the credentials in the deploy script.
Create a deploy token for the repository or for the associated group using the steps mentioned in the documentation

Clone the repository in the production server's folder using the steps from the documentation. Make sure to use the correct repository url.
We are going to use Gitlab CI/CD …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamilarasu S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Node.js using Gitlab CI pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atdigitals/deploy-node-js-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2jod</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atdigitals/deploy-node-js-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2jod"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prerequisite



Repository in Gitlab with Node.js project
Production server for which you have SSH access
Configure a folder in the server for a production Node.js server using steps from this digitalocean guide




  
  
  Goal


Setup the Gitlab CI/CD pipeline to push the Node.js code to the server and deploy it whenever code is merged to master branch.
Using a deploy token ensures that we can pull the code without the need to enter the credentials manually or save the credentials in the deploy script.
Create a deploy token for the repository or for the associated group using the steps mentioned in the documentation

Clone the repository in the production server's folder using the steps from the documentation. Make sure to use the correct repository url.
We are going to use Gitlab CI/CD …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamilarasu S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[learn about The OpenSource End-to-End DevOps tool - Devtron, Heroku for Kubernetes. Livestream on 8th July 3:00 PM UTC]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pghildiyal/learn-about-the-opensource-end-to-end-devops-tool-devtron-heroku-for-kubernetes-livestream-on-8th-july-3-00-pm-utc-2gk5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pghildiyal/learn-about-the-opensource-end-to-end-devops-tool-devtron-heroku-for-kubernetes-livestream-on-8th-july-3-00-pm-utc-2gk5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am Excited to share with everyone that I will be joining Saiyam Pathak, Director of Civocloud and a YouTuber, on a Livestream on 8th july to talk about our OpenSource End-to-End Devops tool, Devtron. 




Devtron is an application-first way of looking at Kubernetes, meaning deep integrations with existing open-source, commercial software and add capabilities on top of them to enable a clean self serve UI for developers and DevOps. 
If any of this interests you, you will definitely have a great time. Come hang out with us on the stream to have a chat with me.
This is our OpenSource DevOps tool link, if you'd like to explore more
 / 
        devtron
      
    

Devtron is an open source software delivery workflow for kubernetes written in go

Explore documentation »


Website
·
Blog
·
Join Discord
·
Twitter












📖 Menu
Why Devtron
Features
Getting Started
Documentation
Compatibility Notes
Community
Contribute
Vulnerability Reporting
License
It is designed as a self-serve platform for operationalizing and maintaining applications (AppOps) on kubernetes in a developer friendly way





 Zero code software delivery workflow 
  


Workflow which understands the domain of kubernetes, testing, CD, SecOps so that you dont have to write scripts
Reusable and composable components so that workflows are easy to contruct and reason through
 Multi cloud deployment 
 
 

Deploy to multiple kubernetes cluster
 Easy dev-sec-ops integration  


Multi level security policy at global, cluster, environment and application for efficient hierarchical policy management
Behavior driven security policy
Define policies and exception for kubernetes resources
Define policies for events for faster resolution
 Application debugging dashboard  


One place…
View on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prashant Ghildiyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and deploy React using Gitlab CI pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atdigitals/build-and-deploy-react-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2bhc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atdigitals/build-and-deploy-react-using-gitlab-ci-pipeline-2bhc"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prerequisite



Repository in Gitlab with react project
Production server for which you have SSH access
NGINX setup for your domain to a folder in the server. See this tutorial on how to do it
Setup the Gitlab CI/CD pipeline to create a react production build and deploy to our server whenever code is merged to master branch. The attached steps can also be used for other SPA like Angular, Vue.js.
We are going to use Gitlab CI/CD Variables to save a private SSH key which Gitlab will use to authenticate with the server.
We are going to use SSH keys to authenticate rather than username and password as it is more secure.
This can be configured at a repository level or at a group level.
Go to your project’s Settings > CI/CD 
Expand the Variables section.
You can also view the same at a group lev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamilarasu S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AIOps Helps in Application Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logiq/how-aiops-helps-in-application-monitoring-2h6i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logiq/how-aiops-helps-in-application-monitoring-2h6i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no one-size-fits-all approach regarding application monitoring, especially for companies using applications in various cloud environments. Companies are rapidly investing in microservices, mobile apps, data science programs, data ops, etc. Subsequently, they’re also integrating monitoring tools to improve domain-centric monitoring abilities.
AIOps tools help streamline the use of monitoring applications. It allows companies that need high application services to efficiently manage the complexities of IT workflows and monitoring tools. AIOps extends machine learning and automation abilities to IT operations. These robust technologies aim to detect vulnerabilities and issues to resolve them, determine operational trends, and simplify the remediation of the problems that affect their …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajit Chelat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Interview Prep Cheatsheet – Ace Your Coding Interviews with These Concepts]]></title>
        <id>60c38e76d3126007592d66cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-interview-prep-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've carefully gone through over 50 resources, I've been through 10 JavaScript interviews, and I've landed a job at a unicorn startup. And throughout this entire process, I started to see a pattern in the most frequently asked JS interview questions.  In this article, I have tried to list the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will we lose if we use regular link instead of React routing in SPA]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arahman1783/what-will-we-lose-if-we-use-regular-link-instead-of-react-routing-in-spa-2e4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arahman1783/what-will-we-lose-if-we-use-regular-link-instead-of-react-routing-in-spa-2e4h"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According some requirements from client to replace routing with real links, as we work Single Page Application there are some features we will lose :
Routing in react is like show and hide some components without reload page so the only part that loaded is the new part only using (virtual Dom), so the transforming between components smooth and easy.
In single page application one of the main concepts is to share data with all components that will use it, so we load it one time and use it many times.
Every time we access any page the application will call again all services that need to call to manage this page although it is called before among of this connecting with Keycloak to get new token even the first not expired 
• https://reacttraining.com/blog/reach-react-router-future/
https://www.pluralsight.com/guides/understanding-links-in-reactjs
https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-the-href-and-routerLink
https://reactjs.org/docs/faq-internals.html
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/23975199/when-to-use-client-side-routing-or-server-side-routing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelrahman Elhussini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typing React Props in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/typescripttv/typing-react-props-in-typescript-5hal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/typescripttv/typing-react-props-in-typescript-5hal"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One advantage of using React with TypeScript is that you can easily type the props of your (function) components. You don't have to use React's PropTypes because TypeScript already has its own typing system.
In the following, I will show you how to define custom props for a component in connection with already existing props like children.
PostPreview.tsx
import React from 'react';

export interface Props {
  title: string;
}

const PostPreview = (props: Props) => {
  return (
    <div>
      <h1>{props.title}</h1>
      {props.children}
    </div>
  );
};

export default PostPreview;

As you can see, our PostPreview component has a title property. The component is supposed to render the title and other components (children) below the title. In technical terms this is called Containment.
B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Neugebauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web’s Worst Default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343388</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-webs-worst-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of great defaults when it comes to browsers and the web. Think about all the accessibility features that are baked into HTML so that you don’t have to do weird stuff, like this example from Manuel…
The post The Web’s Worst Default appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Into DevSecOps (Part 1) w/ John Willis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-1-w-john-willis-47ll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-1-w-john-willis-47ll"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Willis is a legendary DevOps speaker, mentor and author of The DevOps Handbook. He even helped coin the term DevSecOps.
But DevSecOps is one of those buzzwords that can mean a lot of things or nothing at all.
In this special 2-part series of Dev Interrupted, John takes us on a DevSecOps journey from the origin of the term all the way to how software developers at the team level can implement the practice.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights include:



What DevSecOps means at the team-level
First steps for implementing DevSecOps strategies at your organization
Why it’s critical to start thinking about security more holistically
The difference between Security, Compliance, Governance & Risk
What is coming next for software development security
Join the Dev Interrupted Discord Server


With over 1200 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Into DevSecOps (Part 1) w/ John Willis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-1-w-john-willis-47ll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-1-w-john-willis-47ll"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Willis is a legendary DevOps speaker, mentor and author of The DevOps Handbook. He even helped coin the term DevSecOps.
But DevSecOps is one of those buzzwords that can mean a lot of things or nothing at all.
In this special 2-part series of Dev Interrupted, John takes us on a DevSecOps journey from the origin of the term all the way to how software developers at the team level can implement the practice.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights include:



What DevSecOps means at the team-level
First steps for implementing DevSecOps strategies at your organization
Why it’s critical to start thinking about security more holistically
The difference between Security, Compliance, Governance & Risk
What is coming next for software development security
Join the Dev Interrupted Discord Server


With over 1200 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State manager of dream]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/betula/state-manager-of-dream-98i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/betula/state-manager-of-dream-98i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago during one of my interviews, a potential employer asked me to describe a perfect frontend framework in my wildest dreams. I gave quite a thorough answer explaining how it works, and realized that it actually was a description vaguely resembling the synthesis of React and Angular. My dream was born at that moment!
Currently, when it comes to all existing frontend frameworks, those widely popular or not, I prefer React since it has a beautiful integration with the typescript. Using JSX as part of a language is really convenient. It offers a lightweight version with perfect compatibility (4 kB Preact instead of 30), with the possibility to inject it on the Webpack level without changes to your codebase. And React is simply a view system without any special solution builder, appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slava Birch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Binary Search?]]></title>
        <id>60d5ec446e1a1407b6b0bcae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-binary-search/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T13:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binary search is a common algorithm used in programming languages and programs. It can be very useful for programmers to understand how it works. We just released a binary search course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. You will learn how to implement binary search in C and C++, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript: Getting Started]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codingknite/typescript-getting-started-39dm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codingknite/typescript-getting-started-39dm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T13:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript has taken the development world by storm. No wonder it has over 15 million weekly downloads on npm. But what is TypeScript, and what do you need to know about it?


In this article, I am going answer those questions. By the end you'll have a grasp of the following:
What TypeScript is
Main pillars of TypeScript
Main features of TypeScript
Why you should use TypeScript
TypeScript basics to get you started
First, let's address the elephant in the room.
TypeScript is a programming language built and maintained by Microsoft.

It is a superset of JavaScript that adds strong type checking and is compiled into plain JavaScript code.
Being a superset means that TypeScript has all the features of JavaScript as well as some additional features.
TypeScript comes with features such as better…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel P. Mugalu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning how to Build, Secure, and Deploy your Azure Static Web App in C#]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fboucheros/learning-how-to-build-secure-and-deploy-your-azure-static-web-app-in-c-k58</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fboucheros/learning-how-to-build-secure-and-deploy-your-azure-static-web-app-in-c-k58"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I participated in a series of videos about Azure Static Web Apps: Azure Tips and Tricks: Static Web Apps on Microsoft Channel 9. The series is perfect to get started and cover multiple different scenarios in different Javascript frameworks and C#. In this post, I wanted to regroup the four videos related to .Net Blazor. I also added the GitHub links part of the references at to end.
How to create a web app in C# with Blazor & Azure Static Web Apps


In this video, we start from scratch. We will build and deploy a brand new static website with .Net Blazor.

How to add a C# API to your Blazor web app


Now that you built your web app with C# and Blazor, what about adding a serverless C# API to it? Have a look!

How to secure your C# API with Azure Static Web Apps


Prevent unwanted users to access your C# API by configuring authentication and authorization in your Blazor Azure Static Web Apps.

I hope those videos will help you to get started. If you have questions and/or comments don't hesitate to reach out (comments, DM, GitHub issues), it's always a pleasure.
How CI/CD and preview branches work with Azure Static Web Apps


In this video, I wanted to show one of the great features of Azure Static Web App Learn: the creation of pre-production environments. Using the CI/CD workflow, you can preview your pull requests changes before it's in production leveraging the automatic creation of pre-production environments!

Watch the full series: https://aka.ms/StaticWebAppsTipsC9

GitHub Sample: https://github.com/FBoucher/AzureStaticWebApp-CSharp-SimpleDemo

Interactive tutorials on Microsoft Learn: https://aka.ms/Learn/StaticWebApps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Boucher ☁</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the most value out of your Angular Component Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitter at @tim_deschryver | Subscribe to the Newsletter | Originally published on timdeschryver.dev.
I frequently hear that it's hard to know what to test of an Angular component.
In this blog post, I want to share how I think that we can get the most value out of a test.
To accomplish this, I want to closely mimic a user that uses my application.
To help me writing these tests, I'm using the Angular Testing Library. When you're using the Angular Testing Library, you only need the render method and the screen object to test the basics of your component. For interactions with the component, I'm also using userEvent from @testing-library/user-event.
Let's take a look at the first test for a simple component called EntitiesComponent.
import { render, screen } from '@testing-libr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Deschryver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the most value out of your Angular Component Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitter at @tim_deschryver | Subscribe to the Newsletter | Originally published on timdeschryver.dev.
I frequently hear that it's hard to know what to test of an Angular component.
In this blog post, I want to share how I think that we can get the most value out of a test.
To accomplish this, I want to closely mimic a user that uses my application.
To help me writing these tests, I'm using the Angular Testing Library. When you're using the Angular Testing Library, you only need the render method and the screen object to test the basics of your component. For interactions with the component, I'm also using userEvent from @testing-library/user-event.
Let's take a look at the first test for a simple component called EntitiesComponent.
import { render, screen } from '@testing-libr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Deschryver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Crow Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thomasstep/introducing-crow-authentication-3f3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thomasstep/introducing-crow-authentication-3f3j"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last month, I've been underground working on a project that I call Crow Authentication or, lovingly, Crow. It spawned when I set about creating a new application for myself that needed basic authentication. I had already implemented authentication in a previous project of mine so I had the nuts and bolts. As I was about to start copying and pasting code from one project into another a much better idea entered my head. I was going to create a service for myself that handled authentication for all of my projects. That naturally spiraled into creating a service and offering it to anyone. I wanted Crow to be Software as a Service, and this was my first venture into writing an application that offered itself up as a service like this.
I went down quite a few rabbit holes reading and le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Step</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Frontend of BitClout without running node]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itsaditya/run-frontend-of-bitclout-without-running-node-1n4f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itsaditya/run-frontend-of-bitclout-without-running-node-1n4f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might want to make some changes to the frontend of BitClout but running a node is beyond your league ? Well, you are on the right place of the Internet then!
You can easily run the frontend of BitClout locally on your PC without running node by using some browser hacks :)
docs of BitClout, you will have to run your own node (aka backend) and identity service in order to run the frontend. 
Before you get started make sure you are using the latest version of NodeJS and NPM on your PC. Another prerequisite is to have git installed. The frontend of BitClout is made in AngularJS so you must have atleast some basic knowledge of what single page application is.
Fork and Clone the frontend repository.
Fork the repository of the frontend from here. When done open your terminal and run git clone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Chaudhary👨‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pssingh21/docker-97j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pssingh21/docker-97j"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T09:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker?


Docker is a tool that allows developers to package applications and all their dependencies in a container (sandbox) and deploy and run the application on host operating system (Linux). 
A container is a discrete process that has been isolated from all other processes on the host machine. This is made possible by Kernel Namespaces and Cgroups. This decoupling allows applications to run consistently anywhere isolated from the rest of the applications. Containers run images, which contain everything required to run: application code, runtime environment, dependencies, scripts, etc. Containers run layers of stacked images (eg. a base linux image (mostly alpine due to its compact size), node image and application image on top). 
Note that docker containers do not run in their …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pssingh21</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is .map() and how does it work]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-is-map-and-how-does-it-work-4o05</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-is-map-and-how-does-it-work-4o05"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T09:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wandered what is .map() function in Javascript? Then this tutorial is for you! Today we will look at how .map() works, and what does it do.
.map()


In Javascript, map function is a method used on arrays, it cycles through every element and executes a callback on each iteration. After finishing iterating through elements, it returns a newly constructed array, that has been constructed according to values returned by callback functions, ran in each iteration.
map() method takes in 2 parameters
Callback Function
ThisArg (Value to use as this, in callback function)




array.map(callback, thisArg);

As an argument, callback has 3 parameters
Current Element
Current Index
Current Array



array.map((element, index, array) => {});

In today's example, we aren't going to be using Current Array and Index, we'll stay on Current Element.
Let's now look at how it works. Throughout each iteration, our callback function is execute, and returned by this very same function is an element which is pushed into an array that is returned to us at the end. Don't worry, you don't need to store array in anywhere through iterations, it is automatically stored in function memory. Let's now look at examples of the .map()
EXAMPLE
const numberArray = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];

const newArray = numberArray.map((x) => x * 2)
//newArray is [2, 4, 6, 8, 10];

In the script above, as you can see, it make an array with all of the elements multiplied by 2, and then returns it to us. This is basically the whole functionality for .map().
Thanks for reading this post! If you found it helpful, then feel free to leave a reaction and or follow me, but if you didn't, then tell me what you didn't like and I will try to fix it in future.
What are labels and how do they work
Arsenii Gorushkin ・ Jul 7 ・ 2 min read
#javascript
        #node
        #labels]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arsenii Gorushkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript hints in your code samples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/perfect7m/typescript-hints-in-your-code-samples-1g0i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/perfect7m/typescript-hints-in-your-code-samples-1g0i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T08:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding code samples to your website is an excellent idea. It shows how the code should look like. It's hard to image npm package docs without code samples.
Existing solutions are good when we want to show JavaScript code samples. But what, when we want to show TypeScript code, types alongside with code?
… Shiki Twoslash is the library you are looking for.
Shiki is a syntax highlighter. Is based on text mate grammar. The same technology that powers VS Code syntax highlighting.

Twoslash is a Shiki addon. It’s adding TypeScript compiler hints. Same as we can see in VS Code. You can check which
You can display typescript hints in two types.
Static:
const msg = "Hi world" as const;
//    ^?


Dynamic:
ts twoslash
// Removes 'readonly' attributes from a type's properties
type CreateMutable<Type> = {
  -readonly [Property in keyof Type]: Type[Property];
};
type LockedAccount = {
  readonly id: string;
  readonly name: string;
};
type UnlockedAccount = CreateMutable<LockedAccount>;


Note: You need to attach JavaScript code to have interactive code hints.
Shiki Twoslash supports more functionalities:
mixing static with dynamic mode
showing typescript errors
vs code themes
Also, we come with plugins for the most popular tools: Eleventy, Docusaurus, Gatsby, and more.
You can read more about all options on shiki twoslash website.
To get in touch with me you can find me on Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Perfect7M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing with Azure Functions: Mission 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ivan_pesenti/playing-with-azure-functions-mission-2-bjf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ivan_pesenti/playing-with-azure-functions-mission-2-bjf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T08:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys! Welcome back to my Azure Function series. I hope u are ready to play, develop and (more important) learn with me. I'm really excited to be back on track 😎.

🔴IMPORTANT❗🔴: this is the second post of a series so, if u missed the previous one, I strongly suggest u to check it out at this link.

As always if u get in trouble in following the tutorial u can find all the code in "start" folder of my GitHub repo that u can find here.
If u have completed the MISSION 1 (congrats again 🍻) u now have the following weapons in your bag:
A working Azure Function timer-triggered written with C# and .NET Core 3.1
A solution with three projects:


Azure function proj called "azure-function"
Entities class library proj called "azure-function-entities"
Managers class library proj called "azure-f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Pesenti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigitalOcean deploy conference sessions - June 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of my favorite sessions from the recently concluded deploy conference by DigitalOcean:








  
  
  Accelerating Modern App Development Using Managed MongoDB and DigitalOcean










  
  
  Is Kubernetes Right for Me? Choosing the Best Deployment Platform for Your Business










  
  
  Be the Boss of Your Base: Tips to Master MongoDB Like a Pro










  
  
  Finding the Right DigitalOcean Virtual Machine Type for Your Business










  
  
  Grow Your Business with Scalable Apps Using DigitalOcean App Platform










  
  
  Building Production-Ready Apps With App Platform, DigitalOcean's Reimagined PaaS










  
  
  Networking Best Practices To Power Your Kubernetes Deployment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raman Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigitalOcean deploy conference sessions - June 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of my favorite sessions from the recently concluded deploy conference by DigitalOcean:








  
  
  Accelerating Modern App Development Using Managed MongoDB and DigitalOcean










  
  
  Is Kubernetes Right for Me? Choosing the Best Deployment Platform for Your Business










  
  
  Be the Boss of Your Base: Tips to Master MongoDB Like a Pro










  
  
  Finding the Right DigitalOcean Virtual Machine Type for Your Business










  
  
  Grow Your Business with Scalable Apps Using DigitalOcean App Platform










  
  
  Building Production-Ready Apps With App Platform, DigitalOcean's Reimagined PaaS










  
  
  Networking Best Practices To Power Your Kubernetes Deployment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raman Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Download 12,000+ Exclusive Design Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uihut/download-12-000-exclusive-design-resources-25ej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uihut/download-12-000-exclusive-design-resources-25ej"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone!
www.uihut.com Platform with 12000+ Design Resources in this community. UI HUT is a design platform for UX/UI designers, developers, and project managers. Instead of spending your time on a variety of tasks during the design process, UI HUT allows you to focus on what you love most. From last year our team working so hard to achieve our goal. That’s really excited for us that we getting users so rapidly and our user's feedbacks inspiring us to expand our services and features.
Resources:
1000+ web Templates UI
2500+ Illustration
7000+ Icons
500+ Mobile Screen UI
100+ Web App UI
We are uploading Those more design templates Everyday
www.uihut.com
Thanks a lot, everyone for your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>UI HUT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[03-Building first Node.js & Express.js application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wrijugh/03-building-first-node-js-express-js-application-33na</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wrijugh/03-building-first-node-js-express-js-application-33na"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most used Node.js implementations is to build the backend API using Express.js. Express.js is a lightweight library for building REST API which can be consumed by any application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wriju's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are labels and how do they work]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-are-labels-and-how-do-they-work-45o0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-are-labels-and-how-do-they-work-45o0"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T06:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wandered what labels are in javascript? Or have you never even heard of them? In any of these cases I will introduce you to them today. In this post we will break down what are labels, and what they do.
Labels mean pretty much what they spell. Labels are used to identify a certain loop, and give developer the ability to conitnue or break the loop at will, which would either continue or stop the execution of the loop as you might have realized from the keywords.
Label syntax is fairly simple, only things you need to know are 2 keywords, and syntax
This, down here is an example of syntax
label:
  function

Now I will show you how to use continue and break in labels
let i = 0;

label: 
for (i = 0; i < 1000000000; i ++) {
  if (i === 6) {
    break label;
  }
  console.log(i)
}

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arsenii Gorushkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte + Typescript + Tailwind]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rahulbarwal/svelte-typescript-tailwind-2njo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rahulbarwal/svelte-typescript-tailwind-2njo"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T05:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming from the Angular world back to Javascript can sometimes feel lackluster. The power of types is too much to resist. Lately, I've been playing around with React and Svelte. To be fair, I am liking Svelte a lot for a small single-page website. Combining these two was a must for me, So here is a post penning down the steps you will need to make your Svelte project run on TypeScript.
Clone the svelte repo to your directory with:
npx degit sveltejs/template your-project

Now change the current directory to your-project and run this command to convert your current JavaScript project to TypeScript, and install packages
cd your-project
node .\scripts\setupTypeScript.js
npm i

Install required packages by running the command:
npm i tailwindcss@npm:@tailwindcss/postcss7-compat postcss@^7 autoprefixer@^9

To add tailwind.config.js to your project:
npx tailwindcss init  tailwind.config.js

Head over to tailwind.config.js file and add this future property at bottom
future: {
    purgeLayersByDefault: true,
    removeDeprecatedGapUtilities: true,
},

To purge unnecessary classes in production modify purge property to:
purge: {
    content: ["./src/**/*.svelte"],
    enabled: isProduction, // disable purge in dev
},

You won't want purging to be enabled in dev mode, to identify we can use the ROLLUP_WATCH flag.
const isProduction = !process.env.ROLLUP_WATCH;

To enable tailwindss during dev and production builds update preprocess property to
preprocess: sveltePreprocess({
        sourceMap: !production,
        postcss: {
          plugins: [require("tailwindcss"), require("autoprefixer")],
    },
}),

You can add this to your App.svelte or optionally this can also be done by creating a new svelte component and then importing it in App.svelte
<style global lang="postcss">
  @tailwind base;
  @tailwind components;
  @tailwind utilities;
</style>

Now you're ready to rock🤘, run your Svelte project with:
npm run dev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Barwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Serverless Redis as Database for Netlify Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/using-serverless-redis-as-database-for-netlify-functions-2mii</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/using-serverless-redis-as-database-for-netlify-functions-2mii"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T05:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll see how we can use Redis as a database for caching purposes to load the data faster in any type of application.
So let's get started.
Redis is an in-memory data store used as a database for storing data
Redis is used for caching purpose. So If your API data is not frequently changing then we can cache the previous API result data and on the next requests re-send the cached data from Redis
As you know some websites which show live score of matches like cricket match updates the data on the website after every fixed second. So If the user clicks on the refresh button or refreshes the page, the cached data is returned to avoid the unnecessary heavy load on the server.


And after specific seconds of time, the fresh score of data gets updated which is done using Redis d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Record Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hint/active-record-encryption-22j3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hint/active-record-encryption-22j3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T04:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rails 7 will be introducing a very cool new feature for ActiveRecord - application-level encryption, summoned by the mighty encrypts declaration in a model. This new feature provides a layer of encryption that sits between our application code and the database. In essence, when our data using Active Record Encryption has been loaded into an AR object, it will be unencrypted, and when it is sitting in the database it will be encrypted.
In this post, we will take a high-level look at how to use this functionality, discuss some cool things it can do, and acknowledge some of its limitations.
Before we dive in, I would be remiss if I didn't point to the excellent documentation in the Rails guide.
For the duration of the post, I will refer to the feature as encrypts for brevity (and also because…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Dinsmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is .reduce(), and how does it work]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-is-reduce-and-how-does-it-work-20ga</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agorushkin/what-is-reduce-and-how-does-it-work-20ga"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T04:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wandered what is .reduce() function in Javascript? Then this tutorial is for you! Today we will look at how .reduce() works, and what does it do.
.reduce()


In Javascript, reduce() method is used on arrays, it cycles through every element of an array, and for each it executes a function that you have provided in the method.
.reduce() has 2 parameters, which are:
1. Callback Function
2. Initial Accumulator Value




array.reduce(callbackFunction, initialValue)

Callback method has 4 parameters, which are:
1. Accumulator
2. Current Element
3. Index of Current Element
4. Array Method is Used on




array.reduce(() => {accunulator, currentElement, index, array} => {})

In todays example, we will not be using last 2 parameters, we will keep it to just Accumulator (we'll call it a) and Current Element (we'll call it b).
Throughout each iteration, returned value from callback function is added to the accumulator, which is stored until the end of the iteration and then returned as a single value.
EXAMPLE
const array = [1, 2, 3, 4];

console.log(array.reduce((a, b) => a + b))
// 1 + 2 + 3 + 4
//Logs out "10"

console.log(array.reduce((a, b) => a + b, 10))
// 10 + 1 + 2 + 3 + 4
//Logs out "20"

As you can see above, we reduced an array by adding all of the values up into one, single number. If initial values is not provided, then array will take first element's value, and start iteration from the index of 1. If array is empty, then it will throw a TypeError stating Reduce of empty array with no initial value. Although if array only has only one element, then it will return an element, without calling the callback function.
Thanks for reading this post, if you found it helpful then feel free to leave a reaction and or follow for more posts like this, or tutorials on how to make different small things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arsenii Gorushkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to increase the speed of software development]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codecrafttechnologies/how-to-increase-the-speed-of-software-development-3j6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codecrafttechnologies/how-to-increase-the-speed-of-software-development-3j6"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T03:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development is a complex process. And it’s constantly reimagined or repurposed with new features. Unlike the production industry or manufacturing industry, increasing the number of people/resources won’t increase the speed of software development proportionately. The reason being, no other engineering discipline uses Intellectual capital as much as software development. Software development is perhaps the most knowledge-intensive engineering branch. So how does one increase or optimize the speed of an engineering discipline which is more abstract than concrete?
Software development as an activity comprises people, processes, and technology. To increase the speed of development, the math is simple. Assuming everything else is normal, reduce the variables which drag the project down…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Codecraft Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Object Deep Clone vs Shallow Clone. Clone JavaScript Object the right way.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T02:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch This Video To Completely Understand About What is Deep Cloning and Shallow Cloning of Object in JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishan Sheth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Object Deep Clone vs Shallow Clone. Clone JavaScript Object the right way.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T02:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch This Video To Completely Understand About What is Deep Cloning and Shallow Cloning of Object in JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishan Sheth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hello! need help. set up in Mac for React (nvm, node.js, npm) not working. Can anyone please help?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alejsala/hello-need-help-set-up-in-mac-for-react-nvm-node-js-npm-not-working-can-anyone-please-help-3ijb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alejsala/hello-need-help-set-up-in-mac-for-react-nvm-node-js-npm-not-working-can-anyone-please-help-3ijb"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T00:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! Need HELP. i'm trying to set up to use React. i can't get environment to work in Mac.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlejSala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing poor habits with forms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jmau111/losing-poor-habits-with-forms-4c6i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jmau111/losing-poor-habits-with-forms-4c6i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T22:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer is magic but not all web forms.
It's shocking because sometimes, you just cannot use them whether you have impairments or not.
for attributes


Labels allow screen readers to voice the input prompt to the user. Unfortunately, many websites use placeholders only.
It's a terrible practice as screen readers will try to guess things, for example, by taking texts that precede or follow, which might have nothing to do with the inputs.
Besides, placeholders disappear when the inputs are focused.
So don't do that:
<input placeholder="Enter your email" name="email" type="email">

Instead, do something like this:
<label for="email">Your Email address</label>
<input id="email" name="email" type="email" required>

If you have to hide labels, you can still use extra HTML and CSS:
<label for=…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julien Maury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency sandboxing in node.js with Jpex]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackmellis/dependency-sandboxing-in-node-js-with-jpex-3mbi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackmellis/dependency-sandboxing-in-node-js-with-jpex-3mbi"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T21:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React recap


Okay so I've written about jpex a few times, particularly in relation to react
Essentially it allows you to do something like this:
import { useResolve } from 'react-jpex';

const useMyDep = () => {
  const dep = useResolve<IDep>();
  return dep.someValue;
};

and this:
import { encase } from 'react-jpex';

const useMyDep = encase((dep: IDep) => () => {
  return dep.someValue;
})

depending on your preferred flavour.
Jpex uses the service locator pattern to resolve and inject dependencies, plus it's super-powered by Typescript inference for a super slick experience. But the really really cool thing about it is you can test your react components with the provider component to stub your dependencies:
<Provider
  onMount={(jpex) => {
    jpex.constant<IDep>(mockValue);
    // ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automatically Upload an Android App Bundle to the Play Store]]></title>
        <id>60e16e1b134ad707be00d6bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automatically-upload-an-android-app-bundle-to-the-play-store/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T21:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to explain how to automatically upload an Android App Bundle (.aab file) to the Play Store's beta track. We'll use Android Studio and AWS as a cloud infrastructure provider.  Once we've uploaded the app bundle, we'll trigger a Slack notification.  This is a valuable use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Toggle]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343438</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/body-toggle/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I appreciate the clarity of this trick that Mikael Ainalem posted over on Reddit:
It’s a one-liner that toggles the class on the <body> so you can mock up different states and toggle between them on click.
<body onclick="this.classList.toggle("active");"
Could …
The post Body Toggle appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Live lab: Deploying Kubernetes Apps in an Air Gapped Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ogtrilliams/free-live-lab-deploying-kubernetes-apps-in-an-air-gapped-environment-4d9p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ogtrilliams/free-live-lab-deploying-kubernetes-apps-in-an-air-gapped-environment-4d9p"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curious about how to manage #airgapped applications in #K8s but don't know where to start your learning journey? @replicatedhq can help with that! Join our free #airgap lab and gain hands-on experience installing a #Kubernetes application in an air gapped environment. Register here:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>T. Nichole Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343560</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ive-got-one-question-about-jetpack-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And maybe an optional follow-up if you’re up for it.
Automattic, the makers of Jetpack and many other WordPress-y things, have sponsored my site (me = Chris Coyier; site = CSS-Tricks) for quite a while. I use Jetpack myself, …
The post I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test Driven Development With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kalashin1/test-driven-development-with-typescript-1b0p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kalashin1/test-driven-development-with-typescript-1b0p"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody ever liked writing test, when i left school i thought that i had escaped writing test. Enter software development and i realize i still can't run away from tests. Why do we even have to write tests? Tests are important in the software development cycle because it bears witness to these thing;
Your understanding of the problem you are trying to solve, writing tests will prove that you understand the problem and the software requirements.
That your solution is actually doing what you built it to do? How else can you prove that? We can run it in the browser to check the result of our code but that's only good for simple projects where you have a lot of time, and if you are mostly concerned with the look and design.
It is a  really good form of documentation.
When many people hear about…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kinanee Samson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minha instalação do Manjaro para programação]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abraaom/minha-instalacao-do-manjaro-para-programacao-1o4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abraaom/minha-instalacao-do-manjaro-para-programacao-1o4k"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O Manjaro é uma distro Linux baseada no Arch, mas que trás uma instalação muito mais facilitada do que seu irmão maior, a instalação foi feita no Manjaro Gnome, mas os comandos via terminal são todos iguais em qualquer uma das várias interfaces disponíveis para o Manjaro.
A escolha pelo Manjaro ao invés de uma distro mais popular se dá para mim principalmente pela presença do gerenciador de pacotes do Arch, o Pacman, e a possibilidade de acessar o enorme repositório do Arch, considerando o AUR e também a possibilidade de adicionar facilmente o suporte a Flatpack e Snap diretamente no gerenciador de pacotes Pamac, que possui uma GUI, basicamente se existe algo para Linux, então estará disponível para o Manjaro de forma facilitada por meio de algum dos repositórios citados, oficiais ou não. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraão Moreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing Tabular Data in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T18:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | May 2019
A fun dive into everything from custom Directives to advanced ViewChildren




  
  
  Introduction


This article targets beginning to intermediate-level Angular developers and covers a wide variety of topics that arise in production applications. While centered around the concept of editing tabular data, these techniques may be used in a variety of other Angular applications.
For anyone who has read at least one of my articles, you should understand that my background is applied mathematics and scientific computing. So, this article continues the trend of exploring the use of Angular in scientific and business (analytics) applications.
Working with time-series data is a fundamental concept in numerous business and engineering sectors. In this context, f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing Tabular Data in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T18:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | May 2019
A fun dive into everything from custom Directives to advanced ViewChildren




  
  
  Introduction


This article targets beginning to intermediate-level Angular developers and covers a wide variety of topics that arise in production applications. While centered around the concept of editing tabular data, these techniques may be used in a variety of other Angular applications.
For anyone who has read at least one of my articles, you should understand that my background is applied mathematics and scientific computing. So, this article continues the trend of exploring the use of Angular in scientific and business (analytics) applications.
Working with time-series data is a fundamental concept in numerous business and engineering sectors. In this context, f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IvyFinal CTF (Crypto 3) - Silly 400 - points]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wireless90/ivyfinal-ctf-crypto-3-silly-400-points-5ehj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wireless90/ivyfinal-ctf-crypto-3-silly-400-points-5ehj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T16:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can get the binary here .
192.168.40.199 8300
The server code is given to us as such.
from flask import Flask, request, Response
from flask_cors import CORS
from hashlib import md5
import time

app = Flask(__name__)
CORS(app)

def get_flag_length():
    time.sleep(0.05) # Throttling against brute-forcers
    flag = open('../flag.txt','r').read()
    return len(flag)

def get_flag_char(i):
    flag = open('../flag.txt','r').read()
    return flag[i].encode()

def checkflag(userflag):
    for i, c in enumerate(userflag):
        if get_flag_length() <= i:
            return False

        if c.encode() != get_flag_char(i):
            return False

    if get_flag_length() != len(userflag):
        return False

    return True

@app.route("/", methods=['GET'])
def index():
    userflag …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wireless90</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Authenticate Users and Implement CORS in Node.js Apps]]></title>
        <id>60b22e9611ffb70827ef9547</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-authenticate-users-and-implement-cors-in-nodejs-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to authenticate users and secure endpoints in Node.js. You'll also see how to implement Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) in Node. So let's get started.  Prerequisites You'll need the following to follow along with this tutorial:  A working understanding of JavaScript. A good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Effective Way to Protect Client-Side JavaScript Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jscrambler/the-most-effective-way-to-protect-client-side-javascript-applications-1hi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jscrambler/the-most-effective-way-to-protect-client-side-javascript-applications-1hi"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T15:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a programming language with many useful features—it is built around flexibility, giving you all the capability necessary to do what you want with it. JavaScript’s dynamic nature allowed it to become the de facto language for the browser and the most popular programming language in the world.
One of the most useful JS features is, for example, immediate parsing. This feature means that the browser executes the code right as it downloads content, naturally providing benefits. However, with this level of freedom also comes responsibility.
In this article, weʼd like to delve into the JavaScript security risks and how to protect JavaScript code. This time we will cover only front-end code that runs on the browser, but we have another tutorial on protecting Node.js apps.
Imagine al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jscrambler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a forgot password flow (with pseudo code)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/supertokens/implementing-a-forgot-password-flow-with-pseudo-code-fa4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/supertokens/implementing-a-forgot-password-flow-with-pseudo-code-fa4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T15:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table of contents:



  
  
  Security Issues to consider:



Brute Force Attacks
Theft of password reset tokens from the database
Reusing existing tokens
Stealing tokens through email hijacking




  
  
  How to implement a secure password reset flow



User’s enters email in the UI
Creating password reset token and storing it in DB
Sending token to the user and verifying it when used
Applications need to account for the frequency with which users forget their passwords. This opens a potential attack vector because anyone can request a new password on behalf of the legitimate user. Resetting a password requires sending a token to a user’s email address and this provides an opening for attackers. Making sure you have a secure process for handling the password reset tokens will ensure your…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SuperTokens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 JavaScript Tips to Improve Your React Code]]></title>
        <id>60df35f027f80207bcdbccea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-tips-to-improve-your-react-code-today/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's look at five JavaScript tips you can use today to instantly improve your React applications.  Because React is a JavaScript library, any improvements that we make in our JavaScript skills will directly improve the applications that we build with React. For this reason, I've put together a number of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can we build Micro VMs with Dockerfile? : Answer is Yes !!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/can-we-build-micro-vms-with-dockerfile-answer-is-yes-14d3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/can-we-build-micro-vms-with-dockerfile-answer-is-yes-14d3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Answer is : ####Slim
This results in a real VM that can boot instantly, while using very limited resources. If done properly, slim can allow you to design and build immutable unikernels for running services, or build tiny and embedded development environments.
Slim currently supports Virtualbox, KVM, and hyperkit (MacOS only) as providers for running VMs. Slim will discover all available providers, defaulting to virtualbox, if more than one provider is available. The -p flag can be used to force Slim to use a specific provider.
You can find repo here
 / 
        slim
      
    
 

slim will build a micro-vm from a Dockerfile. Slim works by building and extracting a rootfs from a Dockerfile, and then merging that filesystem with a small minimal kernel that runs in RAM.
This results in a real VM that can boot instantly, while using very limited resources. If done properly, slim can allow you to design and build immutable unikernels for running services, or build tiny and embedded development environments.
Create a micro-vm from a Dockerfile. Use build command with a directory containing a Dockerfile.
$ slim build images/alpine3.8-simple



This will add a bootable iso in the slim registry. See example Dockerfile.
slim build will use your default provider unless the -p flag is specified (ie -p hyperkit).
See a list of micro-vm images on your machine.
$ slim images



Provision a new instance…
View on GitHub
Click here for joining my team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>manish srivastava</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect and stop 404 attacks with fail2ban]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/armiedema/detect-and-stop-404-attacks-with-fail2ban-1coo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/armiedema/detect-and-stop-404-attacks-with-fail2ban-1coo"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common penetration test malicious visitors like to deploy is running a script full of not-so-random URIs.
Depending on if they receive a 200, 4xx, or 5xx response, this will let them know certain things about your web app. Such as: 
What tech stack is being used, which can let them know how to exploit the site further
If files that contain sensitive information are exposed
These types of attacks often result in the generation of a plethora of 404 errors. 
"404 attack" isn't the best descriptor of what the attack is, but 404 errors are a byproduct that we can key off of to help stomp these types of attacks. 
In addition to the security issues these attacks expose, another reason to consider stomping these attacks is the server load they expend. These attacks will often occur over a relati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Miedema</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-dilemma-of-naming-font-size-variables/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, a project will have a set of pre-determined font sizes, usually as variables named in such a way that seeks some semblance of order and consistency. Any project of considerable size can use something like that. There are always …
The post The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lexelius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Schedule a Job in Node Using node-cron]]></title>
        <id>60aa196411ffb70827ef5f43</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schedule-a-job-in-node-with-nodecron/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to schedule a job in Node using node-cron.  Node-cron is a handy npm package which you can use to schedule jobs to run at specific times or intervals. It is most suitable for scheduling repetitive jobs such as email notifications, file downloads, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Ready to Pass CISSP Exam]]></title>
        <id>60df6dd827f80207bcdbcf06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-ready-to-pass-cissp-exam/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earning the Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP) Certification proves you have what it takes to effectively design, implement and manage a best-in-class cybersecurity program. The CISSP is one of the most valuable Cyber Security Certificates in the market today.  We just posted a 13-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom ArrayLayout with React and JsonForms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/edge33/custom-arraylayout-with-react-and-jsonforms-2ch0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/edge33/custom-arraylayout-with-react-and-jsonforms-2ch0"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T13:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I started building forms with React and JsonForms library, I found myself in the need of a custom layout for rendering array of items with eventually nested arrays, without all the whistles and bells of the default material-renderers. After some digging in the source code I was able to come out with a custom array layout with my personal style. I will share in this post how to structure your project in order build great custom JsonForms components.
let's create a demo project for our needs. Open a terminal and type:
$ npx create-react-app my-app --template typescript

then install needed dependencies:
$ npm install --save @jsonforms/core
$ npm install --save @jsonforms/react
$ npm install --save @jsonforms/material-renderers

$ npm install --save @material-ui/core
$ npm install --save @…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Maida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an Angular & Amazon IVS player app in less than 15 minutes!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amazonivs/build-an-angular-amazon-ivs-player-app-in-less-than-15-minutes-2668</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amazonivs/build-an-angular-amazon-ivs-player-app-in-less-than-15-minutes-2668"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T13:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro ⭐️


Video & Streaming don't have to be complicated for the web anymore! in this tutorial we will build an Angular app using Amazon IVS & Video.js in less than 15 minutes!!
Amazon IVS (Amazon Interactive Video Service) is a fully managed live streaming solution: simply stream to Amazon IVS, and the service does everything you need to make low-latency live video available to any viewer around the globe. Amazon IVS handles the ingestion, transcoding, packaging, and delivery of your live content, using the same battle-tested technology that powers Twitch.
For more information on Amazon IVS check https://ivs.rocks
Check the twitch stream of this tutorial: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xCsh88xNkKE
I have a personal quest of making infrastructure and development approachable, accessible …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Super Diana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular change detection -OnPush]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-change-detection-onpush-18g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-change-detection-onpush-18g"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T11:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post about change detection, we touched on the basics of it. In this article, we will try to understand more about ChangeDetectionStrategy.OnPush method. So let us get started.
So first thing we will discuss is how to convert the component to the Onpush strategy. Let say we have a Sample component and we are having a default change detection strategy(by default all newly created components are having default change detection), it will be like:
import { ChangeDetectionStrategy, Component, OnInit } from '@angular/core';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-sample',
  templateUrl: './sample.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./sample.component.scss']
})
export class SampleComponent implements OnInit {

  constructor() { }

  ngOnInit(): void {
  }

}

Now let's add the change detection as O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Dhawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Hoisting]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naveenchandar/javascript-hoisting-2pde</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naveenchandar/javascript-hoisting-2pde"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T11:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hoisting is one of the important concepts every javascript or its related frameworks developers should be familiar with. Ever wonder how function calls or variable access can be done even before declaring those. If that's so then, Welcome to Javascript Hoisting World!!!.
This is one of the most common interview questions in front end development and common answer will be 

Hoisting is not what you think!!!😕
If you are trying to search and learn about hoisting, almost everywhere you will be seeing the same definition. May be that's beginner friendly but definitely that's not true. In JavaScript, Nothing will be moved.

Before we start, let us understand how our code will be executed in javascript engine.
Variables are one of the fundamental blocks of any programming language, the way each …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naveenchandar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Data Binding in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedgmurtaza/types-of-data-binding-in-angular-2878</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedgmurtaza/types-of-data-binding-in-angular-2878"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T09:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data binding is the automatic synchronization of data between model and view. In Angular, we have 3 fundamental ways to make to-and-fro binding between view and source.
Source to View (one-way)
View to Source (one-way)
View to Source to View (two-way)
This refers to as Property binding method, it includes all following patterns to share data from source to view.
Interpolation refers to embedding expressions into markup text. By default Angular interpolation uses {{ and }} to encapsulates the expression.
<p>{{title}}</p>
<div><img src="{{itemImageUrl}}"></div>

The [] brackets cause Angular to consider right-hand side value as dynamic, without brackets Angular evaluates the right-hand value as static string.
<img [src]="itemImageUrl">
<app-item-detail childItem="parentItem"></app-item-detail> 


Apart from element properties, we have element attributes ARIA and SVG for which we can use attribute bindings:
<button [attr.aria-label]="actionName">{{actionName}} with Aria</button>

Single class binding
[class.sale]="onSale"

Multiple Class bindings
[class]="'my-class-1 my-class-2 my-class-3'"

Single style binding
<nav [style.background-color]="expression"></nav>

Multiple styles binding
<nav [style]="stylesExpression"></nav>

More specifically, we call this Custom Event binding, utilizing Angular Event Emitter. 
Consider the following code showing button which alerts on click. The alert content is passed through <app-button> component template using custom event showMessage():





  
  
  3. View to Source to View (two-way)


Angular two-way data binding is the combination of square brackets [] and parentheses (). [()] refers to property binding followed by event binding.
<app-sizer [(size)]="fontSize"></app-sizer>





So, which methods you have already used or would love to use soon, or something else? And Why? Let me know in the comments section. 😃
See you again in another exciting article. Until then, happy coding! 💻]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Murtaza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types of Data Binding in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedgmurtaza/types-of-data-binding-in-angular-2878</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedgmurtaza/types-of-data-binding-in-angular-2878"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T09:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data binding is the automatic synchronization of data between model and view. In Angular, we have 3 fundamental ways to make to-and-fro binding between view and source.
Source to View (one-way)
View to Source (one-way)
View to Source to View (two-way)
This refers to as Property binding method, it includes all following patterns to share data from source to view.
Interpolation refers to embedding expressions into markup text. By default Angular interpolation uses {{ and }} to encapsulates the expression.
<p>{{title}}</p>
<div><img src="{{itemImageUrl}}"></div>

The [] brackets cause Angular to consider right-hand side value as dynamic, without brackets Angular evaluates the right-hand value as static string.
<img [src]="itemImageUrl">
<app-item-detail childItem="parentItem"></app-item-detail> 


Apart from element properties, we have element attributes ARIA and SVG for which we can use attribute bindings:
<button [attr.aria-label]="actionName">{{actionName}} with Aria</button>

Single class binding
[class.sale]="onSale"

Multiple Class bindings
[class]="'my-class-1 my-class-2 my-class-3'"

Single style binding
<nav [style.background-color]="expression"></nav>

Multiple styles binding
<nav [style]="stylesExpression"></nav>

More specifically, we call this Custom Event binding, utilizing Angular Event Emitter. 
Consider the following code showing button which alerts on click. The alert content is passed through <app-button> component template using custom event showMessage():





  
  
  3. View to Source to View (two-way)


Angular two-way data binding is the combination of square brackets [] and parentheses (). [()] refers to property binding followed by event binding.
<app-sizer [(size)]="fontSize"></app-sizer>





So, which methods you have already used or would love to use soon, or something else? And Why? Let me know in the comments section. 😃
See you again in another exciting article. Until then, happy coding! 💻]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Murtaza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Display datetime correctly in iOS/Safari using ionic2/angular2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/webrusterkk/display-datetime-correctly-in-ios-safari-using-ionic2-angular2-lof</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/webrusterkk/display-datetime-correctly-in-ios-safari-using-ionic2-angular2-lof"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T07:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The issue is caused by the Intlapi because DatePipe for Angular 2. Release is working fine only for FireFox and Chrome with custom format strings. it Doesn’t work on Safari due to lack of Intl. so as a temporary work around is to include the Intl polyfill
<script src="https://cdn.polyfill.io/v2/polyfill.min.js?features=Intl.~locale.en"></script>
Solution 2 You can use the moment.js which can format your required date as follows
moment(singleTable[0].FromCurrentDate).format("dd/MM/yyyy,h:mm:ss a")]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tummala Krishna Kishore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop!_OS 21.04 on Zephyrus G14 (Ryzen 5)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vinod/pop-os-21-04-on-zephyrus-g14-amd-ryzen-5-5h5e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vinod/pop-os-21-04-on-zephyrus-g14-amd-ryzen-5-5h5e"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T07:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy to report that - the latest Pop!_OS 21.04 is working without any glitches on G14.

Audio, Video, and Mic are working without glitches
Google Chrome and Firefox browsers work with hardware/GPU video decode support
Screenshare, Video conferencing Apps are working without glitches especially using Chrome
Battery Life is as good as Windows if not a bit more
Graphics mode switching between AMD & NVIDIA is seamless
Gnome 4 is performing without bugs and exceptions - unlike Fedora 34
Trackpad gestures animations aren't smooth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinod Ponmanadiyil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET CORE 5.0 TLS 1.2 issue on linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/moliveto/asp-net-core-5-0-tls-1-2-issue-on-linux-1ii5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/moliveto/asp-net-core-5-0-tls-1-2-issue-on-linux-1ii5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T23:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul  5 '21
            Comments: 1
            Answers: 0
        
I have a problem with TLS 1.2 in asp.net core 5.0 and linux
System.Net.Http.HttpRequestException: The SSL connection could not be established, see inner exception
       ---> System.IO.IOException:  Received an unexpected EOF or 0 bytes from the transport stream.
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.<FillHandshakeBufferAsync>g__InternalFillHandshakeBufferAsync|182_0[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adap, ValueTask`1 task, Int32 minSize)
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.ReceiveBlobAsync[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adapter)
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.ForceAuthenticationAsync[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adapter,
…
    
  
Open Full Question]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcelo Adrian Oliveto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package Flutter Linux App Into AppImage Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hosamhasan/package-flutter-linux-app-into-appimage-part-2-1c5o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hosamhasan/package-flutter-linux-app-into-appimage-part-2-1c5o"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now, We are ready to build our first Flutter AppImage app 🚀


Firstly , we will change our working directory to the project directory.
$ cd flutter_appimage

1- Create folder  AppDir
$ mkdir AppDir

2- Generate the YAML recipe file required to build the AppImage
$ appimage-builder --generate

this command will prompt some questions. Here is the final output :
INFO:Generator:Searching AppDir
? ID [Eg: com.example.app]: com.example.flutter_appimage
? Application Name: Flutter AppImage
? Icon: flutter_appimage_icon
? Executable path relative to AppDir [usr/bin/app]: flutter_appimage
? Arguments [Default: $@]: $@
? Version [Eg: 1.0.0]: latest
? Update Information [Default: guess]: guess
? Architecture: x86_64

Now, you will notice a new file AppImageBuilder.yml  added to the root directory of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hosam Hasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Package Flutter Linux App Into AppImage Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hosamhasan/package-flutter-linux-app-into-appimage-part-1-2agj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hosamhasan/package-flutter-linux-app-into-appimage-part-1-2agj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T19:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter is one of the fastest-growing cross-platform UI frameworks with a great and powerful community which has a great part of Flutter success.

Lately, Flutter announced desktop support including Linux which got the attention of big corporates like Canonical (Publisher of Ubuntu), and lately announced that they are rebuilding Ubuntu Desktop Installer using Flutter.
Flutter official docs also have a section on how to build and package Flutter Linux app in Snap (Linux Universal Package Manager) and ship it to Snap Store. here
So it will be interesting if we tried to package Flutter Apps using another universal package manager which is AppImage.
Linux OS (I will use Manjaro)


Flutter with Linux config enabled ( assuming you have latest flutter stable version )


AppImage Tool


AppImage Builder




  
  
  Install AppImage Tool and AppImage Builder


1- Install required deps
$ sudo pacman -Sy python-pip python-setuptools binutils patchelf desktop-file-utils gdk-pixbuf2 wget fakeroot strace

2 - Install Apimage Tool
$ sudo wget https://github.com/AppImage/AppImageKit/releases/download/continuous/appimagetool-x86_64.AppImage -O /usr/local/bin/appimagetool
$ sudo chmod +x /usr/local/bin/appimagetool

3 - Install AppImage Builder
sudo pip3 install appimage-builder

1 - install required deps for building flutter linux app
sudo pacman -Sy clang cmake ninja pkgconf gtk3

2 - Enable Flutter linux desktop configuration
$ flutter config --enable-linux-desktop

3 -  Create flutter project  flutter_appimage
$ flutter create flutter_appimage

3 - Build Linux App
$ (cd flutter_appimage && flutter build linux) 







  
  
  Now, We are good to go to build the AppImage 🥳]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hosam Hasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up Vim for Bash Scripting]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_destructive/setting-up-vim-for-bash-scripting-2ef5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_destructive/setting-up-vim-for-bash-scripting-2ef5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T16:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim and BASH?


Bash Scripting is a powerful skill to have as a programmer because we find Linux almost everywhere and to get through it you must have a command over its interface which is generally the BASH shell. Vim is a great option for doing this, or probably the best out there! Because Vim is pre-installed in almost every Linux distribution. This is not an in-depth setup for BASH on Vim, it is a simple editorial on starting up BASH scripting on the Vim editor. So without wasting time on "Vim features" let's dive in with the setup for BASH in Vim.
Setting up a bash script doesn't require much code but still in some cases it can be a bit hassle and to avoid the repetitive task, one can easily set up a macro for the boilerplate BASH script.
nnoremap bs i#!/bin/bash/<ESC>o

Ok that was p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meet Gor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Angular Applications with GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brandontroberts/building-angular-applications-with-github-copilot-2mj9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brandontroberts/building-angular-applications-with-github-copilot-2mj9"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T15:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot is a new feature in technical preview that uses AI to "pair program" with you, and give you hints, tips, and code snippets in VSCode. Below is a livestream of me walking through creating a TODOs app with Nx, Angular, and adding NgRx Store to manage the todos using code suggested from GitHub Copilot.




I thought it was an interesting journey, and look forward to using it more. Let me know what you think of GitHub's new pair programming tool!
Request an invite: https://copilot.github.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/kubernetes-explained-simply-containers-pods-and-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you zone out every time someone mentions “Kubernetes,” “containers,” or “pods,” this article is for you. No complex diagrams involved!
As a front-end developer, you don’t have to know how to configure an infrastructure from scratch. However, if you …
The post Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lari Maza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343671</id>
        <link href="https://tympanus.net/codrops/2021/06/04/trigonometry-in-css-and-javascript-beyond-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web design is such a rectangle-based design medium that literally any deviation from it feels fresh. Michelle Barker gets into using math in various ways to programmatically draw lines, shapes, and animations that end up looking both beautiful and have …
The post Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Linux installation to a USB external drive with EFI boot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/geraldew/ubuntu-linux-installation-to-a-usb-external-drive-with-efi-boot-46pj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/geraldew/ubuntu-linux-installation-to-a-usb-external-drive-with-efi-boot-46pj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T12:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: this is a tech person's guide, for sharing with other tech folk. I'm not attempting to make this completely newbie friendly - but I'd be happy to see its points used in something that is.
The goal here is to create a fully-functional forever-updateable system. So the two things that this is not:
it is not just a “live boot”;
this is not just something to then use to install Linux onto the internal hard drive of a computer.
Rather, this is Linux ready to plug into the USB port of any computer that can be told to boot from that. Every time you boot this system, it will inspect and deal with the hardware that it finds.
This way, the external USB drive becomes your "system", and the computer is just the commodity used at the time. Depending on your use cases:
a physically small drive is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>geraldew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add Material Design icons to Angular 11]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tony2tones/how-to-add-material-design-icons-to-angular-11-2708</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tony2tones/how-to-add-material-design-icons-to-angular-11-2708"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T11:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick post on how to add material design icons to your angular project with working sample project repo
https://pixel-tones.com/how-to-add-material-design-icons-on-angular-11/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover Data from RAID 5, 1, 0 on Linux (mdadm)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-data-from-raid-5-1-0-on-linux-mdadm-4268</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-data-from-raid-5-1-0-on-linux-mdadm-4268"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T06:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will find a detailed tutorial on data recovery from RAID 0, 1 or 5. The array we have been testing was built on Linux, and the methods described here will help you recover your files even if one or several disks break down.

A Linux-based hardware RAID is hardly a good example of a reliable storage system – if one of the disks within the array gets disconnected, the whole RAID can’t be mounted, and all the information becomes inaccessible in a second. In this case, you will need a special utility to rebuild the array with the remaining (healthy) drives. It will find and display the data which is still there, and restore this information.
We will perform all the tests with Hetman RAID Recovery. Its main purpose is to search and restore information from inoperable drives…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change Timezone on linux (ubuntu)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/goffity/change-timezone-on-linux-ubuntu-3f25</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/goffity/change-timezone-on-linux-ubuntu-3f25"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T19:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check timezone on host
timedatectl

Change timezone
timedatectl set-timezone ${timezone}

List timezone
timezonectl list-timezones]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>goffity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fourteenth Fourth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343496</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-fourteenth-fourth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T13:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s CSS-Tricks birthday! Somehow that keeps coming around every year. It’s that time where I reflect upon that past year. It’s like the annual vibe check. 
I’m writing this just days after my current home state of Oregon has …
The post The Fourteenth Fourth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Width Space]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-width-space/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T20:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The name zero-width space is antithetical, but it’s not without uses. In text, maybe you’d use it around slashes because you want to be sure the words are treated individually but not have any physical space around the slash:…
The post Zero-Width Space appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342995</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/good-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like it or not, meetings are essential to a good working environment and communication. Therefore, it’s crucial that we work on making them as productive as possible. Today we’ll explore myriad ways to keep meetings coordinated, well documented, and talk …
The post Good Meetings appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Testing Flow As It Should Be]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many tools and approaches, email still has quite a few pain points, both for developers and email marketers. Email is difficult because it has too many aspects to set and a few instances with no common rules to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andriy Zapisotskyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trick to Enable Printify Shipping Notifications for Orders in WooCommerce? Customer Notes.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342994</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-trick-to-enable-printify-shipping-notifications-for-orders-in-woocommerce-customer-notes/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T00:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a super niche blog post. But it’s been on my list forever to write down because this caused me grief for far too long.
The setup is that you can use WooCommerce to sell things on a WordPress …
The post The Trick to Enable Printify Shipping Notifications for Orders in WooCommerce? Customer Notes. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS for Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343637</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/css-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T18:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The marketing for Core Web Vitals (CWV) has been a massive success. I guess that’s what happens when the world’s dominant search engine tells people that something’s going to be an SEO factor. Ya know what language can play a …
The post CSS for Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App Platform on Digital Ocean]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342591</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/app-platform-on-digital-ocean/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T18:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is new stuff from DO.
App Platform is a hosting product, no surprise there, but it has some features that are Jamstack-inspired in the best possible way, and an additional set of unique and powerful features. Let’s start with …
The post App Platform on Digital Ocean appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hack the “Deploy to Netlify” Button Using Environment Variables to Make a Customizable Site Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343092</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hack-the-deploy-to-netlify-button-using-environment-variables-to-make-a-customizable-site-generator/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T14:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re anything like me, you like being lazy shortcuts. The “Deploy to Netlify” button allows me to take this lovely feature of my personality and be productive with it.

Clicking the button above lets me (or you!) instantly …
The post Hack the “Deploy to Netlify” Button Using Environment Variables to Make a Customizable Site Generator appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassidy Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A (Front-End Testing) Trap! Six Common Testing Pitfalls And How To Solve Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing front-end tests, you’ll find a lot of pitfalls along the way. Let’s explore common mistakes developers make, and how to avoid them. Testing doesn’t need to be painful, after all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you make a layout with pictures down one side of a page matched up with paragraphs on the other side?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343224</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-do-you-make-a-layout-with-pictures-down-one-side-of-a-page-matched-up-with-paragraphs-on-the-other-side/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T20:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got this exact question in an email the other day, and I thought it would make a nice blog post because of how wonderfully satisfying this is to do in CSS these days. Plus we can sprinkle in polish …
The post How do you make a layout with pictures down one side of a page matched up with paragraphs on the other side? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is single-threaded. This makes it increasingly hard to write smooth and responsive apps. Workers have a bad rep, but can be an important and useful tool in any web developer's toolbelt for these kinds of problems. Let’s get up to speed on Workers on the Web!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Surma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Shades Of July (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome July with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the world, they are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Bulky Builds With Netlify And Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static Generation is great for performance — until the app gets too big and build-times go through the roof. Today, we’ll have a look at how Netlify’s fresh On-Demand Builders can fix that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 40 With Mike Cavaliere: What Is Chakra UI For React?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Chakra UI. What is it and how can it help with your React projects? Drew McLellan talks to expert Mike Cavaliere to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>