<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-28T00:54:16.072Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-28T00:54:16.072Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding the Bootstrap CSS framework to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-bootstrap-css-framework-to-an-angular-application-2k40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-bootstrap-css-framework-to-an-angular-application-2k40"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T00:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
Bootstrap is an open source CSS framework with many components for building responsive WEB interfaces.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the application with the Angular base structure using the @angular/cli with the route file and the SCSS style format.
ng new angular-bootstrap
? Would you like to add Angular routing? Yes
? Which stylesheet format would you like to use? SCSS   [ https://sass-lang.com/documentation/syntax#scss                ]
CREATE angular-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe payment gateway integration in node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jahangeer/stripe-payment-gateway-integration-in-node-js-5733</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jahangeer/stripe-payment-gateway-integration-in-node-js-5733"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T00:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys, Today we gonna implement stripe payment gateway in node. We create simple order and pay with card. Stripe checkout gives us beautiful UI and various payment options. For better understanding watch demo video and support my channel 🙂.
So  let's start coding...
Demo Video 
Project Github Link
Create Node.js App
$ mkdir node-stripe-payment-gateway
$ cd node-stripe-payment-gateway
$ npm init --yes
$ npm install express stripe

Express : Express is minimal and flexible Node.js web applicaton framework.
Stripe : The Stripe Node library provides convenient access to the stripe API.
The package.json look like :
{
  "name": "node-stripe-payment-gateway",
  "version": "1.0.0",
  "description": "Implementing stripe payment gateway in node.js",
  "main": "index.js",
  "scripts": {
    "st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jahangeer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-Post Script en npm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maricarmendev/pre-post-script-en-npm-2i5g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maricarmendev/pre-post-script-en-npm-2i5g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T23:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://docs.npmjs.com/cli/v7/using-npm/scripts
La propiedad script de nuestro package.json admite varios scripts integrados y sus eventos de ciclo de vida preestablecidos, así como scripts creados por nosotros. Todos estos se pueden ejecutar ejecutando npm run <nombreComando>. Pero ademas de estos comandos podemos agregar comandos que se ejecuten antes y después de ellos con solo agregar pre o post antes del nombre del comando por ejemplo:

aquí esta el resultado:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maricarmendev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go programming project tutorial series: Build a Slack Bot with Go]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techwithmoss/go-programming-project-tutorial-series-build-a-slack-bot-with-go-1aia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techwithmoss/go-programming-project-tutorial-series-build-a-slack-bot-with-go-1aia"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T23:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
I wanted to share a YouTube series I developed on Go. The intended audience is primarily people in DevOps roles, but I think it will also be beneficial for those who are just starting to learn Go and are looking for a practical project to help them get started. Below is a detailed outline of the series so you know exactly what you will learn:
++++YouTube Playlist Link++++
Series Outline:
Video 1: Creating a Slack App - This video doesn't include any coding but covers the pre-requisite steps you must complete in order for the Go program that you write in later videos to work properly
Video 2: How to Publish a Message - Now you get to write some code, and I introduce you to the https://github.com/slack-go/slack library. Using the slack-go library, I show you how to send messages to a channel in your Slack workspace
Video 3: Command-line arguments and Block Kit - I walk you through modifying the Go program to accept command-line arguments and I introduce you to Slack's Block Kit.
Video 4 : Run our Slack Bot as a Jenkins Post-Build Action - This video focuses more on integrating the program with Jenkins so most of it is optional if you're more interested in learning Go. I walk you through the development of a Jenkins pipeline that runs the Go program as a post-build action (and sends a notification to your designated Slack channel on whether the Jenkins pipeline build passed or failed).
Video 5: Convert Bot to Microservice and add API Endpoint - I walk you through re-architecting the Go program as a microservice with a single API endpoint, rather than having Jenkins run the program on the Jenkins node.
Video 6: Add JSON processing to our API endpoint - I introduce you to JSON processing in Go using "encoding/json" so that the API endpoint in the microservice accepts JSON arguments.
I hope that you find the series valuable and moreover that you enjoy it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tech-with-moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Entrypoint Techniques for Docker Container]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codingsafari/advanced-entrypoint-techniques-for-docker-container-3dc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codingsafari/advanced-entrypoint-techniques-for-docker-container-3dc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T22:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building good images can be challenging. We want to provide enough abstraction and flexibility for the image to be used in different scenarios without having to rebuild them in every case. We also want to make it easy for users to use the image.
When building docker images, it is oftentimes enough to use normal commands to start the container.
FROM alpine
CMD ["echo", "Hello, world!"]

Occasionally, an additional entry point is used. When written like this, it is mostly for convenience, but there are some elaborate use cases.
FROM alpine
ENTRYPOINT ["echo"]
CMD ["Hello, world!"]

Sometimes, we really need to do more work or operate on environment variables, which can be tricky due to the difference in shell and exec syntax in the Dockerfile. In that case, a script commonly called entrypoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attempt #2 - Workspaces (npm, pnpm)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-2-workspaces-npm-pnpm-336a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-2-workspaces-npm-pnpm-336a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



npm
pnpm
Conclusion
Okay so attempt #1 didn't quite work, but all the package managers have a feature called Workspaces, which npm describes like this:
[Workspaces] provides support to managing multiple packages from your local files system from within a singular top-level, root package.
That sure sounds relevant, so let's give it a try!



The npm documentation is so terse I've honestly no clue how to get anything working 🤷‍♀️. If you know your way around npm workspaces I'm happy to swap stories, but for now I'm giving up on this.



Documentation here is definitely a step up, with more examples to draw inspiration from. Still a bit hard to grasp though, but I also came across this nice "actual complete guide to typescript monorepos" article by @cryogenicplanet
 that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Lauridsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attempt #2 - Workspaces (npm, pnpm)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-2-workspaces-npm-pnpm-336a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-2-workspaces-npm-pnpm-336a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



npm
pnpm
Conclusion
Okay so attempt #1 didn't quite work, but all the package managers have a feature called Workspaces, which npm describes like this:
[Workspaces] provides support to managing multiple packages from your local files system from within a singular top-level, root package.
That sure sounds relevant, so let's give it a try!



The npm documentation is so terse I've honestly no clue how to get anything working 🤷‍♀️. If you know your way around npm workspaces I'm happy to swap stories, but for now I'm giving up on this.



Documentation here is definitely a step up, with more examples to draw inspiration from. Still a bit hard to grasp though, but I also came across this nice "actual complete guide to typescript monorepos" article by @cryogenicplanet
 that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Lauridsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a PWA with Sveltekit | Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/create-a-pwa-with-sveltekit-svelte-a36</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/create-a-pwa-with-sveltekit-svelte-a36"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using sveltekit and svelte for over a year now. I'm also anxiously waiting for it to be matured enought to beat NextJs in terms of community. But I like them both.
So, on this weekend I wanted to turn one of my projects into a PWA. When I wanted to do with NextJs projects there were a lot of tutorials. But I couldn't find many guides for svelte beginners.
That's because svelte has pwa functionality built into it.
 A website
 manifest.json [ basic icons,names,shortcuts]
 service-worker [ for offline cache ]
So let's get on with it.

We'll create a demo Sveltekit project:
npm init svelte@next my-app


Then we'll choose a simple config in vite for the sake of this article:

Choose typescript because ts >>>> js:

Now we have a demo project setup with typescript, it will be straight-forward from here on:

Let's get into our directory:
cd my-app

And run:
yarn


After that,
In the /static directory, We'll create a manifest.json.
When svelte compiles the whole application the static files will be copied over to the build folder.

Then we'll refer our manifest.json in src/app.html.

And finally we'll create our src/service-worker.ts
Svelte will automatically detect the service-worker in the src folder's root and then register our service worker during build.
Isn't that neat?

Now we just need to build or app using yarn build:

Now we can preview our build using yarn preview:

'0' is that a 'install app' button,

Svelte makes it easy to make PWAs.
The source code of this project lies at:
https://github.com/100lvlmaster/svelte-pwa
You can find me at:
https://100lvlmaster.in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navin Kodag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can I get WiFi to work on my installation of Arch? (Mobile data's killing me!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baenencalin/how-can-i-get-wifi-to-work-on-my-installation-of-arch-mobile-data-s-killing-me-cdh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baenencalin/how-can-i-get-wifi-to-work-on-my-installation-of-arch-mobile-data-s-killing-me-cdh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, this is a more detailed version of a post I made on Unix&Linux StackExchange, which is a repost of a (wrongfully placed) post on AskUbuntu.

So I have a WiFi-adapter that is integrated with my motherboard; Network controller: Realtek Semiconductor Co., Ltd. RTL8822CE 802.11ac PCIe Wireless Network Adapter and Ethernet controller: Realtek Semiconductor Co., Ltd. RTL8111/8168/8411 PCI Express Gigabit Ethernet Controller (rev 16).
this package (tomaspinho/rtl8821ce).
So, I tried to install the package way:
First,
I tried the method of git clone, then manually build (using dkms-install.sh), but that produced these errors:
About to run dkms install steps...
Error! Could not locate dkms.conf file.
File: /usr/src/rtl8821ce-v5.5.2_34066.20200325/dkms.conf does not exist.
Error! Could not locat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Calin Baenen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side Project #1 - Crypto FOMO 😱]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jwaang/side-project-1-crypto-fomo-553n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jwaang/side-project-1-crypto-fomo-553n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


I recently rediscovered my passion for coding after taking a Node.js course and decided to create a fun little side project called Crypto FOMO. You can view it below:
👉 Crypto FOMO 😱
Front End Source
Serverless Source
The idea is to make the user wonder how much money they would probably have if they had invested in a cryptocurrency such as Bitcoin a couple years back instead of buying an item such as an Apple Macbook. I actually did not come up with this idea and saw a site similar to this a couple years back but unfortunately do not remember the original site or creator 😢.
Here are the technologies that I worked with for the first time ever 👶:
GatsbyJS - This was my first time working with GatsbyJS and I was intrigued with its server side rendering capabilities and eas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript: Typeguards and Type Narrowing.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hassam7/typescript-typeguards-and-type-narrowing-2cof</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hassam7/typescript-typeguards-and-type-narrowing-2cof"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, 
in operator. 
Note: The in operator is javascript feature not TypeScript.
Consider the following scenario: I am writing a todo application. In my todo application I have two types of Todos:
Anonymous Todo
Validated Todo
Anonymous todo have text and id fields. Lets write an interface for it
interface AnonymousTodo {
    text: string;
    id: number;
}

Validated Todo is similar to anonymous todo but with two extra fields authorName and validationDate. Lets write interface for it too.
interface ValidatedTodo {
    text: string;
    id: number;
    authorName: string;
    validationDate: Date;
}

so far so good, now lets write a method which will print the todo to console. So if anonymous todo is passed we should prepend anonymous logging text and id, but if ValidatedTodo is passed we sh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hassam Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step By Step Guide To Create A Twitter Bot Using Nodejs Hosted On DigitalOcean For Free]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sjcodebook/step-by-step-guide-to-create-a-twitter-bot-using-nodejs-hosted-on-digitalocean-for-free-2ipn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sjcodebook/step-by-step-guide-to-create-a-twitter-bot-using-nodejs-hosted-on-digitalocean-for-free-2ipn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T20:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original Post Link => https://webbrainsmedia.com/blogs/twitter-bot-using-nodejs-hosted-on-digitalocean
Recently, I posted the tweet shown below. The special thing about this tweet is that when the like or retweet counter gets updated my profile name will also get updated to show the current likes and retweet value. This is done by the Nodejs script running behind the scene on a DigitalOcean Droplet.
To see this in action you need to like and retweet the below tweet (It will take a minute to reflect the changes in the profile name)
So, In this article i will explain all the steps that i took to create this twitter bot from scratch and also explain how you can host it on the DigitalOcean Droplet for free.
Firstly, If you are new to DigitalOcean. Then, you need to create a new digitalocean ac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanmati Kumar Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A cheat sheet for JavaScript's fetch API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rahulbanerjee99/a-cheat-sheet-for-javascript-s-fetch-api-3o5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rahulbanerjee99/a-cheat-sheet-for-javascript-s-fetch-api-3o5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T19:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally Posted on realpythonproject.com
Connect with me on LinkedIn, Twitter
The fetch API in JavaScript is used to make requests. It can also be used to consume APIs. Let's take a look at some of the most common operations using fetch API. 
I will be working in a NodeJs environment 
npm install node-fetch

const fetch = require('node-fetch')

Let's make a request to the JSON Placeholder
const fetch = require("node-fetch");
const url = "https://jsonplaceholder.typicode.com/todos/1";

fetch(url)
  .then((response) => response.json())
  .then((json) => console.log(json))
  .catch((err) => console.log(err));

const fetch = require("node-fetch");

const getData = async (url) => {
  const res = await fetch(url);
  const json = await res.json();
  console.log(json);
};

const url = "https://j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Banerjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POC where Angular requests URL of image and Quarkus provides it through a raw copy and base64]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipewind/poc-where-angular-requests-url-of-image-and-quarkus-provides-it-through-a-raw-copy-and-base64-4ia9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipewind/poc-where-angular-requests-url-of-image-and-quarkus-provides-it-through-a-raw-copy-and-base64-4ia9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T19:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A simple POC where Angular requests the URL of an image to the Quarkus back end and then renders the image in the screen. Quarkus returns the image in two ways: (1) a simple copy from the URL of the image; (2) the image encoded in Base64 with the Media Type.
The project is available on GitHub poc-http-copy-images.

Let's imagine a hypothetical situation where only the backend have access to the URL of some images and you want to render these images on the frontend.
In this POC, I propose two ways of solving this problem:
The backend access the URL of the image and expose the same Response object;
The backend access the URL of the image, encode it into Base64 and expose it into a JSON object with the Media Type.
Optionally, you can run a Quarkus mock server which will provide three endpoints with the below images:
http://localhost:8090/image/earth.png
http://localhost:8090/image/moon.jpg
http://localhost:8090/image/solarsystem.svg
*** Optionally, because you can choose any image from the internet to run the test.
Enter inside the mock-server folder and type:
$ mvn quarkus:dev -Ddebug=5006

The swagger will be available at:
http://localhost:8090/q/swagger-ui

Enter inside the quarkus folder and type:
$ mvn quarkus:dev -Ddebug=5006

The swagger will be available at:
http://localhost:8080/q/swagger-ui

Enter inside the angular folder and type:
$ npm install
$ ng serve

The front end will be available at:
http://localhost:4200/
Ok, in this screen, just put the URL of any image you desire (of the mock or the internet) and click on Load Image:

After clicking in the button, the image will be displayed in two columns, the left one is the raw copy from the URL and the right one is the Base64 version:

Any new image searched will be shown and the previous ones will slide down:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Henrique Gross Windmoller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn programming, not a programming language.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amran92/learn-programming-not-a-programming-language-44c9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amran92/learn-programming-not-a-programming-language-44c9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T18:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your learning of a programming language will remain in it forever and you will not be able to move to another language, but by teaching you programming itself, you will be able to identify the concept that transfers you from one language to another easily, and you must understand that programming languages are only tools that can be changed at any time. Watch the following example with me.
If I ask you to search for a specific element inside an Array and bring me the position of the element (Position, Index) inside the Array, what will you do? 
The first thing is if you are learning a language such as PHP, Python, JavaScript, there is a method that does the process very easy. Watch the example in more than one language to understand the idea.

Did you notice anything? 
The idea is the same…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amran Hussein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignore headers of csv files with papaparse]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nardjes/ignore-headers-of-csv-files-with-papaparse-ni7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nardjes/ignore-headers-of-csv-files-with-papaparse-ni7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T18:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a csv file that I need to parse and store in a database. I use sequelize for this 
Here is how I defined the model of my table in sequelize :
    const Person= sequelize.define(
      'person',
      {
        id: {
          type: DataTypes.UUID,
          primaryKey: true,
          defaultValue: uuidv4(),
          allowNull: false
        },
        name: {
          type: DataTypes.STRING,
        },
        age: {
          type: DataTypes.INTEGER,
        }
        }, {
            createdAt: false,
            updatedAt: false,        
            tableName: 'person'
         }
    )
    return Person
  }

then I have a csv file "test.csv":
he ,dd
liza, 23
sarah, 22

basically I can't change the headers in my csv file and I have to keep the same structure defined in the db, I use papaparse to parse this file :
        const papa = require('papaparse');
        const fs = require('fs')

        const file = fs.createReadStream(__basedir + "/test.csv");


        papa.parse(file, {
          header: true,
          step: async function(results, parser) {
            console.log("Row data:", results.data);
            try{
              await Person.create(results.data)

            }catch(e){
              console.log(e)
            }

          }
      });

in output I get the following error :
SequelizeUniqueConstraintError: Validation error

the name, surname and age fields are null in the database
I am looking for a solution to ignore the headers of the csv file, how can I do that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NardjesBen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to convert any input video file format in S3 bucket to any other video file format using Elastic Transcoder and Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-convert-any-input-video-file-format-in-s3-bucket-to-any-other-video-file-format-using-elastic-transcoder-and-lambda-3j5o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-convert-any-input-video-file-format-in-s3-bucket-to-any-other-video-file-format-using-elastic-transcoder-and-lambda-3j5o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T18:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Challenges faced to find the solution of how to convert the video file format from .mp3 to .ts format within some seconds”. I have checked different ways so that I can get my video file format conversion within a few seconds and within my budget. I got the solution by using an amazon elastic transcoder service in which I am able to set the configuration of the transcoding pipeline and able to create my custom presets as well. The cost of the pipeline is in my budget. Even I can create different presets as 1M, 1.5M, 600K and many more as per my need or can use the existing preset as well. I have created code for lambda function with s3 trigger which automatically generates the output in s3 bucket whenever i do input in my bucket of any video file format. My output will be based on the lamb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GargeeBhatnagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up Golang application performance monitoring with open source monitoring tool]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/signoz/how-to-set-up-golang-application-performance-monitoring-with-open-source-monitoring-tool-80d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/signoz/how-to-set-up-golang-application-performance-monitoring-with-open-source-monitoring-tool-80d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T17:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to check our Github repo before diving in 👇
 / 
        signoz
      
    

  
Monitor your applications and troubleshoot problems in your deployed applications, an open-source alternative to DataDog, New Relic, etc.

    
     
     
          


SigNoz helps developers monitor applications and troubleshoot problems in their deployed applications. SigNoz uses distributed tracing to gain visibility into your software stack.
👉 You can see metrics like p99 latency, error rates for your services, external API calls and individual end points.
👉 You can find the root cause of the problem by going to the exact traces which are causing the problem and see detailed flamegraphs of individual request traces.

Application overview metrics like RPS, 50th/90th/99th Percentile latencies, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Anand ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to backup Hashicorp Vault with Raft storage on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michael_lin/how-to-backup-for-hashicorp-vault-with-raft-storage-on-kubernetes-21db</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michael_lin/how-to-backup-for-hashicorp-vault-with-raft-storage-on-kubernetes-21db"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T15:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Context


Our team is experimenting with Hashicorp Vault as our new credentials management solution. Thanks to the offical Vault Helm Chart, we are able to get an almost production-ready vault cluster running on our Kubernetes cluster with minimal effort.
Our 5-node vault cluster is highly available by using the provided Integrated Storage Raft backend. The vault cluster is run as a Kubernetes StatefulSet and each node has its own data storage. Each data storage is powered by a Block Storage on IBM Cloud via PersistentVolumeClaim.
Unfortunately, the open source vault does not provide an out-of-the-box automated backup solution. It is only offer in Vault Enterprise. Apprently, our team doesn't have a deep pocket to pay for the license fee.
That said, the backup feature is still accessible f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between ember serve and npm run start]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jayjayjpg/the-difference-between-ember-serve-and-npm-run-start-2m5p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jayjayjpg/the-difference-between-ember-serve-and-npm-run-start-2m5p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T14:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between ember serve and npm run start


When you have a built a single-page-application using Ember CLI you have two options for starting your app locally. You can either use the CLI's ember serve command directly or you can use the handy npm alias that is created for you after generating a new Ember app: npm run start
But what's the difference between those two?
npm run start is used for


First, npm run start allows you to create your own default boot up command for your application by e.g. passing additional parameters to ember serve and hide this modified booting instruction away in one, single, shorthand command via a definition in your package.json. This makes you type less and can make your life easier when developing your app locally.
If you want to learn more about …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Jordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node Modules — What does require() do?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davey/node-modules-what-does-require-do-139b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davey/node-modules-what-does-require-do-139b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T14:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Node.js allows code to be written and stored in (preferably) small modules.  These modules can then be referenced from other modules to build up larger applications.  What exactly is a module though, and how can code be accessed from within a module?
Let's take a look at a small piece of code that we can easily turn into a Node.js module.  Consider we have a method that allows us to drink tea.
function drinkTea() {
    console.log("Mmm, delicious.");
}

If this method was placed within a large JavaScript file, we could simply invoke the function drinkTea() to enjoy a warm beverage.  To create a module however, we simply place this function within its own file and tell Node about any functions we wish callers of the module to access.
Within Node.js, we could therefore create …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way (in 🎥 video): part 18 – Pod & Node (Anti) Affinities]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-18-pod-node-anti-affinities-1fa2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-18-pod-node-anti-affinities-1fa2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T13:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes can be difficult or time-consuming. In order to spread knowledges about Cloud technologies I started to create sketchnotes about Kubernetes, then I've auto-published a book and since now I've started a new serie of video! :-)
I imagined a serie of short videos with a mix of sketchnotes and speech.
I think it could be a good way, more visual, with audio & video to explain Kubernetes (and others technologies).
In this new episode, let's talk about Pod & Node Affinities and Anti Afinities.




The video is in French BUT I done the subtitles in english (and french too).
If you liked the video and are interested to watch another ones, please give me some feedbacks (and you can also subscribe to my Youtube channel, if you want to ❤️).
If you are interested, I published all the sketchnotes on Kubernetes (and new ones!) to make a "book" of 165 pages: "Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way".
If you like theses sketchnotes, you can follow me, I will publish others sketchs shortly :-).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurélie Vache</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run creat-react-app with HTTPS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pranjaljain0/run-creat-react-app-with-https-4ep6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pranjaljain0/run-creat-react-app-with-https-4ep6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In current days we host websites on Vercel and Netlify and we are automatically assigned a generated SSL to provide with Secured connection(HTTPS), but in the development period we are unaware of the process to run it with HTTPS and we miss out on some testing which works only on HTTPS like google apis, etc.
Configure creat-react-app project to handle https
Generate SSL Certificates for localhost
Add certificates to the project
Trust certificate in browser
Run the project secured
Add a file .env in the root directory of the project with the line
HTTPS=true

Follow this article to generate a SSL certificate for localhost. and place the certificates in the root directory.
Generate an SSL Certificate With the Root Certificate for localhost
Pranjal Jain ・ Jun 24 ・ 1 min read
#security
        #webdev
        #webassembly
      





rootCA.key
rootCA.pem
rootCA.srl
server.crt
server.csr
server.csr.cnf
server.key
v3.ext

in the .env file add these two properties and there paths.
SSL_CRT_FILE=server.crt
SSL_KEY_FILE=server.key

Here you will be using the server.crt as your certificate file & server.key as your key for certificate.
Follow this article to trust the certificate on your browser 
Hence you have HTTPS enabled for your project.

If you're stuck anywhere do leave a comment.
Follow me on Twitter at Twitter/pranjaljain0
github/pranjaljain0
Happy Hacking!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on Kafka: Brokers, Producers, and Consumers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeden/notes-on-kafka-brokers-producers-and-consumers-nkf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeden/notes-on-kafka-brokers-producers-and-consumers-nkf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T12:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had a good overview of what brokers, producers, and consumers are in the previous sections. Now it's time to go deeper! You can simply skip ahead onto the parts you're interested in or you could also check out each one below (which I hope you do!)
Review on Brokers
Replication
Leaders for a Partition
Producers
Message Keys
Consumers
Consumer Groups
Consumer Offsets
Kafka Broker Discovery
As previously tackled, a Kafka cluster is composed of multiple brokers and each broker is basically a server.
Each broker is identified by an ID (integer)
Each broker contains certain topic partitions
good start is 3 brokers
It is also important to note that when you connect to a broker, which is called the bootstrap broker, you're already connecting to the entire cluster.
Also, recall that when you cre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eden Jose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[denosaur faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/3mam/denosaur-faster-3mcc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/3mam/denosaur-faster-3mcc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T12:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[--no-check you can in deno disable type checking.
typescript processing. 
vscode, which validates code on development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konrad Chmielecki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Host your Website/API FOREVER for FREE(Not a Joke!)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pybash/host-your-website-api-forever-for-free-not-a-joke-2mc2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pybash/host-your-website-api-forever-for-free-not-a-joke-2mc2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T10:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome Back! A Little Plug?


Welcome back, today with a post on Web Development mostly! But you can use your creative knowledge to extend it and be sure to leave it in the comments for others as well! Anyways a shameless plug to my Discord server - if you want to chat with me! Or have questions ask in the help channels! Ahh and the plug is over! Let's get into the actual stuff now!
Well, firstly it is going to be hosted on repl.it, so if you want to customize the domain, refer here. Anyways now on to the actual part. So I will be using this simple flask app to demostrate - 
Ok so once you have your website/API written in repl.it, Run the code by using the Run button on the top of the screen, 
 
 
UptimeRobot, this website is going to ping our website every 5 mins to keep the server running for ever. After visiting UptimeRobot, you need to sign up for an account. Once that is complete, Click on Create new Monitor. Once you have done that fill in the details as follows:
Monitor Type - HTTP(s)

Anyways, as you know everything that has a start has an end, similarly, this post has too! So byeeeeeeee!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PyBash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Serverless Observability Workshop, Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/aws-serverless-observability-workshop-4ne3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/aws-serverless-observability-workshop-4ne3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T08:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREREQUISITES


The following prerequisites are required for this workshops:
A computer with an internet connection running Microsoft Windows, Mac OS X, or Linux.
An internet browser such as Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Opera, or Edge.
Familiarity with common Linux commands and the concepts of CI/CD.
If you don’t already have an AWS account with Administrator access:   create one now by clicking here 
 Go to the IAM Management console 
On the left hand navigation, select Users, then click on the Add User button.
Enter the user details:

Attach the AdministratorAccess IAM Policy, and click Next: Tags

We will skip adding tags for the workshop. Click Next: Review
Click to create the new user:

Take note of the login URL and save it for future use:

Click on this URL to go to the AWS Management Console login page, use the username and password for the workshop user you just created.
Launch Cloud9 in your closest region:
Accept the default values for Stack name and Parameters and click Create stack.


Wait until your Stack creating status shows as CREATE_COMPLETE

Go to your Cloud9 Environment.
Find the environment named serverless-observability-workshop, click Open IDE.
When the Cloud9 console is shown, customize the environment by closing the welcome tab and the AWS Toolkit tab, lower work area, and opening a new terminal tab in the main work area:

Your workspace should now look like this:

Run the following commands in the Cloud9 terminal to update nvm (Node Version Manager) and install jq (a command-line JSON processor) and Locust (a load testing tool)





nvm install stable
sudo yum -y install jq 
sudo pip3 install locust


Return to your workspace and click the gear icon (in top right corner), or click to open a new tab and choose “Open Preferences”
Select AWS SETTINGS


Turn off AWS managed temporary credentials


Close the Preferences tab




  
  
  References:


 Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes in Azure DevOps free grants explained]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gtrekter/changes-in-azure-devops-free-grants-explained-3kao</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gtrekter/changes-in-azure-devops-free-grants-explained-3kao"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T08:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the past few days, I received several emails from people asking why their CI/CD pipelines started randomly receiving errors like the following:

Since 2018, Azure DevOps Services has provided free CI/CD pipelines for its users. By default, it allowed a developer to run arbitrary code for up to 1800 free minutes per month on Microsoft-hosted agents and ten parallel jobs for public projects. However, the market capitalization of cryptocurrency has skyrocketed in recent years, and as a result, it has become very profitable for some folks to violate the terms of service of PaaS providers’ free tiers, like Azure DevOps, to run cryptocurrency miners as a step in their build pipeline.
“…cryptocurrency surged from $190 billion in January of 2020 to $2 trillion in April of 2021..” CEO of Dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Porta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load Testing with Azure DevOps and k6]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gtrekter/load-testing-with-azure-devops-and-k6-3j7c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gtrekter/load-testing-with-azure-devops-and-k6-3j7c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T08:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s article, I guide you through your Azure DevOps setup to perform automated load tests using k6. Before we begin, I want to take a minute to explain what load tests are and why they are essential.
There are many different types of testing in software development. For example, some tests check that different models of an application work together as expected (integration testing), some focus on the business requirements of an application by verifying the output of action without considering the intermediate state (functional testing), and others perform different types of testing. Load testing is a type of performance testing as well as a type of stress test and capacity test. It focuses on verifying the application’s stability and reliability under both normal and peak load condit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Porta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[websocket bez frameworka i bibliotek w node]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/3mam/websocket-bez-frameworka-i-bibliotek-w-node-3mbj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/3mam/websocket-bez-frameworka-i-bibliotek-w-node-3mbj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T07:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do napisania tego tekstu zainspirował mnie numer #03 newslettera nodestart, którego autorem jest Adrian Piętka
Zazwyczaj jak potrzeba coś zrobić szybko to używa się gotowych rozwiązań. W przypadku websocket istnieje wiele implementacji tego protokołu. 
Zacząłem od stworzenia w node dwóch serwerów. Pierwszy serwer to serwer http. Jest odpowiedzialny za wyświetlanie strony, dzięki której
tcp jest odpowiedzialny za odebranie i wysłanie tej samej wiadomości.
Pierwszą rzeczą jaką należy zrobić po połączeniu klienta z serwerem jest przygotowanie uścisku dłoni.
Sec-WebSocket-Key.
258EAFA5-E914-47DA-95CA-C5AB0DC85B11.
sha1 a następnie potraktować base64.
createHeader. Należy zwrócić uwagę na formatowanie nagłówka. Ono nie jest przypadkowe. Tak samo
Ten pakiet będzie zawierał ramkę. Skupie się tylko na tej części ramki która pozwala odczytać i wysłać wiadomość tekstową.
Żeby zdemaskować tekst, każdy bajt powinien być przepuszczony przez algorytm który kryje się w funkcji mapUnmask.
Gdy już tekst zostanie przepuszczony przez algorytm. Należy go następnie wysłać. Żeby to zrobić, kopiuje pierwszy bajt.
Omawiany kod.
https://gist.github.com/3mam/57fb002d50d7a5c2b6fb81b46c957f56#file-1-main-js
Źródła z których czerpałem wiedzę na temat websocket.
https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/WebSockets_API/Writing_WebSocket_servers
https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc6455#section-5.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konrad Chmielecki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 Days of React JS: Solving 30 Problems in 30 Days!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/praveenscience/30-days-of-react-js-solving-30-problems-in-30-days-1pjc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/praveenscience/30-days-of-react-js-solving-30-problems-in-30-days-1pjc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T04:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the World of JavaScript! This is the age of JavaScript. JavaScript is everywhere in the Full Stack. I am planning to solve a couple of problems that I faced in my work and other places. Let's try solving 30 crazy problems I had in the next 30 days, starting from Feb 14th! Also, Eddie Jaoude (one of the very few GitHub Stars in this entire Milky Way Galaxy) is going to do the honours of kick-starting this event!
Here's a Pilot that explains why and when:

Here are the current topics that we are covering. They are completely diverse, but some are interconnected (i.e., you have to have watched the previous episode so that you can understand better).
Intro to JSX by Dolly Jain


Componentising your React App by Pooja Singh


States & Props of Components by Tanya Taneja


A Simple Connected Component by Nikita Raghuwanshi


Customising the Branding Part of your App by Sonali Bedade


Changing your Favicon RealTime by Shriya Madan


Bootstrap CSS Header Component by Sohini Pattanayak


Interactively Theming the Header Component by Tanya Taneja


Fetching External Data Using AJAX by Shivam Veer Singh


Fetching External Data with Axios by Ayonika Dey


Converting States into Hooks by Sonali Bedade


Discord Emoji Hover Effect by Kirthana Subramaniam


Layout for 30 Days of React by Shilpa Khelge


GitHub JSON to 30 DoR Layout by Shivani Gangadharan


Display Posts from Public JSON API by Riti Kumari


React Router for Multiple Page Apps by Akhil Rudrawar


Deploying React & Router using GH Pages by Shriya Chadha


Really Making Deployment using GH Pages by Shriya Chadha


Create a Responsive Carousel by Riti Kumari


Basic Web page with Kotlin and React by Khushi Sharma


Build LinkTree App using React JS by Vismita Prabhu


Finish LinkTree App using React JS by Vismita Prabhu


React JS using TypeScript by Vinayak Nirvani


Redux using TypeScript by Vinayak Nirvani


Generics in TypeScript by Vinayak Nirvani]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Praveen Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#The most effective way to utilize the LinkedIn]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sitesh235/the-most-effective-way-to-utilize-the-linkedin-29on</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sitesh235/the-most-effective-way-to-utilize-the-linkedin-29on"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T03:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most effective way to utilize the LinkedIn



   Since LinkedIn has multiple functions, there is more than one way to answer this question depending on what purpose you want to utilize the platform for. Many people use it for exploring the jobs market and making themselves visible to potential employers. But my expertise is in using LinkedIn for B2B lead generation, and so I’m going to talk about the most effective ways to do that.

LinkedIn is an incredible tool for lead generation – there are millions of decision-makers regularly using the platform. But it is still relatively underused for lead generation given the massive potential for great leads it offers.
I’ve found that it’s important to conduct multiple activities on LinkedIn to really make the most of it and get those great le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sitesh Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image to WebP format converter free blogger Script]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/copyrightworker/image-to-webp-format-converter-free-blogger-script-1li3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/copyrightworker/image-to-webp-format-converter-free-blogger-script-1li3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T02:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Dcoders, in this video I have given you an image to web format converter free blogger script. So Please Watch Video Till End. 
Download Script Click Here.
https://copyrightworker.com/
Related Queries:
Dcoder Solutions, Image to WebP format converter free blogger Script, free blogger script, image to webp converter tool html source code, how to create image to webp converter tool website, create jpeg to webp converter tool website in blogger, create image to webp converter tool website in Blogspot, blogger me image to webp converter tool kaise banaye, image to webp converter tool website source code, image to webp converter tool script, jpeg to webp converter tool html code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CopyrightWorker.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate List of Web Development Podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tuckertriggs/ultimate-list-of-web-development-podcasts-4okf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tuckertriggs/ultimate-list-of-web-development-podcasts-4okf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T22:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate List of Web Development Podcasts


Podcasts are a great way to stay informed about what's happening in web development. This comprehensive list has over 350 podcasts covering website design, development, freelancing. Feel free to Contribute on Github. Originally posted on my blog.



  
  
  Learn to Code Podcasts


Learn to Code With Me
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
The freeCodeCamp Podcast
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Command Line Heroes
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
CodePrep
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
CodeNewbie
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Tech Jr
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Second Career Devs
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Learn to Code in One Month
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Base.cs
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
Tech Talk with Mo Sharif
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
The Chau Codes Podcast
Apple•Spotify•Google•Web
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tucker Triggs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alfianardhi/linux-command-line-you-need-to-know-2lgn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alfianardhi/linux-command-line-you-need-to-know-2lgn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T18:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are looking to expand skills about linux. So, out of the hundreds of possible Linux commands you could or have to learn. Here some linux command you need to know.
The pwd command for to know you where you are now. For example your’re in download folder. Try the following type pwd and you will see that you’re in your download directory.
For Linux you can type clear or Ctrl+L to Clear the screen. It works in most terminal.
Command ls is equivalent to the DOS dir command, that it show lists files and directories. This command has some common attributes, example like:
ls -a for show all folders and files including visible and hidden.
ls -l for show the contents of the directory in full, starting from access rights, owner, group and the date the file or directory was created.
ls -i show directory contents and size.
For troubleshooting you can use command tail -f. Example like this tail -f /var/log/daemon.log.
If you want to see the previous commands, you can type history in your terminal. Meanwhile, to search command history in Linux, press ctrl+R, then just type the previous command you want to search or use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfian Ardhi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attempt #1: "Can't we just make project-folders?"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-1-can-t-we-just-make-project-folders-15nh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/attempt-1-can-t-we-just-make-project-folders-15nh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T18:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



The Good
The Bad


Why don't we script that?
What about Yarn?
Let's get the simple solution out of the way first: Can't we just move everything into different projects within the same repository?
To test that out let's extract web and api into two separate apps, and make a libs folder for the shared dependencies. By moving the files around we end up with this structure:
webby
├── apps
│  ├── api/
│  └── web/
├── libs
│  ├── analytics/
│  ├── logging/
│  └── types/
└── tsconfig-base.json

And if we look at web's package.json we see a small list of dependencies that are used entirely by web:
    "express": "^4.17.1",
    "react": "^17.0.2",
    "react-dom": "^17.0.2",
    "react-router-dom": "^5.2.0",
    "types": "file:../../libs/types"

ℹ️ As before I've prepared this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Lauridsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 reasons why you should use Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thatanjan/9-reasons-why-you-should-use-typescript-4e5h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thatanjan/9-reasons-why-you-should-use-typescript-4e5h"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T17:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why should you use Typescript?


Simple. It solves your problem. Let's see.
Type checking: This is why typescript really exist. It adds type checking over javascript. It stops you to write stupid code.

Let's see an example:
const addNums = (a, b) => {
    return a + b
}

a and b should be number. But you stupidly pass strings.
addNums('1', '2')

outupt:
'12'

We don't want this to happen. It was a stupid example. But if you are working on bigger project, this kind of bug can happen easily. You waste hours and hours to fix the code. 

This where typescript rescues us with type checking.
const addNums = (a: number, b: number) => {
    return a + b
}

Now if you pass string it will give you error so that you can fix it.
Gives error at compile time instead of runtime: Instead of your code giv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Shomodder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's learn about few networking side command in Linux/Unix]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/payalsasmal/let-s-learn-about-few-networking-side-command-in-linux-unix-3b7d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/payalsasmal/let-s-learn-about-few-networking-side-command-in-linux-unix-3b7d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi There!
1. netstat:
netstat stands for Network Statistics. This is very basic command used to print network connections, routing tables, interface statistics etc.

Syntax:
netstat [OPTIONS]

There are various options which are supported by netstat command. Listing few of them in below
netstat -i: i stands for Interface.(Network Interface shows that how kernel links up with the software network side to the hardware network side.
Example:

netstat -r: r stands for Routing. It will show kernel IP routing tables.
Example:

2. nslookup:
nslookup stands for Name Server lookup. It helps us to check the IP address mapped to DNS(Domain Name System) and vice versa. This is very useful when we want to troubleshoot the DNS related issue.

Syntax:
nslookup [OPTIONS]

nslookup has two modes Interactiv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Payalsasmal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the Typescript Monorepo (a practical, hands-on adventure, your help is needed! 🙏)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/exploring-the-typescript-monorepo-a-practical-hands-on-adventure-your-help-is-needed-2ggb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonlauridsen/exploring-the-typescript-monorepo-a-practical-hands-on-adventure-your-help-is-needed-2ggb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T16:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents




The Two Extremes of Code Organization


Files & Folders
Everything's a Repository
Finding the middle ground


A note on TypeScript
I need your help!
So what's the plan?
A quick word before we begin
The Attempts
I like simple code, in the "low coupling, high cohesion" sort of way where code is packaged into understandable, self-contained clumps that does an understandable "thing". That way I don't have to understand everything all at once, instead I can get an overview at the high-level and dive into the details when relevant to the work that needs doing.
We all chop our code into understandable abstractions already: We write functions and classes into separate files and folders. But as our project grows so does the need to keep organizing our code's abstractions, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Lauridsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Linux ? 🤔]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cenacr007_harsh/what-is-linux-4d8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cenacr007_harsh/what-is-linux-4d8h"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T15:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have recently started learning Linux and so I decided to document my journey along the way, so I would be writing a Blog series where I will cover everything that I have learned.
The entire content credits goes to my instructor Brian Holt.
So without further ado, let's get on with todays blog.

To learn about how Linux came to be, let’s go back to the beginning to 1969 where Ken Thompson and Dennis Ritchie of Bell Laboratories developed the UNIX operating system. It was later rewritten in C to make it more portable and eventually became a widely used operating system.
A decade or so later, Richard Stallman started working on the GNU (GNU is Not UNIX) project, the GNU kernel called Hurd, which unfortunately never came to completion. The GNU General Public License (GPL), a free software li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KUMAR HARSH</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BE SECURE!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ubuntu/be-secure-30j3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ubuntu/be-secure-30j3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T14:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi!We use smartphone,laptop and other devices. All of them access to the internet. Many files have malware, If you install or use these files, you will have many problems also hackers can access to your data such as accounts and passwords.I wrote name of some apps that you should not use these apps. I will introduce more secure apps.











In conclusion
Many people think google is really safe but it isn't!!!. Google apps are nice in the UI, services and etc,However in security doesn't have standard features.I hope you enjoy this article if it is good, share with your friends and if you have any question or any other review, comment that.HAVE A NICE TIME AND GOOD SECURITY :).
❤️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amoo ubuntu:)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BE SECURE!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ubuntu/be-secure-30j3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ubuntu/be-secure-30j3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T14:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi!We use smartphone,laptop and other devices. All of them access to the internet. Many files have malware, If you install or use these files, you will have many problems also hackers can access to your data such as accounts and passwords.I wrote name of some apps that you should not use these apps. I will introduce more secure apps.











In conclusion
Many people think google is really safe but it isn't!!!. Google apps are nice in the UI, services and etc,However in security doesn't have standard features.I hope you enjoy this article if it is good, share with your friends and if you have any question or any other review, comment that.HAVE A NICE TIME AND GOOD SECURITY :).
❤️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amoo ubuntu:)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composition vs Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hassam7/composition-vs-inheritance-4oo2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hassam7/composition-vs-inheritance-4oo2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T12:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently completed an online course and these are my takeaway from Composition and Inheritance.
With inheritance we can extend the functionality of an existing class by overriding its method in a Child class e.g
class Parent {
  function sayHi() {
    console.log("sayHi from Parent");
  }
}
class Child {
  function sayHi() {
    console.log("sayHi from the Child");
  }
}

Inheritance is characterised by an "is-a" relationship between two classes e.g Apple is Fruit, Car is a Vehicle etc. Inheritance is suited for use cases where there is tight coupling between the classes which is rarely the case in the real world.
Lets say your are building a house and you need to model a window in code. So you might come up with following:
class Window {
  height: number;
  width: number;
  open: boolea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hassam Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Correct Way to Deploy Typescript Express Project to Heroku ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/philippurwoko/correct-way-to-deploy-typescript-express-project-to-heroku-53h8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/philippurwoko/correct-way-to-deploy-typescript-express-project-to-heroku-53h8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T08:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. I have a Github repository for my Typescript Express project. In my project structure, I have src folder to save my .ts file and a dist folder for the output of tsc compiler, and there will be the .js file, just like typical typescript structure.
I used expressjs to create a webserver, everything is working ok. I add the dist folder into .gitignore file, so the only file that got pushed to github repository is the src folder which mean the typescript file. And I want to connect Heroku and my github repository. The problem is, the file that should be in Heroku is the .js file, not the .ts.
What is the correct way to deploy a typescript project to Heroku ?
I really appreciate all of your response. Thank you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Purwoko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Promises with Timeout Error in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikosanif/create-promises-with-timeout-error-in-typescript-fmm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikosanif/create-promises-with-timeout-error-in-typescript-fmm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T06:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Immo Wegmann on Unsplash.
Sometimes we create promises that take too long to finish and we don't want to wait. For example, if we want to make a request and the response takes 20 seconds to finish and for any reason we may want to throw an error in the first 5 seconds and proceed to the next code block.
In this article, we will see how to implement a promise which throws an error after a specific time span. It supports typings with the power of Typescript and accepts a custom error to be thrown when the time comes.
First of all, we create a new promise that rejects an error after a time span in milliseconds. The return type of the timeout promise is never which represents the type of values that never occur. For instance, never is the return type for a function expression or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikos Anifantis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending various TypeScript type declarations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wojciechmatuszewski/extending-various-typescript-type-declarations-36km</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wojciechmatuszewski/extending-various-typescript-type-declarations-36km"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T04:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with TypeScript can be a blissful experience – the type completions, the fast feedback loop, and the confidence gained by the presence of types make up for a great DX.
But yet, sometimes, these experiences are interrupted by moments of frustration. For example, maybe the library you have just pulled from npm does not expose type declarations? Or perhaps TypeScript is not aware of a global variable you know exists?
If that describes your experiences, read on. The following contains tips regarding extending TypeScript type declarations. I believe that by following them, the number of frustrations you experience while working with TypeScript will drastically decrease.
Ever written code similar to the following?
function getData({tableName: process.env.TABLE_NAME as string})

What abou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wojciech Matuszewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the Keyword `as` Needed When Narrowing TypeScript Interfaces With an `if`?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codefinity/why-is-the-keyword-as-needed-when-narrowing-typescript-interfaces-with-an-if-122n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codefinity/why-is-the-keyword-as-needed-when-narrowing-typescript-interfaces-with-an-if-122n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T03:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 26 '21
            Comments: 1
            Answers: 0
        
Given some interfaces for Circle and Square as follows:
export default interface Circle {
  radius: number
}

export default interface Square {
  sideLength: number;
}

I can use as to calculate the area properly:
function getArea(shape: Circle | Square) {
  if ((shape as Circle).radius) {
    return Math.PI * (shape as
…
    
  
Open Full Question]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manav Misra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUXARG, editor for linux !]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-editor-for-linux-4ej9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-editor-for-linux-4ej9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T01:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LINK
LUXARG is another keyboard friendly text editor.
This project started at August 2019 and restarted at 2021 TODAY!
Easy to use and userfriendly !
LUXARG support :
Fedora, CENTOS and RedHat,
Debian and Ubuntu,
OpenSUSE,
Arch and Manjaro, ...


INSERT MODE : <F1>
SAVE   MODE : <F2>
OPEN   MODE : <F3>

$ python<3X> installer.py

$ pip3 install -r requirements.txt

old method(v0.1, v0.1.1){
    $ cd ~/.luxarg
        $ python<3X> update.py
    }


$ luxarg-update (v0.1.2)

pip.txt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amzy 0 |  محمد امین عظیمی</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Angular SPA App to GitHub Pages, implement CI/CD using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rupeshtiwari/deploy-angular-spa-app-to-github-pages-implement-ci-cd-using-github-actions-33a2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rupeshtiwari/deploy-angular-spa-app-to-github-pages-implement-ci-cd-using-github-actions-33a2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to build your first Angular App and deploy over cloud using GitHub Actions? How to deploy/publish Angular App to GitHub Pages automatically? Did you use GitHub Actions to build and deploy  Angular App over GitHub Pages? Stay tuned in this article I will show you step by step from creating angular app to building and deploying using GitHub Actions.

We will build an angular application & deploy over GitHub Pages.
Run Below script to create new angular app.
ng new sample-app

ng add angular-cli-ghpages
✔️ Build
✔️ Lint
✔️ Test
Let’s create GitHub workflow with jobs. Note that now a days GitHub actions runner sets the CI=true by default. Learn more here…
name: Angular GitHub CI # 👈


Let’s trigger the job whenever main branch got new push.
on:
  push:
    branches:
      - main #…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rupesh Tiwari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[()] = Banana in a box]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/micxla81/banana-in-a-box-6o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/micxla81/banana-in-a-box-6o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T22:20:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[...How much Fun is that, isn't???]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michele Perla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 25th June 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-25th-june-2021-4135</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-25th-june-2021-4135"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T21:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 weeks in a row! Hi 5!✋
Introduction


This week's review encompasses what this series is all about: security.
iPhone bug breaks WiFi when you join hotspot with unusual name


I'll say this: be careful with the name you assign to your Wifi network.
The unusual name in question is %p%s%s%s%s%n.
Excerpt from the article:
Once triggered, the bug would render your iPhone unable to establish a WiFi connection, even if it is rebooted or the WiFi hotspot is renamed.
Researcher Claims Apple Downplayed Severity of iCloud Account Takeover Vulnerability


This is yet another piece of news about Apple products. In this case, it's iCloud.
The article title says it all, but, here is an excerpt that summarizes the entire story:
The issue, researcher Laxman Muthiyah says, was a bypass of the various secu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Cybersecurity & Linux Tools] How to install Metasploit?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-linux-tools-how-to-install-metasploit-2c58</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-linux-tools-how-to-install-metasploit-2c58"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T20:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people have been using this tool Metasploit. You came across on it on many tutorials and wondered how do you actually install this?
The Metasploit framework is a very powerful tool which can be used by cybercriminals as well as ethical hackers to probe systematic vulnerabilities on networks and servers. Because it’s an open-source framework, it can be easily customized and used with most operating systems.
With Metasploit, the pen testing team can use ready-made or custom code and introduce it into a network to probe for weak spots. As another flavour of threat hunting, once flaws are identified and documented, the information can be used to address systemic weaknesses and prioritize solutions.
Due to its wide range of applications and open-source availability, Metasploit is used by e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuma-Tsushima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Cybersecurity & Linux Tools] How to install Metasploit?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-linux-tools-how-to-install-metasploit-2c58</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-linux-tools-how-to-install-metasploit-2c58"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T20:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people have been using this tool Metasploit. You came across on it on many tutorials and wondered how do you actually install this?
The Metasploit framework is a very powerful tool which can be used by cybercriminals as well as ethical hackers to probe systematic vulnerabilities on networks and servers. Because it’s an open-source framework, it can be easily customized and used with most operating systems.
With Metasploit, the pen testing team can use ready-made or custom code and introduce it into a network to probe for weak spots. As another flavour of threat hunting, once flaws are identified and documented, the information can be used to address systemic weaknesses and prioritize solutions.
Due to its wide range of applications and open-source availability, Metasploit is used by e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuma-Tsushima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Cybersecurity] How do Reverse shells work?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-how-do-reverse-shells-work-1jfc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/cybersecurity-how-do-reverse-shells-work-1jfc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T20:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse Shells



  
  
  How do reverse shells work?


To make a connection to a typical remote shell, a machine controlled by the attacker connects to the remote network host and it requests a shell connection.
blind shell
But what if the remote host is not directly accessible, like it has public IP or is protected by a firewall?
In this situation reverse shells maybe shouldn't be used, where the target machine initiates connection to the listening network host a shell is now established.
To start you need a listener process on their system to listen the reverse shell connections incoming to their IP address, Eg, 12.12.12.12
nc -lvnp 7070

The netcat listener will listen at port 7070. An attacker needs to execute the code to the listener. Many reverse shells needs programming langs
pente…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuma-Tsushima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption for Protecting Python Source Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/richard_scott/encryption-for-protecting-python-source-code-4ckg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/richard_scott/encryption-for-protecting-python-source-code-4ckg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T19:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is a great programming language, it has so many uses, but one thing that it doesn’t do well is help protect your hard work from others. Python source code is plain-text, which means that anyone with access to your files can see what you wrote. Not great when you’ve just written the latest advancement in artificial intelligence (AI) or the best machine learning (ML) algorithm on the planet.
Python has a great feature where it first compiles your source code into bytecode; this is a low-level platform-independent representation of your source code. Back in the days when computers were slow, this was helpful, but when trying to distribute secure code this is a problem. Most solutions for securing Python code involve the distribution of .pyc files. Now, this isn’t all that bad as it doe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Scott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Property Brain Twisters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342718</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/custom-property-brain-twisters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T18:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am part of that 82% that got the answer to Lea Verou's quiz wrong. Stephen Shaw posted a similar quiz as well and it's a fun exercise sharpen your CSS chops.
The post Custom Property Brain Twisters appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Security, Identity, and Compliance with AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-security-identity-and-compliance-with-aws-3ike</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-security-identity-and-compliance-with-aws-3ike"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T17:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While companies increasingly look to cloud computing as a means to expand, modernize and stay competitive, so too do those companies expose themselves to new risks. In fact, Ermetic and IDC report that 80% of CISOs claim their company has had a cloud data breach in the past 18 months. Nearly half of those (43%) had experienced 10 or more breaches.
The benefits of cloud computing are numerous, but organizations cannot make the switch to this modern platform without understanding the risks involved and, more importantly, how to protect themselves, their staff and their customers.
Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a cloud service provider that’s on almost every company’s radar today. But many AWS customers today wonder what the best approach to security is and how to get there.
companies often str…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adit Modi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animating Angular’s *ngIf and *ngFor]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/animating-angular-s-ngif-and-ngfor-5e12</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/animating-angular-s-ngif-and-ngfor-5e12"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T16:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jared Youtsey | ng-conf | May 2019
*ngIf and *ngFor will remove elements from the DOM. There isn’t a CSS solution for animating a non-existing element in the DOM. But Angular provides us with a simple solution.
For purposes of brevity, wherever I refer to *ngIf it is equally applicable to *ngFor. The complete, working code can be downloaded here.
Let’s start with the default application generated by the CLI and just modify the nice Angular logo in and out of the view based on a button we add.
ng new ngifAnimation

You won’t need routing and can select SCSS for the styling.
Let’s add the button we want to use to toggle our *ngIf on the image. Open app.component.html and add a simple button: (this is the default HTML)
<!--The content below is only a placeholder and can be replaced.--
<div st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342911</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-cancel-pending-api-requests-to-show-correct-data/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T14:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had to create a widget in React that fetches data from multiple API endpoints. As the user clicks around, new data is fetched and marshalled into the UI. But it caused some problems.
One problem quickly became evident: …
The post How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgi Nikoloff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Polyphony - June 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ciconia/what-s-new-in-polyphony-june-2021-edition-5db4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ciconia/what-s-new-in-polyphony-june-2021-edition-5db4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T13:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polyphony 0.58 has just been released. Polyphony is a gem for writing fine-grained, highly concurrent programs in Ruby. Here’s a summary and discussion of the latest changes and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon Rosner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restrict Azure DevOps PAT tokens with Azure AD policy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/restrict-azure-devops-pat-tokens-with-azure-ad-policy-3315</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/restrict-azure-devops-pat-tokens-with-azure-ad-policy-3315"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T13:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is an Azure DevOps Personal Access Token (PAT)?


A personal access token (PAT) is used as an alternative to using a password to authenticate into Azure DevOps. When you're working with third-party tools, APIs or the command line that don't support Microsoft or Azure AD accounts or you don't want to provide your primary credentials to the tool, you can make use of PATs.
PATs are easy to create when you need them and easy to revoke when you don’t.

When creating a new PAT you can select the organization where you want to use the token, and then choose a lifespan for your token. Say for example making it only active and usable for a period of 30 days. A PATs lifetime can be extended if needed, but cannot be longer than the maximum period of 1 year. You can also specify granular permissi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auth0 WebAuthn Passwordless with Device Biometrics is Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/auth0-webauthn-passwordless-with-device-biometrics-is-now-available-5dal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/auth0-webauthn-passwordless-with-device-biometrics-is-now-available-5dal"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T13:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Login to web apps quickly and securely using a finger or face biometrics.



  
  
  
The average person has to keep track of approximately 100 passwords and spends almost 13 minutes every week resetting those passwords. Due to this friction, password reuse is a major issue with over two-thirds of end users reusing passwords across sites, creating widespread security vulnerabilities. The Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report (DBIR) found that credential vulnerabilities are involved in more than 80% of all data breaches. Since password reuse is so common, a single compromised password can endanger multiple accounts. 
Auth0 was the first IAM system to build support for passwordless authentication, and all of these reasons are as pertinent as ever:
Passwords are insecure: users pick insecure passwords and reuse them across sites. Since data breaches are common and they frequently include password information, this creates a situation where more and more sites are vulnerable to hacking attempts.
Passwords are expensive to manage: users forget them, and resetting passwords can be an expensive and time-consuming process.
Passwords negatively impact customer retention: remembering and typing a password, particularly on a phone keyboard, carries friction, and can cause returning customers to abandon the login flow, therefore impacting retention.
We believe that moving away from passwords as an authentication method is key to making the internet safer while reducing friction and positively impacting user acquisition and retention. 
Since our initial release, the authentication industry has been hard at work finding better ways to implement passwordless authentication. For example, the FIDO Alliance successfully led the specification and implementation of WebAuthn. In the last few years, Webauthn has been implemented in all major OS/browsers, with iOS 14 and iPadOS 14 being the latest to join the party in September 2020.  

Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer - Full time remote work]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/darshmt/full-stack-software-engineer-full-time-remote-work-22nh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/darshmt/full-stack-software-engineer-full-time-remote-work-22nh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T13:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A leading company in the Igaming sector is looking for a Fullstack Software Engineer to make a difference in its business needs. The experienced engineer will be required to build enterprise class web applications. 
Responsibilities:
Contribute directly to the success of products by materializing the product teams' visions into a tangible user experience.
Requirements:
You are a team player who readily offers help and shares knowledge with your colleagues.
Front-end Development; you worked with various projects
Bonus Points:
Please apply here:
https://www.castilleresources.com/job/fullstack-software-engineer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DarshMT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Nx workspace based Angular and NestJS apps to Heroku]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/deploying-nx-workspace-based-angular-and-nestjs-apps-to-heroku-13cp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/deploying-nx-workspace-based-angular-and-nestjs-apps-to-heroku-13cp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles, I've shown you how to create an Nx Workspace with Angular and NestJS applications in it. After the applications are ready, we need to host them somewhere. Heroku is one of the services that lets us deploy applications easily. In this article, I'll demonstrate how to deploy the Angular and NestJS applications that are developed using an Nx monorepo. You can find the example code with the aforementioned applications in my GitHub repository. To follow this article, please fork this repo, clone it locally and checkout nxDeployHeroku_entryPoint.
git clone git@github.com:<your_username>/nx-photos.git

# Or using Https
git clone https://github.com/<your_username>/nx-photos.git

cd nx-photos

git checkout nxDeployHeroku_entryPoint

To follow this article, you need to have the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garis Besar Shurikenjutsu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ninjutsujkt/garis-besar-shurikenjutsu-2dib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ninjutsujkt/garis-besar-shurikenjutsu-2dib"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T05:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jepang memiliki sejarah pertarungan tangan kosong yang panjang dan kaya. Sementara kendo dan kenjutsu adalah dua jenis pertarungan tangan kosong yang paling terkenal di Jepang, ada gaya lain yang kurang dikenal, salah satunya adalah shurikenjutsu.
Garis Besar Shurikenjutsu
Shurikenjutsu adalah pertarungan tangan kosong lempar shuriken dari Jepang. Seperti yang mungkin Anda ketahui, shuriken adalah senjata genggam kecil yang biasanya memiliki banyak sisi tajam (namun beberapa komponen memiliki satu sisi tajam). Itu digunakan di Jepang primitif sebagai senjata lempar dan juga senjata melukai.
Semua hal dipertimbangkan, peran dasar shuriken bukanlah untuk melukai atau melempar. Semua hal dipertimbangkan, itu digunakan untuk interupsi. Melempar shuriken dapat mengalihkan musuh juara samurai, m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ninjutsu Jakarta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keycloak Docker setup tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/krishxda/keycloak-docker-setup-tutorial-16ip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/krishxda/keycloak-docker-setup-tutorial-16ip"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T04:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I will show you how to setup Keycloak using docker.
Just before we get into the tutorial, lets see what are the pre-requisites
Docker
Portainer (optional I prefer it personally as it will help you managing docker images/containers)
Basics of Docker
Keycloak is an open-source identity and access management solution for modern applications and services. Keycloak provides both SAML and OpenID protocol solutions.
Keycloak provides identity and access management, it is also open source. It has several deep features integrated which helps in building easier production grade application by including Keycloak for Authentication and Authorization.
First we need to install Keycloak using docker so fire up the terminal/command prompt and type in the following command
docker run -p 8080:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>krishxda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps on Your Ionic4 Project w/ Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferfox1981/google-maps-on-your-ionic4-project-w-angular-48dj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferfox1981/google-maps-on-your-ionic4-project-w-angular-48dj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T02:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ionic


The advantage of Ionic is that if you have knowlegde of some Web Development Framework (e.g.: Angular, React, Vue or pure Javascript), then you can start creating Cross-Platform Mobile Apps right away. This means a reduced learning curve and increased productivity.
My goals in this article are:
Set up a project using Ionic 4 and Angular;
Integrate Google Maps into the project;
Exercise some Maps features like centering, maps inputs and outputs;
The basic dependencies to start your project are: Node.js and Angular. If you do not have Node.js, go here. If you do not have Angular installed, go here. After installing both, you need to install Ionic. Just type:
npm install -g @ionic/cli
here for further details.
ionic start


"Integrate your new app with Capacitor to target native iOS a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Raposo da Camara Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular meetup videos from May, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-may-2021-28bb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-may-2021-28bb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T23:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another month’s gone, another Angular roundup post is here! This time we’ve selected a top 3 video list from some of the most important figures from the Angular community. John Papa, Minko Gechev and Mark Thompson are all featured, covering great topics like the latest changes to the framework, libraries in Angular 12 and using Angular CLI to build new applications.
What’s new in Angular | John Papa
Join Pluralsight author and JS expert John Papa to explore the latest changes to the framework, tooling and developer experience.
State of the Angular | Libraries in Angular 12
Minko Gechev talked about the latest State of the Angular for 30 minutes, and then Joost Koehoorn held a presentation about the libraries in Angular 12, followed by a Q/A session.
Angular CLI | Mark Thompson
In this video Angular team member Mark Thompson will be taking you on a journey with the Angular CLI to build a new application in Angular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MeetupFeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common React Mistakes You Might Be Making – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>60d3ee396e1a1407b6b0b6ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-react-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go over the most common mistakes you might be making in your React code right now, plus how to fix them. If you want to create amazing React applications, it's essential to avoid many common errors along the way. In this article, we'll not only cover how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelemetry to Understand Software Performance]]></title>
        <id>60d4b5e96e1a1407b6b0bac4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want good performance in your application, you need to collect data to figure out where to make improvements. That's where OpenTelemetry comes in. OpenTelemetry offers a single set of APIs and libraries that standardize how you collect and transfer telemetry data. OpenTelemetry provides a specification for instrumentation so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working Remote: A Few Tips and Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/darkwiiplayer/working-remote-a-few-tips-and-tricks-3fbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/darkwiiplayer/working-remote-a-few-tips-and-tricks-3fbg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months of working from home on less than optimal hardware, I've had the chance to pick up some interesting tricks, as well as using some that I've picked up before, while working on remote servers. Here's a short list of the most notable ones:
A few quick words on my "less than optimal" hardware: I basically had to make do with a small laptop that has definitely seen better days (days that have long since passed, I should probably add) with a freshly installed Ubuntu 20. But I could, of course, connect to my PC at the office over company VPN, as I'm sure is the case for many of you as well.
I've been a big fan of Vim for several years now, so editing text from the terminal has always felt very natural for me. This has proven itself to be incredibly useful in working remot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DarkWiiPlayer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 9: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-9-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April of 2009, Yahoo! shut down GeoCities. Practically overnight, the once beloved service had its signup page replaced with a vague message announcing its closure.
We have decided to discontinue the process of allowing new customers to sign up 
…
The post Chapter 9: Community appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React vs Angular vs Vue (briefly)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cicko/react-vs-angular-vs-vue-briefly-52jn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cicko/react-vs-angular-vs-vue-briefly-52jn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Angular’s Core contains most of the functionalities you might need in your application, while with React and Vue, you have to find external libraries, maintained by independent contributors. Luckily most of the basics one, are maintained by the same people that maintain the core. Therefore, when working with React and Vue, you have to be more careful when choosing libraries, being aware that libraries with a poor maintenance might be deprecated in future.
To build an app with Angular you have to learn Typescript, which is a superset of JavaScript, while with Vue and React you can use pure JS. Regarding the view, with Angular and Vue you write it with HTML, where in React you have to write JSX, which is a syntax that allows coexistence between HTML and JS. Thus, Angular and Vue are idea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudolf Cicko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command



  
  
  References



Ahamed, I. (2020, May 13). The find command ~ THM Writeup. Medium; Medium. https://irshadahamedpro.medium.com/the-find-command-thm-writeup-10dba7722261

GNU. (2021). Findutils 4.8.0. GNU. https://www.gnu.org/software/findutils/manual/html_mono/find.html




  
  
  Be more specific



  
  
  Find all files whose name ends with .xml




find / to search for items in the root directory
-type f to filter for files
-name "*.xml" to filter for items with a .xml as a suffix
Answer: find / -type f -name "*.xml"
/home directory (recursive) whose name is user.txt (case insensitive)




find /home to search for items in the /home directory
-type f to filter for files
-iname user.txt to filter for case insensitive name pattern of user.txt



Answer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omri Bornstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover RAID 5 Data from SAN D-Link DSN-1100]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will show you how to recover lost data from a NAS storage system, with the example of D-link DSN-1100. Also, it will help you to retrieve information from the hard disks of an inoperable SAN device.

It is common knowledge that NAS is a server-type storage system designed to store various information at the file level. In fact, this is a computer with an array of disks inside, which is connected to a network. Every authorized user can interact with any files stored in a NAS. Such storage systems are becoming more and more popular because most of them make use of the RAID technology: It provides a serious boost in fault tolerance and increases security of storing large amounts of data. However, there is no system to give you a 100% guarantee against data loss. Sometimes, users ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hire AngularJS Developers to Build Faster & Scalable Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sttlinc/hire-angularjs-developers-to-build-faster-scalable-web-applications-2jmb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sttlinc/hire-angularjs-developers-to-build-faster-scalable-web-applications-2jmb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T05:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hire AngularJs Developers to Build Faster & Scalable Web Applications. With over 60% of the U.S. population using web-based applications, there is no reason why your company shouldn't be one of them. Hire AngularJs developers to build faster and more efficient web applications, with minimal effort.
AngularJs is a JavaScript framework that offers a unique object model and powerful features for creating dynamic web applications. Utilizing advanced technologies and best practices, Angular lets you deliver engaging experiences for your clients while saving you time and money. With easy to use controls, you can create reusable elements that are simple and easy to update. You can also hire a team of AngularJs developers to quickly scale your projects from an initial investment.
Hire a team of An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semaphore Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a REST API with .NET 5 and  C#]]></title>
        <id>60d36eb66e1a1407b6b0b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-rest-api-with-dot-net-5-and-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET is a popular software framework developed by Microsoft. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API end-to-end from scratch using the latest .NET 5 innovations and Visual Studio Code. The course uses the C# programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Great Technical Course]]></title>
        <id>60a406bd906c5207e3a7dfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-great-technical-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to create a great technical video course. I run the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where we post technical courses from a variety of contributors. Video courses that follow the guidelines in this article are often a good fit for freeCodeCamp's channel. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The truth about Angular form]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joseat/the-truth-about-angular-form-2ji7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joseat/the-truth-about-angular-form-2ji7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[introdution


In this article i want to explain how to use angular forms directives in the right way, because i've observed that is not already clear how to use it correctly or what is the diferent about use template forms and built our owned form whith FormBuilder class. I am not going to enter in how to create a form in angular only i want to explain the interesting things.
I'm going to start with something very simple but could be doubs about this. 
The question is:  What happens when we use <form #f="ngForm" ... ?
Someone could think that we're referencing our form, this could be true, but in reality more things are happening behind the scenes.
The truth about this is that when we import FormsModule automatically NgForm is avalilable in our view, this means that NgForm is automatically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Álvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Fallacies – Definition and Fallacy Examples]]></title>
        <id>607f5fafdd38b9088c2bd0c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-fallacies-definition-fallacy-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're debating someone, you want to use all the resources at your disposal to convince them you're right. And that's great – but you should be careful that you don't end up using a logical fallacy to help you make your point. What is a Logical Fallacy?A logical fallacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>