<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-21T01:01:22.111Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-21T01:01:22.111Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The anatomy of a great playbook entry]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tstromberg/the-anatomy-of-a-great-playbook-entry-35od</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tstromberg/the-anatomy-of-a-great-playbook-entry-35od"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T00:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if you could easily reduce the length of outages by 3X?
According to the SRE book, "recording the best practices ahead of time in a playbook produces roughly a 3x improvement in MTTR".  This improvement mirrors my experience with well-written playbooks. 
So what makes a playbook entry "great"?
Remember how you felt in your first on-call rotation, when you were paged at 3am for a system you barely understood? Write your playbook entries for that person.
Playbooks should provide just enough context to co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Strömberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shift Left on Security: EXPLAINED Easily]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security in DevOps is important, but often underrated. So much so that someone has created the DevSecOps word for it. But what does shift left mean? And how to shift left on security?
We will see all of these and more today.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/94AIX5oArIw
If you rath…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shift Left on Security: EXPLAINED Easily]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security in DevOps is important, but often underrated. So much so that someone has created the DevSecOps word for it. But what does shift left mean? And how to shift left on security?
We will see all of these and more today.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/94AIX5oArIw
If you rath…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GLSL Canvas Component for React, Hooks & Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samasastudio/glsl-canvas-component-for-react-hooks-typescript-4p3c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samasastudio/glsl-canvas-component-for-react-hooks-typescript-4p3c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Devs,
Recently I've been spending some creative time in KodeLife and designing a small library of GLSL shaders that I like to have on hand for projects.  When finally rendering these shaders on the web, I can't recommend glslCanvas 👨🏻‍🎨 enough.
There are a few common canvas-related bugs that you may run into when dealing with CSS sizing, resolution and adaptive resizing though.  Usually this comes in the form of pixelated shaders, poor u_mouse movement mapping, and the shader just rendering overall a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samasastudio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Component Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryhenness/angular-component-considerations-118e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryhenness/angular-component-considerations-118e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is more to developing a component than making sure the component looks and works the way it should. Components are a huge portion of what our SPA is made up of so we should consider each component's performance, usability, readability, and more. This will help make sure our code stays maintainable and performant over time.
For the user's sake, we want the component to be as performant as it can be. The SPA's job is to quickly render the data provided by the backend systems. Achieving this can be suppl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Component Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryhenness/angular-component-considerations-118e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryhenness/angular-component-considerations-118e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is more to developing a component than making sure the component looks and works the way it should. Components are a huge portion of what our SPA is made up of so we should consider each component's performance, usability, readability, and more. This will help make sure our code stays maintainable and performant over time.
For the user's sake, we want the component to be as performant as it can be. The SPA's job is to quickly render the data provided by the backend systems. Achieving this can be suppl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular dynamic modules at runtime with Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/seanperkins/angular-dynamic-modules-at-runtime-with-module-federation-mk5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/seanperkins/angular-dynamic-modules-at-runtime-with-module-federation-mk5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 12 recently launched with the added enhancements of Webpack 5 and opening the door to using module federation. If you are looking for a great deep-dive into module federation and micro-frontends, I suggest reading: https://www.angulararchitects.io/aktuelles/the-microfrontend-revolution-module-federation-in-webpack-5/.
Micro frontends and more importantly module federation, allows developers the flexibility of remotely requesting a module on the network and bootstrapping that module into their applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Perkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner's guide to Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maanuanubhav999/beginner-s-guide-to-linux-5eeo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maanuanubhav999/beginner-s-guide-to-linux-5eeo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time I installed Ubuntu, and here is a summary of how it progressed. Here I am trying to write in laymen's terms, and suggestions are welcomed.
Why did I install it?
Which Linux to install as a beginner.
Also GUI of Ubuntu is same as Windows with some difference like you won't find Microsoft office here, instead Libre office, for music you can use Vlc,and for Web browsing Firefox.
There are all alternative tools available for all sorts of work.
What is ubuntu.
https://ubuntu.com/download/desktop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anubhav_sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to MongoDB and Node.js using Monk]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/an-introduction-to-mongodb-and-node-js-using-monk-3492</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/an-introduction-to-mongodb-and-node-js-using-monk-3492"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually programmers entering the Node.js universe for the first time associate it with MongoDB and as I am publishing this article I feel that I am reinforcing this topic even more.
However, I am not here to talk about whether NoSQL databases are better than SQL databases or not. I think that each one has its own use cases and we must always need to take into consideration the context.
There are several options for connecting our Api to a MongoDB database. However, I can safely say that mongoose is the most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add Animation over your favorite Terminal in GNU/Linux.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/antonyjr/add-animation-over-your-favorite-terminal-in-gnu-linux-3g5e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/antonyjr/add-animation-over-your-favorite-terminal-in-gnu-linux-3g5e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T20:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've always wanted to animate my konsole with an animation over it's title bar. I searched everywhere but I can't find a program for that. That's why I've created spirit. It is a small program written in C++ which overlays a gif over your terminal. This is only available currently for KDE Plasma, Gnome, XFCE, Mate and other major X11 based Desktop Environments for Gnu/Linux.
There are plans to support Windows and Mac in the future. 
 $ wget "https://github.com/antony-jr/spirit/releases/download/v0.1.2/spiri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antony Jr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which angular version to use for production environment application development ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/siruvolu/which-angular-version-to-use-for-production-environment-application-2oog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/siruvolu/which-angular-version-to-use-for-production-environment-application-2oog"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T20:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by siruvolu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siruvolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top 5 Reasons I Switched to Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/the-top-5-reasons-i-switched-to-vim-3noo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/the-top-5-reasons-i-switched-to-vim-3noo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T20:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been a happy Vim user for a very long time. I’ve used it at work, in university. I'm glad I did. In this post, I'll list the top five reasons why I've become an avid vim user.
Before that, I used some regular editors like nano and mc.  When I found that many people were using vim, I decided to give it a try.
I can instantly switch between all my operating systems (OSX, Linux and Windows) without having to change anything. Even when logging in over an SSH connection to remote computers.
It's what I use …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to back-end codebase as a front-end for first time.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eulier/contributing-to-back-end-codebase-as-a-front-end-for-first-time-3i27</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eulier/contributing-to-back-end-codebase-as-a-front-end-for-first-time-3i27"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve 4 years of experience working with client-side code (HTML, CSS, JS and Node.js). Thanks to Zero To Mastery i could deep dive in the some major computer science concepts through Data Structure and Algorithm Course on Udemy, JS Advanced Concepts and improve my journey as a Software Developer by following the Junior to Senior Web Development 2021.
It took me (as a non-native english speaker) from april 2020 to feb 2021 to improve myself, daily on it, and eventually i got hired by a startup.
So, after a mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eulier Gonzalez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endpoint Security: Importance & 5 ways to help safeguard IT in the workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sndkcorp/endpoint-security-importance-5-ways-to-help-safeguard-it-in-the-workspace-imf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sndkcorp/endpoint-security-importance-5-ways-to-help-safeguard-it-in-the-workspace-imf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning and earning professionally is something that everyone wants, but what is completely another story, is job security. Ultimately, we all desire job security. We want to know that our job is safe and that we are valued by our management. It’s hard for the employees to perform their best if they have to stress or worry about the future of their job. It’s very important to understand the fact that everyone wants to feel safe and secure. People worry that they could be replaced by a new fresher hired out…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SNDK CORP</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to implement Builder Pattern in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-implement-builder-pattern-in-node-js-3nfb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-implement-builder-pattern-in-node-js-3nfb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/implement-builder-pattern-nodejs-example
How to implement Builder Pattern in Node.js
When we want to create complicated object which has multiple parts, we can use Builder Pattern that separates the building of these parts. This creational process does not care about how these parts are assembled.
In this tutorial, we're gonna look at 2 ways to implement Builder Pattern in Node.js:
using Builder function
using Builder class
Node.js Builder Pattern example using Builder function
Our Build…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordpress along with Rails app with Apache2 and Passenger]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/wordpress-along-with-rails-app-with-apache2-and-passenger-1egd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/wordpress-along-with-rails-app-with-apache2-and-passenger-1egd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordpress along with Rails app with Apache2 and Passenger



  
  
  Intro


This document helps to run Wordpress blog along with Rails app in a same server and make it available / accessible via Rails App. In this example we want to run a Rails app that accsesible via domain name www.dhanesh-example.com and also want to run a Wordpress instance that accessible via /blog.
user access the www.dhanesh-example.com or any paths (except /blog /api), it will refer to the Rails app
user access the www.dhanesh-eamp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Script to get the AWS EC2 Instance Details]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/python-script-to-get-the-aws-ec2-instance-details-3mc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/python-script-to-get-the-aws-ec2-instance-details-3mc9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Used python version 3.7 and Boto3, Kindly configure the AWS IAM Credentials in your local or workstation
AWS Profile Configuration
aws configure --profile name(my_proile)

import boto3
import sys
import time

session=boto3.Session(profile_name="my_profile", region_name="us-east-1") #boto3 session, aws profile 

ec2_resource=session.resource(service_name="ec2") # resource object method

'''
client object method, commented because this script using resource object method
ec2_client=session.client(service_name…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding an Archinstall Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eli_xciv/finding-an-archinstall-bug-43lg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eli_xciv/finding-an-archinstall-bug-43lg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had an older laptop that I've been neglecting to reinstall Arch Linux on, and I came across the new Arch Installer (archinstall). So I decided to try it out.
I used the ArchLinux liveCD (About 2-3 months old) and booted it up. Since my LiveCD was not a newer one, archinstall was not available at default. So I updated the repo's with pacman -Sy and lo-and-behold I could install it with pacman -S archinstall.
I ran archinstall guided to get a feel for it and I made it to the partitioning scheme. At which po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practise the Linux Basic Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/practise-the-linux-basic-commands-31i5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/practise-the-linux-basic-commands-31i5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unix Tools



  
  
  Bash Commands





uname -a                ## Get the Kernel Version
lsb_release -a          # Release or Distibution info
cat /etc/SuSE-release   # Suse Linux Version Check
cat /etc/debian_version # Debian Version check

uptime                  # it will shows how long the system has been running
hostname                # System Host Name
hostname -i             # To Display to the ip address of the Host, Linux based distribution
man hier                # File system hierarchy Descrip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practise the Linux Basic Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/practise-the-linux-basic-commands-31i5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/practise-the-linux-basic-commands-31i5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unix Tools



  
  
  Bash Commands





uname -a                ## Get the Kernel Version
lsb_release -a          # Release or Distibution info
cat /etc/SuSE-release   # Suse Linux Version Check
cat /etc/debian_version # Debian Version check

uptime                  # it will shows how long the system has been running
hostname                # System Host Name
hostname -i             # To Display to the ip address of the Host, Linux based distribution
man hier                # File system hierarchy Descrip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Driven Contract With Pact]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jjoc008/consumer-driven-contract-with-pact-3ioe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jjoc008/consumer-driven-contract-with-pact-3ioe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poc Consumer Driven Contract multi Language



  
  
  Contexto General Arquitecturas microservicio


En la Actualidad a menudo pensamos en microservicios a la hora de hacer nuevas implementaciones o desarrollos. Este tipo de arquitecturas tiene bastantes ventajas a comparacione de aplicaciones monoliticas, pero asi mismo tambien tiene varios problemas que si no sabemos manejarlos podrian ocasionar problemas importantes en la alta disponibilidad de los Microservicios

Mayor Informacion: https://youtu.be/VHV…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Orjuela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroku: Easily Deploy your Vue applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/heroku-easily-deploy-your-vue-applications-5fpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/heroku-easily-deploy-your-vue-applications-5fpn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T16:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📝 Preparation


For all the steps below, it is required that you have installed the HerokuCLI on your computer. It also assumes you have Node.js and npm already installed.
If you are running Homebrew on your Mac, you can simply run the following command:
brew tap heroku/brew && brew install heroku

If you are not using Homebrew, I would recommend installing it.
Installing Homebrew



🚫 If you prefer not to use Homebrew, please consult the official documentation for other options. (Link provided below)
Her…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dewald Els</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ծրագրային անվտանգություն՝ SQL Injection (մաս 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-1-lc0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-1-lc0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL injection֊ը հանդիսանում է վեբ֊ծրագրերի ամենատարածված խոցելիություններից (vulnerability) մեկը և գտնվում է OWASP հիմնադրամի 10 ամենատարածված խոցելիությունների ցանկի OWASP Top 10 առաջին հորիզոնականում։
Իրականում OWASP Top 10 ցանկի առաջին հորիզոնականում տեղ է գտել ավելի ընդհանրական Injection տեսակը, իսկ SQL injection֊ը դրա տեսակների մեկն է։
Փորձենք հասկանալ ինչու է առաջանում խոցելիության այս տեսակը, ինչ հնարավորություններ է ընձեռում հարձկավողին և պաշտպանության ինչ միջոցներ կան։
Օրինական ճանապարհով ծրագրային…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Narek Babajanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript - A Free 7-hour Interactive Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60a36742906c5207e3a7da6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-interactive-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last four months, I have recorded what is probably the most interactive JavaScript course that has ever been created. The reason I have done this is because I often see new coders fall into the same pitfalls again and again when trying to learn JavaScript, with the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's in a tech stack?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackmellis/what-s-in-a-tech-stack-3p76</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackmellis/what-s-in-a-tech-stack-3p76"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's in a tech stack? We always talk about MEAN, MERN, MEVN, LAMP, but honestly I've never understood the point of these acronyms.
I've been a dedicated front end engineer for 5 of my 8 years of professional development. So I've really only ever cared about one letter of these acronyms (and for LAMP I actually have zero investment). Do I care what language the backend is written in or what database we're using? I really don't! I'm using angular/react/vue/etc. and as long as I get a well formatted response…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding on Auth models]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shabash/deciding-on-auth-models-1ncl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shabash/deciding-on-auth-models-1ncl"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding on what authentication model to use has always been a daunting task. With all the different flows that are available in specifications like OAuth it has become more complicated for software engineers to choose an appropriate one.
OAuth talks about using 'Auth code with PKCE' (read PKCE as Pixie) when it comes to mobile applications. But this has always been a 'love it or hate it' kind of thing for me. This is primarily due to the fact that, as a business you want to use a login screen that is custo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahin Basheer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a serious(ish) project - intro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jackmellis/building-a-serious-ish-project-intro-1ke4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jackmellis/building-a-serious-ish-project-intro-1ke4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a developer for 8+ years now, working in all kinds of industries. Some full stack jobs, mostly front end jobs. I've created ~35 open source libraries over the years. I'm technically self-taught but I've also learnt a lot from some pretty smart people I've had the fortune to work with.
I've finally committed to building a full stack application, hopefully even a business, we'll see. I wanted to get some of my thoughts, ideas, and headaches written down as I go through this process. There are a lot …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Netlify Functions to Send Email Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/seancdavis/use-netlify-functions-to-send-email-notifications-25ae</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/seancdavis/use-netlify-functions-to-send-email-notifications-25ae"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Netlify supports email notifications around triggers and features within its system (e.g. deploy events, form submissions), you may want to add custom email notification triggered by actions from users on your site.
Notifications sound tricky, though, don't they?
Well, they don't have to be. We can use Netlify Functions, along with some email-sending service, to make that process a walk in the park.
To keep this example as simple as possible, we're going to use Nodemailer with Ethereal as our email se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean C Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev news and resources: AngularJs dev tools, machine learning glossary, exceptional GitHub repos and more.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deveconomics/dev-news-and-resources-angularjs-dev-tools-machine-learning-glossary-exceptional-github-repos-and-more-3on9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deveconomics/dev-news-and-resources-angularjs-dev-tools-machine-learning-glossary-exceptional-github-repos-and-more-3on9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey dev community, it's time to share the latest news and resources from our biweekly newsletter. Enjoy!
Why programmers should add journaling to their daily routine. See the benefits of tracking moods, goals, happiness and habits. [DEVTO]
AngularJS development tools for 2021. With the help of AngularJS development tools, you can easily create a platform to promote your business—from a simple interface to comparatively complex applications. The following are top trending AngularJS platforms that are growing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Developer Economics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get and Manage Shopping Cart Data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/natalia27070051/how-to-get-and-manage-shopping-cart-data-48bh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/natalia27070051/how-to-get-and-manage-shopping-cart-data-48bh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, the ability to access shopping cart data is becoming increasingly important for various types of eCommerce software. For example, solutions like WMS, ERP, order and inventory management, shipping management software need to manage shopping cart data to perform their key functions.
To grow your software business in 2021 and reach more online sellers, you need to learn how to get and manage shopping cart data. Below, we’ll show you how to do that using the power of eCommerce API integration, and we’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalia API2Cart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Graftini?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/graftini/what-is-graftini-3fp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/graftini/what-is-graftini-3fp0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, if we have to do a task, we try to do it in the most efficient way that we know of. Sometimes that means to do it manually. And, if we need to do it again, we oblige. But if we have to do the same repeatedly, the process soon becomes inefficient. And when that time comes, we find a way to automate it.
In our experience, working with clients and having to develop web apps for their specific problems has allowed us to explore new ways of solving them. Even in seemingly unique problems, we began…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharad Chand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Cognitive Security Market Analysis by Growth Strategies and Forecast to 2027 | Market Research Future]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pranali004/global-cognitive-security-market-analysis-by-growth-strategies-and-forecast-to-2027-market-research-future-2l7g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pranali004/global-cognitive-security-market-analysis-by-growth-strategies-and-forecast-to-2027-market-research-future-2l7g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Market Scenario:
COVID-19 Analysis:
Request a Free Sample @ https://www.marketresearchfuture.com/sample_request/3986 
Segmentation:
Regional Analysis:

The fastest expansion rate can be procured by the APAC market, since more and more enterprises are spending massively on research and development with regard to cognitive security. The expanding IT landscape along with the escalating uptake of internet of things, bring your own device and artificial intelligence technologies by enterprises can also induce ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pranali004</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Node.js app with GraphQL and REST API from Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuvalhazaz/turn-excel-into-code-in-seconds-generate-node-js-app-with-apis-auth-db-docker-and-more-from-an-excel-file-3oco</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuvalhazaz/turn-excel-into-code-in-seconds-generate-node-js-app-with-apis-auth-db-docker-and-more-from-an-excel-file-3oco"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with small businesses over the years, I saw a lot of them working and managing critical business processes using Excel files that start small but quickly grow out of proportion. 
On many occasions, I was asked to build a full-scale app to replace the Excel file once it becomes too risky for the business to keep relying on a spreadsheet.
Like with every project, you have to go through several steps to produce a reliable service:
Design the data model based on the excel file.


Building the infrastruc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuval Hazaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Node.js app with GraphQL and REST API from Excel]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuvalhazaz/turn-excel-into-code-in-seconds-generate-node-js-app-with-apis-auth-db-docker-and-more-from-an-excel-file-3oco</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuvalhazaz/turn-excel-into-code-in-seconds-generate-node-js-app-with-apis-auth-db-docker-and-more-from-an-excel-file-3oco"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with small businesses over the years, I saw a lot of them working and managing critical business processes using Excel files that start small but quickly grow out of proportion. 
On many occasions, I was asked to build a full-scale app to replace the Excel file once it becomes too risky for the business to keep relying on a spreadsheet.
Like with every project, you have to go through several steps to produce a reliable service:
Design the data model based on the excel file.


Building the infrastruc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuval Hazaz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting a .travis.yml file for a react app test]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohithv07/setting-a-travis-yml-file-for-a-react-app-test-27o9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohithv07/setting-a-travis-yml-file-for-a-react-app-test-27o9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Travis Yaml Configuration



First we will tell the Travis we need a copy of docker running.
Now, we need to build the image based on the Dockerfile.dev which is the Dockerfile used for development purpose.
Next we write some script which guides Travis how to run our test suite.
If we are hosting our code to AWS, we also tell Travis to do so (which I do not cover now)




language: generic

# required super user access
sudo: required

# services thhat are required
services: 
  - docker

# series of steps ra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohith V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como debuggar o NodeJS no Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rafaelvieirab/como-debuggar-o-nodejs-no-visual-studio-code-3no4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rafaelvieirab/como-debuggar-o-nodejs-no-visual-studio-code-3no4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incontáveis vezes ocorrem erros inesperados, e precisamos analisar o fluxo da nossa aplicação. Uma forma bem mais eficiente que os famosos "console.log('Até aqui deu certo')", é depurando a aplicação.
Primeiramente acesse a perspectiva de Debug, clicando no menu lateral esquerdo de Debug (caracterizada pela formato de inseto). Depois, clicando em "Add Configurations", irá aparecer um arquivo .vscode/launch.json. 

Porém, somente com esse arquivo criado, não conseguimos depurar a aplicação da forma que quere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rafaelvieirab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Nuxt.js used for?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/what-is-nuxt-js-used-for-2anm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/what-is-nuxt-js-used-for-2anm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons to consider Nuxt for your project:
Create universal applications quite easily
The positive aspect regarding Nuxt JS is the fact that developers can build universal applications quite easily. The majority of the individuals are not acquainted with universal applications, especially beginners.
So, what do you mean by a universal app?
The universal app describes the JavaScript code that will be able to execute on the server-side and the client-side. You will come across lots of contemporary JavaScript …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Resources with AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikhilzadoo/custom-resources-with-aws-cdk-56l5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikhilzadoo/custom-resources-with-aws-cdk-56l5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prerequisite



Understanding of AWS CDK (Cloud development kit)
Understanding of AWS Custom resources
CDK provides a library for conveniently writing custom resources.
As a custom resource author, you can focus on the actual logic for the custom resource and let CDK take care of other boilerplate stuff. Eg- you do not need to worry about sending the response back to the pre-signed S3 URL. Just return PhysicalResourceId using the return statement and you are good to go. Consequently it also makes your code …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Zadoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Angular 12- Update and features]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codedthemes/what-s-new-in-angular-12-update-and-features-3751</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codedthemes/what-s-new-in-angular-12-update-and-features-3751"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released the popular Angular web framework in September 2016 under the MIT License. Angular is a typescript-based open-source web app framework and is a part of the popular MEAN stack.
The Angular community comes up with a major release every six months and on 12th May 2021. The long-term support LTS for Angular 11 will end within a year. And until then it will be active for critical fixes and security patches.
In this article, we will discuss what’s included in version 12 of Angular unveiling the ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CodedThemes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Angular 12- Update and features]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codedthemes/what-s-new-in-angular-12-update-and-features-3751</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codedthemes/what-s-new-in-angular-12-update-and-features-3751"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google released the popular Angular web framework in September 2016 under the MIT License. Angular is a typescript-based open-source web app framework and is a part of the popular MEAN stack.
The Angular community comes up with a major release every six months and on 12th May 2021. The long-term support LTS for Angular 11 will end within a year. And until then it will be active for critical fixes and security patches.
In this article, we will discuss what’s included in version 12 of Angular unveiling the ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CodedThemes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case of the Missing Szechuan Sauce: investigation notes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/christalib/the-case-of-the-missing-szechuan-sauce-investigation-notes-1di7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/christalib/the-case-of-the-missing-szechuan-sauce-investigation-notes-1di7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to solve the challenge of the Case of the Missing Szechuan Sauce proposed by DFIRMadness . This is a Digital Forensic and Incident Response (DFIR) challenge where we will have to investigate the memory and the traces left by an infection on a server and a endpoint computer.
Beyond tools and technical issues, the biggest challenge is the method. Indeed, being able to navigate the large amount of data that we have was the biggest difficulty.
So for that, we started from the netwo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to test React Hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/le_humch/how-to-test-react-hooks-37n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/le_humch/how-to-test-react-hooks-37n6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you use hooks, you can write them in their own file. And you could test them.
Tests are not the answer, but they protect your code from changes, they help to find bugs.
If you have a display component with all the logic in a custom hook, it would be a better idea to test the custom hook.
If you have all specs but you doesn't know how to design it, may be a good time to use TDD.
In short, saying  : "I don't know how to solve that" and stash it, it's a bad habit for a developer (and others people too).
W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabien Schlegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do my Webpack imports not resolve in CI?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wireless25/why-do-my-webpack-imports-not-resolve-in-ci-3de1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wireless25/why-do-my-webpack-imports-not-resolve-in-ci-3de1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your application is building locally perfectly fine, but in CI, imports are not resolving? I maybe have a hint for you.
Let me lay out the issue I had a little bit more. We build web applications with VueJS. We use Webpack to bundle and optimize the JavaScript code. Imagine the following folder structure:
|-resources
  |-js
    |-Components
      |-TheNavigation
        |-Index.vue
        |-NavLink.vue
      |-TheFooter
        |-Index.vue
    |-Layouts
      |-Default.vue

In the Webpack config, we set an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Simonett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for Reviewers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/royluis/looking-for-reviewers-3jif</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/royluis/looking-for-reviewers-3jif"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have published a book 
The TypeScript Workshop

C++ Workshop
We are giving a chance to read and review the book. If interested drop me a mail on royluisr@packt.com or send me a request on https://www.linkedin.com/in/royluis-rodrigues-66479123/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>royluis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Terraform and AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ncribt/get-started-with-terraform-and-aws-468l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ncribt/get-started-with-terraform-and-aws-468l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T09:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is an open-source "infrastructure-as-code" software. Infrastructure-as-code means that instead of using an interface or a CLI (command-line-interface) to configure your infrastructure on a cloud platform such as AWS (Amazon Web Services), you can describe your infrastructure with code then let Terraform do its magic.
AWS provides their own solution for infrastructure-as-code, it is called CloudFormation. They also have a "simplified" one called SAM (Serverless Application Model) to build a serverl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setup Github Actions Angular project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fsystem/setup-github-actions-angular-project-4kn6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fsystem/setup-github-actions-angular-project-4kn6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T08:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I discover this great ci tool for your Github projects, this is easy way to add ci in your projects, and for example validate your pull request before merge.
Here, I am going to put my scripts of my package.json for ci, this is only an example you need to put your own scripts:
    "test:ci": "ng test --browsers ChromeHeadless --code-coverage --watch=false",
    "sass-lint": "sass-lint -v -c ./sass-lint.yml",
    "format:fix": "pretty-quick --staged",
    "lint": "eslint \"**/*.{ts,tsx}\" --quiet --fix",…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Facundo Ezequiel Diaz Cappella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone, a Spy in your Pocket]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shostarsson/smartphone-a-spy-in-your-pocket-mac</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shostarsson/smartphone-a-spy-in-your-pocket-mac"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T08:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've seen the latest episode of Envoyé Spécial (french TV).
Especially about one story about our phones and the numerous data shared through them that are sold, shared and used, most often without our consent.
In my last video, I go over all the data that are shared through our phones.




Understanding the amount of data shared and try to limit it is a good starting point.
But also understanding what data hackers might be trying to get on my phone is important.
And finally, that everyone understands that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rémi Lavedrine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A quoi servent les peerDependencies dans le package.json ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/younup/a-quoi-servent-les-peerdependencies-dans-le-package-json-3g29</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/younup/a-quoi-servent-les-peerdependencies-dans-le-package-json-3g29"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T07:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lors d'une installation npm ou bien de la lecture d'un package.json, vous avez sans doute remarqué qu'il y avait deux grands groupes de dépendances : les dependencies et les devDependencies.
Le premier représente les dépendances directs de votre projet (ce dont on a besoin pour que cela fonctionne).
Le second représente ce qui entoure votre projet dans sa phase de développement (les outils qui vont permettre à celui-ci de fonctionner/builder/deployer par exemple).
Il existe un troisième groupe à ne pas négl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin🦸‍♂️Auzanneau™</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Settings linter in Angular 12]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fsystem/settings-linter-in-angular-12-2mon</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fsystem/settings-linter-in-angular-12-2mon"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T07:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new version of Angular 12 not include linters because TSLint is deprecated.
For that I'm going to put here how to add eslint in Angular 12.
Prerequisites:
Node js -> 12.13.x/14.15.x or later minor
npm
angular/cli -> v12
First step:
 // create project
 ng new my-new-project

Second step:
 // install eslint as dev dependency 
 npm install --save-dev eslint
// install ts rules plugin
npm i --save-dev @typescript-eslint/eslint-plugin 
// install eslint parser
npm i --save-dev @typescript-eslint/parser

The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Facundo Ezequiel Diaz Cappella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customise Your Terminal Using Zsh & powerlevel10k]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pratik_kale/customise-your-terminal-using-zsh-powerlevel10k-1og5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pratik_kale/customise-your-terminal-using-zsh-powerlevel10k-1og5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transform your terminal from this to this !!



  
  
  Before


 

ZSH, also called the Z shell, is an extended version of the Bourne Shell (sh), with plenty of new features, and support for plugins and themes. 
Powerlevel10k is a theme for Zsh. It emphasizes speed, flexibility and out-of-the-box experience.
This package provides syntax highlighting for the shell zsh. It enables highlighting of commands whilst they are typed at a zsh prompt into an interactive terminal. This helps in reviewing commands bef…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pratik Kale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I have deployed my facebook clone on heroku and netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harshmangalam/i-have-deployed-my-facebook-clone-on-heroku-and-netlify-2a15</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harshmangalam/i-have-deployed-my-facebook-clone-on-heroku-and-netlify-2a15"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T05:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Community If you are reading this post definitely you had seen my previous post where i have shown my facebook clone project




  
    
I have created Facebook clone in MERN stack
Harsh Mangalam ・ May 14 ・ 1 min read
#showdev
        #react
        #node
        #socketio
      
I have deployed Nodejs and Mongodb backend on heroku and mongodb cloud.
Media related to post image and profile image has deployed on firebase.



Visit Demo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Mangalam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EC2 Recovery Made Easy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muckitymuck/ec2-recovery-made-easy-21n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muckitymuck/ec2-recovery-made-easy-21n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T04:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It Happens.  You lost the keys, the networking broke, or you inherited a box that already had one of these two things happen.  In any case, the EC2 instance you are looking at is not reachable by normal means.  You are locked out.  If you don't have already have a recovery plan in place for this you have to move to extreme measures.

Fortunately, there are a couple of tricks in AWS to recover the data or even fix the login issues without starting from scratch.  For Linux veterans this will be painfully simp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>muckitymuck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Core Apps on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobrundle/net-core-apps-on-linux-1a0d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobrundle/net-core-apps-on-linux-1a0d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T02:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great benefits in working with .NET Core is knowing that your code will be cross platform.  In particular it will run on Linux.  This opens up a lot of possibilities.  But does it really run on Linux if you have never seen it run?  But even if you have seen it run, is it really working if you have never run the unit tests on Linux? In my way of looking at the world…no.
So in this post I will lay out how to get your cross platform .NET Core apps running and tested on Linux in the most straightforw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Rundle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Redux pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jucian0/implementing-redux-pattern-1oj0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jucian0/implementing-redux-pattern-1oj0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T02:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a software developer and aren't in another world, you have probably read or heard something about Redux. Today Redux is very popular, but not as much as some years ago. The first time that I heard about React, the second word was always Redux, "How to init with react and redux", "Todo app with react redux", and another hundred names. Even though Redux is not as popular today as in the past, I think it's very helpful that you know how Redux works and how you can create a simple version of this fam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jucian0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como implementar Type guards no seu código]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/samuelmpinho/como-implementar-type-guards-no-seu-codigo-2040</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/samuelmpinho/como-implementar-type-guards-no-seu-codigo-2040"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T00:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine que você tem a seguinte situação:
Você tem uma aplicação que busca por músicas no Spotify e nessa aplicação você mostra o email do usuário logado e a música que ele está escutando naquele momento.
Você então cria 2 funções para acessar a API do Spotify
getUser para chamar a API que irá buscar os dados do usuário
getSong que irá retornar uma lista de músicas do Spotify
Então você teria o seguinte código:
type APIResponse<T> = {
  data: T;
  error: Error;
}

type User = {
  email: string;
}

type Song…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors to Style Your Web Page]]></title>
        <id>60a341f5906c5207e3a7da61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-css-selectors-to-style-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors are one of the most important parts of CSS. They give you the ability to target HTML elements on your web page that you want to style. Without CSS selectors, you wouldn't be able to style your page to look how you want. Thankfully CSS selectors have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular directives: Interesting ways to use it.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dwale/angular-directives-interesting-ways-to-use-it-1k4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dwale/angular-directives-interesting-ways-to-use-it-1k4b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will be using the angular directive to create a reusable custom user validation field. A typical use case will be an account lookup field or any user validation field.

I'll be using a bank account validation feature for this document. I came about this idea due to my experience in the fintech industry, where I've had to implement this across various applications, this will allow you to keep your code DRY and it also looks cool 😉.
<input type="text" [appAccountLookup] = "bankInformationForm.va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahman Adewale Hafeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular directives: Interesting ways to use it.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dwale/angular-directives-interesting-ways-to-use-it-1k4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dwale/angular-directives-interesting-ways-to-use-it-1k4b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will be using the angular directive to create a reusable custom user validation field. A typical use case will be an account lookup field or any user validation field.

I'll be using a bank account validation feature for this document. I came about this idea due to my experience in the fintech industry, where I've had to implement this across various applications, this will allow you to keep your code DRY and it also looks cool 😉.
<input type="text" [appAccountLookup] = "bankInformationForm.va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahman Adewale Hafeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Pass Component via @Input() | HOC | Dynamic Wrapper]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sincovschi/angular-pass-component-via-input-hoc-dynamic-wrapper-48jo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sincovschi/angular-pass-component-via-input-hoc-dynamic-wrapper-48jo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intro


I was working with React Projects for a long time. I have evolved a mindset that allows you to abuse HOC to make code more reusable and somewhat clean. But when I got into Angular, it felt weird at first that there is no such concept.
At some point, I got in touch with Modals and there it was the gong that awoke the ninja in me. First, I dove again into angular.io docs and indeed found a way to pass components through @Input() and render them. But that was unsatisfying because of the decorator. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web3? The Decentralized Internet of the Future Explained]]></title>
        <id>60a42386906c5207e3a7dfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is going through a paradigm shift. Learn the differences between Web2 and Web3, and why many developers and companies are shifting their approach in building apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanted: Code reviewers for my first node project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cb80/wanted-code-reviewers-for-my-first-node-project-3jk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cb80/wanted-code-reviewers-for-my-first-node-project-3jk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear fellows, I was searching for a GitHub action to publish releases including assets. Despite the sheer mass of actions out there I failed to find the right one. What I found did either not support GitHub enterprise, or it failed to replace an existing release, or it could not upload assets, or it published the release before uploading the assets, or, or, or. Eventually I wrote an action on my own which turned out to be my first node project using typescript. I am curious what you think. Please tell me wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Burkert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically protect your supply chain from dependency confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sumstrm/automatically-protect-your-supply-chain-from-dependency-confusion-2n35</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sumstrm/automatically-protect-your-supply-chain-from-dependency-confusion-2n35"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T19:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency confusion occurs when a system or user is tricked into fetching a package version from a public registry, instead of the intended trusted package with the same namespace from your private registry.
Like other supply chain attacks it’s all about injecting non-intended packages into a vulnerable supply chain, where malicious code can be executed on installation. A critical security threat for your supply chain if left uncontrolled. And a problem that potentially gets even worse in automated environ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Sommarström</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Typescript to create a Robust API between your frontend and backend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/grouparoo/using-typescript-to-create-a-robust-api-between-your-frontend-and-backend-2f3i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/grouparoo/using-typescript-to-create-a-robust-api-between-your-frontend-and-backend-2f3i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two of the major components of the @grouparoo/core application are a Node.js API server and a React frontend. We use Actionhero as the API server, and Next.JS for our React site generator. As we develop the Grouparoo application, we are constantly adding new API endpoints and changing existing ones.
One of the great features of Typescript is that it can help not only to share type definitions within a codebase, but also across multiple codebases or services. We share the Typescript types of our API response…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Tahler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explore Fullstack modern tools]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harshmangalam/explore-fullstack-modern-tools-51bf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harshmangalam/explore-fullstack-modern-tools-51bf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No doubt javascript is booming the world of software industry . From frontend to backend every where javascript is getting its position.



In this blog post i will share you some  library and framework that i am using for my projects
A JavaScript library for building user interfaces.
React components for faster and easier web development.Material UI is based on google material design specification and provide a lot of ui components.
Next.js gives you the best developer experience with all the features you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Mangalam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSL for Rails developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hint/wsl-for-rails-developers-2a3g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hint/wsl-for-rails-developers-2a3g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is now possible, thankfully, to develop in Rails on Windows. For many years, it seemed one needed a Mac for this purpose; and I have nothing against Macs, and enjoy the MacBook Pro, which I have used throughout my career. But I also have a Windows machine. I like to play games sometimes, and now that I work from home, along with an increasing number of people, I have access to it. I like the idea that developers should be able to enjoy their preference in environment, where reasonable. Some prefer to boo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Hayhurst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize for Change in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>60a469ec906c5207e3a7e1b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-for-change-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you work at Magic Money Corp, which runs on just three lines of JavaScript: let input = { step1: 'collect underpants' } doStuff(input)  profit(input) // $$$!!! Now imagine that something's wrong with doStuff and you need to take it down for maintenance. What happens if you temporarily comment out the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React, Tailwind and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kevin_odongo35/react-tailwind-and-typescript-35hk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kevin_odongo35/react-tailwind-and-typescript-35hk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Dev's
Hope you enjoyed the TypeScript tutorial. Transitioning for the client project was quite a learning process. We have to evolve and allow ourselves enjoy the process of learning different technologies. Next.js and React are similar in many ways just like Nuxt and Vue.
In this tutorial we are going to learn the following:
How to setup a React and TypeScript project
How to add Tailwind to a React application
How to add Cypress e2e Testing to your application
How to configure basic routing.
To get sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Odongo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SpringBoot CRUD MariaDB Example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-mariadb-example-48jb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-mariadb-example-48jb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://loizenai.com/angular-springboot-mariadb-crud/
Tutorial: "Angular SpringBoot CRUD MariaDB Example"
In the tutorial, I introduce how to create an "SpringBoot Angular MariaDB CRUD Example" with POST/GET/PUT/DELETE requests to SpringBoot RestAPIs.
Design overview system by Architecture Diagram that includes: Angular Client, SpringBoot RestAPIs, and MariaDB database.
Implement Angular CRUD Client with Angular built-in HttpClient to communicate with server side.
Implement SpringBoot RestAPIs that gets dat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes Reminder - @Azure Data Factory Security with @narainabhishek - 5/20/2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azure/azurefunbytes-reminder-azure-data-factory-security-with-narainabhishek-5-20-2021-37b5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azure/azurefunbytes-reminder-azure-data-factory-security-with-narainabhishek-5-20-2021-37b5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AzureFunBytes is a weekly opportunity to learn more about the fundamentals and foundations that make up Azure. It's a chance for me to understand more about what people across the Azure organization do and how they do it. Every week we get together at 11 AM Pacific on Microsoft LearnTV and learn more about Azure.

This is part two of our series on Azure Data Factory.  Last time Mark helped get us on the road to understanding how to best get our data into the cloud by using the linked services and tools with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To View And Configure Apache Access & Error Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/betteruptime/how-to-view-and-configure-apache-access-error-logs-4fbl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/betteruptime/how-to-view-and-configure-apache-access-error-logs-4fbl"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this tutorial, you will learn everything you need to know about Apache logging to help you troubleshoot and quickly resolve any problem you may encounter on your server. Logging is a very powerful tool that will give you valuable data about all the operations of your servers. You will learn where logs are stored, how to access them, and how to customize log output to fit your needs.
Apache web server.
Apache writes logs of its events in two different log files.
Access Log - In this file, A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Better Uptime</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ever worked on a project like Wix or Godaddy Site Builder?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/youngquarshie/ever-worked-on-a-project-like-wix-or-godaddy-site-builder-2jjl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/youngquarshie/ever-worked-on-a-project-like-wix-or-godaddy-site-builder-2jjl"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to build a project like that with Angular and Laravel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Quarshie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Vim as a Python IDE]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/use-vim-as-a-python-ide-31e6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/use-vim-as-a-python-ide-31e6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is an awesome text editor that can be used as a Python IDE. For those who use Vim and want to program in Python, here are a few tips on how to do it easily.
Vim is a highly extensible text editor. By adding plugins to your .vimrc and installing other packages, you can tailor Vim to your liking.
I've been using Vim as my primary text editor for several years and I really love it. It has an excellent interface for navigating and editing text, and I've never been able to find a better one.
If you are new t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💳 What Is Credential Stuffing? How To Prevent Credential Stuffing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/what-is-credential-stuffing-how-to-prevent-credential-stuffing-attacks-2e81</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/what-is-credential-stuffing-how-to-prevent-credential-stuffing-attacks-2e81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💻 Credential stuffing is one of the most common types of cyberattacks. Here’s how to prevent credential stuffing.



  
  
  
Credential stuffing is a type of cyberattack in which a cybercriminal uses stolen usernames and passwords from one organization (obtained in a breach or purchased off of the dark web) to access user accounts at another organization.
Credential stuffing attacks are one of the most common causes of data breaches because 65% of all people reuse the same password on multiple (and someti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do we need mega-dropdown hover menus in 2021? Probably not. Let’s explore things to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, alternatives to hover menus and fine details for designing a better UX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 6 HttpClient + Spring Boot + MariaDB example | Spring Data JPA + RestAPIs CRUD example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-6-httpclient-spring-boot-mariadb-example-spring-data-jpa-restapis-crud-example-25n0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-6-httpclient-spring-boot-mariadb-example-spring-data-jpa-restapis-crud-example-25n0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T10:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/frontend/angular/angular-6/angular-6-httpclient-spring-boot-mariadb-example-spring-data-jpa-restapis-crud-example
Angular 6 HttpClient + Spring Boot + MariaDB example | Spring Data JPA + RestAPIs CRUD example
In this tutorial, we show you Angular 6 Http Client & Spring Boot Server example that uses Spring JPA to do CRUD with MariaDB and Angular 6 as a front-end technology to make request and receive response.
Related Posts:
Spring Boot + Angular 6 example | Spring Data JPA + REST + MySQ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the Ways to Prevent an Organization from Phishing Attacks?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhhaavikpatel/what-are-the-ways-to-prevent-an-organization-from-phishing-attacks-2a7c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhhaavikpatel/what-are-the-ways-to-prevent-an-organization-from-phishing-attacks-2a7c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T08:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your company might be at risk of compromising valuable data to unknown sources online. The sad part is, you might not even know about it. There are plenty of websites claiming to give you the right anti-phishing solutions for your company. But not all of them are reliable. We are here to provide you with the latest prevention measures to stop phishing attacks for your organization.  
Before we move into how you can fix the problem, let’s first understand what phishing is and why it’s challenging to combat? …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BHHAAVIK Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break into Ethereum, Crypto, and Web3 as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60a53182906c5207e3a7e588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breaking-into-ethereum-crypto-web3-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I've been talking about my move into the Web3, Ethereum, and crypto space since making the switch from a traditional web, mobile, and cloud background. Since making that move, a shocking number of people have reached out to me who are also thinking about doing the same.  It's really]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🛠 Build and Secure a Laravel API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/build-and-secure-a-laravel-api-5793</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/build-and-secure-a-laravel-api-5793"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📕 In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a simple Laravel API and add authorization to it using Auth0. You can find the final code in this GitHub repository.



  
  
  
In this tutorial, you'll learn how to create a simple Laravel API and add authorization to it using Auth0. You can find the final code in this GitHub repository.
👋 If you already have a Laravel API that you want to secure, you can go ahead and skip to the "Secure your Laravel API" section.
This tutorial uses the latest version of La…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Development Pricing Guide – Should Freelancers Bill by the Hour?]]></title>
        <id>60a3780f906c5207e3a7db5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you offer your services as a freelance developer, you have a major say in how you price your project.  But how do you go about charging for a website project? "Well, I just bill by the hour and send an invoice every week or month." ...I hear you say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Programs – 101 Ways to Learn to Code for Free]]></title>
        <id>6068f146d5756f080ba9402d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/coding-programs-101-ways-to-learn-to-code-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, you can learn to code for free, from the convenience of your own home, and at your own pace. I'm going to show you 101 courses where you can learn computer science and programming for free.  The freeCodeCamp courses are completely free and some of them include a free]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Neon Text With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-neon-text-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon text can add a nice, futuristic touch to any website. I’ve always loved the magic of neon signs, and wanted to recreate them using CSS. I thought I’d share some tips on how to do it! In this article, …
The post How to Create Neon Text With CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia O'Dwyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340716</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Addy Osmani on images in HTML:
The humble <img> element has gained some superpowers over the years. Given how central it is to image optimization on the web, let’s catch up on what it can do and how it can 
…
The post The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Love Letter to HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339522</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-love-letter-to-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see you. In the back there, behind JavaScript and React and PHP and all those “real” programming languages, I see you. And I appreciate you.
The post A Love Letter to HTML & CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Kolodziej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euismod]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340594</id>
        <link href="https://www.euismod.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interactive tool for learning grid syntax from Etesam Ansari. In the Learn section, it teaches you some concepts (involving multiple bits of the grid syntax) then gives you a task to complete by filling out the right syntax. I’m …
The post Euismod appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-stylesheet-feature-flags-with-sass-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[!default is a Sass flag that indicates conditional assignment to a variable — it assigns a value only if the variable was previously undefined or null. Consider this code snippet:
$variable: 'test' !default;
To the Sass compiler, this line …
The post Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Babcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Boilerplates]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340403</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-boilerplates/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzović goes line-by-line through a boilerplate HTML document. I like it. It’s a good reference and has a lot of the same type of stuff I tend to put in the main HTML template. It makes me think about …
The post HTML Boilerplates appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340490</id>
        <link href="https://chenhuijing.com/blog/devtools-for-css-layouts-2021-edition/#%F0%9F%9A%B2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Hui Jing covers some recent movement in DevTools:
Firefox’s grid inspector was pretty full-featured from the get-to and released together with CSS grid in Firefox 52. It was constantly improved upon since. Chrome added a basic grid inspector 
…
The post DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>