<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-25T00:57:24.668Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-25T00:57:24.668Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to calculate confidence interval using R.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxwizard01/how-to-calculate-confidence-interval-using-r-e6g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxwizard01/how-to-calculate-confidence-interval-using-r-e6g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to calculate confidence interval of a proportion using R.


confidence interval of a proportion is now one of the important aspect of statistics use in everyday life in fact almost all big company make use of it especially those companies with artificial intelligent and tech. 
What is the critical value if n = 100 and confidence interval is 99%?
2.58
Out 1500 students in Idia hostel, 1000 are allergic to Zikites so often avoid Zik hall route. Half of the remaining proportion wouldn't use Indy route as well. Obtain 95% confidence interval of the true population proportion of students who would use Zik route?
[0.3095, 0.3572]
In the last revision class, 0.7 actively participated. What is the standard error if the population of students in attendance was 2500?
No answer
If we use a ______…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maxwizard01</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular meetup videos from May, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-may-2021-28bb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/meetupfeedio/angular-meetup-videos-from-may-2021-28bb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T23:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another month’s gone, another Angular roundup post is here! This time we’ve selected a top 3 video list from some of the most important figures from the Angular community. John Papa, Minko Gechev and Mark Thompson are all featured, covering great topics like the latest changes to the framework, libraries in Angular 12 and using Angular CLI to build new applications.
What’s new in Angular | John Papa
Join Pluralsight author and JS expert John Papa to explore the latest changes to the framework, tooling and developer experience.
State of the Angular | Libraries in Angular 12
Minko Gechev talked about the latest State of the Angular for 30 minutes, and then Joost Koehoorn held a presentation about the libraries in Angular 12, followed by a Q/A session.
Angular CLI | Mark Thompson
In this video Angular team member Mark Thompson will be taking you on a journey with the Angular CLI to build a new application in Angular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MeetupFeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate an SSL Certificate With the Root Certificate for localhost]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pranjaljain0/generate-an-ssl-certificate-with-the-root-certificate-for-localhost-18je</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pranjaljain0/generate-an-ssl-certificate-with-the-root-certificate-for-localhost-18je"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The root certificate is trusted now. Let’s issue an SSL certificate to support our local domains — myexample.com, sub.myexample.com, myexample1.com, and localhost for testing.
Create a new OpenSSL configuration file server.csr.cnf so the configurations details can be used while generating the certificate.
[req]
default_bits = 2048
prompt = no
default_md = sha256
distinguished_name = dn

[dn]
C=IN
ST=MP
L=INDORE
O=Tech Forum
OU=Marketing
emailAddress=admin@pranjaljain.me
CN = localhost

Create a v3.ext file with a list of local SAN domains:
authorityKeyIdentifier=keyid,issuer
basicConstraints=CA:FALSE
keyUsage = digitalSignature, nonRepudiation, keyEncipherment, dataEncipherment
subjectAltName = @alt_names
[alt_names]
DNS.1 = localhost

Create a private key and certificate-signing request (CSR) for the localhost certificate.
openssl req -new -sha256 -nodes -out server.csr -newkey rsa:2048 -keyout server.key -config server.csr.cnf

This private key is stored on server.key.
openssl x509 -req -in server.csr -CA rootCA.pem -CAkey rootCA.key -CAcreateserial -out server.crt -days 500 -sha256 -extfile v3.ext

When it says Enter passphrase for rootCA.key, enter the passphrase used while generating the root key.
server.crt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best React UI Component Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mvmilanjain/best-react-ui-component-libraries-25ah</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mvmilanjain/best-react-ui-component-libraries-25ah"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T19:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Material UI


Material UI is a set of react components built based on the Material Design guidelines of Google.
Material UI consists of many accessible and configurable UI widgets.
The components are self-supporting and only inject the styles they need to display, which could lead to performance enhancements in your application.
Material UI has an active set of maintainers and a strong community behind it. It currently has over 69k stars on GitHub, making it one of the most popular component libraries out there.
If you’re looking to build a beautiful, consistent, and light interface quickly without sacrificing accessibility and performance, the material design will help you achieve that.
Chakra UI is a simple, modular and accessible component library that gives you the building blocks you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Milan Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for Mozilla VPN research participants]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heaversm/looking-for-mozilla-vpn-research-participants-bhn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heaversm/looking-for-mozilla-vpn-research-participants-bhn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T18:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Mozilla, we are looking to better understand our customers’ experiences with Mozilla VPN, to learn what could improve the product or the service for them. Specifically we are looking for people who:
• Have used Mozilla VPN
Participants are asked to take part in a 1-hour interview, scheduled sometime between July 7–14, 2021. As a thank you for your time and feedback, you will receive a $75 Amazon gift card. 
If you are interested in participating, please fill out this 5-minute survey and we will reach out to those who qualify with more details. Thank you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Heavers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mis Temas Preferidos | VSCode]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrluisfer/mis-temas-preferidos-vscode-41j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrluisfer/mis-temas-preferidos-vscode-41j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seguramente nosotr@s como developers que pasamos mucho tiempo delante de la computadora haciendo código y desarrollando nuestras aplicaciones queremos cuidar nuestros ojos.
Para eso es que generalmente se utilizan temas de modo oscuro los cuales hacen que pasar mucho tiempo frente a una pantalla y tener menos impacto negativo para nuestra vista.
Y como muchos devs también queremos que nuestro editor VSCode sea lo mas personalizable posible para nuestro gusto, es por eso que quise hacer esta lista con los temas que a mi opinión son muy atractivos a la vista.
Antes de mostrarte los temas quiero mostrarte como puedes cambiar los temas y ver los que ya tengas instalados o por defecto en tu VSCode
Con la combinación de teclas Ctrl + K  Ctrl + T y te mostrara los Color Themes disponibles, puedes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Alvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HRF Asylum- Notification and Form Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/randyo28/hrf-asylum-the-final-stretch-2dca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/randyo28/hrf-asylum-the-final-stretch-2dca"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The First Week


As my time at Lambda School is coming to an end I wanted to talk about my incredible  experience from this past month.  It was the day after Memorial Day and a cohort of developers had to fill out a form to be placed in a Lambda School lab project. Forms were submitted and the wait came to be placed in teams. The notification came in and I was placed in HRF Asylum  where I’ll be working with two teams of developers and data scientists that consisted of over 15 other students. It was the beginning of a memorable experience that had transitioned everyone of us from removing aspiring developers from our vocabulary.
The project that we worked on is for a non for profit organization called HRF (Human Rights First) that has served over three decades in protecting human rights of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Ortiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10+ Must-Have Healthcare Website Features [2021]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/priteshbhoi/10-must-have-healthcare-website-features-2021-cma</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/priteshbhoi/10-must-have-healthcare-website-features-2021-cma"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Health website features may vary, but the desired result for all of them is the same. They exist to make life easier for hospital and clinic patients so that they can keep track of their test results, pay their bills, and so much more. Doctors find them to be equally useful.
Health website features keep getting better and better, and healthcare app trends are a point of focus for any healthcare provider.
You may like 👉 https://bit.ly/3vRZ2ZB
If your practice employs several doctors, a directory is a helpful tool to have on your website. Prospective patients will feel more comfortable going into your practice knowing more about their doctor than just their name. You can include information such as where they went to school, specialties, and a short bio alongside a photograph.
First and for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pritesh Bhoi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common React Mistakes You Might Be Making – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>60d3ee396e1a1407b6b0b6ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-react-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go over the most common mistakes you might be making in your React code right now, plus how to fix them. If you want to create amazing React applications, it's essential to avoid many common errors along the way. In this article, we'll not only cover how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Routes in Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tirthaguha/routes-in-express-5gmp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tirthaguha/routes-in-express-5gmp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all started with a piece of code that I saw while reviewing an express based application. 
express-generator.
var express = require('express');
var router = express.Router();
const authorizationMiddleware = require("../authorizationMiddleware")
const payloadValidationMiddleware = require("../payloadValidationMiddleware")
const createAction = require("createAction")
const serviceRequest = require("serviceRequest")

/* POST request to filter users listing. */
router.post('/', authorizationMiddleware, payloadValidationMiddleware, async function(req, res, next) {
  //Some code
  const action = createAction(req);
  const response = await serviceRequest(action);
  //Some code to modify the response
  res.send(response);
});

module.exports = router;

My obvious questions were, why can't creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tirtha Guha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelemetry to Understand Software Performance]]></title>
        <id>60d4b5e96e1a1407b6b0bac4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want good performance in your application, you need to collect data to figure out where to make improvements. That's where OpenTelemetry comes in. OpenTelemetry offers a single set of APIs and libraries that standardize how you collect and transfer telemetry data. OpenTelemetry provides a specification for instrumentation so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures in TypeScript - Queue]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-queue-4p18</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ricardo93borges/data-structures-in-typescript-queue-4p18"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A queue uses FIFO (first-in-first-out) ordering, that is, items are removed from the queue in the same order that they are added, like a line.

A queue can be implemented using an array or a linked list, can be either fixed or dynamic size.
Add - Add an item to the end of the queue, also called enqueue.
Remove - Remove the first item from the queue, also called dequeue.
Peek - Return the top of the queue, without removing it.
isEmpty - Return true if the queue is empty.
isFull - Return true if the stack is full, used when the queue is fixed size.
Here's an implementation of a queue using an array, in TypeScript an array doesn't have a fixed length, so the operation isFull is not required, however, you can implement a queue with a fixed length and use that operation.
class Queue<T> {
  private array: T[] = [];

  add(data: T): void {
    this.array.push(data);
  }

  remove(): T | undefined {
    if (this.isEmpty()) throw new EmptyQueueException();

    return this.array.shift();
  }

  peek(): T {
    if (this.isEmpty()) throw new EmptyQueueException();

    return this.array[0];
  }

  isEmpty(): boolean {
    return this.array.length === 0;
  }
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Borges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working Remote: A Few Tips and Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/darkwiiplayer/working-remote-a-few-tips-and-tricks-3fbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/darkwiiplayer/working-remote-a-few-tips-and-tricks-3fbg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few months of working from home on less than optimal hardware, I've had the chance to pick up some interesting tricks, as well as using some that I've picked up before, while working on remote servers. Here's a short list of the most notable ones:
A few quick words on my "less than optimal" hardware: I basically had to make do with a small laptop that has definitely seen better days (days that have long since passed, I should probably add) with a freshly installed Ubuntu 20. But I could, of course, connect to my PC at the office over company VPN, as I'm sure is the case for many of you as well.
I've been a big fan of Vim for several years now, so editing text from the terminal has always felt very natural for me. This has proven itself to be incredibly useful in working remot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DarkWiiPlayer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Blockchain in NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codesphere/how-to-build-your-own-blockchain-in-nodejs-3ijh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codesphere/how-to-build-your-own-blockchain-in-nodejs-3ijh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we're trying to learn something new, it can oftentimes be tempting to dive headfirst into documentation, articles, and conceptual explanations. While all of that is certainly important, programmers have a great tool in their arsenal for understanding complex topics that they often take for granted.
Building models for different topics in code can help us understand how different pieces of an idea fit together and operate in practice.
In this tutorial, I'll show you how to build a rudimentary blockchain with some relatively simple Javascript.
It can be helpful to think of blockchains as augmented linked lists, or arrays in which each element points to the preceding array.
Within each block (equivalent to an element in an array) of the blockchain, there contains at least the following:
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saji Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with the LOGIQ PaaS Community Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/logiq/getting-started-with-the-logiq-paas-community-edition-1a88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/logiq/getting-started-with-the-logiq-paas-community-edition-1a88"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been looking for an inexpensive way to run your own observability stack while maintaining complete control over your data and its security, look no further. The LOGIQ PaaS Community Edition is officially live!
With the LOGIQ PaaS Community Edition, you can:
Self-host your observability stack on a cloud provider of your choice – public or private 
Ingest up to 50GB of log data per day with unlimited data retention

Store your log data on any S3-compatible cloud provider via the built-in Minio S3 service
Ingest logs from Syslog, RSyslog, Logstash, Fluent, AWS Firelens, JSON, and plenty more

Run up to 4 ingest worker processes
You’ll also get access to all of the LOGIQ Enterprise Edition’s features along with Community Support, free forever.

What’s more? Deploying LOGIQ PaaS is ri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajit Chelat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 9: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-9-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April of 2009, Yahoo! shut down GeoCities. Practically overnight, the once beloved service had its signup page replaced with a vague message announcing its closure.
We have decided to discontinue the process of allowing new customers to sign up 
…
The post Chapter 9: Community appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQLAlchemy Object Lifecycle]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mahmoudessa/sqlalchemy-object-lifecycle-4k1i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mahmoudessa/sqlalchemy-object-lifecycle-4k1i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object Lifecycle Recall


We can insert new records into the database using SQLAlchemy by running.
person = Person(name='Amr')


db.session.add(person)


db.session.commit()



which will build a transaction for inserting in a person instance in our model/table, and persist it to the database upon calling commit().
It isn't until we execute db.session() that we commit anything to the database.
Every time we want to interact with the database we start a connection and end a connection when all of the interactions are done.
Within that interaction session, We wound up creating transactions that we commit to the database every time that we want to commit work to the database. 
So an important thing to keep in mind:
Proposed database changes are not immediately committed to the database once t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud EL-karuony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple way to serialize objects to JSON in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hansott/simple-way-to-serialize-objects-to-json-in-typescript-27f5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hansott/simple-way-to-serialize-objects-to-json-in-typescript-27f5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we’re building an application we often need to serialize objects to JSON for storing them in a key value store (e.g. Redis) or publishing them on a queue.
While there are libraries available like class-transformer or io-ts, there's an easier way to serialize/unserialize objects to JSON.
class-transformer depends on the reflect-metadata package. Read this blogpost to know why you should be careful with depending on this package.
io-ts requires knowledge of some functional programming concepts. While I'm a big fan of functional programming, it's not for everyone. (The library is very well designed though)
In both cases we also need to depend on an extra package.
We want to keep our dependencies as small as possible.
What none of these packages offer is a way to deal with backwards compa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans Ott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Recommendations with Amazon SageMaker and Apache Spark]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/generate-recommendations-with-amazon-sagemaker-and-apache-spark-1pg5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/generate-recommendations-with-amazon-sagemaker-and-apache-spark-1pg5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker supports serverless Apache Spark (both Python and Scala) through SageMaker Processing Jobs.
We will use Processing Jobs throughout the book to perform data quality checks and feature transformations.
However, in this section we will generate recommendations using SageMaker Processing Jobs with Apache Spark ML’s collaborative filtering algorithm called Alternating Least Squares (ALS).
We would use this algorithm if we already have a Spark-based data pipeline and want to generate recommendations using that pipeline.
Here is the train_spark.py file that generates recommendations with Apache Spark ML and ALS:

import pyspark
from pyspark.sql import SparkSession
from pyspark.sql.functions import *
from pyspark.ml.evaluation import RegressionEvaluator
from pyspark.ml.recommendat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homework Hacks: 10 Tips To Get SAS Tasks Done Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/allanweb/homework-hacks-10-tips-to-get-sas-tasks-done-faster-2pbj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/allanweb/homework-hacks-10-tips-to-get-sas-tasks-done-faster-2pbj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Studying coding assumes overworking and facing continuous tension. Students are not always ready for such an enormous schedule and strict deadlines they have to face after enrolling in a programming course. Some students choose to get support from coding services requesting, "Please, do my SAS programming homework." However, proactive students who already have enough experience coping with a vast amount of coding tasks have many working hacks. We collected these tips to share with you to help you to get your tasks done faster. Read on to get more helpful information below.
You would require reading the details of your future SAS program first. Usually, professors provide students with detailed instructions that contain information on the goals and requirements. Do not begin working if some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>allanweb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React vs Angular vs Vue (briefly)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cicko/react-vs-angular-vs-vue-briefly-52jn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cicko/react-vs-angular-vs-vue-briefly-52jn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is a framework, while React and Vue are libraries, therefore angular is heavier than the other two, due to its big codebase. The Angular’s core contains most of the functionalities you might need in your application, while with React and Vue, you have to find external libraries, maintained by independent contributors. Therefore, when working with React and Vue, you have to be more careful when choosing libraries, being aware that libraries with a poor maintenance might be deprecated in future.
To build an app with Angular you have to learn Typescript, which is a superset of JavaScript, while with Vue and React you can use pure JS. Regarding the view, with Angular and Vue you write it with HTML, where in React you have to write JSX, which is a syntax that allows coexistence between …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudolf Cicko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dotenv Module for managing runtime environments]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkssharma/dotenv-module-for-managing-runtime-environments-3gm3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkssharma/dotenv-module-for-managing-runtime-environments-3gm3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dotenv is a zero-dependency module that loads environment variables from a .env file into process.env. Storing configuration in the environment separate from code is based on The Twelve-Factor App methodology.
Dotenv Module will help us to populate runtime configuration during runtime, like populating mysql connection details while starting up mysql connection with nodejs, or providing mongodb connection url while starting application 
require('dotenv').config() it will populate all .env variables in process.env object
So all required configuration gets populated to process.env and application runs as expected.
Environment variables are supported out of the box with Node and are accessible via the env object (which is a property of the process global object.)
For example, you can create a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tarun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email and Messaging Overload, and Too Many Slack Conversations to Keep Track Of?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paco/email-and-messaging-overload-and-too-many-slack-conversations-to-keep-track-of-114p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paco/email-and-messaging-overload-and-too-many-slack-conversations-to-keep-track-of-114p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overflowing Messaging inboxes do impact our productivity, and the message overload on Slack continues to be an ever-increasing issue. The pain is real!  
Celebrated Author Cal Newport has a fantastic piece on the productivity paradox 👇  
https://www.wired.com/story/email-slack-productivity-paradox/
Do you have more ideas💡? Share in the comments✍ !]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Engineers Need to Know DevOps Too, and That Starts with CI/CD]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thawkin3/software-engineers-need-to-know-devops-too-and-that-starts-with-ci-cd-47n8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thawkin3/software-engineers-need-to-know-devops-too-and-that-starts-with-ci-cd-47n8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is hot right now. It seems like every software engineering job posting requires DevOps experience and expertise regardless of the actual job title.
When a tech company breaks up its monolith into microservices, each of its engineering teams now owns their portion of the application from start to finish. Software engineers no longer just build the application; they also own repo maintenance, set up continuous integration, configure build pipelines, and deploy their application.
In this world of cross-functional teams and microservice architecture, DevOps skills become increasingly important, and that starts with understanding CI/CD (continuous integration, continuous delivery, and continuous deployment).
In this article we’ll talk about best practices for CI/CD and how platforms like…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🥷 Introducing Qui Max!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cheesytimmy/introducing-qui-max-3nd9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cheesytimmy/introducing-qui-max-3nd9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T12:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, everyone! 6 months ago, we released our first open source vue components library Qui. And we got a lot of feedback about it. The most popular question was "Does it work with Vue 3?", and now, It does! We called it Qui-max! Yes, as iPhone Max :)
Vue 3 is getting popular. We like Composition API, it really helps you to keep your code clean and composable. The component's api became more predictable. Making components, we also used new features as Teleports, plural v-model and others.

Types included, you can build your components with clear predictions. (p.s. I couldn't imagine how useful Typescript can be, before I try.)

We build components with Vite (rollup.js inside), with treeshake and separate css files, so you can use a few components only and take care about your bundle size. (but no so fast).




Added simple animations for dropdowns 




The library is under development, so if you find a bug feel free to make an issue in our repo Qui-max]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPA Gatekeeper Policy Manager (GPM)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kalilinux/opa-gatekeeper-policy-manager-gpm-259g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kalilinux/opa-gatekeeper-policy-manager-gpm-259g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T12:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatekeeper Policy Manager is a simple read-only web UI for viewing OPA Gatekeeper policies’ status in a Kubernetes Cluster.
It can display all the defined Constraint Templates with their rego code, and all the Constraints with its current status, violations, enforcement action, matches definitions, etc. 
Gatekeeper Policy Manager]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kalilinux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Hapi Server.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prosenghosh25/getting-started-with-hapi-server-2mp4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prosenghosh25/getting-started-with-hapi-server-2mp4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, you will create a new hapi server. First create a new project folder someproject on your machine so that it contains the necessary files.
Open your terminal (linux hit: Ctrl + Alt + T) and run the following command. Running the command will create a new folder someproject in the current directory and change the current directory to someproject directory.
$ mkdir someproject && cd someproject

To install the dependency of the project, we will use NPM (node package manager) so that the dependency can be installed easily.
Now, we need to run npm init. If you run this command, you will be asked some information. We can keep the default information. If you want, you can change it from the package.json.
$ npm init -y # Generate it without having it ask any questions

Now the package.json h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prosen Ghosh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command



  
  
  References



Ahamed, I. (2020, May 13). The find command ~ THM Writeup. Medium; Medium. https://irshadahamedpro.medium.com/the-find-command-thm-writeup-10dba7722261

GNU. (2021). Findutils 4.8.0. GNU. https://www.gnu.org/software/findutils/manual/html_mono/find.html




  
  
  Be more specific



  
  
  Find all files whose name ends with .xml




find / to search for items in the root directory
-type f to filter for files
-name "*.xml" to filter for items with a .xml as a suffix
Answer: find / -type f -name "*.xml"
/home directory (recursive) whose name is user.txt (case insensitive)




find /home to search for items in the /home directory
-type f to filter for files
-iname user.txt to filter for case insensitive name pattern of user.txt



Answer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omri Bornstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/applegamer22/tryhackme-the-find-command-10jg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe The find Command



  
  
  References



Ahamed, I. (2020, May 13). The find command ~ THM Writeup. Medium; Medium. https://irshadahamedpro.medium.com/the-find-command-thm-writeup-10dba7722261

GNU. (2021). Findutils 4.8.0. GNU. https://www.gnu.org/software/findutils/manual/html_mono/find.html




  
  
  Be more specific



  
  
  Find all files whose name ends with .xml




find / to search for items in the root directory
-type f to filter for files
-name "*.xml" to filter for items with a .xml as a suffix
Answer: find / -type f -name "*.xml"
/home directory (recursive) whose name is user.txt (case insensitive)




find /home to search for items in the /home directory
-type f to filter for files
-iname user.txt to filter for case insensitive name pattern of user.txt



Answer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omri Bornstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 ways to stop spam on your website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/onar/7-ways-to-stop-spam-on-your-website-191l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/onar/7-ways-to-stop-spam-on-your-website-191l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling overwhelmed by the amount of spam you are getting on your website? You're not alone.
This article doesn't list every spam detection strategy under the sun.
Instead, it lists some of the tactics we use at OOPSpam and many more proven to work ones. These are methods that stopped over 1M spam with 99.8% accuracy.
Let's get to it
It is the oldest trick in the book. The honeypot technique is easy to understand and implement. It works both for forms and comments. Here is a simple illustration that shows how honeypot spam filtering works.

A spam bot submits a form by making sure that every field or at least the ones that are required is filled so, no form validation prevents it from submitting. The honeypot technique relies on this assumption.
🎯 Many people use honeypot technique and ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>🐾 Onar A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wanna code with you all!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikita684/wanna-code-with-you-all-4kle</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikita684/wanna-code-with-you-all-4kle"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T09:37:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by nikita684]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikita684</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total.js FlowStream v1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/petersirka/total-js-flowstream-v1-3jh1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/petersirka/total-js-flowstream-v1-3jh1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T09:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce a new project called Total.js FlowStream app. FlowStream algorithm is part of the Total.js framework, and the Total.js FlowStream app is an advanced GUI and mechanism for running and integrating multiple FlowStreams. The performance is incredible.
Try FlowStream now
FlowStream Website
GitHub repository: https://github.com/totaljs/flowstream


Follow install instructions
FlowStream components repository: https://github.com/totaljs/flowstreamcomponents




Minimal requirements:
Node.js v14
The latest version of the Total.js 4 framework $ npm install total4




  
  
  Differences between Flow and FlowStream


Total.js Flow is a single-thread Node.js app that allows you to built only a one-level Flow design divided into multiple tabs. Total.js FlowStream uses a very…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Širka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Set Jenkins Pipeline Environment Variables?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aboywithscar/how-to-set-jenkins-pipeline-environment-variables-3hhp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aboywithscar/how-to-set-jenkins-pipeline-environment-variables-3hhp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T09:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jenkins is an open-source and extensible continuous integration and continuous deployment server. It is used to automate the process of continuous integration and continuous deployment(CI/CD). The importance of monitoring remote jobs and interacting with team members for stable code is immense; Jenkins takes care of all these requirements and allows a smooth integration via plugins, pipelines, and Jenkins environment variables.
If you are amongst the typical Jenkins users who want to add to their knowledge about CI and CD, some fundamental concepts must be learned. In this article, we will learn about the critical concept of Jenkins pipeline environment variables. We will also view and install the Lambatest Jenkins plugin and use the in-build variables from the Jenkins environment variable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abeer Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js PM2 Cheatsheet]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codesharpdev/node-js-pm2-cheatsheet-3dnh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codesharpdev/node-js-pm2-cheatsheet-3dnh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T08:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Guys🖐, I've brought node pm2 cheatsheets, I hope you like it
PM2 CheatSheet 
https://devhints.io/pm2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salman Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do software bugs occur?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maddevs/why-do-software-bugs-occur-144a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maddevs/why-do-software-bugs-occur-144a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T07:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, software bugs: what are they and why do they occur? Most likely, you know the reply to the first question. We all deal with software in everyday life, and it happens that sometimes, a program doesn’t work as expected. In most cases, it is connected with a coding error called a bug.
Why do the bugs appear though and why clients, even though they might hire an experienced team of developers, still have to pay for code with imperfections? Yep, it doesn’t always depend on a developer whether the product is going to function as expected. It depends on many factors, and you better learn more about them if you want to eliminate the possibility of bug occurrence.
It happens sometimes that a client cannot specify what functionality the product shall have. It becomes especially problematic if th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mad Devs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sagemaker Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/sagemaker-workflows-3oc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/sagemaker-workflows-3oc9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T07:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can manage your Amazon SageMaker training and inference workflows using Amazon SageMaker Studio and the Amazon SageMaker Python SDK. With the available tools, you can simplify your SageMaker process and integrate it into your existing project.
The following workflow technologies are supported.
Amazon SageMaker Model Building Pipelines: SageMaker's tool for building and managing end-to-end ML pipelines.


Airflow Workflows: SageMaker APIs to export configurations for creating and managing Airflow workflows.


Kubernetes Orchestration: SageMaker custom operators for your Kubernetes cluster, as well as custom components for Kubeflow Pipelines.


AWS Step Functions: Create multi-step machine learning workflows in Python that orchestrate SageMaker infrastructure without having to provision your resources separately.




  
  
  Amazon SageMaker Model Building Pipelines


Amazon SageMaker Model Building Pipelines is a tool for building machine learning pipelines that take advantage of direct SageMaker integration. Because of this integration, you can create a pipeline and set up SageMaker Projects for orchestration using a tool that handles much of the step creation and management for you. SageMaker Pipelines provides the following advantages over other AWS workflow offerings:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a chat app with Nodejs and Reactjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-a-chat-app-with-nodejs-and-reactjs-4d3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-a-chat-app-with-nodejs-and-reactjs-4d3d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T07:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, in this section I'll show you how to create a simple chat app with Nodejs and Reactjs.
npx create-react-app chatapp-client

After building the client app, We must create a server app to communicate between users.
cd ..

Well, we completely installed dependencies, So we can import and expand our code.
Now, create index.js file in chatapp-server directory and put this code in to it:
const express = require("express");
const app = express();
const sockets = require('socket.io');
const cors = require("cors");
const usernames = [];
let messageId = 0;
const messages = [];

app.use(cors());
app.get("/", (req, res) => {
    res.send("salam");
})

const server = app.listen(80, () => {
    console.log("server started at 80!");
});

const io = sockets(server, {
    cors: {
        origin: "htt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>h_mobarakian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover RAID 5 Data from SAN D-Link DSN-1100]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will show you how to recover lost data from a NAS storage system, with the example of D-link DSN-1100. Also, it will help you to retrieve information from the hard disks of an inoperable SAN device.

It is common knowledge that NAS is a server-type storage system designed to store various information at the file level. In fact, this is a computer with an array of disks inside, which is connected to a network. Every authorized user can interact with any files stored in a NAS. Such storage systems are becoming more and more popular because most of them make use of the RAID technology: It provides a serious boost in fault tolerance and increases security of storing large amounts of data. However, there is no system to give you a 100% guarantee against data loss. Sometimes, users ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover RAID 5 Data from SAN D-Link DSN-1100]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-raid-5-data-from-san-d-link-dsn-1100-bb1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will show you how to recover lost data from a NAS storage system, with the example of D-link DSN-1100. Also, it will help you to retrieve information from the hard disks of an inoperable SAN device.

It is common knowledge that NAS is a server-type storage system designed to store various information at the file level. In fact, this is a computer with an array of disks inside, which is connected to a network. Every authorized user can interact with any files stored in a NAS. Such storage systems are becoming more and more popular because most of them make use of the RAID technology: It provides a serious boost in fault tolerance and increases security of storing large amounts of data. However, there is no system to give you a 100% guarantee against data loss. Sometimes, users ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Template Literal Types in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-literal-types-in-typescript-4fe8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-literal-types-in-typescript-4fe8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will take a closer look at template literal types and how you can take advantage of them in your day-to-day activities as a developer. 
So, what are template literal types?
In order to understand what template literal types are, we first need to have a brief look at literal types. Literal types allow us to define types that are more specific, instead of something that is generalized like string or number. 
Let's say you have a switch; it can have the value of either on or off. One way of defining the types of this, is to use literal types, giving it the type of either On or Off:
type Switch = "On" | "Off"

In the case above, the value of any variable of type Switch can only be On or Off:
const x: Switch = "On"
const y: Switch = "Off"

If you tried to assign any other va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vagrant Development Environment Setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/waqar/vagrant-development-environment-setup-f71</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/waqar/vagrant-development-environment-setup-f71"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T05:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What might happen to the development environment if you upgrade OS. Would Apache configuration need to be changed? Will MySQL work?
Also, programs start stacking up. You would need so many different programs like PHP, Python, MySQL, maybe nodeJS, which get jumbled on your computer.
Vagrant provides a separate OS box, a Virtual Machine loaded with PHP, Python-related development environments. It helps keep your OS free and clean.
Vagrant gets rid of the many development and production environments. Usually, we develop on Mac and need to deploy on a Linux server. Vagrant helps keep the process quick and easy to deploy after coding.
WAMP, MAMP are still much easier to install and needs just a one-click setup. However, vagrant setup without advanced stuff like chef or puppet can be simple.
Hea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waqar Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hire AngularJS Developers to Build Faster & Scalable Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sttlinc/hire-angularjs-developers-to-build-faster-scalable-web-applications-2jmb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sttlinc/hire-angularjs-developers-to-build-faster-scalable-web-applications-2jmb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T05:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hire AngularJs Developers to Build Faster & Scalable Web Applications. With over 60% of the U.S. population using web-based applications, there is no reason why your company shouldn't be one of them. Hire AngularJs developers to build faster and more efficient web applications, with minimal effort.
AngularJs is a JavaScript framework that offers a unique object model and powerful features for creating dynamic web applications. Utilizing advanced technologies and best practices, Angular lets you deliver engaging experiences for your clients while saving you time and money. With easy to use controls, you can create reusable elements that are simple and easy to update. You can also hire a team of AngularJs developers to quickly scale your projects from an initial investment.
Hire a team of An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semaphore Software</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content Security Policy on Netlify (guide)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mannuelf/content-security-policy-on-netlify-guide-4p0c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mannuelf/content-security-policy-on-netlify-guide-4p0c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T05:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After deploy your website to Netlify (or any server) naturally you will run performance tests using WebPageSpeedTest. You might notice an alarming red F or E in the top right of screen.

This is a security score linked to a CSP (Content-Security-Policy), it shows whether any security policies are configured. The CSP provides a way to control the loading and execution of scripts and media in your webpage.
Setting the correct directives will prevent clickjacking, code-injection, cross-site scripting, illegal embedding of your webpage in an offsite frame/iframe and allow only valid MIME types.
In my case, deploying to Netlify...
Created a netlify.toml file and placed the CSP policy like this:
[[headers]]
  for = "/*"
  [headers.values]
    X-Frame-Options = "SAMEORIGIN"
    X-XSS-Protection =…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mannuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React and Material-UI Landing Page/Template Starter Kit — Kanban Taskboard WebApp]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hellomuthu23/react-and-material-ui-landing-page-template-starter-kit-kanban-taskboard-webapp-544i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hellomuthu23/react-and-material-ui-landing-page-template-starter-kit-kanban-taskboard-webapp-544i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for a good/responsive React landing/Template to bootstrap your app?. You are in the right place. This article will help you to get your web app up and running quickly. Ideal for any hackathon or innovation project!.

Github: https://github.com/hellomuthu23/react-material-ui-template
Live site: https://react-material-ui-template.web.app/
The ready-to-go template comes with the most essential tech-stack of React, Typescript, React Router, Material-UI, Lint, Prettier, and Cool Landing Page to bootstrap your web app. The app also has below basic features of creating a Taskboard and managing tasks using Kanban board.
Create a new Taskboard
Open a Task Board
Add Task
Move Task across the different stage using the drag and drop feature
Delete Task
The Landing page is responsive as well, built using material-ui grids.

The Template has a home page with Toolbar for main navigation, the main content area for displaying page content, and a footer. It also offers a smooth transition/animation effect while loading the content on the page.

The Taskboard page displays all the tasks in a kanban style format, task can be moved across to different stages using Drag and Drop feature. Along with this you can Add and Delete tasks. All data is stored in local storage.

You can run the app locally and see how it performs. Follow the below steps to run the app locally.
Clone the repo
git clone https://github.com/hellomuthu23/react-material-ui-template.git

Run yarn command to install the required npm package.
Run yarn start to start the app.
Access the app at http://localhost:3000.
Hope you like this cool template and is of use to you!.
Github: https://github.com/hellomuthu23/react-material-ui-template
https://react-material-ui-template.web.app/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muthu Pandian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dipping toes into Kafka and Node]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joepurnell1/dipping-toes-into-kafka-and-node-49de</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joepurnell1/dipping-toes-into-kafka-and-node-49de"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some upcoming work is on the horizon which I need to work with something I've not had the pleasure before - Kafka.
I thought it best to try out Kafka on my own terms using technologies I'm comfortable with before going into the real world and breaking something in production. 
Two thoughts knocked around:
I wasn't concerned with configuring Kafka itself
I wanted to use Node to communicate with Kafka
As I wasn't too concerned with the configuration of Kafka itself I decided to use this handy blog post from baeldung.com where I was walked through the steps needed to get an instance of Kafka running locally via docker. 
Task one was done ✅
With that out the way it was time to start communicating with the Kafka instance. Kafka is a framework for streaming data - messages are posted to Kafka gr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Purnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting the Request Method with Axios]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masteringjs/setting-the-request-method-with-axios-27n0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masteringjs/setting-the-request-method-with-axios-27n0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axios is our recommended JavaScript HTTP client. While we are opposed to unnecessary outside dependencies, Axios has several advantages over fetch():
Axios is isomorphic, fetch is not
Axios throws an error when a request fails
Automatic JSON and Form-Encoded Serialization and Parsing
Interceptors and instances
Another reason is that Axios has neat helper methods that allow you to set the request method, like GET or POST. For example, below is how you can send an HTTP GET request with Axios.
const axios = require('axios');

const res = await axios.get('https://httpbin.org/get?answer=42');

res.data.args; // { answer: 42 }

Want to send a POST request? That's easy, just change get() for post() and pass the request body as the 2nd parameter.
const res = await axios.post('https://httpbin.org/post', { hello: 'world' });

res.data.json; // { hello: 'world' }

Axios as a Function


If you prefer the named parameters approach that fetch() uses, you can also set the request method by setting the method option as shown below.
let res = await axios({
  method: 'GET',
  url: 'https://httpbin.org/get?answer=42'
});

res.data.args; // { answer: 42 }]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mastering JS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a REST API with .NET 5 and  C#]]></title>
        <id>60d36eb66e1a1407b6b0b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-rest-api-with-dot-net-5-and-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET is a popular software framework developed by Microsoft. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API end-to-end from scratch using the latest .NET 5 innovations and Visual Studio Code. The course uses the C# programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instalando asdf e Golang no Ubuntu 20.04]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexandreliberato/instalando-asdf-no-ubuntu-20-04-17gl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexandreliberato/instalando-asdf-no-ubuntu-20-04-17gl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sobre


Estava tentando testar essa ferramenta para gerenciamento de linguagens e ferramentas, segue o caminho que trilhei da instalação até ter o executável da linguagem que desejava, golang no caso, disponível na linha de comando:
# sudo apt install curl git
$ git clone https://github.com/asdf-vm/asdf.git ~/.asdf --branch v0.8.1

Abra o arquivo ~/.bashrc e adicione as seguintes linhas:
#
# asdf - language/tools version manager
#
source ~/.asdf/asdf.sh
source ~/.asdf/completions/asdf.bash

Execute:
$ . .bashrc
Pronto, basta testar:
$ asdf info
Para instalar a linguagem Go por exemplo, basta:
$ asdf install golang 1.16.5
$ asdf global golang 1.16.5
$ asdf shell golang 1.16.5

E para verificar a instalação:
$ go version]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandre Liberato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Built An Incomplete CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cesd/how-i-built-an-incomplete-cms-4fbn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cesd/how-i-built-an-incomplete-cms-4fbn"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I began building a blog application for a site that I may or may not finish. The bulk of the project is based on the blog-starter-typescript example in the NextJs GitHub repo. Their example loads markdown files from a folder in the root directory and uses remark and gray-matter to convert the markdown into html and to get file metadata. The example code for these function is located in their lib folder as api.ts and markdownToHtml.ts. 
The system they used works very well, however, if you plan on creating many posts and incorporating many images then that is when the system begins to breakdown. Since you store all of the markdown files and images in your root directory then it will perpetually grow and hosting costs for packages that large are affected. This is where I was looking for a so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ces-D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Typescript with React Hooks [2021]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/riyanegi/getting-started-with-typescript-with-react-hooks-2021-5cfd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/riyanegi/getting-started-with-typescript-with-react-hooks-2021-5cfd"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript is the next big thing in the Front End Development domain and if you are looking to upgrade your skills from a junior to an intermediate frontend developer, then it is a must have skill.
This article is for developers who already know react and javascript and want to shift to typescript, so I won't be focusing on any react concepts. This is a crash course on understanding the basics of using Typescript with React.

We will be covering all the topics necessary for understanding the basics of using react with typescript.
Info
Setup
Handling State
Handling Props
Handling Functions
Handling Events
In this article we will be building a simple personal watch list that records the movies you input by taking it's name, rating and review. It looks something like.(It is a little stylised …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RiyaNegi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Great Technical Course]]></title>
        <id>60a406bd906c5207e3a7dfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-great-technical-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to create a great technical video course. I run the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where we post technical courses from a variety of contributors. Video courses that follow the guidelines in this article are often a good fit for freeCodeCamp's channel. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The truth about Angular form]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joseat/the-truth-about-angular-form-2ji7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joseat/the-truth-about-angular-form-2ji7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[introdution


In this article i want to explain how to use angular forms directives in the right way, because i've observed that is not already clear how to use it correctly or what is the diferent about use template forms and built our owned form whith FormBuilder class. I am not going to enter in how to create a form in angular only i want to explain the interesting things.
I'm going to start with something very simple but could be doubs about this. 
The question is:  What happens when we use <form #f="ngForm" ... ?
Someone could think that we're referencing our form, this could be true, but in reality more things are happening behind the scenes.
The truth about this is that when we import FormsModule automatically NgForm is avalilable in our view, this means that NgForm is automatically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Álvarez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 ways to configure Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/typescripttv/6-ways-to-configure-webpack-5a33</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/typescripttv/6-ways-to-configure-webpack-5a33"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T15:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webpack is a build tool to make code, which was not primarily written for execution in browsers, executable in web browsers. With special plugins, webpack can manage many types of code, for example JavaScript, TypeScript, and Rust-generated WebAssembly.
There are webpack plugins to also compile, minify, shim, chunk, and bundle code. However, webpack was not designed to execute tasks such as linting, building, or testing your app. For this purpose, there are task runners such as Grunt, Gulp or npx.
In order to manage the functionality of webpack, it must be configured. Here are six different ways, in which webpack's configuration can be written.
As of webpack version 4, you are not required to specify a configuration. By default, webpack assumes that your code starts at src/index.js and wil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Neugebauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Claudia.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-claudia-js-4cap</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/introduction-to-claudia-js-4cap"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Claudia.js?


Claudia.js is a tool designed to simplify deployment of Node.js projects to AWS Lambda and API Gateway. It automates deployment tasks so you don’t need to worry about introducing errors and configures everything the way you would expect it to be set up out of the box.
According to the official website, Claudia’s primary objective is to help JavaScript developers get started using Lambda microservices easily so they can “focus on solving important business problems instead of dealing with AWS deployment workflows.”
In this section, we’ll walk you through setting up an example Node.js and Express.js app to show Claudia.js in action.
Claudia.js is available on npm. The simplest way to use Claudia.js is to install it as a global utility:

npm install -g claudia


Install the Express.js app generator using npm:

npm install express-generator -g

express claudia-demo

cd claudia-demo

npm i


The Express.js app will be hosted by a Lambda function, so it needs a handler to send data between the app and the API Gateway. This is where Claudia.js comes in. Claudia uses aws-serverless-express to generate a helper function to interface between API Gateway requests and Express.js requests and responses.
Execute the command below in your project directory. If you have renamed your Express.js application module, replace app with the name of the main Express.js application module:
$ claudia generate-serverless-express-proxy --express-module
app

Your app is now ready to go live:

claudia create --handler lambda.handler \ 
   --deploy-proxy-api \ 
   --region us-east-1 


 Claudia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bash cheat sheet: Top 28 commands for you to learn 🤺]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ankit01oss/bash-cheat-sheet-top-28-commands-for-you-to-learn-15ee</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ankit01oss/bash-cheat-sheet-top-28-commands-for-you-to-learn-15ee"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there,
Today I want to bring you a summary of top Bash commands. Bash is a very popular shell program. It stands for 'Bourne Again Shell'. There are also other types of shells, but Bash is the most widely available and used shell.
Anything inside [ ] means that it's optional.
ls - List directory contents


ls is one of the most common commands. It is used to list the contents of a directory.
Syntax: ls [options][files]

ls -a shows hidden(dot) files
ls -l shows file details
echo - Prints text to the terminal window


echo prints text to the terminal window. It is used widely for printing status texts and values of environment variables.
bash-3.2$ echo "hello"
hello

touch - Creates a file


touch can be used to create an empty file quickly. It can also be used to modify file timestamps.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Anand ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Process Injection (Process Hollowing)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wireless90/process-injection-process-hollowing-52m1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wireless90/process-injection-process-hollowing-52m1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code sample in github
Understanding one of the the Process Hollowing technique used by Malware Authors

[The gif above takes awhile (30 sec) to load]
Injecting TvnViewer.exe into notepad++.exe
[+] Creating Victim Process notepad++.exe
        [*] Successfully created victim process notepad++.exe
[+] Retrieving Thread Handle of notepad++.exe
        [*] Thread Handle at  0x2E0
[+] Allocating unmanaged memory for ThreadContext of notepad++.exe
[+] Retrieving ThreadContext of notepad++.exe
[+] Retrieving ImageBase Address of notepad++.exe
        [*] notepad++.exe's ImageBase Address is 0xA5A7162010
[+] Allocating unmanaged memory for notepad++.exe's ImageBase
[+] Reading ImageBase from notepad++.exe's ImageBase Address
        [*] ImageBase is 0xA5A7162010
[+] Unmapping notepad++.exe's Image…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wireless90</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's build Airbnb Home page with Nextjs and ChakraUI - Part 3(final)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/m_ahmad/let-s-build-airbnb-home-page-with-nextjs-and-chakraui-part-3-final-3379</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/m_ahmad/let-s-build-airbnb-home-page-with-nextjs-and-chakraui-part-3-final-3379"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this part, We'll continue with main section and then we'll create footer.
Github Repo: Chakra-airbnb
Demo: Chakra-airbnb

 <Heading
        as="h3"
        fontSize="1.5rem"
        fontWeight="bold"
        textAlign="left"
        mb={{ base: "4", lg: "2" }}
        pb={4}
        borderBottom="1px solid"
        borderColor="gray.300"
      >
        Traveling with AirBnb
      </Heading>
      <Flex
        as="section"
        alignItems="start"
        justify="between"
        flexDirection={{ base: "column", lg: "row" }}
        my={{ base: "1.5rem", lg: "2.5rem" }}
        borderBottom="1px solid"
        borderColor="gray.300"
        pb={8}
      >
        <Box
          w={{ base: "100%", lg: 1 / 3 }}
          px={{ lg: "0.5rem" }}
          mb={{ base: "6", lg: "0" }}
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad  Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Fiber, performant alternative to Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/introduction-to-go-fiber-2m0a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/introduction-to-go-fiber-2m0a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T11:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is go fiber?


Fiber is a web framework for Go similar to Mux. But it's heavily inspired by Express and that makes it perfect to work with for node developers.
It is built on top of Fasthttp engine, here are some benchmarks. It also has quite a low memory allocation overhead. For example while writing this article it only took around only ~16mb of memory, which was amazing!
In this article let's implement very simple mock api routes to get a feel of the Fiber framework
The code from the article is available in this repository
You can install go directly on your system by installing the binary from go docs https://golang.org/doc/install

(optional)
Personally, I like to use docker so I don't have to install anything on my system
Let's pull the golang docker image
docker pull golang

Cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Azure Key Vault with Octopus]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/octopus/using-azure-key-vault-with-octopus-4e1n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/octopus/using-azure-key-vault-with-octopus-4e1n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T11:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently wrote about extending the functionality of Octopus to integrate with HashiCorp Vault using step templates. Afterwards, several people asked if I plan to create step templates to integrate with other secret managers.
In this post, I walk through a new step template, Azure Key Vault - Retrieve Secrets, which is designed to retrieve secrets from an Azure Key Vault for use in your deployments or runbooks.



This post assumes some familiarity with custom step templates and the Octopus Community Library. 
In addition, this post doesn't go into great detail about Azure Key Vault concepts or how to set it up. You can learn more by reading the Azure Key Vault basic concepts guide from Microsoft.
The step template in this post retrieves secrets from an Azure Key Vault using the Az.KeyVau…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim : Keymapping Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrdestructive/vim-keymapping-guide-3olb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrdestructive/vim-keymapping-guide-3olb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T10:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Keymapping or Key binding is a process in which a user or a system can assign certain keys or commands to perform a particular task or commands. This can be quite useful in Vim as well as in other text editors to avoid some repetitive tasks and save time. In Vim this can be a great power to have for programmers as it can be really very flexible to set up for any programming language and it's environment.
This is not a in-depth guide of Vim-keymappings, it is just a overview of how to make keymappings and make the workflow a bit easier, probably give some insights on the strength of Vim to easily integrate with terminal and perform tasks with shortcuts. 
In Vim, you can map a particular keystroke combination to trigger a command or any operation. You can also map a key in pla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meet Gor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[P42 for Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/p42/p42-for-visual-studio-code-1k8o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/p42/p42-for-visual-studio-code-1k8o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[P42 for Visual Studio Code is now available in the Visual Studio Marketplace. 
free extension includes all refactorings and code modernizations that are available in P42. It can be used on all repositories and runs entirely locally.
When you open a JavaScript or TypeScript file, P42 will automatically detect code that could be modernized and highlight it:

You can then effortlessly update your code using the Quick Fix function. 
With P42 for Visual Studio Code, you can learn new JavaScript patterns right in your IDE, make sure new code follows best practices, and modernize older code gradually.
Try out P42 for Visual Studio Code today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Grammel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing custom confirmation modal for canDeactivate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/implementing-custom-confirmation-modal-for-candeactivate-2fan</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/implementing-custom-confirmation-modal-for-candeactivate-2fan"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T08:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, in this article, we will discuss what canDeactivate means and how to have a custom confirmation modal implemented based on our app theme.
In Angular we get in build support for the routes we define to have implementation for canDeactivate guard which is how we can restrict the user from moving away from the view when some work is in progress on the current view. Example User is making an edit on his profile page and didn't click on the save button so at that time if we have implemented the router guard for canDeactivate, the user will be asked for the confirmation.
canDeactivate(
    component: Component,
    currentRoute: ActivatedRouteSnapshot,
    currentState: RouterStateSnapshot,
    nextState?: RouterStateSnapshot): Observable<boolean | UrlTree> | Promise<boolean | UrlTree> |…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Dhawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Damn Vulnerable GraphQL Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/graphqleditor/damn-vulnerable-graphql-application-1jf5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/graphqleditor/damn-vulnerable-graphql-application-1jf5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T08:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually in these when I write about some library or app I try to highlight its strengths. Well this time I’m going to do the complete opposite and talk about weaknesses. Rest assured it won't be some scorching review, because we’re looking at Damn Vulnerable GraphQL Application where weaknesses are completely intentional and exploiting them is the whole point.
As for why it's fairly obvious, as GraphQL continues to grow and become more popular so too do the concerns about its vulnerabilities. After all, if you want to use it for your app you probably want it to be secure. So yes Damn Vulnerable GraphQL Application is full of weaknesses by design, it's meant to test GraphQL’s safety against various attacks. Let’s look at these types of attacks (or scenarios) you can try out:
Batch Query Att…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomek Poniatowicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular structural directives - how to implement your own ngIf]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kreuzerk/angular-structural-directives-how-to-implement-your-own-ngif-367h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kreuzerk/angular-structural-directives-how-to-implement-your-own-ngif-367h"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T06:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch on Youtube »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kreuzerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Password managers for Mac]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/top-5-password-managers-for-mac-3dmc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/top-5-password-managers-for-mac-3dmc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first thing I install is a password manager on every new device. I have so many accounts I want to keep safe and secure. The only way to do this is a good password manager.
Today's article will walk you through my top 5 password managers for Mac.
TL;DR: I'm currently using 1Password as my password manager. It has an excellent user experience.
You might wonder why you should use a password manager, and I've written down some advantages that are trademarks of every password manager.
Safely store passwords and notes in a vault
Generate safe passwords on the fly
Watch passwords, keep track of leaked passwords
I'm currently using 1Password as my password manager for Mac and iPhone. To me, it has a lot of awesome features like:

Family account and vault
Travel mode (remove accounts for x time)
Two-factor for certain websites
Apps for all browsers and devices
1Password is a paid application and starts at \$2.99 per month.
Check out 1Password
At the company, we are using LastPass, and it's a good second choice for me personally as well.

Local Encryption
Great team management
Emergency backup
Apps for all browsers and devices
Dark web monitoring
LastPass has a free mode, so great option to start with.
View LastPass for Mac
Dashlane is a super popular free-tiered option as your new password manager.

Auto logins
Alert for account breaches
Emergency contact mode
VPN wifi protection
U2F authentication
Get Dashlane for Mac
This free option has unlimited storage, which is unheard of for these kinds of systems.

Family plan
Password analysis
Secure file sharing
Open-source
Get bitwarden now
And the last option is keeper, which comes as a fair prices option.

BreachWatch, alert for breaches
Encrypted private messenger
Import existing passwords
Password sharing
Try out Keeper
Thank you for reading my blog. Feel free to subscribe to my email newsletter and connect on Facebook or Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 security best practices for Angular apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hirendhaduk_/top-6-security-best-practices-for-angular-apps-8n1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hirendhaduk_/top-6-security-best-practices-for-angular-apps-8n1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's common to be concerned about security vulnerabilities in frontend frameworks. While Angular is the most preferred frontend framework among the developers for developing single-page applications, there are still security threats that need due attention for protecting Angular apps. 
Keep these top 5 security best practices at hand when building Angular apps. 
To prevent the injection of scripts into DOM elements such as authentication details, social security numbers, web tokens, etc. 
To prevent these malfunctions, use the InnerHTML property to sanitizes all the data that shows in components. But one should bind it to use to keep Angular alert enough to sanitize malicious activity-related strings. This interprets data as HTML in its context and is sanitized. It sanitizes the server-sid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hiren Dhaduk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 6 security best practices for Angular apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hirendhaduk_/top-6-security-best-practices-for-angular-apps-8n1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hirendhaduk_/top-6-security-best-practices-for-angular-apps-8n1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's common to be concerned about security vulnerabilities in frontend frameworks. While Angular is the most preferred frontend framework among the developers for developing single-page applications, there are still security threats that need due attention for protecting Angular apps. 
Keep these top 5 security best practices at hand when building Angular apps. 
To prevent the injection of scripts into DOM elements such as authentication details, social security numbers, web tokens, etc. 
To prevent these malfunctions, use the InnerHTML property to sanitizes all the data that shows in components. But one should bind it to use to keep Angular alert enough to sanitize malicious activity-related strings. This interprets data as HTML in its context and is sanitized. It sanitizes the server-sid…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hiren Dhaduk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Fallacies – Definition and Fallacy Examples]]></title>
        <id>607f5fafdd38b9088c2bd0c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-fallacies-definition-fallacy-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're debating someone, you want to use all the resources at your disposal to convince them you're right. And that's great – but you should be careful that you don't end up using a logical fallacy to help you make your point. What is a Logical Fallacy?A logical fallacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Multi-Control Custom Validator in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karvel/creating-a-multi-control-custom-validator-in-angular-if</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karvel/creating-a-multi-control-custom-validator-in-angular-if"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T03:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom validators in Angular’s reactive form library are one of the most powerful (and in my opinion overlooked) tools a developer has to create better form UI/UX. Custom validators aren’t just limited to a single control. It is easy to evaluate an entire group. This is great for comparing multiple controls. In this article I create a multi-control custom validator that validates two fields if their values match to show an example of what is possible.
As I mentioned in my previous article about custom validators, I like using them to both handle custom logic that the built-in validators don’t, and to be able to create the validation error messages in one spot. This makes custom validators powerful and very reusable.

Creating a multi-control custom validator is very similar to creating a s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elanna Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View code snippets in fullscreen mode]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codever/view-code-snippets-in-fullscreen-mode-16mf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codever/view-code-snippets-in-fullscreen-mode-16mf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T18:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now view the code snippets in fullscreen mode if they are too long or some of the lines too wide:

For the implementation in frontend with Angular I used screenfull.js1, which is a simple wrapper for cross-browser usage of the JavaScript Fullscreen API2.
👉 See How to display an element in full screen in Angular with screenfull.js for complete details about the implementation
👉 The whole source code of the project is available on Github
https://github.com/sindresorhus/screenfull.js/ ↩
https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/Fullscreen_API ↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Matei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge your Angular application using Web Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/supercharge-your-angular-application-using-web-workers-5h9b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/supercharge-your-angular-application-using-web-workers-5h9b"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zama Khan Mohammed | ng-conf | May 2019
UI blocking is a thing of the past!


https://angularprojects.com


If you are building an application where you do a lot of calculations on UI, such as creating CAD documents, doing heavy geometrical calculations, or heavy data table manipulations, then you might have observed that the UI sometimes becomes laggy or janky.
This happens because JavaScript is not the only thing that runs on the main thread, but other things like the painting of pixels, style calculations, and many others also run on it. When we run heavy long-running JavaScript on the browser, occasionally we see that frames are missed, which does not provide a great User Experience.
We have heard that Web Workers is one of the promising solutions to such a problem, but we never knew t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backup your file server or any data using Hybrid Cloud - Storage Gateway Solution (AWS)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/backup-your-file-server-or-any-data-using-hybrid-cloud-storage-gateway-solution-aws-1pn0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/backup-your-file-server-or-any-data-using-hybrid-cloud-storage-gateway-solution-aws-1pn0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T17:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


You can use cloud storage for on-premises data backups to reduce infrastructure and administration costs. There is several ways to backup your on-premise infrastructure to cloud, here I’ll use hybrid cloud (part of your infrastructure is on the cloud and part of your infrastructure is on the on-premise) to accomplish it. In this post I’ll show AWS Storage Gateway solutions to bridge between on-premise data to cloud. The common use case is disaster recovery, backup & restore and tiered storage.
There is 3 types of Storage Gateway:

Before show how I implemented it, I’ll show a brief overview about each one.
Databases and applications are often backed up directly to a file server on-premises. You can now simply point these backups to the File Gateway, which copies the data to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Filipe Motta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axios vs Fetch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpiteng/axios-vs-fetch-1eh5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpiteng/axios-vs-fetch-1eh5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Developers! All we are using either Axios OR fetch to communicate/exchange data with server. Both works perfect as per your requirement. Today we will go in detail and see how they are differ in terms of features they provide.
Axios — has url in request object
axios
  .get(url, {
    headers: {
      'Content-Type': 'application/json',
    },
    timeout: 1000 * 60,
  })
  .then(res => {

  })
  .catch(err => {

  })

Fetch — has no url in request object.
 fetch(url)
  .then((response) => response.json())
  .then((json) => {  

  })
  .catch(() => {

  })

Axios — third-party package that you need to install manually. 85.3k Star in Github — Well managed & rich features library.
npm i axios
Fetch — is in-build into most of the browser, no more need of installation.
Axios — having in-b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kpiteng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BASIC COMMANDS IN UBUNTU  (PART1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ubuntu/basic-commands-in-ubuntu-part1-2ch1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ubuntu/basic-commands-in-ubuntu-part1-2ch1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:14:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! Today we are going to know about some useful commands. In this part we will learn important commands about system info and if you enjoy i will publish second part. :)
Linux has many commands some of them are very useful and some of them are dangerous don't try to run all commands on your terminal. I will publish another article about dangerous commands in linux. I hope you enjoy this if it is helpful share with your friends :).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amoo ubuntu:)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Blockchain is a natural evolution of open source". Thoughts?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mirhsquadri/blockchain-is-a-natural-evolution-of-open-source-thoughts-3ch0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mirhsquadri/blockchain-is-a-natural-evolution-of-open-source-thoughts-3ch0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T15:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am writing an article for a magazine on how blockchain is a natural evolution of open source. Now I know that open source is conceptual whereas blockchain is an actual technology. But I was wondering if blockchain could be considered a new form of open source implementation of systems given that they both find their roots in the same principles of decentralisation and transparency. Would love to get thoughts of fellow developers on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mirhsquadri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replace FTP with the SCP command in the terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/waqar/replace-ftp-with-the-scp-command-in-the-terminal-4kk2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/waqar/replace-ftp-with-the-scp-command-in-the-terminal-4kk2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCP comes in handy to copy files to a remote server from a computer or vice versa. You can also copy server files to another server.
All you need is your server’s IP address and user credentials to start copying. Here are some common SCP commands use cases.
scp file.zip user@hostip:/home/directory

This command will copy file.zip in your terminals present working directory to the home directory of the server.
scp user@hostip:/home/directory/file.zip ~/Downloads

You are copying file.zip from the server’s home directory to your local downloads folder.
Another use case of the SCP command is during site migration to a new server. Zip your site’s root directory and copy it to the new server.
Provide login credentials and file paths of both servers to SCP in your computer’s terminal.
scp user@remotehost1:/home/file.zip user@remotehost2:/home

Add -p flag to add port of remote host
scp -p 1122 file.zip user@hostip:/home/directory

Add a -C flag to enable the gzip compression in SSH transfer
scp -C localfile.zip user@hostip:/home/directory

-v Verbose SCP operation
-p <port> Mention remote host port
-P Save the file’s modification and access times
-r Copy recursively
-c <cipher> Specify the cipher for data encryption
So if you are still using an FTP client, use the SCP command in the terminal for a secure transfer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waqar Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 tools all developers should use]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saluki/4-tools-all-developers-should-use-212g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saluki/4-tools-all-developers-should-use-212g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are always looking for simpler ways to do more advanced things in less time, and one of the many ways that they can achieve this is by using a selection of tools to supplement their workflow. The aim of this article is to cover some of the major tools that people use, and to give you an insight into what they can do to make your life easier.
And to seal the deal, all the tools I’ll be mentioning are completely free to use, which is an incredible price for what you’re getting from them.
Git / Version Control
Git is the most well-known version control tool out there. It allows you to store your code on a server (thereby reducing data-loss risks), collaborate with other developers and share your code online. Another huge plus to Git is that it allows you to go and look at other people’s public repositories, and see how they solved certain problems. This can then help you solve the problem in your application, and it can save you lots of time and effort.
Git is open-source itself and it comes with a huge selection of extensions that allow you to modify the functionality of the system in a huge range of different ways.
The fact that Git allows you to go back and review previous versions of your code, see how it’s changed and keep track of issues as well as provide you with lots of automation tools makes it quite clear that Git, or a Git alternative is a must-have for nearly every project.
Whilst you could install a system like Gitea on a VPS and then run your own Git server, there is a selection of different services out there that provide Git repository hosting as a service. These services often come with lots of extras too, and usually a very generous free tier. The most notable Git host out there is definitely GitHub, but it is closely rivalled by GitLab among other solutions.
Want to read more? You can find the full article on my blog: https://www.saluki.tech/2021/06/18/4-tools-all-developers-should-use/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting login page element after hard reload page ANGULAR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prahatravichandan/getting-login-page-element-after-hard-reload-page-angular-3i3i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prahatravichandan/getting-login-page-element-after-hard-reload-page-angular-3i3i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T05:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When i try to hard reload website after login it's getting login page element also after login in angular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>prahatravichandan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>