<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-11T01:05:09.565Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-11T01:05:09.565Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Project Template, Written in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arifintahu/api-project-template-written-in-typescript-5dmk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arifintahu/api-project-template-written-in-typescript-5dmk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T23:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building project with standardized structure could save much our time. We could focus on business process without considering too much on project structure. On the other hand, a good project structure should be clean, nice refactored, and easy to maintain.
Here's why:
Your time should be focused on creating something amazing. A project that solves a problem and helps others.
You shouldn't be doing the same tasks over and over like structuring project
You should implement dry principles to the rest of your life
This time, I created complete project template for API written in Typescript which is available in this github. Of course, no one template will serve all projects since your needs may be different. 
This project structure is built using
Express.js
Sequelize
Swagger
Typescript
JsonWeb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIftahul Arifin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Project Template, Written in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arifintahu/api-project-template-written-in-typescript-5dmk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arifintahu/api-project-template-written-in-typescript-5dmk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T23:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building project with standardized structure could save much our time. We could focus on business process without considering too much on project structure. On the other hand, a good project structure should be clean, nice refactored, and easy to maintain.
Here's why:
Your time should be focused on creating something amazing. A project that solves a problem and helps others.
You shouldn't be doing the same tasks over and over like structuring project
You should implement dry principles to the rest of your life
This time, I created complete project template for API written in Typescript which is available in this github. Of course, no one template will serve all projects since your needs may be different. 
This project structure is built using
Express.js
Sequelize
Swagger
Typescript
JsonWeb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIftahul Arifin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Carefull With rm!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giorgikeburia/be-carefull-with-rm-7h9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giorgikeburia/be-carefull-with-rm-7h9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T23:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📣 The world is amazing ,but Not so ideal as we think!🤔
💡 Unix-like operating systems such as Linux do not have an undelete command.
When we delete something with rm , it's gone.Linux assumes we're smart and we know what we're doing.

One of the big problem can cause wildcards. so be particularly with them.
For Example : if we want to delete just the JS files in directory we type:
rm *.js
* and the .js like so:
rm * .js
.js
There is many ways to avoid this problem, here is 2 useful tip: 
-i (interactive) option, which prompt the user for confirmation  ,before deleting an existing file.
rm i *.js
rm: remove regular empty file 'mk.js'?
2 - whenever we use wildcards with rm, test the wildcard first with ls. This will let we see the files that will be deleted. Then we can press the up arrow ☝️ to recall the command and replace ls with rm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GiorgiKeburia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux for Hackers | EP. 01]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gayankod/linux-for-hackers-ep-01-e1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gayankod/linux-for-hackers-ep-01-e1h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T20:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Linux?
This series is not only for hackers but also for all beginners who are interested in Linux. By the way, if you want to become a hacker,

Hold on, If you read this…
Let me know why are you here in the comment box… Just put why you are interested in Linux, why you want to learn Linux? okay, you put… fine!!! Perfect! Thank you! Let’s move on…

Okay, First of all, you need to install Linux OS on your machine…
Otherwise, I recommended using a Virtual Machine. Oracle Virtual Box is pretty much cooler and easy to use. But It’s all your choice.
What you want to do is, Install and run Kali/ubuntu/Parrot or any Linux distro on your virtual machine or your alternative device!!!

So this is Linux. I put the screenshot of a Kali Linux Distro. This is specifically optimized for Cyber Secu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gayan Kodithuwakku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t let your RxJS observables die]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pruttned/don-t-let-your-rxjs-observables-die-4ckd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pruttned/don-t-let-your-rxjs-observables-die-4ckd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T20:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS is a powerful library for reactive programming. We use it in Angular all the time, from simple reactions to HTTP client responses to full-blown state management solutions. But sometimes, it is easy to miss some details and create a code that can break at the worst possible moment. 
Let’s start with an example right away.
of(1, 2, 3, 4, 5)
  .pipe(
    tap(v => {
      if (v === 3) {
        throw new Error('some error');
      }
    })
  )
  .subscribe({
    next: console.log.bind(null, 'next:'),
    error: (err: Error) => console.log('error:', err.message),
  });

We have an observable that emits numbers from 1 to 5, and if the number is 3, we throw an error.
We can see the following output.
next: 1
next: 2
error: some error

Numbers 4 and 5 were not processed at all.
This might be s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Ruttkay-Nedecký</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the most boring website ever with TypeScript, NestJs, React and others. Part 3.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/making-the-most-boring-website-ever-with-typescript-nestjs-react-and-others-part-3-3i6a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/making-the-most-boring-website-ever-with-typescript-nestjs-react-and-others-part-3-3i6a"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T19:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series is about making a generic website for a local business with TypeScript, NodeJs, NestJs, Prisma, React and NextJs. I'm trying to make my videos quite short, about 10 minutes each (except for the first one), while putting as much content there as I can. Here is the full playlist.
In this video we will implement file uploading on our server. Then we will add picture setting for the barbers in the admin panel. And finally we'll create a new page for barbers on the client website.
Enjoy :).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NordicBeaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the most boring website ever with TypeScript, NestJs, React and others. Part 3.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/making-the-most-boring-website-ever-with-typescript-nestjs-react-and-others-part-3-3i6a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/making-the-most-boring-website-ever-with-typescript-nestjs-react-and-others-part-3-3i6a"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T19:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series is about making a generic website for a local business with TypeScript, NodeJs, NestJs, Prisma, React and NextJs. I'm trying to make my videos quite short, about 10 minutes each (except for the first one), while putting as much content there as I can. Here is the full playlist.
In this video we will implement file uploading on our server. Then we will add picture setting for the barbers in the admin panel. And finally we'll create a new page for barbers on the client website.
Enjoy :).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NordicBeaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Mutations in React Query]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkdodo/mastering-mutations-in-react-query-dm6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkdodo/mastering-mutations-in-react-query-dm6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've covered a lot of ground already when it comes to the features and concepts React Query provides. Most of them are about retrieving data - via the useQuery hook. There is however a second, integral part to working with data: updating it.
For this use-case, React Query offers the useMutation hook.
Generally speaking, mutations are functions that have a side effect. As an example, have a look at the push method of Arrays: It has the side effect of changing the array in place where you're pushing a value to:
const myArray = [1]
myArray.push(2)

console.log(myArray) // [1, 2]

The immutable counterpart would be concat, which can also add values to an array, but it will return a new Array instead of directly manipulating the Array you operate on:
const myArray = [1]
const newArray = myArra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominik D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Migration Methodology]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devyetii/container-migration-methodology-3gll</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devyetii/container-migration-methodology-3gll"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T18:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Businesses have recently developed great interest in Container-based architectures as it's more suitable for agile architectures.
The following chart from Grand View Research shows the growth of the application

In this guide; you as Architect or Ops engineer will find your way through migrating to an AWS container service.
Agility and product improvement over regular instances
Cost Savings by improving resource utilization and flexible scaling up/down
Elasticity of scaling up/down according to the business needs.
Faster Innovation by hosting control plane to the cloud and releasing more resources for innovation
Deploy globally in minutes via 77 AZs across 24 geographic Regions worldwide
DevOps driver using managed container technology to support DevOps on the
cloud platform…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ebrahim Gomaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Ceph in a multi-node setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T18:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Caph is the future of data storage whether it was objects, blocks or a file system. It provides a great alternative to self-hosted solutions such as GlusterFS in the realm of file systems and to managed services such as AWS S3 as an object storage where it makes more sense to host your own data because you have to store it on private cloud or simply to reduce costs as S3 costs sometimes grow to be pretty insane.
I used Vagrant to create a declarative configuration of my environment.
My setup consist of three virtual machines with Ubuntu 20.04 and attached disk storage of 10 GiB to each one of them (except the first machine it has two disks). Ceph documentation says the minimum disk size is 5 GiB but I had problems in the past working with storage less than 10 GiB so I wanted…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Khaled</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Ceph in a multi-node setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T18:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Caph is the future of data storage whether it was objects, blocks or a file system. It provides a great alternative to self-hosted solutions such as GlusterFS in the realm of file systems and to managed services such as AWS S3 as an object storage where it makes more sense to host your own data because you have to store it on private cloud or simply to reduce costs as S3 costs sometimes grow to be pretty insane.
I used Vagrant to create a declarative configuration of my environment.
My setup consist of three virtual machines with Ubuntu 20.04 and attached disk storage of 10 GiB to each one of them (except the first machine it has two disks). Ceph documentation says the minimum disk size is 5 GiB but I had problems in the past working with storage less than 10 GiB so I wanted…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Khaled</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert Update and Delete Data in MySQL Database | Insert Data Using PHP mysqli]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hmawebdesign/how-to-insert-update-and-delete-data-in-mysql-database-insert-data-using-php-mysqli-1jap</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hmawebdesign/how-to-insert-update-and-delete-data-in-mysql-database-insert-data-using-php-mysqli-1jap"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T17:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert Update and Delete Data in MySQL Database | Insert Data Using PHP mysqli
In this video, I will also show you how to insert, update and delete data in a MySQL database. And if you're not sure which programming language to use, it doesn't matter because I demonstrate using PHP mysqli!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HMA WebDesign</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enable SSL for Local Laravel Sail Development Caddy and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adrianmejias/how-to-enable-ssl-for-local-development-using-laravel-sail-and-docker-51ee</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adrianmejias/how-to-enable-ssl-for-local-development-using-laravel-sail-and-docker-51ee"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T17:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk SSL and local development; don't worry, I've been searching too.
There is an issue with developing locally, not just with Laravel, where developers who are building saas products aren't able to get a clean setup for SSL in the browser. This makes setting things up like PWAs or Google sign-in buttons impossible if the certificate isn't valid.
Given the power of Docker and Caddy, the dream is real. You can absolutely use this for non-Laravel Sail web applications as well.
The end result of implementing the code below should give you a couple of certificates (intermediate.crt, laravel.test.crt) that you can install to your local system.
GitHub Gist: https://gist.github.com/adrianmejias/0997f2b8a20715428f594a4798e034f5
docker/


caddy/
authorities/ (intermediate.crt)
certificates/

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Mejias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comment approvisionner ses environnements avec vagrant #DevOpsRoadMap]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/teamdevops/comment-approvisionner-ses-environnements-avec-vagrant-devopsroadmap-4d5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/teamdevops/comment-approvisionner-ses-environnements-avec-vagrant-devopsroadmap-4d5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T17:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qu’est-ce que Vagrant ? et à en quoi il peut vous servir ?


Vagrant est un outil permettant de créer et de gérer des environnements de machines virtuelles dans un seul workflow. Il réduit considérablement le temps de configuration de l'environnement de développement.
Dans ce tutoriel vagrant, je vais vous apprendre à configurer Vagrant sur votre ordinateur afin de créer et gérer des machines virtuelles pour votre environnement de développement.
Vagrant peut utiliser de nombreux providers de machines virtuelles tels que VirtualBox , VMware et Docker, mais à mon avis VirtualBox est le plus simple à utiliser et il est également l'option par défaut dans Vagrant.
Notre première étape consiste à installer VirtualBox, vous pouvez télécharger et installer la dernière version pour votre système d'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teamdevops</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Your First App Using C++ Builder (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ideradevtools/building-your-first-app-using-c-builder-part-2-44lk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ideradevtools/building-your-first-app-using-c-builder-part-2-44lk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T17:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to our series about creating a reminder application in C++Builder!
Our last article discussed how to set up C++Builder, design the user interface by dragging and dropping components, and write code to control some components.
If you haven’t read: Building Your First App Using C++ Builder (Part 1)
This part will integrate SQLite into the application and attempt to store reminders added by users into the database.
After adding reminders to the database, we will display reminders to users when they are requested.
C++Builder allows you to make use of several databases in one program with its FireDAC library. We will integrate our SQLite database into this application.
To accomplish this, we need to begin by downloading and installing the SQLite database. Feel free to choose whiche…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IderaDevTools</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safe and simple AWS credential management for your Symfony/PHP application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikolastojilj12/safe-and-simple-aws-credential-management-for-your-symfony-php-application-29i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikolastojilj12/safe-and-simple-aws-credential-management-for-your-symfony-php-application-29i"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T16:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


If you have a Symfony/PHP application which needs to connect to AWS and use some of its services (S3, Secrets Manager,...) and you want to avoid pushing credentials to your Git repository or revealing them to any third party (ex. deployment, testing or code review tools), then follow this guide. 
This guide will show you how to quickly and safely integrate AWS authentication both on your local development environment and on the server, both on bare metal and by using Docker.
Note that this is all available on the official AWS Documentation portal... scattered across multiple pages and documentation sections and buried in walls of text.
AWS SDK for PHP (install in your project with composer require aws/aws-sdk-php) is a library which you'll use the most when working with AWS …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikola Stojiljkovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instalando somente atualizações de segurança no Amazon Linux 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rafaelonline/instalando-somente-atualizacoes-de-seguranca-no-amazon-linux-2-1k7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rafaelonline/instalando-somente-atualizacoes-de-seguranca-no-amazon-linux-2-1k7k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T16:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sabe aquele servidor solitário ou então que a aplicação só roda em um IaaS? 
É muito provável que as atualizações tenham ficado um pouco de lado (leia-se nunca feito) e chega um momento que será necessário fazer a atualização, nesse momento bate aquele medo de atualizar e quebrar algo, não é?.
O que podemos fazer é atualizar o mínimo necessário (e rezar), normalmente só atualizar o que representa um problema de segurança.
Para nos ajudar podemos utilizar a flag --security na execução do yum.
Antes de começarmos vamos olhar uma saída padrão de um yum update, repare na quantidade de pacotes que serão instalados (10) e atualizados (96)

1 – Garante que o pacote yum-plugin-security esteja instalado:
# yum -y install yum-plugin-security

2 - Você pode listar todas as atualizações de segurança disponíveis com o seguinte comando:
# yum --security check-update

3 – Agora vamos fazer a instalação somente as atualizações de segurança com o menor update possível
# yum --security update-minimal

Compare com a primeira imagem, agora serão instalados (7) e atualizados (50).

Dica extra.
Precisa fazer isso em vários servidores? Utilize o Ansible, com o parâmetro security: yes, para isso :)
- name: Upgrade all packages
  yum:
    name: '*'
    state: latest
    security: yes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Conceição</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript and why should you care?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abhirajb/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-care-285k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abhirajb/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-care-285k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T15:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I  am sure that in your web development career you must have used JavaScript at least once. And I am sure you must have found it very useful and very powerful. But what if I say there is another language that is just as powerful as JavaScript and has way lesser bugs when compared to when you use JavaScript in your app.
That language is TypeScript.
What is TypeScript?
If you know JavaScript, it mustn't be a problem switching to TypeScript as it essentially has the same concepts as JavaScript except a few of TypeScript's own concepts.
So what are the advantages of using TypeScript?
Concepts similar to JavaScript


TypeScript is type-safe


It keeps JavaScript in check


Runs on multiple places


Type Inference


It is developed and maintained by Microsoft



Let's move on to some testimonials!
TypeScript is widely used and loved by developers around the world. Here are some testimonials given by popular companies which is another indication that switching to TypeScript is worth it.
According to Slack, the switch to TypeScript made their life a lot easier in terms of bug-fixing and productivity. They also said Static Analysis which analyzes your code and tries to infer types and warns the developer in advance before the code even runs.


According to Airbnb, TypeScript prevented 38% of the bugs based on their analysis.



TypeScript lets developers be productive and safe at the same time.
In StackOverflow's developer survey in 2020, TypeScript was declared to be the 2nd most loved programming language
I hope I was able to share some knowledge through this post.
Let's connect!
Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhiraj Bhowmick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React with TypeScript: Optional Props with Default Values]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fullstackchris/react-with-typescript-optional-props-with-default-values-33nc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fullstackchris/react-with-typescript-optional-props-with-default-values-33nc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T15:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Straight to the Code


There's an example repository scaffolded with create-react-app which I've created for this post. Probably of most interest is the component FancyTitle which uses the default props pattern discussed in this blog post.
Now let's get into the details of the pattern.
When using TypeScript with React, it's easy enough to define optional props. With your props interface, you simply apply the optional parameter symbol ?:
interface IMyComponentRequiredProps {
  someRequiredProp: string;
  someOptionalProp?: string;
}

But what if we want default values for our optional props in the case when they are not specified? 
A rather elegant way to do it is to define two separate interfaces, one for the required props, and one for the optional props. For example, if our component is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Frewin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a simple portfolio with Argo Tunnels and containers for fun 🚀 - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afrocoder/deploying-a-simple-portfolio-with-argo-tunnels-and-containers-for-fun-part-2-2n8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afrocoder/deploying-a-simple-portfolio-with-argo-tunnels-and-containers-for-fun-part-2-2n8l"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T15:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alright so now that I finally got done with part one of this blog post, here is part 2!
By now you should have Cloudflare Argo tunnel and Gitlab runner running.
$ podman ps
CONTAINER ID  IMAGE                                  COMMAND               CREATED     STATUS                PORTS       NAMES
31f46243cbe9  docker.io/gitlab/gitlab-runner:alpine  run --user=gitlab...  8 days ago  Up About an hour ago              gitlab-runner

$ systemctl --user status cloudflared
Loaded: loaded (/home/leon/.config/systemd/user/cloudflared.service; enabled; vendor preset: enabled)
Active: active (running) since Sun 2021-10-10 14:51:26 IST; 1h 8min ago

For Gitlab CI/CD to work you need to add a .gitlab-ci.yml, in the root folder of your project This is like the main ingredient.
This is what my .gitlab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor M1 MacBook Air Power Use with InfluxDB®]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luiyongsheng/monitor-m1-macbook-air-power-use-with-influxdb-fc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luiyongsheng/monitor-m1-macbook-air-power-use-with-influxdb-fc9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T14:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some reasons, I want to monitor the power usage of my M1 MacBook Air. The quickest way to grab power related system information directly from the macOS Terminal is actually using the powermetrics command. However, printing out the results on screen doesn’t meet my monitoring requirements, therefore, I try to think of a better solution to store and visualise the data.
After a quick search on Google, I decided to use InfluxDB as my Time-Series Database to record the power usage signal because it provides an easy-to-use and easy-to-configure dashboard feature.
Read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lui Yong Sheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an acquisition Funnel in React with Xstate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jbrocher/building-an-acquisition-funnel-in-react-with-xstate-4hna</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jbrocher/building-an-acquisition-funnel-in-react-with-xstate-4hna"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T14:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building (and maintaining) an acquisition funnel is something that most development teams will be asked to do at some point. This is no small task as this funnel will often be the  main entry point to the company products or services. This means that such a funnel needs to be completely reliable to avoid losing customers to bugs, and fully flexible to allow the marketing team to optimize the conversion rate. 
In this two-part article we'll see how to accomplish that easily by using a strong programming pattern: a Finite State Machine. We'll be using React and Xstate for the implementation, but the principles can be applied to any stack really. 
Today in part 1, we'll see how to implement the state machine that powers the funnel, and building the actual steps and handling user data will be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jbrocher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to send emails using Gmail and NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abohalema98/how-to-send-emails-using-gmail-and-nodejs-2g02</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abohalema98/how-to-send-emails-using-gmail-and-nodejs-2g02"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T14:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this artical we will learn How to send emails using Gmail and NodeJS
Nodemailer:
Sending emails is a common feature that is present in many applications. This feature is used to notify user about news, like a newsletter, about your product status when it’s facing to an issue, recovery password and so on.
Step 1: Installing the nodemailer.
Step 2: Connecting with the Gmail
// create reusable transporter object using the default SMTP transport
let transporter = nodemailer.createTransport({ service: 'gmail', auth: { user: youremail@gmail.com, pass: youremail password, }, });
Step 3: Configure Gmail account to accept less secure apps
To enable it you need to go to https://myaccount.google.com/ and select your Google Account. Then go to Security in the left sidebar and search by “Less secure app access”.
step 4: Definitely sending emails.
transporter.sendMail({ from: '"Your Name" youremail@gmail.com', // sender address to: "receiverone@gmail.com, receivertwo@outlook.com", // list of receivers subject: "Medium @edigleyssonsilva ✔", // Subject line text: "There is a new article. It's about sending emails, check it out!", // plain text body html: "There is a new article. It's about sending emails, check it out!", // html body }) .then(info => { console.log({info}); }) .catch(console.error);
Note that in the createTransport we only pass an attribute called service where we define it asgmail and the auth with our credentials.
{ info: { accepted: [ 'receiver@gmail.com' ], rejected: [], envelopeTime: 871, messageTime: 651, messageSize: 747, response: '250 2.0.0 OK 1615152446 m6sm5222884qtx.3 - gsmtp', envelope: { from: 'fromemail@gmail.com', to: [Array] }, messageId: '95e9c9a0-9c20-fcda-1873-7f16aec2b293@gmail.com' } }]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamed Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu/Debian/Ceph/Pardus Local Mirror, Repository Kurulum with Ftp, Http and Https Used apt-mirror, Rsyncmirror and Wget]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aslanfatih/ubuntu-debian-ceph-pardus-local-mirror-repository-kurulum-with-ftp-http-and-https-used-apt-mirror-rsyncmirror-and-wget-2em8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aslanfatih/ubuntu-debian-ceph-pardus-local-mirror-repository-kurulum-with-ftp-http-and-https-used-apt-mirror-rsyncmirror-and-wget-2em8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[İnternet hızından, güvenlik sebebiyle ya da intranet ağınızdan dolayı apt için local yansı kurmanız gerekebilir.
Aşağıda ülke bazında yakın depoları kullanarak yansı oluşturabiliriz.
Ubuntu: https://launchpad.net/ubuntu/+archivemirrors 

Debian: https://wiki.debian.org/SourcesList#Repository_URL | https://debgen.simplylinux.ch/ 

Ceph: https://download.ceph.com/ 

Pardus: https://belge.pardus.org.tr/display/PYMBB/Pardus+Repo+Mirrorlama
Bu işlem için ilgili makinede yeterince disk alanı(TB olması tavsiye edilir) ayrıca bonding nic ve simetrik yüksek seviyede net bandwidth olması tavsiye edilir.
sudo apt install apt-mirror proftpd-basic apache2 rsync wget git

Konuya girmeden önce, defaultta yüklenen apt-mirror paketinde bazı sorunlar mevcut bu yüzden aşağıdaki ilgili repodaki apt-mirror’u k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatih ASLAN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#5 Best Website To learn Web Development 💯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepakguptacoder/5-best-website-to-learn-web-development-6cj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepakguptacoder/5-best-website-to-learn-web-development-6cj"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T13:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Due to COVID 19 situation The whole world has shifted to digital platform which affect the website field a lot that result to a better future and New generation.
Web development is a going popular since 2019 to now a days 25lakh people are making the website and also the children are making application or website.

W3School

FreeCodeCamp
[Mozilla Developer Network]

Mozilla Developer Network

Coursera
Some of the useful courses by Coursera

Udemy
If you found this post helpful then please give it a unicorn and share to those who wanted to learn Web Development. Your support will be appreciated!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux sistemlere sertifika ekleme]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aciklab/linux-sistemlere-sertifika-ekleme-m34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aciklab/linux-sistemlere-sertifika-ekleme-m34"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T12:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 standartı, özellikle HTTPS'in de içinde bulunduğu TLS/SSL protokollerinin kullandığı şifreleme standartı olarak kullanılmaktadır. Açık kaynak kodlu openssl uygulaması da bu standartı kullanarak bir çok süreci yürütmektedir.
Windows sertifika sistemlerinde genellikle üretilen sertifikalar CER uzantılı olmaktadır. Bu sertifikalar çıktı alınırken DER encoded ve Base64 encoded (PEM) olarak seçilebilmektedir. Genellikle varsayılan olarak DER seçili olduğu için çoğunlukla DER olarak tanımlanmış .CER dosyasıları görebilirsiniz.

DER formatındaki sertifikaları gördüğünüzde dosyanın içinde binary olarak karmaşık formlar olduğunu görürsünüz. (ornek.der)
0A0)N   *�H��
N��*�0
     *�H��
�9�{aGk��.�M�.EV��"!\�H�� �iMN���w��k�3�1H�Ў�<!�s��V%3�}�/�t��?�H���V�;���^��nȯ��3qe�|�M�����&*}CXs|M����.8���…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Orhun Akkirman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do Docker Volumes enable persistence for Containers? | Docker made easy #4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alubhorta/how-do-docker-volumes-enable-persistence-for-containers-docker-made-easy-4-5fgc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alubhorta/how-do-docker-volumes-enable-persistence-for-containers-docker-made-easy-4-5fgc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T12:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand the persistence issue with Containers, how Volumes and Bind mounts address them, how to manage them using the docker cli and some useful persistence topics
What the heck is a Docker Volume and why does it matter?
TL;DR - persistence.
If you wanna know what that means or how, that's what we will discuss in this blog.
This blog is the fourth in a series of blogs and videos I call - Docker Made Easy.
I recommend going through the previous ones to help you get a more wholesome understanding of Docker.
Links to the previous blogs -
What is Docker?
How do Docker Images work?
The Docker Container Lifecycle
Alright. Here's a quick agenda for this blog:
the problem we're dealing with
the solution
types of mounts, their differences, and reasoning behind the preferred option
docker cli usa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhim Ferdous</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 years working on a daily basis with Typescript and I had no idea generics were capable of doing that 🤯!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxime1992/5-years-working-on-a-daily-basis-with-typescript-and-i-had-no-idea-typescript-generics-were-capable-of-doing-that-21p6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxime1992/5-years-working-on-a-daily-basis-with-typescript-and-i-had-no-idea-typescript-generics-were-capable-of-doing-that-21p6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T11:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Context


An API which we don't own can return an object containing the same property, with a suffix going from 1 to 3. Example:
interface Order {
  // some unique keys
  id: string;
  name: string;

  // some keys "grouped" by 3 
  price1: number;
  price2: number;
  price3: number;

  quantity1: number;
  quantity2: number;
  quantity3: number;

  shippingDate1: string;
  shippingDate2: string;
  shippingDate3: string;
}

Notes:
Why is that API not exposing prices, quantities and shippingDates as arrays is beyond the point here. Let's just assume we consume an API that we cannot modify
This is just an example and the returned type could have way more properties like that, so we don't want to have to make the whole remapping manually
While the backend may expose it this way for a good rea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typesafe express routes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/japiirainen/typesafe-express-routes-4293</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/japiirainen/typesafe-express-routes-4293"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T10:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I've spent a lot of time writing Haskell. In Haskell-land there's a lot of bleeding-edge research stuff, which is cool, but most likely not very applicable for my day-to-day work. If there's one thing that all haskellers love, it must be type-safety. That's what this post is about, bringing some type-safety to our node.js apps, more specifically express or koa apps. I'll try to point to some flaws I see in the typical way of writing express/koa apps with typescript and propose a "better" way.
Let's start by defining routes we would like to implement. Suppose you are writing some CRUD operations for some "users" resource. We will use the following endpoint schema as an example.
GET /users     => Ok<[User]>
GET /users/:id => Ok<User> | NotFound
POST /users    => Ok | BadRequest
PUT …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joona Piirainen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typesafe express routes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/japiirainen/typesafe-express-routes-4293</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/japiirainen/typesafe-express-routes-4293"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T10:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I've spent a lot of time writing Haskell. In Haskell-land there's a lot of bleeding-edge research stuff, which is cool, but most likely not very applicable for my day-to-day work. If there's one thing that all haskellers love, it must be type-safety. That's what this post is about, bringing some type-safety to our node.js apps, more specifically express or koa apps. I'll try to point to some flaws I see in the typical way of writing express/koa apps with typescript and propose a "better" way.
Let's start by defining routes we would like to implement. Suppose you are writing some CRUD operations for some "users" resource. We will use the following endpoint schema as an example.
GET /users     => Ok<[User]>
GET /users/:id => Ok<User> | NotFound
POST /users    => Ok | BadRequest
PUT …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joona Piirainen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mootools Fx.Scroll bug with IE6/IE7]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wpsyed/mootools-fx-scroll-bug-with-ie6-ie7-3ig8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wpsyed/mootools-fx-scroll-bug-with-ie6-ie7-3ig8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T09:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ou may be having trouble getting Fx.Scroll to scroll to the correct coordinates in Microsoft browsers. Apparently Mootools 1.2.1 introduced a new bug that as yet has not been cured by the developers.
There's a temporary solution posted in this forum that involves a replacement for Fx.Scroll. The author created a class called Fx.Scroll2 that corrects these issues.
Simply place the class somewhere in your JS load sequence after mootools itself, and call Fx.Scroll2 instead of Mootools own Fx.Scroll. Problem fixed. Hopefully the Mootools team will have this one resolved on their next update. Here is the class:
Simply place the class somewhere in your JS load sequence after mootools itself, and call Fx.Scroll2 instead of Mootools own Fx.Scroll. Problem fixed. Hopefully the Mootools team will ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed Saadullah Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triggering File Downloads with Mootools]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wpsyed/triggering-file-downloads-with-mootools-3bi0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wpsyed/triggering-file-downloads-with-mootools-3bi0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T09:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a javascript links that uses AJAX (or, more accurately, an asynchronous http request) to trigger a file download, usually results in disappointment. Headers returned by a PHP script called asynchronously do not trigger a download in the browser.
If you want to have a link to a file download that does not cause a page refresh or opening a superfluous browser window in order to make a file download happen, it's actually quite easy with only a few lines of JS. There's no "AJAX" here, but it sure feels like it. The method relies on adding an invisible iFrame to the DOM, and simply loading the script triggering the download into that iFrame:
[download a file]
if($('download')){
$filename = 'download.csv';
//this is where you would format your data, selecting and looping through rows from your database for example.
//here we just output one line:
$out = "this, is, a , csv\n";
header("Cache-Control: must-revalidate, post-check=0, pre-check=0");
header("Content-Length: " . strlen($out));
header("Content-type: text/x-csv");
header("Content-Disposition: attachment; filename=$filename");
echo $out;
exit;]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed Saadullah Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage your Node.js version on Replit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/canaris/how-to-manage-your-node-js-version-on-replit-3n0p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/canaris/how-to-manage-your-node-js-version-on-replit-3n0p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T09:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage your Node.js version on Replit



First, go to Replit and create a REPL. Select BASH and NOT Node.js (We'll install it later). Funnily enough, at the time of writing, if you ran node -v, you would see v14.17.1 (which is an LTS version, and also considering we didn't install Node).
Select Shell (which is just beside Console)
Copy and paste the following code below into Shell. On Windows, it's Ctrl+Shift+V. You can change the 16 below to any version you desire.




  curl -o- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nvm-sh/nvm/v0.37.2/install.sh | bash
  export NVM_DIR="/config/nvm"
  [ -s "$NVM_DIR/nvm.sh" ] && \. "$NVM_DIR/nvm.sh"  # This loads nvm
  [ -s "$NVM_DIR/bash_completion" ] && \. "$NVM_DIR/bash_completion"  # This loads nvm bash_completion
  nvm install 16 
  nvm use 16

Wait for a while. You may choose to go to the toilet or grab a few bites in the meantime.
After the code below has finished running and installing Node.js, run node -v && npm -v. You should see an updated Node.js (v16.x.x) and NPM (v8.x.x at time of writing) version. 
Run the following to test:




 echo console.log(`Node version: ${process.versions.node}`) > test.js
 node test.js

You should now see an updated/different Node version, depending on which version you installed and used earlier on.
That's it! You can now install and use any Node.js version you wish!
Post was last updated on 10/10/2021]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DET171</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NativeScript vs React Native: which one to choose for Native app development in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akveo/nativescript-vs-react-native-which-one-to-choose-for-native-app-development-in-2021-1j71</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akveo/nativescript-vs-react-native-which-one-to-choose-for-native-app-development-in-2021-1j71"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T07:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React Native and NativeScript occupy a special place in the cross-platform development sphere. These frameworks, once created, have changed the multiplatform development paradigm, allowing developers to create both performant and user-friendly applications. Since then, they’ve been gaining fans and contributors from all over the world, facilitating the app's development process and making it easy, cheap, and enjoyable.  
However, despite the common traits and purpose, React Native and Native Script do the job in their way. That’s exactly what this article will be centered about.
Here, we will clash React Native vs Native Script and reveal:
The essence of the React Native and Native Script; 
What apps you can create with each framework;
The difference between them by the several vital perfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Tsurbeliov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips Every React Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/5-tips-every-react-developer-should-know-1ghh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ruppysuppy/5-tips-every-react-developer-should-know-1ghh"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T05:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React is an amazing tool to build Front End Applications. This article will provide you some tips which you can immediately implement to up your React game and help you become a better React Developer, Write better code and even help you ace the interviews that you were initially scared of.
Lazy Loading is the design pattern which delays the loading or initialization of objects or resources until they are required. This improves performance drastically. In the case of React, the reduced bundle size leads to faster initial load time, which is crucial these days with dwindling attention span.
Luckily for us, React makes implementing Lazy Loading very easy for developers. All you need to do is wrap dynamic import statement import() with React.lazy.
Let's consider we have a Counter.js file.
//…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapajyoti Bose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My first Hacktoberfest PR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jli/my-first-hacktoberfest-pr-3c9j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jli/my-first-hacktoberfest-pr-3c9j"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T00:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So during this past week of October, Hacktoberfest started and I've been trying to get started with some PRs. This is my first time participating Hacktoberfest and I wasn't really sure what to expect. It's very intimidating for me to see so many huge projects that I don't feel like I'm experienced enough to help with, and try to find something in them to help fix or add to. So I wanted to start with something maybe smaller and work my way up to a larger project I am interested in.
It felt a lot harder to find something simple than I expected it to be, there were a lot of cool projects that looked very complicated and I wasn't really sure how to solve their issues. It really helped that my professor taught us how to use GitHub's search features to find specific labels such as the "good firs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JLi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debut to Bug-Hunting Cybersecurity and writing Quality Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mannangoyal/debut-to-bug-hunting-cybersecurity-and-writing-quality-code-272c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mannangoyal/debut-to-bug-hunting-cybersecurity-and-writing-quality-code-272c"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T22:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Bugs?
A software bug is an error in a computer program that causes it to produce unexpected results or to behave in a disruptive fashion.
Albeit a bug can be a very innocent flaw, a careless mistake the impact it can have can still be exponentially larger than an exploit due to a big logical error in a code base.
eg. a small rounding error in the calculation of an orbit of a satellite can cause major financial damages with many other implications like space pollution.
Hence, every developer should be aware of basic cybersecurity practices!
How to reduce the number of bugs in your code?
Bringing a structure to your project can be immensely helpful, This structure can be brought by organizing your code but more importantly in your project and amongst your team.
To achieve this we ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mannan Goyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Data Structure - Linked list]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/riviergrullon/javascript-datastructure-linked-list-2ocn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/riviergrullon/javascript-datastructure-linked-list-2ocn"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T22:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Definition


A linked list is a linear data structure that represents a collection of elements that we'll call nodes , where each node points to the next one or previous one, the first node in the linked list is the head and the last is the tail

In the linked list each node must be have the following properties:
The main properties of the linked list are:
Size: The number of nodes in the linked list 
Head: The first node
Tail: The last node
and the main operations of a linked list data structure are: 
insertAt: Inserts a node at the specific index.


removeAt: Removes the node at the specific index.


getAt: Retrieves the element at the specific index.


Clear: Empties the linked list


Reverse(in this case): Reverses the order of nodes in the linked list




  
  
  Implementation





c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rivier Grullon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como desabilitar o cache no Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/como-desabilitar-o-cache-no-angular-5bog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/como-desabilitar-o-cache-no-angular-5bog"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T19:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Um dos grandes problemas que enfrentei ao atualizar o frontend de aplicações angular foi o cache. 
Praticamente todos os navegadores mantêm um cache da aplicação no computador do cliente para conseguir carregar a aplicação de forma mais rápida e com menor consumo de dados e isso é excelente. Entretanto, um efeito colateral é que as atualizações podem demorar para serem entregues para o cliente. Como consequência, o cliente pode ficar horas ou dias com uma versão com um bug que já foi corrigido.
Em sistemas internos de empresas, isso pode resultar em ligações ou tickets constantes para a equipe de suporte técnico, causando uma sobrecarga na equipe. Quando estamos falando de aplicações fornecidas para clientes externos à empresa, pode ser um ponto de frustração e insatisfação com o produto.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to bypass input filter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ks1912/how-to-bypass-input-filter-59kd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ks1912/how-to-bypass-input-filter-59kd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T18:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before going into client-side filters let’s understand what client-side filters are. As we know nowadays there are a lot of safer websites available in the market and to make themselves safer they use different kinds of filters also which can be categories in two parts :
Client-Side Filters
Server-Side Filters
We can also say that when we give input and if it satisfies the criteria then it will be accepted otherwise it will raise an error.
For example: Entering letters in the phone number field or Inserting email without @ symbol
Client-Side Filter
On the client-side, the input is being checked on the by browser only which means before sending the input to the server Where on the server-side the input is being sent to the server, and then the server checks whether is valid or not. It is ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bscript/application-security-engineer-5dn8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bscript/application-security-engineer-5dn8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T18:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When you start working as an application security engineer, you'll expect to find straightforward tasks to do. But this is not the case because each company has its vision and strategies to handle data security, which can let us infer that every organization's security maturity may differ from one to another.
Viewing data breaches and cyber incidents all the time proves that no one out there has a mature cyber security program.
If you are already working in this field, I imagine that you sometimes feel that you're achieving nothing and you are more invisible inside the organization. The bigest challenge I see is how to increase your visibility and have more transparency with your manager and the rest of your co-workers.
In this article, I'd like to share what I've learned wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bour Abdelhadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple CRUD App with Express.js and SQLite based on MVC pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dejansdev/simple-crud-app-with-express-js-sqlite-mvc-pattern-4nd8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dejansdev/simple-crud-app-with-express-js-sqlite-mvc-pattern-4nd8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T17:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DISCLAIMER: This is not "the best way" or "should do" blog post, instead I will just try to share my experience and what I find to work out.
The goal is to create an application that will implement CRUD operations in Node.js using the Express.js framework and SQLite database, using the MVC design pattern. It will be a simple To Do List Application in which the user can Create, Read, Update and Delete a task.
The application is available on the following link To Do Application, and the complete code is available on the GitHub repository.
Getting started
Template engine
Routes
Database
MVC architectural pattern
More setup
Create task
Delete and update task
Data validation
Conclusion
The first step is to create a new directory and initialize the project using a terminal.
~/To-Do-Application$ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dejan Samardzija</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In case anyone is looking to learn serverless by doing a hands-on project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daltonfury42/in-case-anyone-is-looking-to-learn-serverless-by-doing-a-hands-on-project-kcd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daltonfury42/in-case-anyone-is-looking-to-learn-serverless-by-doing-a-hands-on-project-kcd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T17:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In case anyone is looking to learn serverless by doing a hands-on project, let me know. 
I have a beginner friendly backend requirement. 
It will be simple CRUD of three resources.


Data will be stored to DynamoDB.


For language, you can use golang or node.


All code you write will be open source under GPL. 


Our repositories are participating in Hatoberfest.



The project: simplq.me is an open source queue management software. The backend is written in Springboot and we want to migrate it to serverless as it's more economic given our traffic volume.
https://github.com/SimplQ/simplQ-frontend
https://github.com/SimplQ/simplQ-backend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daltonfury42</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a SOC Team Members Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rahulwoll/what-does-a-soc-team-members-do-3ocg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rahulwoll/what-does-a-soc-team-members-do-3ocg"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T16:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security operations center, known as a SOC – pronounced “sock” 🧦 - is a team of experts that proactively monitor an organization’s ability to operate securely.
Members of a SOC team are responsible for a variety of activities, including proactive monitoring, incident response and recovery, remediation activities, compliance, and coordination and context.
Proactive Monitoring
Incident Response and Recovery
For example, that recovery can include activities such as handling acute malware or ransomware incidents. 
Remediation Activities 
For Example, using information obtained from log files and other sources, a SOC member can recommend a better network segmentation strategy or a better system patching regimen. Improving existing CyberSecurity is a major responsibility of a SOC. 
Compliance
Organisation secure themselves through conformity to a security policy, as well as external security standards, such as ISO 27001x, the NIST CyberSecurity Framework(CSF) and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Organisations need a SOC to help ensure that they are compliant with an important security standards and best practices. 
Coordination and Context
Above all, a SOC team member helps an organisation coordinate desperate elements and services and provide visualized, useful information. Part of this coordination is the ability to provide a helpful, useful set of narratives for activities on the network. These narratives help shape a company's CyberSecurity policy and posture for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promisify setTimeout]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sakethkowtha/promisify-settimeout-2knn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sakethkowtha/promisify-settimeout-2knn"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T15:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code to promisify setTimeout





const delay = (time) => new Promise((resolve, reject) => setTimeout(resolve, time))

delay(2000).then(() => console.log('Hello i will get logged after 2 second(s)'))]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sakethk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding the loading component (spinner) to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-loading-component-spinner-to-an-angular-application-4mk0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-loading-component-spinner-to-an-angular-application-4mk0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T12:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
ngx-spinner is a loading (spinner) component library with more than 50 different types.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the application with the Angular base structure using the @angular/cli with the route file and the SCSS style format.
ng new angular-spinner
? Would you like to add Angular routing? Yes
? Which stylesheet format would you like to use? SCSS   [ https://sass-lang.com/documentation/syntax#scss                ]
CREATE angular-spinner/README.md…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look into Node.Js Interview Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudytech147/look-into-node-js-interview-questions-2l2k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudytech147/look-into-node-js-interview-questions-2l2k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T12:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is a cross-stage server-side JavaScript runtime climate that is a very incredible stage for applications. Node.js is lightweight when contrasted with different adversaries that make it very proficient for the advancement of information escalated huge scope applications, for example, video web-based locales, and other web applications. 

Node.js is very like Ruby's EventMachine and Python's Twisted yet a stride in front of them. It has an occasion-driven design that has the ability of nonconcurrent I/O tasks, which makes it equipped for dealing with numerous simultaneous solicitations. 
One of the principal up-sides of Node.js which makes it more famous is that it runs on different stages like Windows, Linux, macOS, Unix, and some more.
node js interview questions for freshers & experienced professionals.



What can you tell me about Node.js?
Highlight some of the key features of Node.js?
Is Node.js completely based on a single thread?
What does event-driven programming mean?
Define “I/O” operations?
How Node.js works?
Name the various API functions supported by Node.js?
What do you understand by the control flow functions?
Explain NPM.
What are the two arguments that async.queue takes as input?
State the difference between Node.js vs Ajax?
Describe the advantages and disadvantages of Node.js?
What are the types of streams present in Node.js?
Name some of the popularly used libraries in Node.js?
What is libuv?
Mention the types of modules offered by Node.js.
What do you know about callback hell?
What is package.json?
Does Node.js support multi-core platforms?
Explain the role of the request process in Node.js.
What is the chaining process in Node.js?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cloudytech147</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create and remove network on Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-create-and-remove-network-on-docker-1lig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-create-and-remove-network-on-docker-1lig"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T12:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now i will show you how to create and remove network on Docker, lets follow the instructions :)
first, lets see the list of network
docker network ls

then create new network by type this command with name  'demo'
docker network create --subnet=172.16.0.0/24 --gateway=172.16.0.1 demo

at the end, to see the details of 'demo', you can type
docker network inspect demo

to remove network on Dokcer, you can type this
docker network rm demo

N/B : ip address and name of network can custom by you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Pepuho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhanced social share card | @dsabyte.com]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ats1999/enhanced-social-share-card-dsabyte-com-4nb1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ats1999/enhanced-social-share-card-dsabyte-com-4nb1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T08:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Share blog after writing it, with just one click



Previously, there was just social media icons, but now the card has a personalize message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic CRUD Service in Angular: Part 2 - What is CRUD?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-2-what-is-crud-30ek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-2-what-is-crud-30ek"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T08:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Tobias Fischer on Unsplash.
This article is a part of a series about how to create Generic CRUD Service & Models in Angular:
Part 1 - Understanding Generics
👉 Part 2 - What is CRUD?

Part 3 - Generic CRUD Model (coming soon...)

Part 4 - Generic CRUD Service in Angular (coming soon...)




  
  
  What is CRUD?



Create, Read, Update, and Delete 👉 CRUD
Starting from the acronym, CRUD means create, read, update, and delete. These are the four main functionalities that must be provided by all models when building APIs.
Firstly let's explain some basics... An API is a set of definitions and protocols for building and integrating application software. It's the main contract between frontend and backend regarding their communication. An API in order to be RESTful, it should fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikos Anifantis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How Service Works when injected in different Levels]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dasaradhanimmala/angular-how-service-works-when-injected-in-different-levels-5e7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dasaradhanimmala/angular-how-service-works-when-injected-in-different-levels-5e7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T07:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video , I clearly explained about how service works when it is injected in different Levels like Component Level, Module Level and App Level.
Explained step by step with practical examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dasaradh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are your Angular Services Singleton ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sanketmaru/are-your-angular-services-singleton-307f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sanketmaru/are-your-angular-services-singleton-307f"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T07:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular has the concept of services which allows to share the data between components.
In this blog we will learn about service instances creation in Angular.
What happens when we inject service in root of a lazy module, is the same instance used for multiple lazy modules.
What if we want to have a separate instance per module and per component ?
We will use the same code example as used in common chunks example. If you haven't gone through that blog do checkout to learn on why common chunks are created.
Let's begin then.
Let's start where we ended in the previous post. We have two lazy modules user and account and currently share the same toast module which is built in a separate chunk.
As we have given as @Injectable({ providedIn: "root" }) for the toast service, a singleton instance of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanket Maru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Easily Add Google Map to Your Webpage]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/how-to-easily-add-google-map-to-your-webpage-2jce</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/how-to-easily-add-google-map-to-your-webpage-2jce"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T06:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On most of the company websites, you will find locations or contacts page that displays that company location in that country or state in a google map along with the company address.
This is a pretty common requirement even for food or hotel business-related websites.
So in this article, we will see how to add a google map with the preferred location on your website.
Create a new folder with the name google-map-location-demo and create an index.html file inside it. Now, type ! (exclamation mark) in the file and press tab, so the default HTML code will automatically be added by emmet.
If you're not aware of emmet and its useful shortcuts, check out my this article.

You can change the title tag content as per your choice.
For this demo, we will show the Eiffel tower's location on the map.
So follow the below steps.
Navigate to https://maps.google.com/ and search for Eiffel Tower in the search box
Now, click on the Share icon and select the Embed a map option
Click on the COPY HTML button to copy the iframe tag into your clipboard
Now, open the index.html file, and inside the body tag, add the copied content

Now, If you open the file in the browser, you will see the map displayed

That's it about this short tutorial.
Check out my recently published Mastering Redux course.
In this course, you will build 3 apps along with a food ordering app and you'll learn:
Basic and advanced Redux
How to manage the complex state of array and objects
How to use multiple reducers to manage complex redux state
How to debug Redux application
How to use Redux in React using react-redux library to make your app reactive.
How to use redux-thunk library to handle async API calls and much more
and then finally we'll build a complete food ordering app from scratch with stripe integration for accepting payments and deploy it to the production.

Want to stay up to date with regular content regarding JavaScript, React, Node.js? Follow me on LinkedIn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 IT Company India And Best IT Company India]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/webforest/top-10-it-company-india-and-best-it-company-india-24ab</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/webforest/top-10-it-company-india-and-best-it-company-india-24ab"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T05:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1.Tata Consultancy Service
https://www.tcs.com/
Tata Consultancy Service is the largest IT Company in Revenue. TCS is a provider of IT services, consulting, and business solutions that have partnered with the world's largest corporations in their journey of change over the past fifty years. Top 10 it company India.
TCS offers a consulted, empowered, comprehensive, integrated business portfolio, technology, and engineering solutions and solutions. TCS is the largest company in India in terms of Market Capitalization. It is the largest of the top 10 IT companies in India in 2021. And top it company India.
Part of the Tata team, India's largest business group, TCS has more than 420,000 highly trained consulting professionals around the world in 50 countries. TCS is the largest software compan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Webforest Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-prepare-for-ransomware-attacks-81h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-prepare-for-ransomware-attacks-81h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T00:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks continue to increase, using techniques that are growing more and more sophisticated and targeted. Security and risk management leaders need to look beyond just the endpoints to help protect the organization from ransomware.
What exactly is Ransomware:
How does ransomware work?
Why is ransomware spreading?
Ransomware Defense Life Cycle

How to defend against ransomware:

Anatomy of a Ransomware Attack

Final and more important:
Thank you very much for your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pablosalas81</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to host a Wordpress site on AWS Lightsail FOR FREE!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/howtoubuntu/how-to-host-a-wordpress-site-on-aws-lightsail-for-free-f18</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/howtoubuntu/how-to-host-a-wordpress-site-on-aws-lightsail-for-free-f18"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T00:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Wordpress?


WordPress is the simplest, most popular way to create your own website or blog. In fact, WordPress powers over 40.0% of all the websites on the Internet. Yes – more than one in four websites that you visit are likely powered by WordPress!
To begin go to the AWS Control Panel and find the search bar. 
Lightsail and click the first service. Now you should see something like the following:

Create instance. Now scroll down and you will see Lightsail by default selected Wordpress. 
$5/month deal. Name your instance and then press the big button saying Create instance. Now wait 3 minutes for your VM (Instance) to load up. To know it is loaded up you will see the Wordpress icon blue and not gray. 
13.59.157.149. Once copied go to your broswer and paste it in with the following line:
13.59.157.149/wp-admin

You should see the following:

user is user but to find the password we need to go back to the terminal.
cat bitnami_application_password

Select the output and paste it into the password. Once you logged in you are done! You should see the following once logged in:

If you found this usful then please share this and follow me! Also check out my website where I also post everything from here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HowToUbuntu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure a Rails API with Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sirech/secure-a-rails-api-with-auth0-3o72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sirech/secure-a-rails-api-with-auth0-3o72"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to expose an API publicly on the Internet, authorization will be a requirement for you sooner or later. You want to verify that the client consuming the API has the appropriate permissions.
This guide is exactly about that. We’ll be securing an API written using Ruby On Rails, with Auth0 as the authorization server.
There’s a repository with the code so that you can follow along in Github.
I didn’t explain what I mean by securing an API yet. Essentially, we’re ensuring that protected routes are accessible only for the users with enough rights.
When it comes to security, it’s generally considered a bad idea to roll your own bespoke implementation. Instead, I’m using OAuth, a battle-tested and widely used authorization framework for web applications.
In this context, Auth0 fulfil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Fernández</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If you're not using linux...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/faulty/if-you-re-not-using-linux-22do</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/faulty/if-you-re-not-using-linux-22do"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T21:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Then, what are you doing?
But for real, Linux is open source, there is no telemetry, You can customize it to what you want it to be, it's lightweight and honestly it's just epic.
You can install it in 15~30 minutes and then you can enjoy your free and open source software!
The (basic) distro's
Elementary OS (Mac like)
Zorin OS (Windows-y)
Solus OS (Also Windows-y)
Ubuntu (Mac/Windows 11-y)
Manjaro (Arch-based and in many flavours.)
"Hands on" distro's
Arch (What I use.)
Gentoo (Very hands on)
Void (in musl version and glibc version)
kiss (super sexy distro)
GOD TIER
LFS (absolutely your distro, very hard)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Didier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nova ferramenta do Facebook para encontrar falhas de segurança em apps Android]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dgbarreto/nova-ferramenta-do-facebook-para-encontrar-falhas-de-seguranca-em-apps-android-4kia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dgbarreto/nova-ferramenta-do-facebook-para-encontrar-falhas-de-seguranca-em-apps-android-4kia"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T20:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Há alguns dias o Facebook liberou para o público uma ferramenta, até então caseira, para descobrir falhas de segurança e privacidade em aplicações Anndroid e Java. 
Batizada de Mariana Trench (MT) e distribuida de forma Open Source a ferramenta está em constante evolução e suporte pelo time de engenharia do Facebook. Ela é usada hoje em milhões de linhas de código no Whatsapp, Instagram e, claro, no próprio app do Facebook. Segundo o Facebook, na primeira metade de 2021, 50% das vulnerabilidades encontradas foram de forma automatizada.
O MT foi desenvolvido em Python e roda de forma estática no código. Está disponível (aqui)[https://github.com/facebook/mariana-trench/). O Facebook também deixou pronto um tutorial para facilitar nos primeiros passos. O tutorial pode ser acessado (aqui)[https://mariana-tren.ch/docs/getting-started/].]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Barreto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for ‘Developer Experience’]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353429</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-case-for-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T20:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good essay from Jean Yang. 
What I mean by developer experience is the sum total of how developers interface with their tools, end-to-end, day-in and day-out. Sure, there’s more focus than ever on how developers use and adopt tools, and 
…
The post The Case for ‘Developer Experience’ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Manage Open edX Environment Variables Using Doppler and Automating The Deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-manage-open-edx-environment-variables-using-doppler-and-automating-the-deployment-4c5e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-manage-open-edx-environment-variables-using-doppler-and-automating-the-deployment-4c5e"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets are a pain to manage and If you are using Ansible to maintain your application and its components there is a better way to do it. In this article, we see how Doppler can help us to simply and quickly manage environment variables for a complex system called Open edX. 
Open edX is an open-source platform you can use to create and host online courses. It was originally developed in 2012 by MIT and Harvard University and has since been adopted by organizations of all shapes and sizes to power a wide range of online learning use cases.
We use Ansible to provision and maintain our platform. If you are not familiar with Ansible, it's an open source Devops tool that automates the software provisioning and configuration. It building blocks are:
Ansible Playbooks which has 1 or multiple role…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cubite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Computer Programming?]]></title>
        <id>615d55e60d91c9077974d408</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's world, we are all heavily reliant on various software products that were carefully programmed by developers. But what is computer programming? In this article, I will provide a definition of programming, as well as examples of different types of programmers. I will also suggest a list of courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn On Dark Mode on Google – Chrome Black Theme Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6160836e804854468fda67bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-on-dark-mode-on-google-chrome-black-theme-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, lots of developers like to use dark mode. And it's no surprise, as activating dark mode reduces eye strain and leads to better eye health. It also helps both machines and humans perform better overall.  In this article, I will show you how to turn on the dark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>613f3c5e852f4307d372c7c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-drop-a-pin-on-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to save a new location you discovered on Google Maps, you need to drop a pin on that location.  In this article, I will show you how to drop a pin in Google Maps from your phone or computer. How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 8th October 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-8th-october-2021-554o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-8th-october-2021-554o"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T18:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello and welcome to this week's review. If you've been following this series for a while, I'll take a guess you already know my name, nevertheless, I'll state it again for those of you reading this for the first time. I am Habdul Hazeez, and I am your host for this series.
This week's review is packed with the entire theme of this series. From scam,  malware, bugs, you name it, this week's review has got it all.
Grab a cup of coffee, and let's get started.
Hundreds of scam apps hit over 10 million Android devices


One of the things I like about the folks at Arstechnica is that the title of their articles makes you want to read the article because it's always a complete summary of what the article entails, this one is not an exception.
For this article, I'll advise you to b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353374</id>
        <link href="https://katiekodes.com/jekyll-components-wysiwyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T17:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the pushback from Katie Kodes here. I’ve said in the past that I don’t think server-side languages haven’t quite nailed “building in components” as well as JavaScript has, but hey, this is a good point:
1. Any basic 
…
The post Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Excel File that Pulls Customer Data with WooCommerce and Python]]></title>
        <id>615dbaeb0d91c9077974defb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-excel-file-with-customers-data-with-woocommerce-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Hey, could you please send me our customers' emails? We’re about to launch a new marketing campaign and…we need them ASAP.” If you work in the Web department on a corporate level, you've probably heard this sentence hundreds of times. So, today I want to share how I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export your table data to a .csv file]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nisachampagne/export-your-table-data-to-a-csv-file-4ca0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nisachampagne/export-your-table-data-to-a-csv-file-4ca0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that my job has me learning a new thing ( or two :) ) every day. This time it was exporting table data to a .csv file that could therefore be used whichever way needed. Of course, there are many ways to go about this.
Lets set the project in view here: 
Now to figure out how to approach it. 
As I was figuring out how I wanted to work on this, my mind was on simple and to the point as we just want to create the file client-side. I found https://www.npmjs.com/package/file-saver to which suits my needs. Now all that's left is to implement the exportCSV function. 
In my typescript file,  I added the following:
 exportFile(data: any) {
    const replacer = (key, value) => value === null ? '' : value;
    const header = Object.keys(data[0]);
    let csv = data.map(row => header.map(fieldN…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisa Champagne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353066</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-tennis-trivia-app-with-next-js-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will be learning how to build a tennis trivia app using Next.js and Netlify. This technology stack has become my go-to on many projects. It allows for rapid development and easy deployment.
Without further ado let’s jump in!…
The post Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenley Dueck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353062</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-google-analytics-and-plausible-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw this blog post the other day: 58% of Hacker News, Reddit and tech-savvy audiences block Google Analytics. That’s an enticing title to me. I’ve had Google Analytics on this site literally from the day I launched it. …
The post Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Examples of 5 Common Observable Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/real-world-examples-of-5-common-observable-operators-48i7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/real-world-examples-of-5-common-observable-operators-48i7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article was originally published to my blog StackBlogger: Real World Examples of 5 Common Observable Operators
Reactive Extensions of JavaScript is a library for reactive programming. It is commonly known for its operators. The RxJS Operators are also known as Observable Operators.
What are Operators?
Operators are pure functions. They take observable as input and return output as observable.
map– a transformation operator works similar to Array.prototype.map
switchMap– cancels the inner observable when outer observable emits a value
catchError– catches the error and passes to error handling function
debounceTime– discards values if emitted in less than specified time
takeUntil– automatically unsubscribes from an observable
distinctUntilChanged– emits only distinct values and duplicate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filter in Angular with code example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tizhad/filter-in-angular-with-code-example-18g1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tizhad/filter-in-angular-with-code-example-18g1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T13:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being honest, I'm not a senior developer, but I do want to share things that I'm learning. Hopefully, it can be helpful.
If you are looking for an answer for this question " How can I filter an array in Angular", this post can help you.
You have an array of cars:
cars: ICar[] = [
    {
      'carId': 1,
      'carName': 'Toyota',
      'carCode': 'CAR-0023',
      'releaseDate': 'March 18, 2019',
      'description': 'this is a description',
      'price': 35000,
      'starRating': 4.2,
      'imageUrl': 'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1525609004556-c46c7d6cf023?ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxzZWFyY2h8M3x8Y2Fyc3xlbnwwfHwwfHw%3D&ixlib=rb-1.2.1&w=1000&q=80'
    },
    {
      'carId': 2,
      'carName': 'Bugatti test',
      'carCode': 'CAR-1123',
      'releaseDate': 'March 18, 2020',
      'desc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tizhad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS forkJoin: Definition and Real World Uses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/rxjs-forkjoin-definition-and-real-world-uses-98k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/rxjs-forkjoin-definition-and-real-world-uses-98k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The complete article is published here: RxJS forkJoin: Definition and Real World Uses
RxJS is Reactive Extensions of JavaScript. It is a library to work with Observables which make developers life easier. RxJS provides various operators to work with in Angular. In this article we will discuss about RxJS Observable forkJoin operator, its definition, real world uses, error handling, is it deprecated etc.
What is RxJS forkJoin
Is it deprecated ?
I will explain what I mean!
Initially forkJoin was accepting object arguments as rest parameter. That is deprecated and no longer used.
Now they updated the operator and ask to provide array of observables instead of object arguments. As the line itself saying in above screenshot- @deprecated
 — Use the version that takes an array of Observables inste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Method to Setup the Amped Wireless Extender]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wifiissues/method-to-setup-the-amped-wireless-extender-59c7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wifiissues/method-to-setup-the-amped-wireless-extender-59c7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T09:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The days we had no choice but to make all our connections with wire, are far gone. Technology has made it a lot easier. With a few technical tips, you will know how to complete the amped wireless setup. The wireless setup can be seen as very difficult but with the proper expert tips, you will get it done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Router Login Support</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance issues? Find your bottleneck with console.time()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/timetc/performance-issues-find-your-bottleneck-with-console-time-1bm1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/timetc/performance-issues-find-your-bottleneck-with-console-time-1bm1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T06:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My, since a little while beautiful, app called What?! was a little slow when opening files. A lot slower since the version before the big redesign. When you changed a lot it is hard to find a starting point. What you can do about this? You already read the title so you know the answer. Tldr; just try it.
The console.log() function is something most JS developers know, you can output anything to the console (for Node as well as the browser). I think a lot of developers do not know about console.time() though. Probably something you will use a lot less, but can be very useful.
Okay, so let’s find that slow little bastard of a function. What you need to know:
console.time(‘example’) will start a timer, where you also give it a name. You can start multiple timers (simultaneously), if choose di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim etc.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Your Own Code Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353112</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/writing-your-own-code-rules/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T23:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time on a project when it’s worth investing in tooling to protect the codebase. I’m not sure how to articulate when, but it’s somewhere after the project has proven to be something long-term and rough edges …
The post Writing Your Own Code Rules appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penetration and Security in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/didof/penetration-and-security-in-javascript-probing-double-getter-p47</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/didof/penetration-and-security-in-javascript-probing-double-getter-p47"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T23:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premise


Are you sure you are ensuring your code to be used as intended? Are you preventing it from beeing used in a malicious way?
If what comes your way is putting guards in your functions, this post will open up a world for you as this one was for me. Using checks is not enough.
You will be both wolf and sheep. I created the function below so that it had everything you need to learn attack and related defenses from the techniques:
Probing & Double Getter
Prototype Bribing
Primitive Illusion
The function is Connector, which receives an options configuration object. This must contain a property named address which must be the same as one of those listed in validAddresses, otherwise an exception is thrown.
Once the connection with one of the valid addresses has been established, the insta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Di Donato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353386</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T21:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog posts that get into the whole “how to think like a front-end developer” vibe are my favorite. Michelle Barker nails that in this post, and does it without sharing a line of code!
We simply can no longer 
…
The post Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Go? Golang Programming Language Meaning Explained]]></title>
        <id>615de4da0d91c9077974e23f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-go-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go, also known as Golang, is an open-source, compiled, and statically typed programming language designed by Google. It is built to be simple, high-performing, readable, and efficient.  In this article, you'll learn:  Where Go came from and where it is now, Why I think you should learn it, How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a simple portfolio with Argo Tunnels and containers for fun 🚀 - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afrocoder/deploying-a-simple-portfolio-with-argo-tunnels-and-containers-for-fun-part-1-24f0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afrocoder/deploying-a-simple-portfolio-with-argo-tunnels-and-containers-for-fun-part-1-24f0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other day I was stoked when I got to use Argo Tunnels, its a neat piece of software that builds a bridge to the internet from your local machine, I wrote about it a few days back Argo Tunnels are fun!

The problem with me is I have an interest based learning, if the project doesn't interest me I won't be able to go ahead with it. So I decided to update my portfolio! but using Continuous deployment, podman and Argo tunnels!
Gitlab Runner Setup using podman
Cloudflared tunnel setup using systemd
Continuous deployment using Gitlab CI/CD using containers!!
Running a completely rootless setup
Lets get started with cloudflared installation and setup.
Before starting please make sure you go through the following
As of now you need a domain name and you need to change the nameservers to that o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353024</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-in-typescript-with-vanilla-extract/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vanilla-extract is a new framework-agnostic CSS-in-TypeScript library. It’s a lightweight, robust, and intuitive way to write your styles. vanilla-extract isn’t a prescriptive CSS framework, but a flexible piece of developer tooling. CSS tooling has been a relatively stable space over …
The post CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353242</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-themeable-react-data-grid-with-great-ux-focused-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
KendoReact can save you boatloads of time because it offers pre-built componentry you can use in your app right away. They look nice, but more importantly, they are easily themeable, so they look however …
The post A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Websites We Like: MD Nichrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353219</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/websites-we-like-md-nichrome/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a beautiful website: it’s a type specimen for Mass-Driver’s ever-so-lovely type family MD Nichrome. There’s a ton of nifty animations and graphics explaining all the features inside…
If you’re wondering how those animations work, they’re actually styled <video>…
The post Websites We Like: MD Nichrome appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Single Page App Morality Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353320</id>
        <link href="https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2021/single-page-app-morality-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur Bjarnason brings some baby bear porridge to the discussion of  Single Page App (SPA) vs. Multi Page App (MPA).
Single-Page-Apps can be fantastic. Most teams will mess them up because most teams operate in dysfunctional 
…
The post The Single Page App Morality Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C String – How to Declare Strings in the C Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>615beb720d91c9077974c716</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-string-how-to-declare-strings-in-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers store and process all kinds of data.  Strings are just one of the many forms in which information is presented and gets processed by computers.  Strings in the C programming language work differently than in other modern programming languages.  In this article, you'll learn how to declare strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python range() Function – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>612f4388d6679a07b7d3fee4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-range-function-explained-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, can use use the range() function to get a sequence of indices to loop through an iterable. You'll often use range() in conjunction with a for loop.  In this tutorial, you'll learn about the different ways in which you can use the range() function – with explicit start and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux tar Command – How to Compress Files in Linux]]></title>
        <id>614870b9852f4307d3731030</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compress-files-in-linux-with-tar-command/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File compression is an essential utility across all platforms. It helps you reduce file size and share files efficiently. And compressed files are also easier to copy to remote servers.  You can also compress older and rarely used files and save them for future use which helps you conserve disk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Runtime in Rust - Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/penumbra23/container-runtime-in-rust-part-ii-34em</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/penumbra23/container-runtime-in-rust-part-ii-34em"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part I of the series described the filesystem layout and how the runtime jails the container process inside the root filesystem of the container.
Part 0 briefly explained the clone syscall. It's like fork/vfork, but with more options to control the child process. Actually, some implementations of fork propagate the call to clone().
Besides controlling which parts of the execution context get shared from the parent process, the clone call offers the possibility for us to create a separate memory block for the child's stack. The nix implementation of clone has the following signature:
pub fn clone(
 cb: CloneCb<'_>, 
 stack: &mut [u8], 
 flags: CloneFlags, 
 signal: Option<c_int>
) -> Result<Pid>

The signal argument, if specified, is sent back to the parent when the child process terminates…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>penumbra23</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insert Into SQL – How to Insert Into a Table Query [Example Statement]]]></title>
        <id>615d55b40d91c9077974d3f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/insert-into-sql-how-to-insert-into-a-table-query-example-statement/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to add data to your SQL table, then you can use the INSERT statement.  In this article, I will show you how to use the INSERT statement to add a single row, multiple rows, and to copy rows from one SQL table to another. Basic INSERT syntaxHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Developer Résumé Without Job Experience]]></title>
        <id>6155429464aefe07d3fa1019</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-developer-resume-without-job-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T15:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have observed a fascinating phenomenon amongst folks applying for their first developer jobs.  The behavior seems consistent across college graduates, Bootcampers, and self-taught folks. When asking for a résumé review, they almost always get the answer "build more projects".  This is great advice, but you can do more to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352959</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/considerations-for-using-markdown-writing-apps-on-static-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you run or have recently switched to a static site generator, you might find yourself writing a lot of Markdown. And the more you write it, the more you want the tooling experience to disappear so that …
The post Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Barnard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Options for Password Revealing Inputs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352676</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-options-for-password-revealing-inputs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, there is a very clear input type for dealing with passwords:
<input type="password">
If you use that, you get the obfuscated bullet-points when you type into it, like:
••••••••
That’s the web trying to help with security. If …
The post The Options for Password Revealing Inputs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🚀 The Missing Docker Crash Course for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-missing-docker-crash-course-for-developers-2ccb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-missing-docker-crash-course-for-developers-2ccb"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T11:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Docker





It is more likely than not that Docker and containers are going to be part of your IT career in one way or another.
In this blog post series I'll cover the following:
  What are Docker images, containers and Docker Hub
  Installing Docker on Ubuntu Linux on a DigitalOcean Droplet
  Working with Docker containers
  Working with Docker images
  Deploying a Dockerized app
I'll be using DigitalOcean for all of the demos, so I would strongly encourage you to create a DigitalOcean account follow along. You would learn more by doing!
To make things even better you can use my referral link to get a free $100 credit that you could use to deploy your virtual machines and test the guide yourself on a few DigitalOcean servers:
DigitalOcean $100 Free Credit
Once you have you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Tor Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rabist/php-tor-controller-1ii3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rabist/php-tor-controller-1ii3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Control your Tor service with a PHP script.
Renew - Change current mask IP.
Restart - Restart Tor service.
Display connected clients to the service.
It must be used on the same server with the Tor service.
Visit Gist Page and contribute to add more features.
<?php

/**
 * Desc: PHP Tor Controller
 * Author: Rabist - https://www.linkedin.com/in/rabist
 * Source URI: https://gist.github.com/geraked/334c6f1c3b8fbd607f8c7788e7d92f81
 * Date: 2021-07-14
 */


// Set config parameters
$IP = '127.0.0.1';
$SOCKS_PORT = 9050;
$CONTROL_PORT = 9051;
$CONTROL_PASSWORD = '';

// Fetch user's cookie and the requested operation
$usr = $_COOKIE['usr'] ?? null;
$op = $_GET['op'] ?? null;
$ct = time() + (86400 * 30);
$class = '';

// Handle logout request
if ($op == 'logout') {
    setcookie('usr', '', $ct)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rabist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll Shadows With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352754</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scroll-shadows-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T22:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll shadows are when you can see a little inset shadow on elements if (and only if) you can scroll in that direction. It’s just good UX. You can actually pull it off in CSS, which I think is …
The post Scroll Shadows With JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional Border Radius In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353261</id>
        <link href="https://ishadeed.com/article/conditional-border-radius/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T19:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed documents a bonafide CSS trick from the Facebook CSS codebase. The idea is that when an element is the full width of the viewport, it doesn’t have any border-radius. But otherwise, it has 8px of border-radius. …
The post Conditional Border Radius In CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Branching Strategies in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352508</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/branching-strategies-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T14:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to talk about branching strategies and different types of Git branches. I’m also going to introduce you to two common branching workflows: Git Flow and GitHub Flow.
The post Branching Strategies in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>