<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-12T01:07:48.972Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-12T01:07:48.972Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aura Theme v2.0.0 is out now! 🥳 🎉]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daltonmenezes/aura-theme-v2-0-0-is-out-now-565h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daltonmenezes/aura-theme-v2-0-0-is-out-now-565h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T00:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi folks, I'm glad to share with you Aura Theme v2.0.0 with a lot of cool new features.
The entire project was recreated from scratch using TypeScript
Color schemes have been improved
Added Aura CLI
Added Aura API
New ports have been added, the current full list of ports is:


Visual Studio Code
Sublime Text
CodeSandbox
Hyper
Windows Terminal
Alacritty
iTerm
rxvt-unicode
Terminal.app
GNOME Terminal
Kitty
Chrome
Firefox
Vivaldi
Insomnia
Telegram Desktop
Slack
And more ports will come soon! 🚀
You can find all themes at:
https://github.com/daltonmenezes/aura-theme
Now, let's take a look at some of the available ports:




I hope you guys enjoy it as much as I do 💜
The repo is participating in the Hacktoberfest, so If you would like to contribute by creating new ports, you can open an issue or get an existing one asking for it and reading the docs, also you can reach me here or on GitHub if you need some help. 💜]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalton Menezes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meu primeiro mês como desenvolvedor backend JR.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/x8ing_/meu-primeiro-mes-como-desenvolvedor-back-end-jr-43k4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/x8ing_/meu-primeiro-mes-como-desenvolvedor-back-end-jr-43k4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T00:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antes de começar à falar sobre minha breve experiência, recomendo que se atentem bastante aos pontos que falo com propriedade em que devo melhorar, pois recebi feedbacks solicitado por mim, e isso viabiliza melhoria na sua jornada ao longo tempo na empresa que você está atuando. Caso contrário, você não melhore esses pontos, poderá acarretar em permanecer errando e prejudicando sua equipe/empresa. Assim como, levará essa atitude errante para outra empresa. 
Pra facilitar a leitura e entender como foi o meu processo de adaptação ao onBoarding da empresa, vou descrever e dividir por tarefas, certo? Então, vamos lá.
Na minha primeira semana estava muito nervoso porque era, ou melhor, ainda é, algo muito novo para meu dia-a-dia. Afinal, estou dando os meus primeiros passos agora na carreira qu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ítalo Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Laptop for Coding in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/annamitchell/best-laptop-for-coding-in-2021-2om6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/annamitchell/best-laptop-for-coding-in-2021-2om6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T23:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to the best laptop for programming, it's not just mobility you need. Storage, speed, and a comfortable keyboard are more vital than clock speeds, cores, and threads. Playing around with code and programming software is a necessity for many professions, and even for many hobbies. Of course, if it’s something that you’ve ever tried before, you will know that having a high quality computer is important for getting tasks done to the highest standards. If you’re still relatively new to programming or you haven’t bought a new laptop in a while, you may not know what sorts of specifications you should be looking out for.




Model
Score
Buy




1.
 Apple Macbook Air

 ★★★★★ 
 View at Amazon 


2.
 Google Pixelbook Go

 ★★★★★ 
 View at Amazon 


3.
 Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Extreme

 ★★★★★…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Mitchell ∞</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recarregando o inventário do Ansible durante a execução]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stefanomartins/recarregando-o-inventario-do-ansible-durante-a-execucao-5ghm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stefanomartins/recarregando-o-inventario-do-ansible-durante-a-execucao-5ghm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T23:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução


Esta dica surgiu a partir de uma dúvida no Telegram da LINUXtips e é ótima para quem precisa trabalhar com inventários dinâmicos ou realiza modificações em seu arquivo de inventário.
Imagine o seguinte cenário: Você possui um playbook que realiza modificações no seu inventário como adicionar um novo host, e durante a mesma execução do playbook precisa que este host recém-adicionado seja levado em consideração para uma próxima task ou role.
Para melhor ilustrar, criei abaixo um arquivo de inventário e um playbook que simplesmente irá imprimir todos os hosts do inventário, adicionar um novo host chamado host-03 e depois imprimir novamente os hosts:
# hosts
[all]
host-01
host-02

# playbook.yml
--- 
- hosts: localhost
  become: true
  connection: local
  tasks:

    - name: Print…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefano Martins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vue3 + Quasar 2.1 + TypeScript Sample CRUD Application Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/unfor19/vue3-quasar-2-1-typescript-sample-crud-application-project-ld2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/unfor19/vue3-quasar-2-1-typescript-sample-crud-application-project-ld2"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T22:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
AWS SSM Parameters API to test the application and it is being served with localstack so I can test the application locally. In case it's not clear, AWS SSM Parameters (served by localstack) is my local "backend server".
To run the application and test it immediately, you need to have Docker and Docker-Compose installed - that's it.
Project link @ GitHub - https://github.com/unfor19/aws-webui
Sidenote- I'm not a frontend developer, so it was quite tough, but eventually, it was a great experience.
Feel free to ask any questions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meir Gabay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those “Get The App” Banners]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352907</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/those-get-the-app-banners/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T22:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would a company promote a native app over their perfectly usable website?
We’d have to ask them, I suppose. But it’s hard not to see this push to native as a matter of priorities: that these companies consider native 
…
The post Those “Get The App” Banners appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mocking Back-ends for React Apps with MirageJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anikcreative/mocking-back-ends-for-react-apps-with-miragejs-jgb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anikcreative/mocking-back-ends-for-react-apps-with-miragejs-jgb"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T22:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seven tips to help you avoid bottlenecks and future-proof your mock back-end








⚠️ Disclaimer




This article assumes you have some familiarity with the React framework, and Javascript and Typescript fundamentals. It also assumes you are comfortable with concepts and terms related to relational databases.



What led me to consider Mirage
(1) Don't put everything in one file

(2) Start with a plan

(3) Define Typescript interfaces for models

(4) Consider a "hybrid" approach for generating realistic seed data

(5) Split up and aggregate route handlers

(6) Create API client functions for UI components

(7) Set up passthroughs and a unique namespace for mock routes

Closing thoughts



I recently helped create a high-fidelity React-based prototype for a new product still in its early …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create audio play with reactjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/non1k/create-audio-play-with-reactjs-pkn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/non1k/create-audio-play-with-reactjs-pkn"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T21:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello devs, i'm new to the community and i can't speak english. I hope the translation can be understood, I have a problem. I have an API on node and on the front end I'm using Reactjs. my api returns a static audio file, i want to know how i create an audio play from this file that the API gives me using reactjs. thank you if you want parts of the code and just ask. XD]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>100n1k</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test your PowerShell code with Pester]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azure/test-your-powershell-code-with-pester-4hlc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azure/test-your-powershell-code-with-pester-4hlc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T20:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; this article covers the testing framework Pester that you use to test your PowerShell scripts. 
The reason you want to have tests are many:
Correctness. Ensure your code works as as intended for certain scenarios.
Confidence. When you have a lot of tests covering your code it creates a level of confidence. With this confidence you start daring to change this, if you for example would need to refactor code and ensure it still works after those changes.
Architecture. Another reason for having tests is that it drives architecture. If you create tests around what you do, you ensure you build your code in a way that makes it testable. That, drives the architecture.
There are many other reasons for wanting to have tests but the three above are quite compelling.
Pester is a test framework m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Noring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWT how does it work and is it secure?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/darken/jwt-how-does-it-work-and-is-it-secure-37n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/darken/jwt-how-does-it-work-and-is-it-secure-37n"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T20:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JWT stands for JSON web token
the common definition says that it is an open industry standard RFC 7519 method for representing claims securely between two parties 
so lets break it up into a simpler logic to understand its utility and the way it works!
In security processes, authentication validates a user's identity, it also grants that user permission to access a resource.
A JWT is composed by :
header . payload . signature
eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJzdWIiOiIxMjM0NTY3ODkwIiwibmFtZSI6IkpvaG4gRG9lIiwiaWF0IjoxNTE2MjM5MDIyfQ.SflKxwRJSMeKKF2QT4fwpMeJf36POk6yJV_adQssw5c
The Header is the metadata about the token, its the result of
const base64Url = require("base64-url") 
// used for Base64 and URL Encoding Decoding 
const header = base64Url.encode(
  JSON.stringify({
    alg :"HS2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Achraf Affes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353431</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cash-tiny-jquery-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T20:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The README for Cash is straightforward:
Cash is an absurdly small jQuery alternative for modern browsers (IE11+) that provides jQuery-style syntax for manipulating the DOM. Utilizing modern browser features to minimize the codebase, developers can use the familiar chainable methods 
…
The post Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Music Downloader API Integrated to Frontend in 15 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/korconnect/free-music-downloader-api-integrated-to-frontend-in-15-minutes-4629</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/korconnect/free-music-downloader-api-integrated-to-frontend-in-15-minutes-4629"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T19:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This YouTube music download API integration is done on the client side without a backend (I did not want to deal with backend infrastructure to hide the API key). I used KOR Connect as the middleware platform (free) to quickly and easily integrate the API in a secure way. Firstly I will go over why I chose this route. 
We all know that API keys and connections can not be secured on the client side of an application. Hard coding API keys on the frontend is a quick and surefire way to have your API connection shutdown, API keys stolen, and have your API provider’s bill skyrocket. So what options are there if you do not want to maintain back end infrastructure? I will explore the recommended techniques for integrating 3rd party APIs into client side applications without having to build a back…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clemenshemmerling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL & REST with Typescript, Prisma and Azure SQL: love at first sight!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/azure/graphql-rest-with-prisma-and-azure-sql-love-at-first-sight-12ni</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/azure/graphql-rest-with-prisma-and-azure-sql-love-at-first-sight-12ni"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T19:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're into Typescript and prefer a code-first approach when working with databases, you'll be happy to learn about Prisma! Prisma is a next-generation Node.js and TypeScript ORM, that allows you to define a schema using a dedicated DSL so that you can then have all the comforts of modern development environments like intellisense, static type checking, automatic scaffolding and more.
To help everyone, even those who just started working as coders - or those who want to start a career as software engineers - we have created a fully working end-to-end full-stack solution that has:
a frontend written with Vue.Js

a backend, written in Typescript and using Prisma

an Azure SQL database (for the reasons explained here)
to make it consumable by really everyone, we also decided to support both REST and GraphQL protocols and we also decided to make sure that everyone can take advantage of a streamlined CI/CD experience, so we used Azure Static Web Apps and GitHub Actions to glue everything together.
Last, but not least, the sample also support Authentication and Authorization (which is super simple thanks to Azure Static Web Apps!)
I must say I'm happy and proud of what has been done, as this example is a great learning experience and starting point for everyone interested in becoming a better developer.
So, look at the article here to learn more about Prisma:
Modern application development with Prisma, GraphQL (or REST) and Azure SQL
and to the repository hear to deploy the code on your own:
 / 
        azure-sql-db-prisma
      
    
The repository is fully documented. You should be easily able to set up your working environment in no time. If you want to see it in action and learn about it before starting to use it, I did a session at the Prima Meetup that you can watch here:




As usual, enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Mauri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Collective: Real-time Data Integration with Webhooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/egeninc/cloud-collective-real-time-data-integration-with-webhooks-2l2d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/egeninc/cloud-collective-real-time-data-integration-with-webhooks-2l2d"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T19:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk about ways to integrate and push data out to external systems in near real-time with polling, streaming, and Webhooks.




Cloud Collective is a meetup for technologists interested in the Cloud Native approach towards developing and deploying web & mobile applications, streaming analytics, ETL pipelines, microservices, containers, functions, and applying Infrastructure as Code principles for automating infrastructure on AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud.  In this recorded meetup, we focus on polling, streaming, and Webhooks.
Here are a few things covered in this video:
Overview of Polling, Streaming, and Webhook Integrations
Webhook Architecture: Registration, Security, API clients
A quick demo of Webhook implementation
Takeaways
If you enjoyed this talk, join our cloud collective group here ► https://www.meetup.com/cloud-collective/ and participate in our next meetup!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Build Amazing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Learn Kubernetes - Basics - 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pghildiyal/let-s-learn-kubernetes-basics-2-2a9a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pghildiyal/let-s-learn-kubernetes-basics-2-2a9a"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T18:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is a container management tool that automates the deployment, scaling, and operations of an application. It has become the de facto container orchestrator, with more than 80% of companies using it in some capacity. 
'Let's learn Kubernetes' Series, we have seen the basic definition of Kubernetes, pods, Nodes, controllers among others. 
Let's Learn Kubernetes - Basics Part 1
Prashant Ghildiyal ・ Sep 29 ・ 3 min read
#kubernetes
        #devops
        #beginners
        #go
      
In this series we will go a little deeper to understand concepts like services, Load balancers and others. In this we'll give a short explanation of each concept and then post a link that explains the same in-depth. 
Before diving in, it would be great if you can check out our repo Devtron, End-to-End Ku…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prashant Ghildiyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side Project Journey Part 4 – Back End Coding]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lucsedirae/side-project-journey-part-4-back-end-coding-1k2o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lucsedirae/side-project-journey-part-4-back-end-coding-1k2o"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T18:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post I laid out the scaffolding for my back end code. It took a little time to think through the code I would need. I referred to some past projects and a tutorial I had taken when I was first learning React. During the process of pseudo-coding there were a couple times where I felt like the effort was outweighing the eventual benefits. What’s the point of writing one comment line to describe another single line importing a model after all?
After completing the process, I felt different about that “extra work”. The result was akin to painting by numbers. Once I finished pseudo-coding, it only took a fraction of the time I would normally spend writing up a node API to get all of the pieces in place and functioning properly. I was able to cut and paste some code from older pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Deavers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start a Blog [Free 70-Page Book]]]></title>
        <id>6159ab734aa03507d9412321</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-a-blog-book/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T17:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What follows is a full-length book on how to create a successful blog. I am a software developer and I've written 1,500 posts on my blog over the past few years. Millions of people have read my writing. And my blog is now one of the top 20,000]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Content Marketing Landing Page 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gphmoinul/best-content-marketing-landing-page-2021-2309</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gphmoinul/best-content-marketing-landing-page-2021-2309"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T17:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Content Marketing Landing Page 2021
Hello Designer!
Best Content Marketing Landing Page 2021 Content marketing is one of the most profitable ways to get traffic to your website. This is because it combines SEO, social media, and design. If you want to learn how to create an effective landing page, you can read more here.
Download up to Fourteen Thousand web templates, mobile app templates, illustrations, 3d illustrations, SVG icons, and graphic assets for Figma, Sketch, and Adobe XD. from UIHUT.
This Best Content Marketing Landing Page 2021 web app design available file Figma, Sketch, Adobe XD
UIHUT is a design resources platform for UX/UI designers, developers, and founders. Our high-quality design resources will help you to speed up the design process. Resources:
1000+ Web Templates (Figma, Sketch, XD)
After all, you can go to UIHUT use this coupon code ‘moy10’ to get a 10% extra off for a lifetime deal.
We are uploading more resources every day.
Thanks for cordiality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moinul_h</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[helmfile: difference between sync and apply (Helm 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/derlin/helmfile-difference-between-sync-and-apply-helm-3-28o1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/derlin/helmfile-difference-between-sync-and-apply-helm-3-28o1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helm and helmfile are great tools to automate kubernetes deployments. However, they have some subtleties that are sometimes hard to understand, and may lead to catastrophic problems. One of it is the difference between helmfile sync and helmfile apply, a question raised many times, for example in StackOverflow.
Running helmfile -h, the explanation of those two commands is:
sync → sync all resources from state file (repos, releases and chart deps)
apply → apply all resources from state file only when there are changes
But what does it mean exactly ? What are the differences and pitfalls ? Let's dive in together, starting at the basics of Helm 3 up to helmfile.
Note: if you are familiar with how Helm 3 upgrades work, you can skip directly to the last section.
The first thing to understand is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Linder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An acquisition Funnel in React with Xstate - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jbrocher/building-an-acquisition-funnel-in-react-with-xstate-part-2-1i33</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jbrocher/building-an-acquisition-funnel-in-react-with-xstate-part-2-1i33"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building An acquisition Funnel in React with Xstate - Part 2


This is part 2 of a two parts article. If you haven't done it yet, checkout part one ! 
In part one, we used a strong programming pattern to model our funnel: a state machine. We also built a FunnelProvider that provides us with a flexible api to synchronize it with React. 
Today we'll implement the actual steps of the funnel and see how we can update our state machine to store the data entered by the customer at each step. 
As always the code we'll write in this article is fully available here. However if you feel like coding along you can start from where we left off by cloning the repository from part 1
As we did last time, let's start with a bit of state machine theory ! If you're in a hurry, and you just want to see how it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jbrocher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Virtual! with Python Virtual Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeden/get-virtual-with-python-virtual-environments-4ci7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeden/get-virtual-with-python-virtual-environments-4ci7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are used to isolate environments and resolve dependency conflict resolution.
This ensure projects have isolated siloes where they live and have their own dependency tree that don't interfere with one another.
Another thing, feel free to jump to sections that you're only interested in!
Python Dependencies
Installing Libraries
Using a requirements.txt
Using env
Using venv
Using virtualenvwrapper
Errors


mkvirtualenv: command not found
virtualenvwrapper Command '' not found, but can be installed with ...
References
You will often use 3rd-party libraries - non-default libraries which doesn't come along with Python.
normally installed using pip or easy_install 
libraries are pulled from the pupi.org or Python Package Index which as an enormous index of libraries
 
To install a library, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eden Jose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Virtual! with Python Virtual Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeden/get-virtual-with-python-virtual-environments-4ci7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeden/get-virtual-with-python-virtual-environments-4ci7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are used to isolate environments and resolve dependency conflict resolution.
This ensure projects have isolated siloes where they live and have their own dependency tree that don't interfere with one another.
Another thing, feel free to jump to sections that you're only interested in!
Python Dependencies
Installing Libraries
Using a requirements.txt
Using env
Using venv
Using virtualenvwrapper
Errors


mkvirtualenv: command not found
virtualenvwrapper Command '' not found, but can be installed with ...
References
You will often use 3rd-party libraries - non-default libraries which doesn't come along with Python.
normally installed using pip or easy_install 
libraries are pulled from the pupi.org or Python Package Index which as an enormous index of libraries
 
To install a library, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eden Jose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce in 5 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kirkcodes/reduce-in-5-minutes-462i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kirkcodes/reduce-in-5-minutes-462i"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a quick intro to the reduce() method in Javascript/Typescript arrays, which is frequently perplexing when encountered in working code.
The code here is written in Typescript but I've tried to keep it friendly for JS readers, and I'll post a link to the equivalent JS at the end. 
Reduce allows us to take a container of data (like an array) and fold it into another data structure.
The reduce() method involves three parts:
A container of values, like an array, with which we need to update another structure (in sequence)
A function that lets us update a value (typically called the accumulator) based on an element from our array




function updater(accumulator:SomeType, nextValueFromArray): SomeType {
    ... // whatever operations we want
    return updatedAccumulator
}

Frequently thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirk Shillingford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Node JS - Open-Source Fullstack Starters]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-node-js-open-source-fullstack-starters-5192</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sm0ke/react-node-js-open-source-fullstack-starters-5192"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Coders!
This article presents a curated list with open-source source seed projects crafted in React and Node JS on top of modern UI kits and templates. All products are actively supported and the permissive license allows the usage for commercial projects (unlimited copies). For newcomers, Node JS is an open-source, cross-platform, back-end JavaScript runtime environment, and React is a popular JavaScript library for coding user interfaces backed by Facebook. 
Thanks for reading! - Content provided by Admin Dashboards.
✨ React Node JS - Berry Dashboard
✨ React Node JS - Soft UI Dashboard
✨ React Node JS - Datta Able 
All starters are crafted using an identical design pattern where the React UI is decoupled from the Node JS backend and the communication is secured by web tokens. To ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sm0ke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Node.js API in Under 30 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sagarbarapatre/build-a-node-js-api-in-under-30-minutes-57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sagarbarapatre/build-a-node-js-api-in-under-30-minutes-57"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js can be intimidating to beginners. But its flexible structure and lack of strict guidelines makes it seem more complicated than it is.
Who This Tutorial Is For: You should have a basic understanding of REST APIs and CRUD operations, plus basic JavaScript knowledge. I use ES6 (mainly fat-arrow functions), but nothing too complex.
Google Keep. You want to be able to do all four CRUD actions on your notes: create, read, update, and delete.
If you don’t have Node installed, see here.
npm init

Once that’s done, you should have a package.json ready to go in your directory. This means you can start installing the dependencies you need for your project.
npm install --save express mongodb@2.2.16 body-parser

I also highly recommend installing Nodemon as a dev dependency. It’s a simple littl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sagar Barapatre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medusa: Create A Fast and Highly Customizable E-Commerce Store]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shahednasser/medusa-create-a-fast-and-highly-customizable-e-commerce-store-39cm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shahednasser/medusa-create-a-fast-and-highly-customizable-e-commerce-store-39cm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published on my personal blog.
E-commerce platforms and frameworks are usually built on a complex architecture to provide you with the best features as a developer and as a business owner.
Although this is good as they pack all useful features in one framework in the hopes no additional work needs to be done to launch a store, this can result in some issues. The store can be slow which would require a set of external tools to make it faster and in some cases big hosting plans to ensure the customers get the best experience.
In addition to that, customizing an e-commerce store to fit your or your client's needs using some platforms can be hard due to their tightly bound or complicated architecture.
This is where Medusa comes in. Medusa is an open-source headless …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahed Nasser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containerization for beginners: Running a nodeJS application using Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/containerization-for-beginners-running-a-nodejs-application-using-docker-4f58</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/containerization-for-beginners-running-a-nodejs-application-using-docker-4f58"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T15:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few questions that would come up when seeing the title. 
"Hey, why would I run my nodeJS application in a container? I can use node server, nodemon or n number of live servers available"


"When would I have to run it as a container?"



The answer is pretty simple if you're planning to not go through the tedious docker documentation out there.
We mostly work as a team. Our peers install and work with dependencies, pulling from the repository and getting the code running in our development server is usually cumbersome. Dependencies may be missing, system requirements need to be met, storage issues, version control, quite a lot of other obstacles. Here comes the containers!!
Applications running in containers are isolated from each other and have their own storage and environmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muzammil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desenvolvimento, arquitetura e boas praticas]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bernardo/desenvolvimento-arquitetura-e-boas-praticas-11o4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bernardo/desenvolvimento-arquitetura-e-boas-praticas-11o4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T15:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eu sempre fui fã de desenvolvimento de boas arquiteturas, talvez por já ter sofrido muito na vida na sustentação de sistemas ruins.
Alguns decisões ruins poderiam ter sido evitadas se tivessem simplesmente "parado para planejar". 
Normalmente esse profissional quando questionado começa com o checklist do GoHorse:
[ ]  O prazo era apertado
Nesse momento eu gosto de lembrar de um principio do manifesto ágil que e esquecido em alguns casos. 
"Contínua atenção à excelência técnica e bom design aumenta a agilidade."
Isso tem mudado com o surgimento do padrão Build & Run.
As equipes de desenvolvimento têm autoridade total sobre os serviços que criam, não apenas criando, mas também implantando e apoiando-os

Quando as equipes de desenvolvimento são responsáveis por construir um sistemas e suportá…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luiz Felipe Bernardo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SSR with Angular Universal and Deploy with Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-ssr-with-angular-universal-and-deploy-with-docker-13i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-ssr-with-angular-universal-and-deploy-with-docker-13i"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post explains the process to enable Angular Server Side Rendering(SSR) with Angular Universal and the process to deploy it in Docker container
The source code of the application demonstrated in this post present in Github https://github.com/pavankjadda/angular-ssr-docker
If you already have an existing Angular application, you can skip this step
Create new application




   ng new angular-ssr-docker

Add Angular material and




ng add @angular/material

Import indigo-pink theme to application. Add following line to styles.scss




@import "~@angular/material/prebuilt-themes/indigo-pink.css";

Create two components, Login and Home. When user logs in, it redirects him to home page
Based on instructions from Angular docs,
Add Angular Universal to the project




ng add @nguniversa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan K Jadda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SSR with Angular Universal and Deploy with Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-ssr-with-angular-universal-and-deploy-with-docker-13i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-ssr-with-angular-universal-and-deploy-with-docker-13i"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post explains the process to enable Angular Server Side Rendering(SSR) with Angular Universal and the process to deploy it in Docker container
The source code of the application demonstrated in this post present in Github https://github.com/pavankjadda/angular-ssr-docker
If you already have an existing Angular application, you can skip this step
Create new application




   ng new angular-ssr-docker

Add Angular material and




ng add @angular/material

Import indigo-pink theme to application. Add following line to styles.scss




@import "~@angular/material/prebuilt-themes/indigo-pink.css";

Create two components, Login and Home. When user logs in, it redirects him to home page
Based on instructions from Angular docs,
Add Angular Universal to the project




ng add @nguniversa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan K Jadda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kept running "source .bashrc" every time I open WSL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeden/kept-running-source-bashrc-every-time-i-open-wsl-43bm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeden/kept-running-source-bashrc-every-time-i-open-wsl-43bm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was playing around and testing some stuff in Linux when i suddenly did a tweak which changed how my WSL terminal opens up. This is what my terminal looks like - notice it doesn't the distinct green + blue colors.

After some searching I found two articles (links at the bottom) which describes the "sequence" which Unix follows when reading files. As summary, here's the files (in order):
/etc/profile
~/.bash_profile
~/.bash_login
4 ~/.profile
I added the function for .bashrc at the top of the .bash_profile:
## Loads .bashrc
if [[ -f ~/.bashrc ]] ; then
        . ~/.bashrc
fi

Closed terminal and reopened it 

Adding this great explanation from the reference link:
By default, Terminal starts the shell via /usr/bin/login, which makes the shell a login shell. On every platform (not just Mac OS X) bash does not use .bashrc for login shells (only /etc/profile and the first of .bash_profile, .bash_login, .profile that exists and is readable). This is why "put source ~/.bashrc in your .bash_profile" is standard advice
Why doesn't .bashrc run automatically?
How do I set up my shell execution PATH?

What is the difference between .bash_profile and .bashrc?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eden Jose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kept running "source .bashrc" every time I open WSL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeden/kept-running-source-bashrc-every-time-i-open-wsl-43bm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeden/kept-running-source-bashrc-every-time-i-open-wsl-43bm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was playing around and testing some stuff in Linux when i suddenly did a tweak which changed how my WSL terminal opens up. This is what my terminal looks like - notice it doesn't the distinct green + blue colors.

After some searching I found two articles (links at the bottom) which describes the "sequence" which Unix follows when reading files. As summary, here's the files (in order):
/etc/profile
~/.bash_profile
~/.bash_login
4 ~/.profile
I added the function for .bashrc at the top of the .bash_profile:
## Loads .bashrc
if [[ -f ~/.bashrc ]] ; then
        . ~/.bashrc
fi

Closed terminal and reopened it 

Adding this great explanation from the reference link:
By default, Terminal starts the shell via /usr/bin/login, which makes the shell a login shell. On every platform (not just Mac OS X) bash does not use .bashrc for login shells (only /etc/profile and the first of .bash_profile, .bash_login, .profile that exists and is readable). This is why "put source ~/.bashrc in your .bash_profile" is standard advice
Why doesn't .bashrc run automatically?
How do I set up my shell execution PATH?

What is the difference between .bash_profile and .bashrc?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eden Jose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Dynamic Twitter Header]]></title>
        <id>615408e064aefe07d3fa0743</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-dynamic-twitter-header/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-2021, a new Twitter design trend emerged: dynamically updated headers. Developers decided that static headers were boring, and dynamic Twitter headers were the way to go.  Ever since then, many developers (including me) have been creating dynamic banners on Twitter. But what does this actually mean? The idea is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crack DevOps Interview by these top questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudytech147/crack-devops-interview-by-these-top-questions-3kg4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudytech147/crack-devops-interview-by-these-top-questions-3kg4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.sevenmentor.com/ 
The most popular set of skills that organizations look out for in an ideal candidate applying for a DevOps role is –
Experience in tools that allow us to automate the infrastructure such as Ansible, Puppet, Chef, etc.
Hands-on expertise on container orchestration and management tools like Docker, Kubernetes, etc. can be helpful.
Popular backend languages for programming such as Java, PHP, etc.
Cloud computing platforms and infrastructures such as GCP, Amazon Web Services, etc.
Version control and management tools like Git, BitBucket, etc.
Once you are confident that you have enough of these skills to ace any DevOps job interview with flying colors, you can move ahead and start practicing some of the most frequently asked DevOps job interview questions and answ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cloudytech147</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Collaboration With Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352569</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-collaboration-with-pull-requests/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is part of our “Advanced Git” series. Be sure to follow us on Twitter or sign up for our newsletter to hear about the next articles!
In this third installment of our “Advanced Git” series, we’ll look at …
The post Better Collaboration With Pull Requests appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux buffered write latency]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fritshooglandyugabyte/linux-buffered-write-latency-10mc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fritshooglandyugabyte/linux-buffered-write-latency-10mc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blogpost is about doing buffered writes to a linux filesystem, and latency fluctuations that it could show you, especially when performing a lot of writes, and other implications.
The first thing to discuss is buffered writes. Any write to a linux local filesystem is done 'buffered', unless explicitly defined it not to, which is done by opening the file with the O_DIRECT flag. So all file interactions from the shell likely are done buffered, and the Postgresql database is also using buffered IO.
What happens when you perform a buffered write is that you don't actually write to the disk, but instead you write to memory. Because currently the latency of most disk IO/writes is still much higher than memory IO latency (~ 25us/modern SSD vs 160ns/memory, although very configuration specifi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frits Hoogland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RabbitMQ]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luizcrrds/rabbitmq-3nd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luizcrrds/rabbitmq-3nd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Olá, hoje vou falar um pouquinho do que aprendi durante meu estudo e aprendizagem sobre o RabbitMQ que é uma das ferramentas de mensageria mais utilizadas atualmente.
Mas pra que serve isso?

O RabbitMQ é um message broker utilizado para fazer a gestão e controle de envio e recebimento de mensagens, mas para entender melhor sobre ele você vai precisar entender o que é um message broker.
Bem, um message broker é uma ferramenta que possibilita a comunicação entre dois aplicativos, sistemas e até serviços de uma forma confiável e segura, não importando a linguagem em que eles foram desenvolvidos, ou até mesmo plataformas. 
Ele funciona como um intermediador na comunicação entre os dois aplicativos, permitindo que os remetentes se comuniquem sem saber onde um ou outro está, o remetente pode en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luiz Carlos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling A Node JS Server For Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jamiescript/scaling-a-node-js-server-for-performance-15jo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jamiescript/scaling-a-node-js-server-for-performance-15jo"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using NodeJS one is likely to quickly run into scaling problems as compared to other programming language. This is a good thing as it allows you to make adjustment earlier on how to scale your application.
Let us create a small app that shows how we can make use of the cluster module to create different instances of our app
  const cluster = require("cluster");
  const http = require("http");
  //importing the necessary module







  //lets create a http server to serve a request from our 
  server.The server will respond with a random quote from an 
  array

  const quotes = [
     "The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step",
     "That which does not kill us makes us stronger",
     "Life is what happens when you’re busy making other 
     plans",
    "When the going ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamiebones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a parser and a filter?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/noriller/how-to-make-a-parser-and-a-filter-4g98</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/noriller/how-to-make-a-parser-and-a-filter-4g98"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T13:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've waited to post this on Monday morning because... well, even if you don't like coffee, more than any morning, the start of the week is certainly for "Coffee and Contemplation". 
(I prefer tea, but unfortunately, "Tea and Contemplation" doesn't roll of the tongue.)
Now that you're primed, what am I talking about?
Parser takes a input (generally text) and transforms it in a data structure that can be used in the following steps.
Filter is a... filter... that filter things. More enter and less get out. 
Anyway...
What can you do if you combine then?
Of course there's a lot more behind the biggest ones you can think, but in essence it's that it.
From the query you create a structure that the filter consumes, and at the end of the pipeline you have the results you want.
The easiest thing yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Noriller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET health checks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anton_ilin/asp-net-health-checks-12eh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anton_ilin/asp-net-health-checks-12eh"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T13:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Health check types


Sometimes you need to implement endpoint, which tells outside world if everything is OK with your application. For example you need to tell k8s that your application in unhealthy and let it restart pod.
There are 3 different types of health checks: 
Startup - happens after your app is started.
Liveness - happens time to time after app is started and tells if it needs to be restarted.
Readiness - happens time to time after app is started and tells if it able to handle requests.
Startup and Liveness checks are the most important, so let's focus on them. 
Any health check can be Dumb or Smart: 
Dumb checks only indicate that app is not crushed and check as few as possible.
Smart checks indicate that app is working correctly and check as much as possible (db, service bus, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Ilin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Command Thee...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joetags/i-command-thee-mfd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joetags/i-command-thee-mfd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T12:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Command Line
Can anyone tell me what day of the week Christopher Colombus landed in what is now the Bahamas? A quick Google search will tell you that he arrived on October 12th, 1492. But, it doesn’t mention the day of the week.  The answer happens to be Friday. And, if you make it to the end of this article, I will show you how I used the command line to find out the answer.
In honor of Indigenous People’s Day, I figured I would use a little bit of history to teach you about a topic you’re probably not interested in. The command line interface.
The command line is a powerful tool that can be used to interact with a computer’s operating system. It can access information in a computer’s file system. It can interact with an application’s database.  It can make API calls(e.g. Git). In fac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JoeTags</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ngx-lazy-dialog: Lazy loading dialogs in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gesielrosa/ngx-lazy-dialog-lazy-loading-dialogs-in-angular-25do</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gesielrosa/ngx-lazy-dialog-lazy-loading-dialogs-in-angular-25do"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T12:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create lazy load and fully customized dialogs in Angular with ngx-lazy-dialog
Install dependencies:
npm install ngx-lazy-dialog --save

Generate dialog component and dialog module:
ng g module dialogs/alert
ng g component dialogs/alert

How was the structure:
app   
└───dialogs
│   │   alert
│   │   │   alert.component.html
│   │   │   alert.component.css
│   │   │   alert.component.ts
│   │   │   alert.module.ts

Component and module created:
alert.component.ts
import { Component, OnInit } from '@angular/core';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-alert',
  templateUrl: './alert.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./alert.component.scss']
})
export class AlertComponent implements OnInit {

  constructor() {
  }

  ngOnInit(): void {
  }

}

alert.module.ts
import { NgModule } from '@angular/core';
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gesiel Rosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a backend in Javascript (part 5): Node Package Manager (NPM)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericchapman/create-a-backend-in-javascript-part-5-node-package-manager-npm-584g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericchapman/create-a-backend-in-javascript-part-5-node-package-manager-npm-584g"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T11:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a series of articles to help you create backend applications in Javascript.
Node.js is now a must, so it is essential for a developer to master it.
I will publish a new article every two days and little by little you will learn everything there is to know about Node.js
To not miss anything follow me on twitter: https://twitter.com/EricTheCoder_
Do you want to create a NodeJS function or module? Why re-invent the wheel? Chances are, the function you want to code has already been created by another developer.
NodeJS, allows you to use libraries created by the community. To do this, there is a tool called NPM (Node Package Manager) which allows you to download, install and manage these packages.
NPM is already pre-installed with NodeJS. It is a command line application that will allow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric The Coder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best UI Frameworks for React.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raftlabs/best-ui-frameworks-for-react-js-b49</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raftlabs/best-ui-frameworks-for-react-js-b49"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T11:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React (also known as React.js or ReactJS) is a free and open-source JavaScript library for building user interfaces or UI components. It is maintained by Facebook and a community of individual developers and companies. React is a prevalent Front end framework with over 172k stars on GitHub. There is a growing range of support libraries that helps us customize our UI components efficiently.
Here we will look at some of the best React UI Frameworks that you can adopt in your project.
The comparison made here is based on user reviews from the following trusted sources:
  GitHub
  npm.js
  StackShare
  Stackoverflow
Ant Design --- The world's second most popular react UI framework


It is an enterprise-class UI design language with a set of high-quality React UI components.It is one of the bes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RaftLabs - Product Development Agency</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux vs Windows 10 IoT. How to Choose the Best OS for Your Medical Device?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/integrasourcesltd/linux-vs-windows-10-iot-how-to-choose-the-best-os-for-your-medical-device-56h0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/integrasourcesltd/linux-vs-windows-10-iot-how-to-choose-the-best-os-for-your-medical-device-56h0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T11:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you choose an operating system for medical devices, you can easily get confused by the wide choice of options. They may differ in the nature of their source code, cost, size, architecture, performance, and area of application. In this article, we would like to take a look at the options of the most popular open-source and closed-source OS families.
When it comes to the choice of operating systems, many medical device manufacturers may have the following questions in mind: What is the best OS for medical devices? Should I choose a Microsoft product? Is Linux better than Windows 10 IoT? The list goes on. A quick spoiler: There is no absolute answer to the question of what is better: Linux or Windows 10 IoT for medical devices. Both operating systems have a broad range of abilities and f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrey Solovev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile app development dubai]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appmena/mobile-app-development-dubai-356p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appmena/mobile-app-development-dubai-356p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppMena is a fastest growing Mobile app development dubai, founded in the year 2017. We love to make your dreams a reality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Appmena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[makeStyles is dead, long live makeStyles!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/garronej/makestyles-is-dead-long-live-makestyles-i67</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/garronej/makestyles-is-dead-long-live-makestyles-i67"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Material-ui decided to deprecate the hook API in v5 in favour of the styled API.

I worked with them to provide an alternative under the form of a third party module for people who prefers JSS over styled. Ref.

It's mentioned in mui's migration guide from v4 to v5.
It also features a, type-safe by design, version of the withStyles HOC.  

Checkout tss-react]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrone Joseph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best skilled required for mobile application developer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sparxitsolution1/best-skilled-required-for-mobile-application-developer-1j2o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sparxitsolution1/best-skilled-required-for-mobile-application-developer-1j2o"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accreditation and profile creation
Communication and Geolocation
App designing
Monetization Strategies
Technology Stack 
A skilled mobile application developer will help you develop a user-friendly and captivating app like Tinder. Companies must have the skill and expertise required to create such apps. Stacks of technologies are as follows:
Android/iOS mobile app stacks
Swift
Backend/API Stack
Redis
Website Stack
Node.js
Developing each of the features above will take a certain amount of time. For an idea of how many hours the basic functionality of a dating app like Tinder needs to be programmed on iOS and Android, check out the table below.
Authorization - 22 hours 
The above are all approximations of the time it would take for a function to be developed. You can increase the functions of your dating app at a cost but also increase the development time. If you know the total time required for development, you can calculate what it will cost by checking the hours charged by the developer. 
The location of the team should also be taken into account. You should prepare to double the cost of an app if you hire someone to build it in the USA or Western Europe. Conversely, developers in Eastern Europe can create the same app for a much lower cost.
Therefore, development of an app like Tinder the requires a specialized team. If you're building a Tinder clone, your team should probably include:
2 Backend developers
Wrapping It Up!!
All of the data above tells us clearly that the popularity of dating apps is growing and that a decline in such amazing apps is not expected in the future. Whenever you plan to develop a dating app, decide on the essential feature first. Depending on how long each feature is going to take, you can estimate the development costs. For that intent on building their dating app like Tinder, seek guidance from a company with experience and expertise. Hiring experienced developers is necessary to make a user-friendly and market-ready app in the first go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sparxitsolution1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SvelteKit GraphQL Type Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/askrodney/sveltekit-graphql-type-generation-5753</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/askrodney/sveltekit-graphql-type-generation-5753"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💫 GraphQL with TypeScript and SvelteKit


In this post we look at how you can do automatic SvelteKit GraphQL type generation.  If that means nothing, read on and hopefully, by the end it makes sense! TypeScript builds on JavaScript to add variable types (like you see in Rust, C++ or Java), making it easier to spot mistakes in your code. Adding types to TypesScript code can get old quickly! GraphQL is a typed language which means you just have to reference the GraphQL schema in the right way to be able to generate types automatically for your TypeScript code base.
Using the graphql-codegen tool, we will see how you can generate a single file containing all the types from the GraphQL API you are using. Then when you run a query, you will just need to import the type from that file. If you a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodney Lab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage object in Angular FormControl]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-manage-object-in-angular-formcontrol-2ph4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-manage-object-in-angular-formcontrol-2ph4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T09:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn how to manage object in FormControl and handle conversion for input
Generally we use FormControl with either string or boolean types and hence it manages only simple values. But what if we want to manage just more than primitive data types? We can do that, let’s see how.
For example, in this tutorial we will learn how to get country-code and number as separate entities from the same form-control, and we will also create custom input for the same to handle the conversion between UI and value.
Let’s assume that we have a Telephone class, which will hold the related values:
export class Telephone {
  constructor(
    public countryCode: string,
    public phoneNumber: string
  ) {}
}

Next, let’s take an input[type=tel] in which we want to hold the Telephone:
@…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dharmen Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage object in Angular FormControl]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-manage-object-in-angular-formcontrol-2ph4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shhdharmen/how-to-manage-object-in-angular-formcontrol-2ph4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T09:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn how to manage object in FormControl and handle conversion for input
Generally we use FormControl with either string or boolean types and hence it manages only simple values. But what if we want to manage just more than primitive data types? We can do that, let’s see how.
For example, in this tutorial we will learn how to get country-code and number as separate entities from the same form-control, and we will also create custom input for the same to handle the conversion between UI and value.
Let’s assume that we have a Telephone class, which will hold the related values:
export class Telephone {
  constructor(
    public countryCode: string,
    public phoneNumber: string
  ) {}
}

Next, let’s take an input[type=tel] in which we want to hold the Telephone:
@…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dharmen Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add fancy to your Amplify Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jolo/how-to-add-fancy-to-your-amplify-project-4h8g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jolo/how-to-add-fancy-to-your-amplify-project-4h8g"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T07:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this part of the series, we want to make your Amplify project more fancy by adding Typescript to your Amplify functions and/or to turn your function- folder to a Monorepo. Just fancy sh*t ;)
This post also contains a project for #Hacktoberfest 🥳
We all know the benefits of Typescript. If you want to know more about Typescript, I encourage you to read the provided link.
Monorepo aka Multi-Project repository aka monolithic repositories is useful when synchronise packages along the functions. Monorepo also allow to share libraries across them.
node_modules. 

The following steps are used with the Amplify CLI and will install Typescript within its function-folder and add types to your Lambda- function
# Add a Lambda Function
amplify add function

? Select which capability you want to add: …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JoLo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Web Server For Bug Bounty Hunters (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fulplan/insight-of-a-web-server-part-1-g00</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fulplan/insight-of-a-web-server-part-1-g00"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T07:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello respectful readers. I am Mutasim Abubakar known as fulplan a bug bounty hunter and cybersecurity enthusiasm in today’s write-up. I want to explain the concept of web server, web server attack, and web server attack methodology. And in the conclusion of my write-up, I will explain the preventive measures to take to prevent web server attacks.
Web Server Concept
Web Server Attack
Web Server Attack Methodology
Web Server Preventive Measures
Web Server Concept
To be able to completely compromise a server, you have to understand the theory of a web server and its architecture.
1.Document Root: This is used to store critical HTML files related to the web pages of a domain that will be rendered when a client user sends an HTTP request or communicate with the server. This is mostly found in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mutasim Abubakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaks on our website. How we got hacked?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amersikira/security-leaks-on-our-website-how-we-got-hacked-2lcp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amersikira/security-leaks-on-our-website-how-we-got-hacked-2lcp"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T05:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was originally published on webinuse.com
From 0 to 5.000.000 monthly views, so it will be good if you read it, to have some idea of how we got here. Today we are going to continue by speaking about security issues we had.
In From 0 to 5.000.000 monthly views I mentioned that because of misuse of PDO we were prone to hackers’ attacks. But that was not the only mistake we made, so let’s start from the beginning.
We had a form on the front where readers could send their stories. They just needed to fill in name, email, phone and write their story in textarea or upload a document and send it along with personal information.
Since I was assigned to the front-end I validated every field, even I had validation for the file once the user picked it, but the problem was backend.
Since this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amer Sikira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Detailed Report on
SQL INJECTION]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ks1912/a-detailed-report-on-sql-injection-439m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ks1912/a-detailed-report-on-sql-injection-439m"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T02:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is SQL?
SQL is a language that is used to access and manipulate databases or relational databases. 
What is SQL Injection (SQLi)?
INSERT INTO t1(column_list) SELECT column_list FROM t2; Insert rows from t2 into t1
avoid-spaces/password//FROM//Members
logical operator it'll return 0. A better way to do it is using the CONCAT()function in MySQL.
@version
,sleep(10),3        --+
@version
,sleep(10),3,"'3'"#    --+
), concat(0x3a,0x3a,(select database()),0x3a,0x3a, floor(rand()*2))a from information_schema.columns group by a)
), concat(0x3a,0x3a,(select database()),0x3a,0x3a, floor(rand()2))a from information_schema.columns group by a)b)        --+
), concat(0x3a,0x3a,(select current_user,0x3a,0x3a, floor(rand()2))a from information_schema.columns group by a)b)        --+
), concat(0x3a,0x3a,(select table_name from information_schema.tables where table_schema=database() limit 2,1),0x3a,0x3a, floor(rand()2))a from information_schema.columns group by a)b)        --+
), concat(0x3a,0x3a,(select column_name from information_schema.columns where table_name='users' limit 2,1),0x3a,0x3a, floor(rand()*2))a from information_schema.columns group by a)b)        --+
https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/sql-ddl-dml-tcl-dcl/
https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/sql-ddl-dql-dml-dcl-tcl-commands/
https://www.w3schools.com/sql/sql_injection.asp
https://portswigger.net/web-security/sql-injection
https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/SQL_Injection
https://portswigger.net/web-security/sql-injection/cheat-sheet
https://www.sqltutorial.org/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/SQL-cheat-sheet.pdf
https://www.netsparker.com/blog/web-security/sql-injection-cheat-sheet/
https://www.hackingloops.com/sql-injection-cheat-sheet/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Site Scripting or XSS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ks1912/cross-site-scripting-or-xss-4ppf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ks1912/cross-site-scripting-or-xss-4ppf"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T02:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks are a type of injection, in which malicious scripts are injected into otherwise benign and trusted websites. XSS attacks occur when an attacker uses a web application to send malicious code, generally in the form of a browser side script, to a different end user. 
Let us understand it with an example:
Suppose we visited a website named abc.com who sell some good cloths but prices were high and we close the website later we received a mail where we actually got an off of 90% and there was a link 
www.abc.com/shirts/fullsleves/productid=1asd212Sda/!@a1 
so we ordered some clothes from that link and completed our transaction online. Suddenly we got an update and we came to know that some more transactions happened from our account which were not done by us. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Carefull With rm!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/giorgikeburia/be-carefull-with-rm-7h9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/giorgikeburia/be-carefull-with-rm-7h9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T23:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📣 The world is amazing ,but Not so ideal as we think!🤔
💡 Unix-like operating systems such as Linux do not have an undelete command.
When we delete something with rm , it's gone.Linux assumes we're smart and we know what we're doing.

One of the big problem can cause wildcards. so be particularly with them.
For Example : if we want to delete just the JS files in directory we type:
rm *.js
* and the .js like so:
rm * .js
.js
There is many ways to avoid this problem, here is 2 useful tip: 
-i (interactive) option, which prompt the user for confirmation  ,before deleting an existing file.
rm i *.js
rm: remove regular empty file 'mk.js'?
2 - whenever we use wildcards with rm, test the wildcard first with ls. This will let we see the files that will be deleted. Then we can press the up arrow ☝️ to recall the command and replace ls with rm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GiorgiKeburia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EP 01 | What is Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gayankod/linux-for-hackers-ep-01-e1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gayankod/linux-for-hackers-ep-01-e1h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T20:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series is not only for hackers but also for all beginners who are interested in Linux. By the way, if you want to become a hacker,
YOU JUST START LEARNING LINUX RIGHT NOW!!! GO!!!
Anyway if you’re a kid, like 10 years old, No problem… Don’t be afraid… You can follow through this series and learn about Linux for free. But yes, you have to read, men!!! you cannot watch till I don’t create videos ;)
If you are thinking like “No men I can’t do this, Linux is too hard… How can I learn this? How can I practice this?…” These are all bullcrap…

Hold on, If you read this…
Let me know why are you here in the comment box… Just put why you are interested in Linux, why you want to learn Linux? okay, you put… fine!!! Perfect! Thank you! Let’s move on…

Okay, First of all, you need to install Linux …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gayan Kodithuwakku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t let your RxJS observables die]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pruttned/don-t-let-your-rxjs-observables-die-4ckd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pruttned/don-t-let-your-rxjs-observables-die-4ckd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T20:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS is a powerful library for reactive programming. We use it in Angular all the time, from simple reactions to HTTP client responses to full-blown state management solutions. But sometimes, it is easy to miss some details and create a code that can break at the worst possible moment. 
Let’s start with an example right away.
of(1, 2, 3, 4, 5)
  .pipe(
    tap(v => {
      if (v === 3) {
        throw new Error('some error');
      }
    })
  )
  .subscribe({
    next: console.log.bind(null, 'next:'),
    error: (err: Error) => console.log('error:', err.message),
  });

We have an observable that emits numbers from 1 to 5, and if the number is 3, we throw an error.
We can see the following output.
next: 1
next: 2
error: some error

Numbers 4 and 5 were not processed at all.
This might be s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Ruttkay-Nedecký</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Ceph in a multi-node setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akhal3d/exploring-ceph-in-a-multi-node-setup-3c8h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T18:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Caph is the future of data storage whether it was objects, blocks or a file system. It provides a great alternative to self-hosted solutions such as GlusterFS in the realm of file systems and to managed services such as AWS S3 as an object storage where it makes more sense to host your own data because you have to store it on private cloud or simply to reduce costs as S3 costs sometimes grow to be pretty insane.
I used Vagrant to create a declarative configuration of my environment.
My setup consist of three virtual machines with Ubuntu 20.04 and attached disk storage of 10 GiB to each one of them (except the first machine it has two disks). Ceph documentation says the minimum disk size is 5 GiB but I had problems in the past working with storage less than 10 GiB so I wanted…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Khaled</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instalando somente atualizações de segurança no Amazon Linux 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rafaelonline/instalando-somente-atualizacoes-de-seguranca-no-amazon-linux-2-1k7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rafaelonline/instalando-somente-atualizacoes-de-seguranca-no-amazon-linux-2-1k7k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T16:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sabe aquele servidor solitário ou então que a aplicação só roda em um IaaS? 
É muito provável que as atualizações tenham ficado um pouco de lado (leia-se nunca feito) e chega um momento que será necessário fazer a atualização, nesse momento bate aquele medo de atualizar e quebrar algo, não é?.
O que podemos fazer é atualizar o mínimo necessário (e rezar), normalmente só atualizar o que representa um problema de segurança.
Para nos ajudar podemos utilizar a flag --security na execução do yum.
Antes de começarmos vamos olhar uma saída padrão de um yum update, repare na quantidade de pacotes que serão instalados (10) e atualizados (96)

1 – Garante que o pacote yum-plugin-security esteja instalado:
# yum -y install yum-plugin-security

2 - Você pode listar todas as atualizações de segurança disponíveis com o seguinte comando:
# yum --security check-update

3 – Agora vamos fazer a instalação somente as atualizações de segurança com o menor update possível
# yum --security update-minimal

Compare com a primeira imagem, agora serão instalados (7) e atualizados (50).

Dica extra.
Precisa fazer isso em vários servidores? Utilize o Ansible, com o parâmetro security: yes, para isso :)
- name: Upgrade all packages
  yum:
    name: '*'
    state: latest
    security: yes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafael Conceição</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu/Debian/Ceph/Pardus Local Mirror, Repository Kurulum with Ftp, Http and Https Used apt-mirror, Rsyncmirror and Wget]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aslanfatih/ubuntu-debian-ceph-pardus-local-mirror-repository-kurulum-with-ftp-http-and-https-used-apt-mirror-rsyncmirror-and-wget-2em8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aslanfatih/ubuntu-debian-ceph-pardus-local-mirror-repository-kurulum-with-ftp-http-and-https-used-apt-mirror-rsyncmirror-and-wget-2em8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T13:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[İnternet hızından, güvenlik sebebiyle ya da intranet ağınızdan dolayı apt için local yansı kurmanız gerekebilir.
Aşağıda ülke bazında yakın depoları kullanarak yansı oluşturabiliriz.
Ubuntu: https://launchpad.net/ubuntu/+archivemirrors 

Debian: https://wiki.debian.org/SourcesList#Repository_URL | https://debgen.simplylinux.ch/ 

Ceph: https://download.ceph.com/ 

Pardus: https://belge.pardus.org.tr/display/PYMBB/Pardus+Repo+Mirrorlama
Bu işlem için ilgili makinede yeterince disk alanı(TB olması tavsiye edilir) ayrıca bonding nic ve simetrik yüksek seviyede net bandwidth olması tavsiye edilir.
sudo apt install apt-mirror proftpd-basic apache2 rsync wget git

Konuya girmeden önce, defaultta yüklenen apt-mirror paketinde bazı sorunlar mevcut bu yüzden aşağıdaki ilgili repodaki apt-mirror’u k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatih ASLAN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux sistemlere sertifika ekleme]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aciklab/linux-sistemlere-sertifika-ekleme-m34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aciklab/linux-sistemlere-sertifika-ekleme-m34"/>
        <updated>2021-10-10T12:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[X.509 standartı, özellikle HTTPS'in de içinde bulunduğu TLS/SSL protokollerinin kullandığı şifreleme standartı olarak kullanılmaktadır. Açık kaynak kodlu openssl uygulaması da bu standartı kullanarak bir çok süreci yürütmektedir.
Windows sertifika sistemlerinde genellikle üretilen sertifikalar CER uzantılı olmaktadır. Bu sertifikalar çıktı alınırken DER encoded ve Base64 encoded (PEM) olarak seçilebilmektedir. Genellikle varsayılan olarak DER seçili olduğu için çoğunlukla DER olarak tanımlanmış .CER dosyasıları görebilirsiniz.

DER formatındaki sertifikaları gördüğünüzde dosyanın içinde binary olarak karmaşık formlar olduğunu görürsünüz. (ornek.der)
0A0)N   *�H��
N��*�0
     *�H��
�9�{aGk��.�M�.EV��"!\�H�� �iMN���w��k�3�1H�Ў�<!�s��V%3�}�/�t��?�H���V�;���^��nȯ��3qe�|�M�����&*}CXs|M����.8���…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Orhun Akkirman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debut to Bug-Hunting Cybersecurity and writing Quality Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mannangoyal/debut-to-bug-hunting-cybersecurity-and-writing-quality-code-272c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mannangoyal/debut-to-bug-hunting-cybersecurity-and-writing-quality-code-272c"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T22:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Bugs?
A software bug is an error in a computer program that causes it to produce unexpected results or to behave in a disruptive fashion.
Albeit a bug can be a very innocent flaw, a careless mistake the impact it can have can still be exponentially larger than an exploit due to a big logical error in a code base.
eg. a small rounding error in the calculation of an orbit of a satellite can cause major financial damages with many other implications like space pollution.
Hence, every developer should be aware of basic cybersecurity practices!
How to reduce the number of bugs in your code?
Bringing a structure to your project can be immensely helpful, This structure can be brought by organizing your code but more importantly in your project and amongst your team.
To achieve this we ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mannan Goyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como desabilitar o cache no Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/como-desabilitar-o-cache-no-angular-5bog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/como-desabilitar-o-cache-no-angular-5bog"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T19:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Um dos grandes problemas que enfrentei ao atualizar o frontend de aplicações angular foi o cache. 
Praticamente todos os navegadores mantêm um cache da aplicação no computador do cliente para conseguir carregar a aplicação de forma mais rápida e com menor consumo de dados e isso é excelente. Entretanto, um efeito colateral é que as atualizações podem demorar para serem entregues para o cliente. Como consequência, o cliente pode ficar horas ou dias com uma versão com um bug que já foi corrigido.
Em sistemas internos de empresas, isso pode resultar em ligações ou tickets constantes para a equipe de suporte técnico, causando uma sobrecarga na equipe. Quando estamos falando de aplicações fornecidas para clientes externos à empresa, pode ser um ponto de frustração e insatisfação com o produto.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to bypass input filter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ks1912/how-to-bypass-input-filter-59kd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ks1912/how-to-bypass-input-filter-59kd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T18:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before going into client-side filters let’s understand what client-side filters are. As we know nowadays there are a lot of safer websites available in the market and to make themselves safer they use different kinds of filters also which can be categories in two parts :
Client-Side Filters
Server-Side Filters
We can also say that when we give input and if it satisfies the criteria then it will be accepted otherwise it will raise an error.
For example: Entering letters in the phone number field or Inserting email without @ symbol
Client-Side Filter
On the client-side, the input is being checked on the by browser only which means before sending the input to the server Where on the server-side the input is being sent to the server, and then the server checks whether is valid or not. It is ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bscript/application-security-engineer-5dn8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bscript/application-security-engineer-5dn8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T18:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When you start working as an application security engineer, you'll expect to find straightforward tasks to do. But this is not the case because each company has its vision and strategies to handle data security, which can let us infer that every organization's security maturity may differ from one to another.
Viewing data breaches and cyber incidents all the time proves that no one out there has a mature cyber security program.
If you are already working in this field, I imagine that you sometimes feel that you're achieving nothing and you are more invisible inside the organization. The bigest challenge I see is how to increase your visibility and have more transparency with your manager and the rest of your co-workers.
In this article, I'd like to share what I've learned wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bour Abdelhadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a SOC Team Members Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rahulwoll/what-does-a-soc-team-members-do-3ocg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rahulwoll/what-does-a-soc-team-members-do-3ocg"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T16:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security operations center, known as a SOC – pronounced “sock” 🧦 - is a team of experts that proactively monitor an organization’s ability to operate securely.
Members of a SOC team are responsible for a variety of activities, including proactive monitoring, incident response and recovery, remediation activities, compliance, and coordination and context.
Proactive Monitoring
Incident Response and Recovery
For example, that recovery can include activities such as handling acute malware or ransomware incidents. 
Remediation Activities 
For Example, using information obtained from log files and other sources, a SOC member can recommend a better network segmentation strategy or a better system patching regimen. Improving existing CyberSecurity is a major responsibility of a SOC. 
Compliance
Organisation secure themselves through conformity to a security policy, as well as external security standards, such as ISO 27001x, the NIST CyberSecurity Framework(CSF) and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Organisations need a SOC to help ensure that they are compliant with an important security standards and best practices. 
Coordination and Context
Above all, a SOC team member helps an organisation coordinate desperate elements and services and provide visualized, useful information. Part of this coordination is the ability to provide a helpful, useful set of narratives for activities on the network. These narratives help shape a company's CyberSecurity policy and posture for the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding the loading component (spinner) to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-loading-component-spinner-to-an-angular-application-4mk0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-loading-component-spinner-to-an-angular-application-4mk0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T12:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
ngx-spinner is a loading (spinner) component library with more than 50 different types.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the application with the Angular base structure using the @angular/cli with the route file and the SCSS style format.
ng new angular-spinner
? Would you like to add Angular routing? Yes
? Which stylesheet format would you like to use? SCSS   [ https://sass-lang.com/documentation/syntax#scss                ]
CREATE angular-spinner/README.md…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create and remove network on Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-create-and-remove-network-on-docker-1lig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-create-and-remove-network-on-docker-1lig"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T12:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now i will show you how to create and remove network on Docker, lets follow the instructions :)
first, lets see the list of network
docker network ls

then create new network by type this command with name  'demo'
docker network create --subnet=172.16.0.0/24 --gateway=172.16.0.1 demo

at the end, to see the details of 'demo', you can type
docker network inspect demo

to remove network on Dokcer, you can type this
docker network rm demo

N/B : ip address and name of network can custom by you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Pepuho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic CRUD Service in Angular: Part 2 - What is CRUD?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-2-what-is-crud-30ek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-2-what-is-crud-30ek"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T08:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Tobias Fischer on Unsplash.
This article is a part of a series about how to create Generic CRUD Service & Models in Angular:
Part 1 - Understanding Generics
👉 Part 2 - What is CRUD?

Part 3 - Generic CRUD Model (coming soon...)

Part 4 - Generic CRUD Service in Angular (coming soon...)




  
  
  What is CRUD?



Create, Read, Update, and Delete 👉 CRUD
Starting from the acronym, CRUD means create, read, update, and delete. These are the four main functionalities that must be provided by all models when building APIs.
Firstly let's explain some basics... An API is a set of definitions and protocols for building and integrating application software. It's the main contract between frontend and backend regarding their communication. An API in order to be RESTful, it should fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikos Anifantis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How Service Works when injected in different Levels]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dasaradhanimmala/angular-how-service-works-when-injected-in-different-levels-5e7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dasaradhanimmala/angular-how-service-works-when-injected-in-different-levels-5e7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T07:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video , I clearly explained about how service works when it is injected in different Levels like Component Level, Module Level and App Level.
Explained step by step with practical examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dasaradh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are your Angular Services Singleton ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sanketmaru/are-your-angular-services-singleton-307f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sanketmaru/are-your-angular-services-singleton-307f"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T07:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular has the concept of services which allows to share the data between components.
In this blog we will learn about service instances creation in Angular.
What happens when we inject service in root of a lazy module, is the same instance used for multiple lazy modules.
What if we want to have a separate instance per module and per component ?
We will use the same code example as used in common chunks example. If you haven't gone through that blog do checkout to learn on why common chunks are created.
Let's begin then.
Let's start where we ended in the previous post. We have two lazy modules user and account and currently share the same toast module which is built in a separate chunk.
As we have given as @Injectable({ providedIn: "root" }) for the toast service, a singleton instance of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanket Maru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-prepare-for-ransomware-attacks-81h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-prepare-for-ransomware-attacks-81h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T00:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks continue to increase, using techniques that are growing more and more sophisticated and targeted. Security and risk management leaders need to look beyond just the endpoints to help protect the organization from ransomware.
What exactly is Ransomware:
How does ransomware work?
Why is ransomware spreading?
Ransomware Defense Life Cycle

How to defend against ransomware:

Anatomy of a Ransomware Attack

Final and more important:
Thank you very much for your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pablosalas81</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for ‘Developer Experience’]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353429</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-case-for-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T20:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good essay from Jean Yang. 
What I mean by developer experience is the sum total of how developers interface with their tools, end-to-end, day-in and day-out. Sure, there’s more focus than ever on how developers use and adopt tools, and 
…
The post The Case for ‘Developer Experience’ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Computer Programming?]]></title>
        <id>615d55e60d91c9077974d408</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-programming/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's world, we are all heavily reliant on various software products that were carefully programmed by developers. But what is computer programming? In this article, I will provide a definition of programming, as well as examples of different types of programmers. I will also suggest a list of courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn On Dark Mode on Google – Chrome Black Theme Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>6160836e804854468fda67bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-turn-on-dark-mode-on-google-chrome-black-theme-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, lots of developers like to use dark mode. And it's no surprise, as activating dark mode reduces eye strain and leads to better eye health. It also helps both machines and humans perform better overall.  In this article, I will show you how to turn on the dark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></title>
        <id>613f3c5e852f4307d372c7c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-drop-a-pin-on-google-maps/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T19:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to save a new location you discovered on Google Maps, you need to drop a pin on that location.  In this article, I will show you how to drop a pin in Google Maps from your phone or computer. How to Drop a Pin on Google Maps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353374</id>
        <link href="https://katiekodes.com/jekyll-components-wysiwyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T17:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the pushback from Katie Kodes here. I’ve said in the past that I don’t think server-side languages haven’t quite nailed “building in components” as well as JavaScript has, but hey, this is a good point:
1. Any basic 
…
The post Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Excel File that Pulls Customer Data with WooCommerce and Python]]></title>
        <id>615dbaeb0d91c9077974defb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-excel-file-with-customers-data-with-woocommerce-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Hey, could you please send me our customers' emails? We’re about to launch a new marketing campaign and…we need them ASAP.” If you work in the Web department on a corporate level, you've probably heard this sentence hundreds of times. So, today I want to share how I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export your table data to a .csv file]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nisachampagne/export-your-table-data-to-a-csv-file-4ca0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nisachampagne/export-your-table-data-to-a-csv-file-4ca0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T15:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that my job has me learning a new thing ( or two :) ) every day. This time it was exporting table data to a .csv file that could therefore be used whichever way needed. Of course, there are many ways to go about this.
Lets set the project in view here: 
Now to figure out how to approach it. 
As I was figuring out how I wanted to work on this, my mind was on simple and to the point as we just want to create the file client-side. I found https://www.npmjs.com/package/file-saver to which suits my needs. Now all that's left is to implement the exportCSV function. 
In my typescript file,  I added the following:
 exportFile(data: any) {
    const replacer = (key, value) => value === null ? '' : value;
    const header = Object.keys(data[0]);
    let csv = data.map(row => header.map(fieldN…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nisa Champagne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353066</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-tennis-trivia-app-with-next-js-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will be learning how to build a tennis trivia app using Next.js and Netlify. This technology stack has become my go-to on many projects. It allows for rapid development and easy deployment.
Without further ado let’s jump in!…
The post Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenley Dueck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353062</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-google-analytics-and-plausible-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw this blog post the other day: 58% of Hacker News, Reddit and tech-savvy audiences block Google Analytics. That’s an enticing title to me. I’ve had Google Analytics on this site literally from the day I launched it. …
The post Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real World Examples of 5 Common Observable Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/real-world-examples-of-5-common-observable-operators-48i7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/real-world-examples-of-5-common-observable-operators-48i7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article was originally published to my blog StackBlogger: Real World Examples of 5 Common Observable Operators
Reactive Extensions of JavaScript is a library for reactive programming. It is commonly known for its operators. The RxJS Operators are also known as Observable Operators.
What are Operators?
Operators are pure functions. They take observable as input and return output as observable.
map– a transformation operator works similar to Array.prototype.map
switchMap– cancels the inner observable when outer observable emits a value
catchError– catches the error and passes to error handling function
debounceTime– discards values if emitted in less than specified time
takeUntil– automatically unsubscribes from an observable
distinctUntilChanged– emits only distinct values and duplicate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filter in Angular with code example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tizhad/filter-in-angular-with-code-example-18g1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tizhad/filter-in-angular-with-code-example-18g1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T13:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being honest, I'm not a senior developer, but I do want to share things that I'm learning. Hopefully, it can be helpful.
If you are looking for an answer for this question " How can I filter an array in Angular", this post can help you.
You have an array of cars:
cars: ICar[] = [
    {
      'carId': 1,
      'carName': 'Toyota',
      'carCode': 'CAR-0023',
      'releaseDate': 'March 18, 2019',
      'description': 'this is a description',
      'price': 35000,
      'starRating': 4.2,
      'imageUrl': 'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1525609004556-c46c7d6cf023?ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxzZWFyY2h8M3x8Y2Fyc3xlbnwwfHwwfHw%3D&ixlib=rb-1.2.1&w=1000&q=80'
    },
    {
      'carId': 2,
      'carName': 'Bugatti test',
      'carCode': 'CAR-1123',
      'releaseDate': 'March 18, 2020',
      'desc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tizhad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing Your Own Code Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353112</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/writing-your-own-code-rules/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T23:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time on a project when it’s worth investing in tooling to protect the codebase. I’m not sure how to articulate when, but it’s somewhere after the project has proven to be something long-term and rough edges …
The post Writing Your Own Code Rules appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353386</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T21:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog posts that get into the whole “how to think like a front-end developer” vibe are my favorite. Michelle Barker nails that in this post, and does it without sharing a line of code!
We simply can no longer 
…
The post Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Go? Golang Programming Language Meaning Explained]]></title>
        <id>615de4da0d91c9077974e23f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-go-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go, also known as Golang, is an open-source, compiled, and statically typed programming language designed by Google. It is built to be simple, high-performing, readable, and efficient.  In this article, you'll learn:  Where Go came from and where it is now, Why I think you should learn it, How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353024</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-in-typescript-with-vanilla-extract/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vanilla-extract is a new framework-agnostic CSS-in-TypeScript library. It’s a lightweight, robust, and intuitive way to write your styles. vanilla-extract isn’t a prescriptive CSS framework, but a flexible piece of developer tooling. CSS tooling has been a relatively stable space over …
The post CSS in TypeScript with vanilla-extract appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353242</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-themeable-react-data-grid-with-great-ux-focused-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T14:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
KendoReact can save you boatloads of time because it offers pre-built componentry you can use in your app right away. They look nice, but more importantly, they are easily themeable, so they look however …
The post A Themeable React Data Grid With Great UX-Focused Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Websites We Like: MD Nichrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353219</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/websites-we-like-md-nichrome/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a beautiful website: it’s a type specimen for Mass-Driver’s ever-so-lovely type family MD Nichrome. There’s a ton of nifty animations and graphics explaining all the features inside…
If you’re wondering how those animations work, they’re actually styled <video>…
The post Websites We Like: MD Nichrome appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Single Page App Morality Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353320</id>
        <link href="https://www.baldurbjarnason.com/2021/single-page-app-morality-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T22:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baldur Bjarnason brings some baby bear porridge to the discussion of  Single Page App (SPA) vs. Multi Page App (MPA).
Single-Page-Apps can be fantastic. Most teams will mess them up because most teams operate in dysfunctional 
…
The post The Single Page App Morality Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C String – How to Declare Strings in the C Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>615beb720d91c9077974c716</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-string-how-to-declare-strings-in-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computers store and process all kinds of data.  Strings are just one of the many forms in which information is presented and gets processed by computers.  Strings in the C programming language work differently than in other modern programming languages.  In this article, you'll learn how to declare strings in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python range() Function – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>612f4388d6679a07b7d3fee4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-range-function-explained-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T17:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Python, can use use the range() function to get a sequence of indices to loop through an iterable. You'll often use range() in conjunction with a for loop.  In this tutorial, you'll learn about the different ways in which you can use the range() function – with explicit start and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux tar Command – How to Compress Files in Linux]]></title>
        <id>614870b9852f4307d3731030</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compress-files-in-linux-with-tar-command/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T16:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File compression is an essential utility across all platforms. It helps you reduce file size and share files efficiently. And compressed files are also easier to copy to remote servers.  You can also compress older and rarely used files and save them for future use which helps you conserve disk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352959</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/considerations-for-using-markdown-writing-apps-on-static-sites/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you run or have recently switched to a static site generator, you might find yourself writing a lot of Markdown. And the more you write it, the more you want the tooling experience to disappear so that …
The post Considerations for Using Markdown Writing Apps on Static Sites appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Barnard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Options for Password Revealing Inputs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352676</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-options-for-password-revealing-inputs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T14:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, there is a very clear input type for dealing with passwords:
<input type="password">
If you use that, you get the obfuscated bullet-points when you type into it, like:
••••••••
That’s the web trying to help with security. If …
The post The Options for Password Revealing Inputs appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>