<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-10T00:54:35.705Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-10T00:54:35.705Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.5.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 obstacles of a beginner junior developer and how to overcome them]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/3-obstacles-of-a-beginner-junior-developer-and-how-to-overcome-them-2edc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/3-obstacles-of-a-beginner-junior-developer-and-how-to-overcome-them-2edc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T23:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a junior developer at a startup is a tough job, for a self-taught developer and who is also getting a degree in Computer Science. I started out as an intern and transitioned to a full stack junior developer position. And these are the three things that became my kryptonite for a short time.
Since these are problems and since we are problem-solvers, these are my analyzes.

1.Procrastination



A good approach would be to remind yourself to snap out of it, but like all habits this will take time to stic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>100lvlmaster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Vue.js, Angular, or Ember do data store?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/klappleseed/how-does-vue-js-angular-or-ember-do-data-store-25k6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/klappleseed/how-does-vue-js-angular-or-ember-do-data-store-25k6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T21:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How does Vue.js, Angular, or Ember do data store? I found React's Redux a bit complicated / messy and have a lot of boilerplates, usually with a lot of selectors after selectors and createSelector(), and tons of reducers.
I know I don't have to use Redux with React, but most projects I have seen (and have to use at work) use Redux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>klappleseed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QR Code Generator Website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bibekkakati/qr-code-generator-website-gmo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bibekkakati/qr-code-generator-website-gmo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T20:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can we generate a QR Code for any content in JavaScript?
Check out this article: Generate QRCode]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bibek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a nodeJS server without using express.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bonicellimattia/build-a-nodejs-server-without-using-express-52ed</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bonicellimattia/build-a-nodejs-server-without-using-express-52ed"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how to build a server without using express?
Well, look no further...
 
While a very convenient framework express is not necessary to get up and running with a server built on nodeJS.
Looking at how express operates you'll realize that under the hood it utilizes the http module, and as such you can think of express as a wrapper for http.
With this in mind we shall attempt to spin up a server using the http module alone.
 
The amount of code we need to write to achieve this is minimal.
const ht…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattia Bonicelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codetree ! Or why i create a new Codepen.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/philippetedajo/codetree-or-why-i-create-a-new-codepen-c8m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/philippetedajo/codetree-or-why-i-create-a-new-codepen-c8m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T19:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codepen and codesandbox are great, but honestly they are slow and even more if you have a weak internet connection, so i created Codetree, an ultra-fast, high-performance online playground with automatic npm module detection.
Codetree is a powerful online editor, we will:




Understand how codepen works.


Find a bundler that can be executable inside our browser.


Build a simple react app transpiler.




  
  
  First, how Codepen/Codesandbox works ?


Thanks to the great instructor Stephen Grider, i foun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Tedajo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript = Javascript with benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amansethi00/typescript-javascript-with-benefits-8eo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amansethi00/typescript-javascript-with-benefits-8eo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T18:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone,hope you are taking good care of yourself in these times and coding everyday.Js is a must learn language when working with web related projects,be it frontend related or just backend.Modern libraries and frameworks use JS and many developers love using it but it doesn't mean we should totally outlook areas where JS is not efficient.Since JS is dynamic typed languages, variables can be abused in the codebase and it will not be known to the program until it is executed, that is during runtime.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Sethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Install or Update Node by Using nvm (Node Version Manager)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mxkvl/how-to-install-or-update-node-by-using-nvm-node-version-manager-1ip1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mxkvl/how-to-install-or-update-node-by-using-nvm-node-version-manager-1ip1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T18:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


There are few ways to install Node on your local machine. The most popular way is to install it following official website instructions. But if you use this way you will install just one specific (latest) version of Node. What if you need to install a specific version of Node? Or you need to upgrade from one version to another but only for a short while. 
For that purpose, you can use a tool called nvm (Node Version Manager).
Because I use macOS on my local machine these instructions are specific to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kovalevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publishing Python Apps at Anaconda and further Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/niklastiede/publishing-python-apps-at-anaconda-and-further-automation-10a0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/niklastiede/publishing-python-apps-at-anaconda-and-further-automation-10a0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T17:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya fellows,
The code of this post can be found on Github (see here).
When a setup.py file was already created, it's pretty simple to go a step further and create an Anaconda package. Anaconda packages store the necessary metadata within a meta.yaml file but when a setup.py file was already created its data can be easily imported by jinja2 templating.
{% set data = load_setup_py_data() %}

package:
  name: 'tihttp'
  version: {{ data['version'] }}

source:
  path: ..

build:
  number: 0
  entry_points:
   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niklas Tiede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HostListener how to use]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fsystem/hostlistener-how-to-use-h7j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fsystem/hostlistener-how-to-use-h7j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T17:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, today I will explain how to use the HostListener decorator easily.
First, this decorator we use for:
This decorator is listening for a specific event by the host element
Go to the code example:
Each time you click inside the component, the counter will increase by 1
  @HostListener("click", ["$event"])
  onClickEvent(event: Event) {
    this.clicksCounts += 1;
  }





If you want to know all the events that you can play with HostListener you can see it in w3school  list here -&gt;[https://www.w3schools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fsystem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCP DevOps Certification - Pomodoro Eleven]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eggsy84/gcp-devops-certification-day-eleven-4njh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eggsy84/gcp-devops-certification-day-eleven-4njh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T16:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data processing SLI's


There is a high likelihood that you'll be working working with a platform that works with user provided or user generated information to provide a service.
Google recommend four different types of SLI's for that use case:
Freshness
Correctness
Coverage
Throughput
Let's review each of them, much along the similar lines of previous blogs Google uses the term "valid", this time in regards to the data and "proportions" to reflect things as percentages.
The data "freshness" can be conside…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Heggs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular CLI shortcuts for generating components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fsystem/angular-cli-shortcuts-240</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fsystem/angular-cli-shortcuts-240"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T16:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when we need to create a new element, we copy a component and paste renaming the files instead of using the proper command of angular CLI.
I think is important to follow the right approach and use the angular CLI commands because in this way, take it for sure
For that, I will share with you, what I use the most.



element
command
short way




Component
ng g component nameComponent
ng g c nameComponent


Service
ng g service nameService
ng g s nameService


Enum
ng g enum nameEnum
ng g e nameEnum…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fsystem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to migrate a  MySQL Database from DigitalOcean to AWS RDS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cristianllanos/how-to-migrate-a-mysql-database-from-digitalocean-to-aws-rds-3o82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cristianllanos/how-to-migrate-a-mysql-database-from-digitalocean-to-aws-rds-3o82"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T15:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objective


At the end of this process, we'll have successfully moved our selected MySQL schemas onto another MySQL Database (to AWS RDS for instance). We'll make use of some automated bash scripts to ease our way.
Warning: the strategy shown in this guide will incur downtime for the clients of our databases while the migration process is running.  Use this guide as a learning resource at your own risk.
If you are looking for the lowest migration downtime possible, I suggest having a look at AWS Database Mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cristian Llanos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish NuGet packages via Docker Release Container]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikiforovall/publish-nuget-packages-via-docker-release-container-21ej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikiforovall/publish-nuget-packages-via-docker-release-container-21ej"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T15:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR


You can use Docker to push packages to a NuGet feed. This blog post shows how to release a NuGet package to Amazon CodeArtifact via Docker. Source code can be found at https://github.com/NikiforovAll/docker-release-container-sample.
The idea behind having a release container is pretty straightforward - you can bundle artifacts and tools so the release mechanism is portable and unified because of Docker. Also, another advantage of building NuGet packages in Docker is that you don't need any dependenc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleksii Nikiforov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nginx HTTP Basic Authentication(Kimlik Doğrulama) Kurulumu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aslanfatih/nginx-http-basic-authentication-kimlik-dogrulama-kurulumu-445o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aslanfatih/nginx-http-basic-authentication-kimlik-dogrulama-kurulumu-445o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T14:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aşağıdaki paketlerin kurulumunu gerçekleştirin.
Ubuntu;
sudo apt install nginx apache2-utils

Redhat/CentOS;
yum install epel-release nginx httpd-tools

Nginx “/etc/nginx/sites-available/sites.conf” altındaki kaynak konfig dosyalarının “/etc/nginx/sites-enabled/sites.conf” altında link’li olduğunu düşünerek, Yapılandırma şekli aşağıdaki gibi yapılabilir.
İlk önce aşağıdaki komutları yürütün,
- mkdir /www/sites/indexpage
- mkdir /www/sites/files
- mkdir /www/sites/files/exclude
- echo “Welcome to nginx” &gt;…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatih ASLAN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Node to Go | Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sid__/from-node-to-go-part-1-2dib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sid__/from-node-to-go-part-1-2dib"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T14:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Reader! Welcome to the From Node to Go series. 
This series is basically for all the Node.js developers who want to switch to or learn Golang. But since I am starting this from very very basics of Nodejs as well, this can be used to learn web dev in Node.js as well. 
PRE-REQUISITE for this series: You should know how to run node and go programs and you know the basics of Go. If not, I would recommend doing a quick walk through here  (Excellent stuff)
2 - in - 1 !! Oh Yeah!
END-GOAL of this series: Writin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Udeniya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i3 Ricing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/i3-ricing-19ih</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/i3-ricing-19ih"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T14:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys!!!
Linux Mint 20.1 XFCE using the i3-window manager. Developers mostly use upgraded ricing tools like the Awesome window manager for their ricing models. Ricing in Arch-based systems is comparatively easier than in Ubuntu-based systems. Although, I preferred i3-window manager as it is good for beginners and we get to build the ricing model from scratch. 
My Ricing model is uploaded on YouTube on my friend's channel:
i3-riced model 




The configuration file for the ricing model is uploaded on Gi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritabrata Das</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How useful is learning VI/VIM for a new programmer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/how-useful-is-learning-vi-vim-for-a-new-programmer-1h57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/how-useful-is-learning-vi-vim-for-a-new-programmer-1h57"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using a text editor called "vim" for more than a year now, and it has changed my programming life. Let's take a look.
If you are going to be writing code in Python, then it would be useful to learn to use a text editor called "Vim". I don't say that because I wrote the book on this topic (I didn't), but because it will help you be more efficient as a programmer. 
Vim is an extremely powerful text editor used by programmers and system administrators around the world. Often described as a "programme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Head Start to Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shiv008/head-start-to-express-55c6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shiv008/head-start-to-express-55c6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Express



  
  
  what the heck Express is ??


*So the answer is Express.js or Express is backend web application framework for node.js so that you can go and create your backend logic there for your web app or mobile application such as API *
Before creating your first API using express let's know few things that we are going to cover in this post in this post we will learn to create API express.js using replit that provides you node environment so you can use it.
*open replit and cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSL,VSCode Terminal: "Coddled and Cosseted"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sunishsurendrank/wsl-vscode-terminal-coddled-and-cosseted-aio</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sunishsurendrank/wsl-vscode-terminal-coddled-and-cosseted-aio"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLAG:   "If you have more time as a developer to improve your Terminal look and also if you're a Windows user, this blog can help you!"
Here we try out some fancy stuff for the WSL terminal.
The plan is to use WSL via windows Terminal. For this first install WSL and Windows Terminal on your machine.
Go through the below 6 steps and have the awesome terminal on your machine.
STEP 1 : Install zsh in WSL




apt-get install zsh


STEP 2 : Install "Oh My Zsh"
visit the website https://ohmyz.sh/#install
sh -c "$…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunish Surendran K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring TypeScript - Const Assertions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zsgomoridev/exploring-typescript-const-assertions-2h9j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zsgomoridev/exploring-typescript-const-assertions-2h9j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published at zsgomori.dev. Head over there if you like this post and want to read others like it!
The const assertion was released with TypeScript 3.4. It's a special type of type assertion in the sense that the const keyword is used in place of the type.
By definition, the const assertion has the following effects:
Literal types will not be widened.
Object literals will get readonly properties.
Array literals will become readonly tuples.
Here's an example:
let foo = "foo" as con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zsolt Gomori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VSCode server on Azure Ubuntu VM. A step by step guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/buttonfreak/vscode-server-on-azure-ubuntu-vm-a-step-by-step-guide-38h5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/buttonfreak/vscode-server-on-azure-ubuntu-vm-a-step-by-step-guide-38h5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T12:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'll explain step-by-step on how to create your own VSCode server running on a VM in Microsoft Azure.
After following these steps, you'll end up with a development server which you can use to work on Node.js frontend and backend projects. You could probably use it for other stacks. From my experience working with this setup is almost the same as running VSCode on your own machine, except it's not on your local machine.
You can connect your local VSCode editor with the VSCode server using SSH…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivo Toby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a simple Node.js RESTful API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/youssefallalix/build-a-simple-node-js-restful-api-5g40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/youssefallalix/build-a-simple-node-js-restful-api-5g40"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T11:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



What is REST?
Prerequisites
Set up the workspace
Set up the database
Set up the routes
Set up the controller
Set up the server
Test the API
Conclusion
Final words




REST is an acronym for Representational State Transfer and it is a software architectural style which uses a subset of HTTP
A base URI, such as http://api.example.com/;
Standard HTTP methods (e.g., GET, POST, PUT, and DELETE);
Media types, such as application/json.
In this tutorial, we will learn how to create a RESTful AP…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Youssef Allali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Release and Publish Python Apps at PyPI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/niklastiede/how-to-release-and-publish-python-apps-at-pypi-3nn9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/niklastiede/how-to-release-and-publish-python-apps-at-pypi-3nn9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T11:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya fellows,
The code of this post can be found on Github (see here).
As stated in previous posts our project can now be downloaded from Github and installed via pip locally. But Python packages are usually installed from the Python Packaging Index (PyPI) with a simple name easy to remember.
So how do we release our project so others can download it conveniently? We make sure that our main line is in a releasable state and then we
Tag our project and stick thereby to a versioning scheme
Release it on Githu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niklas Tiede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp Clone (Backend & FrontEnd)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devstack06/whatsapp-clone-backend-frontend-254b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devstack06/whatsapp-clone-backend-frontend-254b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T10:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, I created the WhatsApp Clone using Flutter. Please check out the screenshots of the app &amp; source code in my GitHub -https://github.com/DevStack06/Whatsapp-Clone-Flutter And please do star the repo if you liked it!!
You can also check the Youtube Playlist, which will cover both Front-End and Backend Development: https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLtIU0BH0pkKovuEaNsrGE_Xd5Tz3m1zeC
Any suggestions are warmly welcomed, and it is open source so feel free to contribute ✌️✌️✌️.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balram Rathore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to integrate Angular 4 with SpringBoot RestApi using SpringToolSuite]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-integrate-angular-4-with-springboot-restapi-using-springtoolsuite-5179</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-integrate-angular-4-with-springboot-restapi-using-springtoolsuite-5179"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T09:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/integrate-angular-4-springboot-web-app-springtoolsuite
How to integrate Angular 4 with SpringBoot RestApi using SpringToolSuite
Angular 4 is the next version of Angular2 that comes with almost everything you need to build Across All Platforms frontend web or mobile apps with high speed &amp; performance. So in the tutorial, JavaSampleApproach will guide you through the steps of integrating Angular 4 with SpringBoot Web App and SpringToolSuite for development.
Angular 6:
How to Integrate …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Reasons Why New Businesses Fail]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/top-10-reasons-why-new-businesses-fail-217p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/top-10-reasons-why-new-businesses-fail-217p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T09:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one starts a business expecting to fail. Starting a business can be a lot of fun and excitement. Success requires a lot of planning and starting the business the right way.
https://anchor.fm/dami-okoro/episodes/Top-10-Reasons-Why-New-Businesses-Fail-evo63l
Enjoy! Don't forget to feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Reasons Why New Businesses Fail]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/top-10-reasons-why-new-businesses-fail-217p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/top-10-reasons-why-new-businesses-fail-217p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T09:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one starts a business expecting to fail. Starting a business can be a lot of fun and excitement. Success requires a lot of planning and starting the business the right way.
https://anchor.fm/dami-okoro/episodes/Top-10-Reasons-Why-New-Businesses-Fail-evo63l
Enjoy! Don't forget to feedback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools you need for making your own Linux distribution.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/tools-you-need-for-making-your-own-linux-distribution-23eg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/tools-you-need-for-making-your-own-linux-distribution-23eg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T09:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You need have your own Linux Distibution then know these tools so that you can build your own Linux Distibution for your own purpose that you need example hacking,pentesting and so on.
Thus, you can use these following tools.
You can install an Virtual box and then go and get the OS installed on to the virtual box as a OVA file and also change it and then publish as your own Custom OS which is one of the best technique that you can adopt to build your own distribution.

Linux Respin is an offshoot of the no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vishwasnarayanre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access Key Vault secret from Web Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivappa/access-key-vault-secret-from-web-application-4nem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivappa/access-key-vault-secret-from-web-application-4nem"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous parts we have learnt how to create Azure Key Vault and how to add the principal in Azure Key Vault by whom it must be accessed.
Let's write a simple flask app to fetch the secrets from Key Vault.
KeyVaultDemo on your computer and open it in VS Code.
requirements.txt which contains the packages required.
flask
azure-keyvault-secrets
azure-identity


azure-keyvault-secrets: It is a client library in python to access the secrets stored in Azure Key Vault. More information on this package can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivappa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequelize belongstomany Example – Nodejs/Expresss]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/sequelize-belongstomany-example-nodejs-expresss-4gj9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/sequelize-belongstomany-example-nodejs-expresss-4gj9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://loizenai.com/sequelize-belongstomany-example/
Sequelize belongstomany Example – Nodejs/Express
In the previous post, we had setup a Spring Kafka Application succesfully by explicitly configuration Kafka Factories with SpringBoot. But the messages had been used have String type. While in the development, POJO (Plain Old Java Object) are often used to construct messages. So with the tutorial, JavaSampleApproach will show how to use Spring Kafka JsonSerializer (JsonDeserializer) to produce/consume Java…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing extraneous NPM packages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/removing-extraneous-npm-packages-43n4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/removing-extraneous-npm-packages-43n4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsis





npm prune [[&lt;@scope&gt;/]&lt;pkg&gt;...] [--production] [--dry-run] [--json]

This command removes "extraneous" packages. If a package name is provided, then only packages matching one of the supplied names are removed.
Extraneous packages are those present in the node_modules folder that are not listed as any package's dependency list.
If the --production flag is specified or the NODE_ENV environment variable is set to production, this command will remove the packages specified in your dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM Behind A Proxy Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/npm-behind-a-proxy-server-2954</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/npm-behind-a-proxy-server-2954"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your internet access is through a proxy server, you might need to modify npm install commands that access remote repositories. npm uses a configuration file which can be updated via command line:
npm config set

You can locate your proxy settings from your browser's settings panel. Once you have obtained the proxy settings (server URL, port, username and password); you need to configure your npm configurations as follows.
$ npm config set proxy http://&lt;username&gt;:&lt;password&gt;@&lt;proxy-server-ur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js : How to get a basic HTTPS web server up and running!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-how-to-get-a-basic-https-web-server-up-and-running-9ke</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-how-to-get-a-basic-https-web-server-up-and-running-9ke"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you have node.js installed on your system, you can just follow the procedure below to get a basic web server running with support for both HTTP and HTTPS!
1.1. create the folder where you want to store your key &amp; certificate :
mkdir conf

1.2. go to that directory :
cd conf

1.3. grab this ca.cnf file to use as a configuration shortcut :
wget https://raw.githubusercontent.com/anders94/https-authorized-clients/master/keys/ca.cnf

1.4. create a new certificate authority using this configuration :
ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TLS Socket: server and client]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/tls-socket-server-and-client-1pe8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/tls-socket-server-and-client-1pe8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only major differences between this and a regular TCP connection are the private Key and the public certificate that you’ll have to set into an option object.
The first step in this security process is the creation of a private Key. And what is this private key? Basically, it's a set
openssl genrsa -out private-key.pem 1024

Once we have our private key, we can create a CSR (certificate signing request), which is our request to have the private key signed by a fancy authority. That is why you have to in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Techniques to scale your Relational Databases - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/techniques-to-scale-your-relational-databases-part-2-5be</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/techniques-to-scale-your-relational-databases-part-2-5be"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T07:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Techniques to scale your Relational Databases - Part 1
Vishnu Chilamakuru ・ May 7 ・ 3 min read
#database
        #architecture
        #performance
        #devops
      
This blog post is a continuation of my previous blog post mentioned above. In my previous post, I mentioned Scaling Relational Databases using Replication. In this post, I will mention more about 
Federation
Sharding
Denormalization

  
Federation (or functional partitioning) splits up databases by function.  For example, instead of a sing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Chilamakuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust CI with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bampeers/rust-ci-with-github-actions-1ne9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bampeers/rust-ci-with-github-actions-1ne9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T07:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI(Continuous Integration) is a concept that would interest most developers in a collaborative environment. CI automates the post-coding process of building and testing rather than doing it manually.
Through CI, developers can smoothly integrate their code with other people’s code. This allows developers to focus on coding without wasting their time on integration, which in turn increases productivity.
However, setting up CI can be troublesome and time-consuming, so developers have to decide the extent thei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Candy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types vs. Interfaces in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ananta/types-vs-interfaces-in-typescript-1g3p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ananta/types-vs-interfaces-in-typescript-1g3p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T07:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: The term "Types" in this article is referring to the"type" aliases in Typescript
According to the official Typescript document: "TypeScript is an open-source language that builds on JavaScript, one of the world’s most used tools, by adding static type definitions." Implementing typescript on our project saves a lot of time in the long run. But as a developer, we should follow the best practices and standards when working with types in typescript. 
type aliases and interface. Many developers don't real…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ananta Bastola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand and use Azure Key Vault Easily (Most Secured Secrets Storage)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivappa/understand-and-use-azure-key-vault-easily-most-secured-secrets-storage-19n0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivappa/understand-and-use-azure-key-vault-easily-most-secured-secrets-storage-19n0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T06:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now a days the term security becoming the must follow topic for all the organizations to have a good brand name.
To solve this issue we can use Azure Key Vault resource.
Securely store the keys, secrets and certificates.
Only authorized user can access the key vault.
Frequently rotate the secrets, keys.
Automatically renew the certificates.
Centralized storage for all keys, secrets and certificates.
Azure Key Vault can be used in many services, here I will be showing how to use it in Azure app service.
Prer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivappa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sarjeant/diving-into-devops-18oo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sarjeant/diving-into-devops-18oo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T02:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the beginning of a deep dive into DevOps.
My career is pivoting into DevSecOps. I am strong and certified on the "Sec" (AWS Security Specialty; Azure Security Engineer; CISSP).  I wish to be just the same for DevOps.
The plan:-
AWS DevOps Engineer Professional - Q2
Azure Developer Associate - Q3
Node.js - Q4 or Q1 2022
To kick of AWS DevOps Engineer Professional Certification:-
AWS free tier plus AWS credits compliments of AWS Community Builders
AWS DevOps Professional Course by Stephane Maarek
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Judith Sarjeant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Yubikey works and why you should use one]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/theashwinmenon/how-a-yubikey-works-and-why-you-should-use-one-jb3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/theashwinmenon/how-a-yubikey-works-and-why-you-should-use-one-jb3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T00:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I research topics to write about and share with the community, I thought I'd post an article I'd written a while ago. Here goes...
As part of efforts to improve security, my workplace has issued us Yubikeys. What is a Yubikey? It’s a device you plug into your computer’s USB port and when you touch it for a few seconds, it spits out a string. This string is used for authentication (to identify you). The device has a capacitive sensor to detect touch, just like most phones today (old phones that used a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashwin Menon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[picoCTF 2021 -The Numbers writeup-]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karapto/picoctf-2021-the-numbers-writeup-5ggd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karapto/picoctf-2021-the-numbers-writeup-5ggd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T00:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description


The numbers... what do they mean?
When the image is opened, the following image is displayed.

Since { appears in the seventh character of the image, we can a find out that the flag format is picoctf{***}. This means that 16→P, 9→I, 3→C, 15→O, 3→C, 20→T, and 6→F are used.

All you need to do is decode A1Z26 with Cyberchef or convert it manually to get the flag.
Flag: PICOCTF{THENUMBERSMASON}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shitian Daxiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[picoCTF 2021 -The Numbers writeup-]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karapto/picoctf-2021-the-numbers-writeup-5ggd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karapto/picoctf-2021-the-numbers-writeup-5ggd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T00:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Description


The numbers... what do they mean?
When the image is opened, the following image is displayed.

Since { appears in the seventh character of the image, we can a find out that the flag format is picoctf{***}. This means that 16→P, 9→I, 3→C, 15→O, 3→C, 20→T, and 6→F are used.

All you need to do is decode A1Z26 with Cyberchef or convert it manually to get the flag.
Flag: PICOCTF{THENUMBERSMASON}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shitian Daxiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing Bluetooth in Debian 9]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/foqc/fixing-bluetooth-in-debian-9-4k17</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/foqc/fixing-bluetooth-in-debian-9-4k17"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago I bought a Lenovo Thinkpad E580 computer, then I decided to install GNU/Linux as my operating system, I chose Debian Wheezy but unfortunately my wifi and bluetooth did not work. 
After searching the internet I found a controller that was compatible with my wifi, however I couldn't fix the bluetooth. Back then it wasn't a major problem so I gave up!.
Two months ago I bought a wireless headphone, which works via bluetooth, so this time I decided to fix it.
I followed many instructions that I fou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabian Quijosaca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web scrapping introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/web-scrapping-introduction-2dlf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/web-scrapping-introduction-2dlf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T19:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping is the method of crawling different websites and extracting the required data with spiders. This data is interpreted and stored in a hierarchical format using a data pipeline. Web crawling is now commonly used and has a wide range of applications: This is also applicable in the advanced Recons and many more application can be delivered from it.
Marketing and sales firms can obtain lead-related information by using site scraping. Web scraping is useful for Real Estate companies to obtain informa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vishwasnarayanre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools and Skills to be the Bug Bounty Hunting.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/tools-and-skills-to-be-the-bug-bounty-hunting-55e9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishwasnarayan5/tools-and-skills-to-be-the-bug-bounty-hunting-55e9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T19:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bug bounties are a perfect way to obtain cybersecurity expertise while still earning some extra cash. I strongly believe that engaging in bug bounties is an excellent way to get into the cybersecurity industry.
The bug bounty scheme, commonly known as the vulnerability rewards programme (VRP), is a crowd-sourced platform that helps businesses to compensate individual hackers for their efforts in finding bugs in their applications.The bug bounty policy should be integrated into an organization's processes to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vishwasnarayanre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript - What Is All About and Why Should You Use It?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mxkvl/typescript-what-is-all-about-and-why-should-you-use-it-59jb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mxkvl/typescript-what-is-all-about-and-why-should-you-use-it-59jb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T17:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript?


TypeScript is a JavaScript Superset. It means that TypeScript is a language that is built upon JavaScript. It is based on JavaScript syntax, constructions, advantages (and disadvantages) but it also brings new features, syntax, and capabilities. 
What's the purpose of this language? TypeScript brings to developers some features that help to write code on JavaScript easier and safer. One of the most important features that TypeScript provides is Static typing. Basically, static typing a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kovalevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating HTTP Form Submissions Using Python and Cronjobs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fusleor/automating-http-form-submissions-using-python-and-cronjobs-3o6c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fusleor/automating-http-form-submissions-using-python-and-cronjobs-3o6c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T15:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes doing tedious and repetitive tasks. I received an email notifying me that I had to submit a daily ‘health declaration check’ as a form on a website before playing my favorite slots on https://gamblersarea.com/. Since I lead a boring and routine lifestyle, I thought I would automate this task. It would be a good excuse to refresh my knowledge on Python’s Requests module as well as get more hands on experience with cron jobs.


HTTP Requests are sent out by hosts (your browser or computer) for sp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fusleo Rigaton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ng-sq-ui project is back more customizable than ever! + Brand new Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ardentia/the-ng-sq-ui-project-is-back-now-more-customizable-than-ever-brand-new-rewards-program-3339</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ardentia/the-ng-sq-ui-project-is-back-now-more-customizable-than-ever-brand-new-rewards-program-3339"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T14:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some exciting component enhancements ✨


This project was started with the idea of being flexible when it comes to styling; it allows the developer to opt-out of the pre-packaged theme, without leaving the theme-specific classes in the markup.
Staying true to its original intent, the latest version - 1.3.1 - now comes with form controls that are not only style-independent but also allow custom templating.
Here is an example of the above with the TagsInputComponent: 




The component was enhanced to employ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Plamena Radneva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ng-sq-ui project is back more customizable than ever! + Brand new Rewards Program]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ardentia/the-ng-sq-ui-project-is-back-now-more-customizable-than-ever-brand-new-rewards-program-3339</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ardentia/the-ng-sq-ui-project-is-back-now-more-customizable-than-ever-brand-new-rewards-program-3339"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T14:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some exciting component enhancements ✨


This project was started with the idea of being flexible when it comes to styling; it allows the developer to opt-out of the pre-packaged theme, without leaving the theme-specific classes in the markup.
Staying true to its original intent, the latest version - 1.3.1 - now comes with form controls that are not only style-independent but also allow custom templating.
Here is an example of the above with the TagsInputComponent: 




The component was enhanced to employ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Plamena Radneva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quality SEO Services: Link Building, Social Media Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jtrout/quality-seo-services-link-building-social-media-marketing-1109</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jtrout/quality-seo-services-link-building-social-media-marketing-1109"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T12:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking to boost your web traffic one of the best ways to do so is with video submission. This is the latest trend in SEO link building. The main purpose of a video submission is to get an SEO to assign a higher ranking to help your internet marketing. This working best with Google SEO; and can be plain text or a type of power point presentation.
Another good internet marketing strategy is article writing and submission. Some SEO services like https://writeanypapers.com/write-my-essay/ will write…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JTrout13</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quality SEO Services: Link Building, Social Media Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jtrout/quality-seo-services-link-building-social-media-marketing-1109</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jtrout/quality-seo-services-link-building-social-media-marketing-1109"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T12:20:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking to boost your web traffic one of the best ways to do so is with video submission. This is the latest trend in SEO link building. The main purpose of a video submission is to get an SEO to assign a higher ranking to help your internet marketing. This working best with Google SEO; and can be plain text or a type of power point presentation.
Another good internet marketing strategy is article writing and submission. Some SEO services like https://writeanypapers.com/write-my-essay/ will write…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JTrout13</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress: modify user roles dynamically with functions.php]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nabbisen/wordpress-modify-user-roles-dynamically-with-functions-php-1671</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nabbisen/wordpress-modify-user-roles-dynamically-with-functions-php-1671"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress provides variety of user roles and capabilities.
It is able to modify user roles with functions.php dynamically as well as capabilities.
WordPress: modify user capabilities dynamically with functions.php
Heddi Nabbisen ・ May 8 ・ 1 min read
#wordpress
        #authorization
        #php
        #security
      
In other words, in terms of security, it is able to act as administrator when there is a way to edit functions.php such as FTP.
Here is a code example.
# functions.php
function custom_user_r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heddi Nabbisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional content projection/injection in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/remshams/optional-content-projection-injection-in-angular-2jnn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/remshams/optional-content-projection-injection-in-angular-2jnn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T11:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optional content projection/injection in Angular


Recently I had the requirement to make part of a component (the header of a custom table) replaceable with custom content. In case nothing is provided the implementation was supposed to render "default" content. A simple property was not sufficient as the injected/projected content could be anything ranging from simple text to a slider/toggle...

The requirements could be summarized as follows:
Render custom content in case it is provided
Render default con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathias Remshardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The near-ultimate guide to printing anything using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fasidongit/the-near-ultimate-guide-to-printing-anything-using-angular-5h4j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fasidongit/the-near-ultimate-guide-to-printing-anything-using-angular-5h4j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T09:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Printing on the web can become quite overwhelming. In this guide, we will dive deeper into different ways (that I found peace with) to print pretty much anything using Angular.
We will see two ways of performing a print:
using &lt;iframe&gt;

new browser tab printing
For simple trivial web page printing could be tackled by dropping the following hide-print class  on elements that you wouldn't want to show up in a print,
&lt;div class="hide-print"&gt;
  ...
  ...
&lt;/div&gt;

@media print {
  .hide-print {
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kader Mohideen Fasid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Nuxt/Vue Micro-Service]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ifarhad/implement-nuxt-vue-micro-service-1oo1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ifarhad/implement-nuxt-vue-micro-service-1oo1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T08:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here I've explained the basics of micro-service architecture for the front end and how to choose your services.
Front-End MicroService Architecture
Farhad Mehryari ・ Apr 15 ・ 2 min read
#microservices
        #vue
        #nuxt
        #javascript
      
In this post, we consider a shopping website that has three main parts and we name it myshop.com.
Account
Shop
Profile
Account service will mount on myshop.com/account that has the following routes
/account/login
/account/register
/account/forget-password
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhad Mehryari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ngx Slick Carousel In Angular Material Card with Custom Arrows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/w3hubs/ngx-slick-carousel-in-angular-material-card-with-custom-arrows-2ei1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/w3hubs/ngx-slick-carousel-in-angular-material-card-with-custom-arrows-2ei1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T08:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Material is a UI component-based framework with use to build web applications in an attractive interface. So here we try to make a carousel slider help of Ngx-slick-carousel npm with an angular material card.
In these elements, we used font awesome CDN for left and right-click action. Also, we used SCSS to make this element user-friendly. Here we used icon and CSS properties ts file and IMG binding in the same ts. These fully responsive and mobile-friendly elements.
Make it yours now by using it, do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>w3hubs.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create back-end server in Node.js in less than 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/create-back-end-server-in-node-js-1o4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/create-back-end-server-in-node-js-1o4h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T07:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World HTTP server with Core Module


First, install Node.js for your platform.
In this example we'll create an HTTP server listening on port 1337, which sends Hello, World! to the browser. Note that, instead of using port 1337, you can use any port number of your choice which is currently not in use by any other service.
The http module is a Node.js core module (a module included in Node.js's source, that does not require installing
http.createServer() method. 
To create the application, create a file…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautifully encapsulate table related logic using a custom data source + sorting using directives]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/beautifully-encapsulate-table-related-logic-into-a-custom-data-source-sorting-using-directives-1pc7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/beautifully-encapsulate-table-related-logic-into-a-custom-data-source-sorting-using-directives-1pc7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T07:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tables are a fundamental part of the web. It is used in most of the applications out there to present data in a readable and digestible way. Tables can come out as very simple components, but they can be a real pain to work with if things are not organized properly. 
When the table we are dealing with has a lot of columns, rows, and multiple functionalities like sorting, filtering, etc, things can get real complex real fast.
If we are not very careful in architecting tables for our applications, there can b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beautifully encapsulate table related logic using a custom data source + sorting using directives]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/beautifully-encapsulate-table-related-logic-into-a-custom-data-source-sorting-using-directives-1pc7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/beautifully-encapsulate-table-related-logic-into-a-custom-data-source-sorting-using-directives-1pc7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T07:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tables are a fundamental part of the web. It is used in most of the applications out there to present data in a readable and digestible way. Tables can come out as very simple components, but they can be a real pain to work with if things are not organized properly. 
When the table we are dealing with has a lot of columns, rows, and multiple functionalities like sorting, filtering, etc, things can get real complex real fast.
If we are not very careful in architecting tables for our applications, there can b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress: modify user capabilities dynamically with functions.php]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nabbisen/wordpress-modify-user-capabilities-dynamically-with-functions-php-383n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nabbisen/wordpress-modify-user-capabilities-dynamically-with-functions-php-383n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T06:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress provides variety of user roles and capabilities.
It is able to modify user capabilities with functions.php dynamically. In other words, in terms of security, it is able to act as administrator when there is a way to edit functions.php such as FTP.
Here is a code example.
# functions.php
function custom_user_cap() {
    // get user
    $user = new WP_User( &lt;user-ID&gt; );
    //$user = new WP_User( '&lt;user-login-name&gt;' );
    //$user = wp_get_current_user();

    // modify capabilities  
  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heddi Nabbisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've made a Spotify clone with React, Redux, and Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/diogo405/i-ve-made-a-spotify-clone-with-react-redux-and-typescript-1fh2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/diogo405/i-ve-made-a-spotify-clone-with-react-redux-and-typescript-1fh2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T03:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, I'm sharing this Spotify Clone that I made with React, Redux, and Typescript. If you wanna head straight to the live version you can click on this link: http://spotifyclooone.netlify.app/.

If you wanna check the source code head to my Github by clicking here https://github.com/diogo405/spotify-clone.
The project is actually very simple, it's just two pages: Home and Album that pull data from a fake API. 
I'm not gonna lie if you are new to Typescript your chances to hate it gonna be 100%. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diogo Goncalves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should we dig deeper into the development tools we use?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/janosvajda/should-we-dig-deeper-into-the-development-tools-we-use-5gne</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/janosvajda/should-we-dig-deeper-into-the-development-tools-we-use-5gne"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T01:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I want to answer concisely, then I can write only that: yes, we should.
But, of course, this topic is much more complicated because we are usually busy and cannot check out our dev tool's source code. Furthermore, developers are humans, so we can be lazy or think digging in a big codebase is useless and tiring. 
I share a story that happened about 7-8 years ago, and it might be able to explain what I exactly mean. 
I usually start to work very early (between 2 am and 5 am), so before the Covid era, I qui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Janos Vajda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install WordPress and LAMP with one click. 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thetrebelcc/how-to-install-wordpress-and-lamp-with-one-click-2021-1p61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thetrebelcc/how-to-install-wordpress-and-lamp-with-one-click-2021-1p61"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[git clone https://github.com/thetrebelcc/Wordpress-Ubuntu-20-Install.git



CD into the cloned directory 
sh wordpress_install.sh
That is all!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabian Anguiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Systems Book Recommendations – Learn How to Build and Understand ML Systems]]></title>
        <id>609558382cd0545b5e943c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-systems-book-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life.” ― Mark TwainI hope you’re reading this blog in your pjs looking forward to a rejuvenating and healthy weekend.  I have been working on multiple projects lately, from creating Machine Learing Engineering and Machine Learning Operations courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aggregating and Visualizing DMARC Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n1try/aggregating-and-visualizing-dmarc-reports-fa5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n1try/aggregating-and-visualizing-dmarc-reports-fa5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMARC, DKIM and SPF


If you are using a custom domain for your e-mail with providers like mailbox.org or even host your own mail server, it is likely that you came across these terms at some point. All three are technologies for improving e-mail security and authentication. Their whole purpose is to ensure that a mail was actually sent by the person who appears to have sent it, i.e. the person mentioned in the mail's From header. I don't want to go too much into detail here and only explain each of them ve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ferdinand Mütsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SlideMenu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/angular-slidemenu-1bb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/angular-slidemenu-1bb5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SlideMenu displays submenus with slide animation.
Refer to PrimeNG setup documentation for download and installation steps for your environment.
import {SlideMenuModule} from 'primeng/slidemenu';
import {MenuItem} from 'primeng/api';

SlideMenu uses the common menumodel api to define its items, visit MenuModel API for details.
SlideMenu requires nested menuitems as its model.
&lt;p-slideMenu [model]="items"&gt;&lt;/p-slideMenu&gt;

export class SlideMenuDemo {

    items: MenuItem[];

    ngOnInit()…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Trees Images, Part 3. From Fractal to a Real Tree]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bespoyasov/generating-trees-images-part-3-from-fractal-to-a-real-tree-26nb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bespoyasov/generating-trees-images-part-3-from-fractal-to-a-real-tree-26nb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T19:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's finish our trees images generator!
In the first part, we designed the application architecture, set up the environment and dependency injection. In the end, we created an L-Systems module that could generate a string representation of a tree.
In the second part, we created a geometry module and a DOM adapter for accessing canvas elements. In the end, we displayed the first image on the screen.
In this final post, we're going to create a “translator” for L-System characters. Also, we will generate the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MFA With WebAuthn for FIDO Device Biometrics Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/mfa-with-webauthn-for-fido-device-biometrics-now-available-38pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/mfa-with-webauthn-for-fido-device-biometrics-now-available-38pk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T18:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last few years, the FIDO Alliance has been working relentlessly towards the vision of helping users authenticate with maximum security and minimum friction. The resulting WebAuthn standard provides the foundation for that to happen. Now it is up to the industry to make that technology available to end users. 
WebAuthn is the only standard-based authentication method that makes phishing impossible, as it binds the public/private key to a specific web domain. You cannot mistakenly authenticate into a p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion Might Seem Scary – But it Doesn&#x27;t Have to Be]]></title>
        <id>609551f02cd0545b5e943bc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-doesnt-have-to-be-scary/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any concept that we don't fully understand can be scary at first. Recursion is a topic that programming students don't learn right away. But that doesn't mean it needs to be scary or cause anxiety. In fact, recursion is a concept that we can define rather simply. According to Wikipedia:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonarCloud vs LeftShift for automated code quality and security checks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cbaggini/sonarcloud-vs-leftshift-for-automated-code-quality-and-security-checks-m30</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cbaggini/sonarcloud-vs-leftshift-for-automated-code-quality-and-security-checks-m30"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I have been looking for automated tools to improve the quality and security of my apps. I have looked at two online apps for this, SonarCloud and LeftShift.

SonarCloud provide a more extensive report, including three sections: reliability (are there any bugs?), maintainability (is the code clear and well-structured?) and security (are there any vulnerabilities?).

At first sight, SonarCode is more comprehensive, as it looks at the general code structure and how maintainable it is as well as securit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cecilia Baggini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript The Big Picture]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anonymousramsey/typescript-the-big-picture-18b1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anonymousramsey/typescript-the-big-picture-18b1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming up soon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mohamedramsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conditional Tasks in Dynamic Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/conditional-tasks-in-dynamic-forms-43be</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/conditional-tasks-in-dynamic-forms-43be"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T14:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR
@myndpm/dyn-forms documented at mynd.dev and we are able to provide them easily like the Controls, Validators, AsyncValidators, etc.
In complex forms use-cases, some controls directly depend on the value or status of some other form control. Then we implement custom behaviors, like hiding a field when another control has some value, or disabling it depending on a complex condition, etc.
To support this, we've added Matchers and Conditions, which can be provided just like the Validators and AsyncValida…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mateo Tibaquirá</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CSS a Programming Language?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339781</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-css-a-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a real distaste for this question. It might seem like a fun question to dig into on the surface, but the way it enters public discourse rarely seems to be in good faith. There are ulterior motives at &#8230;
The post Is CSS a Programming Language? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are a few great links about typography that have been burning a hole in my saved bookmarks folder that I'm just now getting around to sharing. There's good stuff in there, from how to choose typefaces for app design to ideas for how to fix the concept of font sizing in CSS.
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TShark - TryHackMe]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hextrace/thm-tshark-4kji</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hextrace/thm-tshark-4kji"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T12:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a quick writeup of the TShark room of tryhackme.com.
TShark is a network protocol analyzer. It lets you capture packet data from a live network, or read packets from a previously saved capture file, either printing a decoded form of those packets to the standard output or writing the packets to a file. 
TShark will display and number the packets. We can also use wc -l to count them:
$ tshark -r dns.cap
    1   0.000000 192.168.170.8 → 192.168.170.20 DNS 70 Standard query 0x1032 TXT google.com
    2 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hextrace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubearmor – container-aware runtime security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kalilinux/kubearmor-container-aware-runtime-security-599</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kalilinux/kubearmor-container-aware-runtime-security-599"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T12:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KubeArmor is a container-aware runtime security enforcement system that restricts the behavior (such as process execution, file access, networking operation, and resource utilization) of containers at the system level.
kubearmor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kalilinux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Email…]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339822</id>
        <link href="https://www.caniemail.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T02:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I&#8217;m 85% certain you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Use&#8230;, I bet there is only a 13% chance that you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Email&#8230;. It&#8217;s the same vibe—detailed support information for web platform features—except instead &#8230;
The post Can I Email&#8230; appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is &quot;Lifting State Up&quot; in React?]]></title>
        <id>609409c201fc34080ef81f97</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-lifting-state-up-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a simple and practical example what it means to "lift state up" in React, and how it can help you build your applications. Lifting state up is a common pattern that is essential for React developers to know. It helps you avoid more complex (and often unnecessary) patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently, You Can Use Route53 as a Blazingly Fast Database]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340015</id>
        <link href="https://betterprogramming.pub/apparently-you-can-use-route53-as-a-blazingly-fast-database-dd416b56b005"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Route53 is DNS management service by AWS. DNS is absolutely not a database, and yet here&#8217;s Nicholas Martin writing up some very clever trickery originally done by Corey Quinn:
When you think about it, DNS configuration is actually a 
&#8230;
The post Apparently, You Can Use Route53 as a Blazingly Fast Database appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Google’s New Page Experience Update Means for Images on Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339936</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-googles-new-page-experience-update-means-for-images-on-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T19:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to forget that, as a search engine, Google doesn’t just compare keywords to generate search results. Google knows that if people don’t enjoy their experience on a web page, they won’t stay on the page long enough to &#8230;
The post What Google’s New Page Experience Update Means for Images on Your Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use the Chrome DevTools to Troubleshoot Websites]]></title>
        <id>609415eb2cd0545b5e943534</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-use-the-chrome-devtools-to-troubleshoot-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome DevTools is a set of web developer tools built directly into the Google Chrome browser. They can be super helpful for web developers. We just published a crash course that will teach you how to use Chrome DevTools to improve your productivity as a web developer. You will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional Types in Swift – How to Use and Unwrap Optionals]]></title>
        <id>60939bde01fc34080ef81a19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-types-in-swift/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coming from Java, C++, or other object-oriented languages, chances are that you've never come across optional types or "optionals". And you might be quite surprised to know that such a concept exists in Swift. Optionals are a fundamental topic that you need to thoroughly understand to code in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom State Pseudo-Classes in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339586</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/custom-state-pseudo-classes-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T14:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an increasing number of “custom” features on the web platform. We have custom properties (--my-property), custom elements (&#60;my-element&#62;), and custom events (new CustomEvent('myEvent')). At one point, we might even get custom media &#8230;
The post Custom State Pseudo-Classes in Chrome appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339563</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can&#8217;t even look at code or documentation for Astro (publicly) yet — it&#8217;s an in-progress idea — but you can watch a video of Fred showing it off to Feross. 
I gotta admit: it looks awesome. I&#8217;m bullish &#8230;
The post Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python and OpenCV Course –Create Computer Vision Apps in the Cloud]]></title>
        <id>609307e801fc34080ef8191e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-computer-vision-apps-in-the-cloud-with-opencv-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCV is a library of programming functions mainly aimed at real-time computer vision.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use OpenCV in the cloud with Python. Misbah Mohammed created this course. He has a lot of experience with machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Delayed Is Progress Denied]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339954</id>
        <link href="https://infrequently.org/2021/04/progress-delayed/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T16:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bombshell article of the week is from Alex Russell of Google/Chrome. Alex has long been super critical of Apple, particularly about how there is literally no option to run any other browser than Safari on iOS. This article isn&#8217;t &#8230;
The post Progress Delayed Is Progress Denied appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Vendor Prefixing Dead?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339518</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-vendor-prefixing-dead/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let‘s take a quick stroll down memory-lane to revisit how vendor prefixing CSS properties came to be. I hope I don’t trigger PTSD for anyone!
It‘s not clear who started prefixing, or when it began exactly. What is clear, is &#8230;
The post Is Vendor Prefixing Dead? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob O'Leary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T07:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source. See documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.6]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: The output website didn't have favicon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Item description didn't use the description property from feed item.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: MIT license
Added: cache.json is stamped with the version of the builder. This allows future builder with breaking change to ignore incompatible cache.
Added: Feed source retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Item enrichment retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Console log for cache restore and update behavior.
Added: npx command: npx osmosfeed
Changed: Improved console log that breaks down rendered item count into "new" and "cached".
Fixed: Item…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.0.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.0.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Runtime dependencies are moved out of devDependencies. This is not a breaking change, but to receive performance benefit, you need to make sure @osmoscraft/osmosfeed is listed as dependencies instead of devDependencies in the package.json of your rss reader site.
Changed: Build target from node12 to node14.
Changed: Switched to a more robust rss parser: rss-parser
Fixed: RSS 1.0 feed &lt;dc:date&gt; was not parsed as publish date.
Chore: npm dependencies version updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16px or Larger Text Prevents iOS Form Zoom]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339455</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/16px-or-larger-text-prevents-ios-form-zoom/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T21:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was a great &#8220;Today I Learned&#8221; for me from Josh W. Comeau. If the font-size of an &#60;input&#62; is 16px or larger, Safari on iOS will focus into the input normally. But as soon as the font-size is &#8230;
The post 16px or Larger Text Prevents iOS Form Zoom appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Backup: Roll Back Your WooCommerce Site Without Losing Orders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339867</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-backup-roll-back-your-woocommerce-site-without-losing-orders/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T21:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s a dilemma: what happens if your WooCommerce site has a problem and the quickest and best way to fix it is to roll back to a previous version? The dilemma is, if you roll back the database, you would &#8230;
The post Jetpack Backup: Roll Back Your WooCommerce Site Without Losing Orders appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Async Await Tutorial – With Asynchronous JavaScript Examples]]></title>
        <id>609011fd8eb3fb07cf09a034</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/node-js-async-await-tutorial-with-asynchronous-javascript-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T16:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete guide to Node.js async await]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copy a Directory in Linux – How to cp a Folder in the Command Line in Linux and Unix (MacOS)]]></title>
        <id>608f5ad48eb3fb07cf099ddb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/copy-a-directory-in-linux-how-to-cp-a-folder-in-the-command-line-in-linux-and-unix-macos/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T15:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To copy files or directories in Unix-based operating systems (Linux and MacOS), you use the cp command. The cp command is a relatively simple command, but its behavior changes slightly depending on the inputs (files vs directories) and the options you pass to it. To view the documentation or manual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s use (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339449</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/lets-use-x-x-x-x-for-talking-about-specificity/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was just chatting with Eric Meyer the other day and I remembered an Eric Meyer story from my formative years. I wrote a blog post about CSS specificity, and Eric took the time to point out the misleading nature &#8230;
The post Let’s use (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Colorful, Smart Shadows]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339742</id>
        <link href="https://www.kirupa.com/html5/creating_colorful_smart_shadows.htm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bona fide CSS trick from Kirupa Chinnathambi here. To match a colored shadow with the colors in the background-image of an element, you inherit the background in a pseudo-element, kick it behind the original, then blur and filter it. &#8230;
The post Creating Colorful, Smart Shadows appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 8: CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339419</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-8-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June of 2006, web developers and designers from around the world came to London for the second annual @media conference. The first had been a huge success, and @media 2006 had even more promise. Its speaker lineup was pulled &#8230;
The post Chapter 8: CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fetch Data in React from a GraphQL API]]></title>
        <id>6090187c8eb3fb07cf09a060</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/5-ways-to-fetch-data-react-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T17:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go through the five best ways that you can fetch data with React from a GraphQL API. While there are a couple of popular libraries which are made to interact with GraphQL APIs from a React application, there are many different ways to fetch data with GraphQL. I've included]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Mistakes React Developers Make – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>608f553c8eb3fb07cf099da7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-mistakes-react-developers-make-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T16:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll see some of the common mistakes that React developers make, and how you can avoid them. So let's get started. Don't Forget that Every Route Change Mounts and Unmounts a ComponentWhenever you're using routing in a React application, you declare routes inside the Switch component. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swipey Image Grids]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339384</id>
        <link href="https://www.cassie.codes/posts/swipey-image-grids/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T14:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope people think of SVG as a vector format that is good for drawing things. There is plenty more to know, but here&#8217;s one more: SVG is good for composition. You draw things at very specific coordinates &#8230;
The post Swipey Image Grids appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early &mdash; when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Mistakes To Avoid In Your Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that the technical interview process leaves something to be desired; it’s often riddled with anxiety and stress. In this article, we’ll take a look at seven of the most common mistakes candidates make in their technical interviews and explore ways you can avoid them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emma Bostian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Web Design Clients Fast (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling is key to growing your web design business, but it doesn’t have to be complicated! With clear goals, customer research, and proven closing techniques, anyone can find new clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephen Roe)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cats With Love: New Navigation, Guides And Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Smashing, we’ve been busy over the last few months. We’ve set up new workshops, redesigned our navigation, refined performance and improved accessibility. There are subtle UX changes coming in, and we’d love to share what we’ve been cooking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overflow Issues In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/css-overflow-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/css-overflow-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the causes of overflow issues and how to solve them. We will also explore how modern features in the developer tools (DevTools) can make the process of fixing and debugging easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Video Streaming App With Nuxt.js, Node And Express]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/building-video-streaming-app-nuxtjs-node-express/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/building-video-streaming-app-nuxtjs-node-express/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building a video streaming app using Nuxt.js and Node.js. Specifically, we’ll build a server-side Node.js app that will handle fetching and streaming videos, generating thumbnails for your videos, and serving captions and subtitles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deven Rathore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To HTML Email]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-html-email-templates-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-html-email-templates-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently we’ve covered CSS generators, SVG generators and accessible front-end components. This time we look into HTML email, with tools, templates and guides for designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>