<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-22T01:04:35.093Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-22T01:04:35.093Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Dynamic Module Import]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/louisgv/typescript-dynamic-module-import-2dln</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/louisgv/typescript-dynamic-module-import-2dln"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you tell the difference between these two import statements?
import Button from "@kenaz/button";

VS
const buttonModule = await import("@kenaz/button");
const Button = buttonModule.default;

Simple right? - The first imports the module statically at build-time, whereas the second imports the module dynamically at run-time. 
With the first code snippet, most ES bundler will include the button component in our final bundle. Whereas with the second snippet, our button could be split into a separate chunk. This could be an advantage when your page gets super duper complex with 1000 states, but the button is only needed in 1 of those states.
Now, can you tell the difference between these twos?
async function loadButton() {
  const buttonModule = await import("@kenaz/button");
  return butto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Dynamic Module Import]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/louisgv/typescript-dynamic-module-import-2dln</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/louisgv/typescript-dynamic-module-import-2dln"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you tell the difference between these two import statements?
import Button from "@kenaz/button";

VS
const buttonModule = await import("@kenaz/button");
const Button = buttonModule.default;

Simple right? - The first imports the module statically at build-time, whereas the second imports the module dynamically at run-time. 
With the first code snippet, most ES bundler will include the button component in our final bundle. Whereas with the second snippet, our button could be split into a separate chunk. This could be an advantage when your page gets super duper complex with 1000 states, but the button is only needed in 1 of those states.
Now, can you tell the difference between these twos?
async function loadButton() {
  const buttonModule = await import("@kenaz/button");
  return butto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Docker container for kiterunner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/building-a-docker-container-for-kiterunner-56ca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/building-a-docker-container-for-kiterunner-56ca"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last few weeks, I've finally wrangled my head around Docker a bit. 
As a demo, I've built a docker container for kiterunner.
Kiterunner is an API-fuzzing tool, very useful for bug bounty hunters and pen-testers. Shoutouts to @insiderphd for introducing me to the tool. I should have watched that video sooner!
Like any good tool, it requires some installation stuff beforehand.
I realized this is a good opportunity to begin integrating Docker into my workflow in a potentially useful way.
To quickly get Docker installed on debian or ubuntu:
# Install Docker
sudo apt-get install \
    ca-certificates \
    curl \
    gnupg \
    lsb-release
curl -fsSL https://download.docker.com/linux/debian/gpg | sudo gpg --dearmor -o /usr/share/keyrings/docker-archive-keyring.gpg
echo \
  "deb [arch=$(…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>darkmage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read this before you start using the multistage builds for your docker images]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mtk3d/read-this-before-you-start-using-the-multistage-builds-for-your-docker-images-21e7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mtk3d/read-this-before-you-start-using-the-multistage-builds-for-your-docker-images-21e7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post, I showed how to refactor the Dockerfile in your project. I didn't want to make the previous post too long, so I didn't touch the multistage builds. Here is the post where I will show you how to improve the Dockerfile even more, using multistage builds. Using stages in your builds is not hard to use, but there are some things where the below knowledge may help you 😃
Let's take the result of the last article:
FROM php:7.4.25-fpm
WORKDIR /app

COPY --from=composer:2.1.11 /usr/bin/composer /usr/bin/composer

RUN apt update && \
    apt install -y \
    libicu-dev=67.1-7 \
    libgd-dev=2.3.0-2 \
    libonig-dev=6.9.6-1.1 \
    unzip=6.0-26 && \
    apt purge -y --auto-remove

RUN docker-php-ext-install \
    exif \
    gd \
    intl \
    mbstring \
    mysqli \
    opcache \…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mateusz Cholewka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intigriti 1121 - XSS Challenge Writeup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealbrenu/intigriti-1121-xss-challenge-writeup-23mj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealbrenu/intigriti-1121-xss-challenge-writeup-23mj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T23:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another month, another amazing XSS Challenge from Intigriti, made by Ivars Vids. My first solution for this was not the intended one, but I hope you guys somehow appreciate it. 🤗
In the end of the writeup, I am going to be presenting you the intended solution, which I just figured out with a few hours of challenge remaining.
When we access the page https://challenge-1121.intigriti.io/challenge/index.php, it's possible to see that there is a list of security issues, as known as the 2021 edition of OWASP TOP 10. There is also a search bar from where it's possible to look for specific vulnerabilities. Whatever we type into this input will appear with the s query parameter when submitted.

If we try to submit, for example, a s value like <h1>example</h1>, we will get this text being present o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breno Vitório</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graphic Artist makes APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/drango/graphic-artist-makes-apis-37bk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/drango/graphic-artist-makes-apis-37bk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T23:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always wanted to mess around with programming. I studied International Relations and right after that, at the beginning of my working days, I started as Logo designer, continued as a UI designer, then moved to front-end development and ultimately I ended up being a graphic artist for a board game company called Final Frontier Games. Obviously, zero coding at the current workplace. Although I really enjoy working my current job, I needed to find a way to keep this feeling of satisfaction when I'm coding.
During my spare time while working as a graphic artist, I've been tinkering and creating few side projects in Python / Django. These are basically few tools that are supporting some of the internal processes of my company, such as board game rating tracking (I guess I will release an API …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bojan Drango</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Type of Mojolicious Frontend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/preaction/a-new-type-of-mojolicious-frontend-3i52</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/preaction/a-new-type-of-mojolicious-frontend-3i52"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T23:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has evolved quite a bit from its humble beginnings. Unfortunately, some of those advances have been difficult to take advantage of. Some require features not supported by all browsers, others require complicated tools. For my latest Mojolicious web app, I wanted to see how I could use Typescript with a minimum of fuss.
We'll start from a simple Mojolicious::Lite app, created using mojo generate lite_app:
From there, we can install Typescript using Node. Since Typescript cannot bundle itself into a single file, we will also install Webpack:
npm install --save-dev typescript webpack webpack-cli ts-loader

After installation we can configure Typescript using its tsconfig.json file. We'll use the public directory for our output, since this directory is served by Mojolicious.
{
  "co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy your Angular app with GitHub and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ewaldvanveen/deploy-your-angular-app-with-github-and-netlify-ci2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ewaldvanveen/deploy-your-angular-app-with-github-and-netlify-ci2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T22:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building your own projects, it would be nice if some of them will actually see the light of the world wide web instead of sadly sinking into oblivion. However, going through the whole process of successfully deploying your website to a hosting platform somewhere may sound a bit too discouraging for some developers. 
And that’s where a developer platform like Netlify comes to the rescue. With the use of their free starter plan, you can have your own personal project running in just a few steps.
In this tutorial I’ll show you these steps:
Setting up the environment.
Creating a new project. In this example I’ll create a new Angular demo project, but you can choose any other of the popular frameworks.
Creating a new repository on GitHub and pushing the demo project to the repository.
Depl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ewald van Veen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When IoT Attacks: Hacking a Linux-Powered Rifle]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/scriptautomate/when-iot-attacks-hacking-a-linux-powered-rifle-4b0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/scriptautomate/when-iot-attacks-hacking-a-linux-powered-rifle-4b0j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T21:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premise: Let's place a computer on a gun, and give it WiFi.
DefCon Response: Let's hijack it, and install our own malicious updates.
This is one of my DefCon 23 Debriefs, from the blog archives back in 2015! If you ever have the opportunity to get your work to ship you to Defcon, take it. If you ever get the opportunity to ship yourself, don't think: just go.
Presentation Title: When IoT Attacks: Hacking a Linux-Powered Rifle
The Presenters: Runa Sandvik and Michael Auger
The Twitters: @RunaSand /// @LM4K


The YouTubes: Runa A. Sandvik



If you weren't aware, TrackingPoint creates guns that use "lock-and-launch technology found in military fighter jets in its Precision-Guided Firearms." Using a Linux OS, these guns allow for the ability to strengthen your abilities to shoot targets. Gun …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Ardolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick TS Tips: How to extract a type from an array]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/diballesteros/quick-ts-tips-how-to-extract-a-type-from-an-array-5afk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/diballesteros/quick-ts-tips-how-to-extract-a-type-from-an-array-5afk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T20:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I had to work with some automatically generated types whilst using GraphQL. This is a very extremely useful feature! However, it can be a little cumbersome to specifically reach different custom nested types from the requests without it being too verbose.
But, being a little creative with some native Typescript functions we can find a way to handle this exact use case!

Let’s take for example this generated type (For the sake of the example, this will be a fairly simple type with a nested subtype):
If we wanted to extract the type of the array without it getting too verbose we could use some conditional typing from Typescript.

The following type allows us to extract it:
It can be a little confusing at first glance but let’s break down every portion. First, we have our ArrayElement which is a generic receiving the array itself as T.
Here the infer keyword from typescript (which must be used with extends) to declaratively introduce a new generic type U based on the given array.
Now let’s assume that the TStuff type is an array and we want to extract a singular TStuff. We could then supply the type of TStuff[] to ArrayElement
type TNestedStuff = ArrayElement<TStuff[]>;

Looking at the result of the extracted type we can now use it however we wish or even assign it as its own type to make it less verbose!

Here is the code sandbox to play around with the type and the Typescript documentation :
Documentation - Conditional Types
https://codesandbox.io/s/array-type-extraction-1eohh
If you have any other way to extract a type from an array let me know in the comments below!
Originally published at https://relatablecode.com on November 21, 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Ballesteros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Save Your Photos When Traveling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-save-your-photos-when-traveling-20ie</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-save-your-photos-when-traveling-20ie"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T19:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six hints to make sure your photos don’t get lost. Recommendations on taking pictures, storing them wisely, and recovering lost photos (if things come from bad to worse).
No matter how reliable modern gadgets are, nobody can feel safe from unexpected loss of photos for various reasons. The situation can be especially nasty when you come back home only to find the memory cards containing your photos to be broken or damaged, which means that the images of your remarkable impressions are gone.
To make sure you never face this situation, take our advice before going on a long-awaited trip, especially if the photographs you expect to bring home are one of the main reasons behind the route you have finally chosen.
YouTube: 




  
  
  Don’t delete individual photos


The very moment you take a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Guide to Typescript - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anuradha9712/quick-guide-to-typescript-part-1-3494</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anuradha9712/quick-guide-to-typescript-part-1-3494"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T19:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get started with some quick guide to Typescript.
In this article we'll cover the following concepts:
Introduction
Type Inference
Explicit Types
Union Types
Dynamic Types
Functions
Type Aliases
Typescript is superset of Javascript which means it is an extension of Javascript, adding new features and syntax on top of the core language.
Typescript is a strongly typed, object-oriented & compiled language.
Typescript is designed to be compiled into fully compatible Javascript, so it works in any browser, any host, and any OS. 
We need typescript compiler to compile it to Javascript code because browsers do not understand typescript.
Typescript strongly encouraged static-typing which means it will validate all the assertions before the code executes. It allows you to do a type check during…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anuradha Aggarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiment with Date Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pathanlog/experiment-with-date-command-58em</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pathanlog/experiment-with-date-command-58em"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T19:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a requirement to create Live date or True time digital clock not exactly like above animation but at least show you running time live. For this you have to know basic Linux Command, Shell syntax & Manual of Date command.
So Let's Accomplished the Task ! (bold text are command).
If you want to create a delay in program we always use sleep Command an if you want to echo-back the command we always use $(date). But if you have requirement to remove a new-line in terminal we have -n option in echo. or If you have some other requirement to do operations like New-line, Backspace & Tabulation. Then we have a options called -e stand for Sequence and you have to pass a sequence Character in string
For Example :-
    echo -e "Hello\nWorld" = To add a New-line.
    echo -e "Hello\bWorld" = To Backspace a letter.
    echo -e "Hello\tWorld" = To add a Tabulation.

After know this syntax we are able to create live running time Clock. So let's begin .
echo $(date +%r) = It will give the output of this date command format.
echo -e "$(date +%r)\b\b\b\b\b\b" = It will backspace the output (if command not work use below one).
echo -n  -e "$(date +%r)\b\b\b\b\b\b" = It will backspace the output (Why we have to do this you will know in a minute).
echo -n  -e "$(date +%r)\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b" = It will backspace all the output of command.
echo -n  -e "$(date +%r)$(sleep 1)\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b" = It will add 1s delay in command.
Now we have to add this thing in Loop. So it will keep on running .
While :
    > do
    > echo -n  -e "`date +%r``sleep 1`\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b\b"
    > done

Now you will see the magic here the command is keep on running (Tick Tock).
If you want to save this command for some project like when creating your own module that time this mite be useful for you, So select a command and copy and create a file you can give any name and past it and save the file. To execute this file you can use bash filename.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nadeem Pathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A modern, ergonomic Unix shell configuration with Fish]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yonkeltron/a-modern-ergonomic-unix-shell-configuration-with-fish-4dio</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yonkeltron/a-modern-ergonomic-unix-shell-configuration-with-fish-4dio"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T18:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many others, I spend enough time in the shell that even small improvements can yield huge productivity gains. This post is an attempt to catalog several of quality-of-life enhancements I've made over recent months to my shell setup.
Like most folks I know, I began my command-line life with good 'ol Bash and actually still do most of my shell scripting in Bash. Even if I eventually rewrite the command in another language, many of my tools begin life as a Bash script.
At some point, perhaps ~10 years ago, I was introduced to ZSH with the venerable Oh My ZSH framework. For me, this was a huge awakening because it taught me about how much shell improvements can impact your life. I gradually evolved my ZSH setup to use package managers like antigen and began to invest more in creature comf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan E. Magen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[C3.js][TypeScript] Draw line charts 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masanori_msl/c3jstypescript-draw-line-charts-2-a31</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masanori_msl/c3jstypescript-draw-line-charts-2-a31"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T16:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


This time, I will try saving the line charts as images.
[C3.js][TypeScript] Draw line charts 1
The chart what I created last time, the positions of 0 weren't at start point.

To set offset values as 0, add "padding" into "axis".
import c3 from "c3";
import { ChartValues } from "./chart.type";

export class ChartViewer {
    private chartElement: HTMLElement;
    private chart: c3.ChartAPI|null = null;
...
    public draw(value: ChartValues): void {
        const valueXList = this.getValueX(0, 10);
        const ticksX = this.getTicks(valueXList);
        const valueYList = value.values.map(v => v.y);
        const gridLineY = valueYList.map(t => this.generateGridLine(t));
        const gridLines = valueXList.map(t => this.generateGridLine(t));

        this.chart = c3.generate({
  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masui Masanori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respondiendo a un ladrón de contraseñas]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rleo/respondiendo-a-un-ladron-de-contrasenas-2k2p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rleo/respondiendo-a-un-ladron-de-contrasenas-2k2p"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T15:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contenido
El engaño
Construyendo perfiles inexistentes
Enviando datos con urllib
Level up: enviando datos masivamente
Importante: unas palabras de advertencia
⚠️ IMPORTANTE
Por favor considera que el propósito de este artículo es informativo, y tiene como objeto mostrar cómo hacer requests POST en Python usando las librerías nativas. Conviene tener en cuenta un par de puntos importantes al manipular correos electrónicos fraudulentos y al interactuar con los servidores que están diseñados para recibir datos obtenidos de forma ilícita. Por favor lee la sección correspondiente al final del post.
Recibí hace poco un correo electrónico fraudulento que incluía un archivo adjunto que trataba de robar la contraseña de mi cuenta. Si bien los métodos para robar información de los usuarios evoluciona…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Leo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Token based authentication in nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/singhutkarshh/token-based-authentication-in-nodejs-4amm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/singhutkarshh/token-based-authentication-in-nodejs-4amm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T15:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when we need to authenticate the user before giving him access to specific pages on our website.This authentication ensures that user has access to only those data that he has privileges on.
An entry level programmer would just fetch username and password stored in database at the time of login and if they match would give him access , which is not wrong but only half  a step in the process of authentication.
It is also necessary to ensure that of all the data stored in database only data related to user is shown.
This can be achieved in two ways:
Today we will talk and implement token based authentication in NodeJs.
1- Install following packages and dependencies which we are going to work with - 
npm install --save express jsonWebToken dotenv
npm install -D nodemon

2- .en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Utkarsh Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quovery- the worst behaviour from a company]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/whyseriousbro/quovery-the-worst-behaviour-from-a-company-3n4m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/whyseriousbro/quovery-the-worst-behaviour-from-a-company-3n4m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T15:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a target post or something. Just sharing my experience which i faced today
https://discuss.qovery.com/t/hey-i-got-banned-from-discord-for-asking-help/819?u=why-serious-bro
https://github.com/Qovery/engine/issues/501#event-5649956303
https://te.legra.ph/file/552a969b196d60d80e802.jpg - screenshot of the issue i posted in thier GitHub and they deleted and banned me from thier too
Hey i got an account before i have created one using GitHub account. This is the account which i created, its been 2 months since i created it and for some unknown reasons i didnt came to quovery until 1 week back. I came and asked for help in discord to approve me as i have been waiting since week even after filling the forum which they gaved. So i came yesterday and asking help to login my account in quovery discord server and my comments are getting deleted and after asking why do i need to wait for weeks even if i have an account then some ambassador banned me without any notice 
Just because i questioned i got a bann even without doing anything bad. I just want JUSTICE. 
It seems they also deleted my posts in their forum and github too, they like a dictator
I just want to use website for my bot which is not against any rules or terms of service but without helping me or telling me what to do some ambassador straight banned me
I dont know if that ambassador got any issues or got grudge. I just want JUSTICE its my right to use website if i didn't do ANYTHING wrong
people who faced my situation please share and also join me to help this UNJUSTICE which companies are doing once they reached some popularity


  
  
  iwantjustice #quovery]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>why-serious-bro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video conference project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hoainam10th123/video-conference-project-4mf4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hoainam10th123/video-conference-project-4mf4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T13:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just built a video conference using angular 12 and .net 5, invite everyone to watch the demo: https://youtu.be/kjU-_6IHyRE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hoainam10th123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ViewChild, ViewChildren and ContentChild, ContentChildren are undefined in Angular Material Dialog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rammurthykota/viewchild-viewchildren-and-contentchild-contentchildren-are-undefined-in-angular-material-dialog-1c7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rammurthykota/viewchild-viewchildren-and-contentchild-contentchildren-are-undefined-in-angular-material-dialog-1c7k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T13:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Angular Material Dialog Component that takes Inputs and uses them in header and footer of modal. I want to pass some html elements in modal's body section from another component.
I want to have a reference of child elements of a component in that component. I have tried both ElementRef, TemplateRef and QueryList with ViewChild, ViewChildren, ContentChild, ContentChildren but no luck.
dashboard.component.html displays a 'show/hide columns' button.
dashboard.component.html
<app-modal [title]="title" [btnText]="text'>
   <section #template>
    <mat-form-field appearance="outline" *ngIf="!showForm && viewParams.length > 0 && cn_hostname_index >= 0">
      <mat-label>Search Columns</mat-label>
      <input 
        matInput
        id="columnSearchTxt"
        placeholder="Search Colu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Murthy Kota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ViewChild, ViewChildren and ContentChild, ContentChildren are undefined in Angular Material Dialog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rammurthykota/viewchild-viewchildren-and-contentchild-contentchildren-are-undefined-in-angular-material-dialog-1c7k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rammurthykota/viewchild-viewchildren-and-contentchild-contentchildren-are-undefined-in-angular-material-dialog-1c7k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T13:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Angular Material Dialog Component that takes Inputs and uses them in header and footer of modal. I want to pass some html elements in modal's body section from another component.
I want to have a reference of child elements of a component in that component. I have tried both ElementRef, TemplateRef and QueryList with ViewChild, ViewChildren, ContentChild, ContentChildren but no luck.
dashboard.component.html displays a 'show/hide columns' button.
dashboard.component.html
<app-modal [title]="title" [btnText]="text'>
   <section #template>
    <mat-form-field appearance="outline" *ngIf="!showForm && viewParams.length > 0 && cn_hostname_index >= 0">
      <mat-label>Search Columns</mat-label>
      <input 
        matInput
        id="columnSearchTxt"
        placeholder="Search Colu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Murthy Kota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 8 Docker Best Practices for using Docker in Production ✅]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/top-8-docker-best-practices-for-using-docker-in-production-1m39</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techworld_with_nana/top-8-docker-best-practices-for-using-docker-in-production-1m39"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T12:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker adoption rises constantly 📈 and many are familiar with it, but not everyone is using Docker according to the best practices. 👀
Before moving on, if you don't know what Docker is, you can learn everything you need to get started in this free Docker Crash Course 🐳
So, in my new video 'Top 8 Docker Production Best Practices' I want to show you 8 ways you can use Docker in a right way in your projects to:
✅ improve security,
✅ optimize the image size, 
✅ take advantage of some of the useful Docker features 
✅ and also write cleaner and more maintainable Dockerfiles







  
  
  1️⃣ Best Practice



Use an official and verified Docker image as a base image, whenever available.
Let's say you are developing a Node.js application and want to build and run it as a Docker image. 
Instead…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techworld with Nana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Auth nodejs auth system with mysql]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mahmoud_bebars/universal-auth-nodejs-auth-system-with-mysql-1pdf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mahmoud_bebars/universal-auth-nodejs-auth-system-with-mysql-1pdf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T12:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since i struggled finding an setup for Authorization uses the Nodejs with Mysql.
I thought It might be a god idea to make my own setup which seemed to be a good start for any project you might start and it will save some time for those who like to work with Mysql rather than mongodb so I wish this help some people to start fresh in there projects.
Seems that my frontend not enough for that so if you like to make changes in it in my github repo you are welcomed to help other people with your changes.
Did I forget to mention that I used react-bootstrap to handle the UI,
You can check the project from here : https://github.com/mahmoud-bebars/UA-MERN
& sorry for not having a live demo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>m.bebars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using DevOps to export a Power Platform solution into source control]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/diskdrive/using-devops-to-export-a-power-platform-solution-into-source-control-56hk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/diskdrive/using-devops-to-export-a-power-platform-solution-into-source-control-56hk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T10:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post, we setup a Service Principal that allowed DevOps to access and perform actions in an Power Platform environment.
In this article, we'll actually utilise the service principal to export a solution and then save it into a DevOps repo.
You need a Power Platform environment with a solution you'd like to export. Your solution can be whatever you want. To make it very simple , I've just created a model driven app with one table that stores zoo animals.
You need a DevOps project with a repo you'd like the solution to be saved into.
You need a service principal with access to the Power Platform environment (see here)
Just a few things that's important after you've set up your repo 



Secondly, you should limit merge types which will prevent anyone from committing to the main…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wai Liu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different ways to connect react frontend and node backend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rakeshpotnuru/different-ways-to-connect-react-frontend-and-node-backend-1pik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rakeshpotnuru/different-ways-to-connect-react-frontend-and-node-backend-1pik"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T09:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are different ways to connect react backend and NodeJS frontend. In this blog, I am going to tell you three ways how you can connect backend and frontend. These are the ways most of the developers prefer.
React and NodeJS

The first way is having a single server that serves both Node API and React SPA under same domain. Here data is still exchanged through JSON. As you can see in the above picture, all the routes which do not start with /api will be handled by React SPA.
CORS errors🥶.
Copy build folder files from react app and paste them in public folder of NodeJS server.
Now server the static index.html which in the public folder




app.use(express.static(path.join('public')));
app.use((req,res) => {
   res.sendFile(path.resolve(__dirname, 'public', 'index.html'));
});

Single server.
No more CORS errors 😅
Ideal for small applications.
As both frontend and backend will be handled by the same server, you may face performance issues.

As we use two different servers for backend and frontend, we get better performance.
Ideal for bigger applications.
Have to maintain two different servers.
The third way and the least preferred way is server-side rendering with template engines like ejs, handlebars, pugjs etc... Here we don't create any REST API.
So, what other ways you know and what is your preferred way? Comment below 👇
Hope this helps you!
Twitter and LinkedIn. Follow me for more 😃.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Potnuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APFS: Data Recovery Algorithm and File System Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/apfs-data-recovery-algorithm-and-file-system-structure-2gmk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/apfs-data-recovery-algorithm-and-file-system-structure-2gmk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T09:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ApFS offers an opportunity to restore certain states of the file system, including restoration of old or removed versions of files.. The container superblock contains a link to the element known as checkpoint. Such checkpoint refers to the preceding container superblock which stores the information on an older state of the file system.This way, several older states can be restored by analyzing the chain of the container superblock.
The structure of ApFS file system is that of a B-tree, where the root directory containing data is the leaves of such tree. All branch nodes only contain links to the following node until they reach the leaf nodes. This file system uses containers as storage cells, and such cells can contain multiple ApFS volumes. Also, a container is the primary object for stor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Build Visualizer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryansiu1995/google-cloud-build-visualizer-254m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryansiu1995/google-cloud-build-visualizer-254m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T08:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Build (GCB) is a building system provided by GCP. Considering all the competitors like GitLab CI, CircleCI and Travis CI, GCB is definitely not a common option for building CI CD pipeline.
In fact, I have tried to test GCB in my work at the early stage of adoption in GCP. The pros of GCB is definitely a full integration with GCP's resources. If you are using GCP and have no preference at the CI pipeline platform, I highly suggest you to try it out.
Circling back to the GCB's pipeline, all the configurations are written in JSON or YAML format. Here is an example for the GCB configuration.
steps:

  - id: 'compile web app'
    name: 'gcr.io/cloud-builders/npm'
    dir: 'web'
    args: ['install']

  - id: 'web app unit tests'
    name: 'gcr.io/cloud-builders/npm'
    dir: 'web'
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan, Siu Long Wa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Ingress Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jmbharathram/kubernetes-ingress-part-1-15g8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jmbharathram/kubernetes-ingress-part-1-15g8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T08:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by jmbharathram]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmbharathram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch Linux machine-EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/upender18/launch-linux-machine-ec2-2a8a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/upender18/launch-linux-machine-ec2-2a8a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T07:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launch Linux machine


Create new EC2  Machine --

If any key pairs - delete
Observation:
AMI -  Amazon Linux 2 --->  T2.micro --> No of instance 2 -- tag - MyLinux ---> Change security group Security group name - LinSG , Description - LinSG ( optional ) - Review launch -- Create new keypair -- download key pair --  View Instances
Observation - Two machines created.
Credentials required for windows machines are (  dns,  username and password )
We use putty tool , to connect to linux machine.
We use puttygen  to get the ppk file.
Download from google using the  keywords "putty and puttygen"
Under alternate binary files
Open puttygen  --  load  -- Save private key -- Save key without passphrase  ( Yes )  -- Save 
Credentials required for putty -- 
select SSH -- Auth  -  selecy ppk file using browse option --> Open
username is - ec2-user   ( We get this from ssh command )
Now lets connect to 2nd linux machine 
We do not need to conver the pem to ppk, as both the machines have same pem file.
Right click on title bar of putty -- new session -- provide details -- change colors ( for easy identification )
Note: Both machines have different DNS names.
++++++++++++++++++++++
Session terminated abnormaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Banoth Upender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launch Linux machine-EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/upender18/launch-linux-machine-ec2-2a8a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/upender18/launch-linux-machine-ec2-2a8a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T07:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launch Linux machine


Create new EC2  Machine --

If any key pairs - delete
Observation:
AMI -  Amazon Linux 2 --->  T2.micro --> No of instance 2 -- tag - MyLinux ---> Change security group Security group name - LinSG , Description - LinSG ( optional ) - Review launch -- Create new keypair -- download key pair --  View Instances
Observation - Two machines created.
Credentials required for windows machines are (  dns,  username and password )
We use putty tool , to connect to linux machine.
We use puttygen  to get the ppk file.
Download from google using the  keywords "putty and puttygen"
Under alternate binary files
Open puttygen  --  load  -- Save private key -- Save key without passphrase  ( Yes )  -- Save 
Credentials required for putty -- 
select SSH -- Auth  -  selecy ppk file using browse option --> Open
username is - ec2-user   ( We get this from ssh command )
Now lets connect to 2nd linux machine 
We do not need to conver the pem to ppk, as both the machines have same pem file.
Right click on title bar of putty -- new session -- provide details -- change colors ( for easy identification )
Note: Both machines have different DNS names.
++++++++++++++++++++++
Session terminated abnormaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Banoth Upender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Aware of the !-- script Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/labnan/a-string-that-might-break-your-front-end-1pgp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/labnan/a-string-that-might-break-your-front-end-1pgp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T07:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lets say you have this string in a variable (case insensitive):
`etc etc etc<!-- etc etc<scRipT> etc`

This will break any html tag after it.
Or lets say you divided that into some variables:
const first = `etc etc etc <!--`;
const second = `anything`;
const third = `<script>`

This will also break the html page.
Therefore please carefully assign any string that contains
`<!--<script>` 

or similar into a variable, if it is inside <script> tag.
codepen example
Edit: The original title is changed
Feel free to ask any question related to this in the comments :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Labnan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/upender18/amazon-elastic-compute-cloud-amazon-ec2-40po</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/upender18/amazon-elastic-compute-cloud-amazon-ec2-40po"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T07:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EC2  --  Elastic  compute cloud
Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) provides scalable computing capacity in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) cloud. Using Amazon EC2 eliminates your need to invest in hardware up front, so you can develop and deploy applications faster. 
Synonyms
Ex 1: Launch windows instnace

Step 2: Choose a region that is near?  ( Asia pacific - Mumbai )
Services -- EC2 --- Launch Instance 


Stage 1  -- Select AMI  ( Note: Select free tier eligible ) Win Server 2012
Stage 2  --  t2.micro
Stage 3   --  No of instances  --  1
Stage 4  --  Storage - 30GB ( Observation - we have root - it is same as C Drive)

Stage 5  --  Add Tag --  Giving name to the machine 
        Add Name Tag
        Value - MyWindows
Stage 6  -- Security group  --  ( It deals with ports )
        We have 0 to 65535  ports
        Every port is dedicated to special purpose

        RDP -- 3389
        SSH -- 22
        HTTP -- 80
        HTTPS - 443

        For windows machine , we need to open RDP port  ( Remote Desktop Protocol )
        He by default , we have RDP

Stage 7     Just observe the warnings, Just verify the options, Launch

Create a new keypair--  download key pair -- launch instance
We get the instance ID  i-0dddc6c37c9dfb460
Now, the new windows machines ,is having its own DNS Name, Username and password
We need to provide all the above 3 details in our laptop, so that we can connect.
We use an application called Remote Desktop Connection
AWS , gives us  DNS name , username, it does not give the password.
AWS gives an option to convert .pem to password





  

  How to connect .pem to password
Connect to instance Get password -- upload pem file -- Decrypt  
Open Remote Desktop
Hurray!!
Lets check the hardware configuration
To disconnect, just close the remote desktop window.
Explain about  Stop and reboot and terminate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Banoth Upender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHAT IS DOCKER]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akilaliyanage/what-is-docker-42m9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akilaliyanage/what-is-docker-42m9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T06:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is a software platform for developing applications based on containers, which are tiny and efficient execution environments that share the operating system kernel but execute in isolation. While containers as a concept have been around for a while, Docker, an open-source project founded in 2013, helped popularize the technology and helped push the cloud-native development trend of containerization and microservices in software development.
One of the aims of contemporary software development is to keep apps running on the same host or cluster isolated from one another so that they don’t interfere with each other’s operation or maintenance. Due to the packages, libraries, and other software components necessary for them to execute, this might be tricky. Virtual machines are one answe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M.L.Akila Liyanage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Commands in Linux That Will Make You Feel Like a Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abstract/simple-commands-in-linux-that-will-make-you-feel-like-a-pro-3nde</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abstract/simple-commands-in-linux-that-will-make-you-feel-like-a-pro-3nde"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T04:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is a very popular and interesting operating system (OS), especially for programmers. The Linux terminal is a very important part of a Linux OS. That means that if you know the basic commands to enter the terminal, you'll be more comfortable and confident in using this OS.
ls and cd. I use some of these commands myself, and I can't imagine the programmer's life without them.
Touch is one of the easiest commands that will help you to create a new empty file (you can also create a bunch of files) in the directory that you're currently in.
touch file.txt


If you have a slow PC or just want to kill all running processes that are interfering with your work, use this command:
killall Notes

But you should remember that it deletes any data and won't let any application save it. By default, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Vassilevskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the best way to manage the messages shown to users?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joaomarcos160/what-is-the-best-way-to-manage-the-messages-shown-to-users-3493</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joaomarcos160/what-is-the-best-way-to-manage-the-messages-shown-to-users-3493"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T02:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to return messages for user actions, like "Successfully registered" or things like that, and I was wondering what is the best way to do this, to have a file with all messages or make them hard code?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Marcos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the best way to manage the messages shown to users?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joaomarcos160/what-is-the-best-way-to-manage-the-messages-shown-to-users-3493</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joaomarcos160/what-is-the-best-way-to-manage-the-messages-shown-to-users-3493"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T02:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to return messages for user actions, like "Successfully registered" or things like that, and I was wondering what is the best way to do this, to have a file with all messages or make them hard code?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Marcos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to connect your local host to your Virtual Machine using Virtual Box]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmed_adel_fahmy/how-to-connect-your-local-host-to-your-virtual-machine-using-virtual-box-2fcp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmed_adel_fahmy/how-to-connect-your-local-host-to-your-virtual-machine-using-virtual-box-2fcp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T01:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, in this article I am going to simplify how to connect your local host to the Virtual Machine your created using Oracle Virtual Box, using SSH.
First of all, I am using Ubuntu 20.04 LTS and I installed virtual box for some practicing on ubuntu - I don't want to miss with my guy actually - and after installing Ubuntu on the virtual machine, I faced a problem while connecting my local host to the VM as most of us do while using VMs over the cloud or connecting to remote servers using SSH.
Below, is the steps in a simplified way to be able to connect to your VM from your local host using SSH
1- open the Virtual Box and select your virtual machine and click on settings.

2- you will go to networks and click on it, then click on advanced, then click on Port Forwarding.

3- once you click on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Adel Fahmy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributing to IPC144 Repo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/belokond/contributing-to-ipc144-repo-568k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/belokond/contributing-to-ipc144-repo-568k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T01:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I was mostly focused on contributing to IPC144 repo. I was once a student who was using the old IPC144 website, and it wasn't the best experience, so I was so happy to see that people care about improving it and I was excited to contribute there too. Hopefully, it will make future students' experience so much better, now that fellow contributors and I have added so many improvements.
I was working on the following issues/PRs:
issue-51
PR#91
PR#68
I really liked that there was a clear list with all the requirements in the issues, so everyone knew what exactly to look for.
I also learned more about markdown syntax. For example, when I was trying to convert tables from HTML to markdown syntax, I noticed that markdown syntax does not support very complicated tables with a bunch of c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbelokon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling an Electron Application to pre-defined OS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/talr98/compiling-an-electron-application-to-pre-defined-os-446e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/talr98/compiling-an-electron-application-to-pre-defined-os-446e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T22:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


Electron.JS, in its main purpose - is for creating desktop applications using Javascript. Most popular way of doing so is using React & Node.js.
I will introduce a code architecture for building scalable Electron application - and on the fly - compile the code on chosen OS platform.
I am not going to focus on implementing it with an Electron application because there is no need for this tutorial, but you should know that the best application of this tutorial resides in Electron applications.
We are going to code the application to both Darwin and Windows platforms in one workspace - but as we'll see, in compilation we will be compiling only one (chosen by us) platform code. Because in most cases, you will need to code a code for 2 (at-least) platforms. But, we of-course don't want …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TalR98</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro/Creating a Database with MongoDB and testing it on Postman]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sefrangi/introcreating-a-database-with-mongodb-and-testing-it-on-postman-164o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sefrangi/introcreating-a-database-with-mongodb-and-testing-it-on-postman-164o"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T22:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! My name is Samantha, a brand new software dev! 
I have been learning to code for five years and this year I joined a bootcamp to get a structured curriculum and have a community to lean on when I’m stuck and need to see things from a new perspective.
My goal with this account is to practice what I learn by creating examples and talking through it. I hope to be able to reflect and see my progress and learn new techniques.
If you are also a new learner, I hope this helps you. Aight, let's get into it! 
By the end of this post you and I will be able to:
You’ll want to start by creating a directory (folder) with your project name. Mine will be fav-shows and inside of fav-shows i will touch (create) and file named server.js . Once they are created, I will open Visual Studio Code and start! …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samantha elaine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elementary OS - Dev Environment Setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skino2020/elementary-os-dev-environment-setup-1jjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skino2020/elementary-os-dev-environment-setup-1jjh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T22:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview


So every now and then i see something that catches my eye. Recently that seems to be Linux Distributions, over the last few months i have changed my distribution's a few times to try and find one i'm comfortable with. I moved from my iMac (getting a bit sluggish) to Ubuntu originally and it worked but i didn't "enjoy it", i then tried Manjaro, then Pop!_OS and then finally thought id have a go with Elementary OS.
So far i am really enjoying it! it feels a bit "Mac'ish", Looks nice and feels quick!
But compared to Ubuntu its a little bit different with the Setup of the dev environment, so i thought id write up a little tutorial on setting a Laravel Dev Environment on Elementary OS.
So as with any tutorial i do with Linux, we start with an update/upgrade.
sudo apt update
sudo apt …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you should choose Node.js for developing server-side applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ra1nbow1/why-you-should-choose-nodejs-for-developing-server-side-applications-3jkf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ra1nbow1/why-you-should-choose-nodejs-for-developing-server-side-applications-3jkf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.JS is a technology that has transformed JavaScript, which is familiar to all web developers, from a client-side scripting language to a general-purpose language that has a large number of application use cases.
 
At the heart of how Node works.js is asynchronous. In addition to non-blocking I / O, this allows a server-side application on Node.js can handle much more client requests per unit of time than a similar application developed on most other server-side development technologies.
What does this mean for your business?
You can start your own project with relatively low costs for the server infrastructure.
With the right architecture, this allows you to scale your business without investing a lot of money.
What does this mean for developers?
If you don't have an understanding of a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matvey Romanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a crawler]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yugely/lets-build-a-web-crawler-4jf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yugely/lets-build-a-web-crawler-4jf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T19:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I haven't written in a while. It's a slow day so I thought, how about we write a web crawler tutorial?
so, this code can easily be switched to js, and you can find a deno_dom replacement in cheerio with node js. 
The main thing a crawler needs is valid markup.
tl;dr
https://github.com/yugely/smooth_crawl]
I am currently building out my project for a deno/rust search engine with mellisearch as part of a larger project.
Since this is a deno backend, I'm taking advantage of the ability to use typescript OOB. Its handy, especially with the ability to create interfaces that can extend others.
What should a web crawler do?
Crawl to a depth blindly
Be rate limited in the calling
Crawl unique links
Parse URLs
Handle edge cases
probably some other stuff
We are going to make one that does all of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yugely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spread Operator and Rest Parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sturpin/spread-operator-and-rest-parameters-4dij</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sturpin/spread-operator-and-rest-parameters-4dij"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T18:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- English Version -





There are many pages wich explain what the Spread Operator (also know as three dots) and Rest Parameters are. 
It is an operator that I really like and I would like to share with you some ways that I use it.
📓 Spread Operator
let numbers = [1, 2, 3, 4];
console.log( numbers );

// => [ 1, 2, 3, 4 ] (print as array)

When we use the spread operator we get the values ​​independently:
let numbers = [1, 2, 3, 4];
console.log( ...numbers );

// => 1 2 3 4

Add an array to another:
let customers = [ 'Claudia', 'Borja', 'May' ];
let otherCustomers = [ 'Sergio', 'Jose' ];

customers.push( ...otherCustomers );
console.log( customers );

// => [ 'Claudia', 'Borja', 'May', 'Sergio', 'Jose' ]

Concat arrays:
let customers = [ 'Claudia', 'Borja', 'May' ];
let otherCustomers = …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Turpín</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reuse Angular Material Dialog with dynamic content]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-reuse-angular-material-dialog-with-dynamic-content-4edm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-reuse-angular-material-dialog-with-dynamic-content-4edm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T16:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Angular Material Dialog Component that takes Inputs and uses them in header and footer of modal. I want to pass some html elements in modal's body section from a component.
dashboard.component.html displays a 'show/hide columns' button.
dashboard.component.html
<app-modal [title]="title" [btnText]="text'>
   <section #template>
    <mat-form-field appearance="outline" *ngIf="!showForm && viewParams.length > 0 && cn_hostname_index >= 0">
      <mat-label>Search Columns</mat-label>
      <input 
        matInput
        id="columnSearchTxt"
        placeholder="Search Columns"
        name="columnSearchTxt"
        [(ngModel)]="colSearch.title"
      />
      <button *ngIf="colSearch.title" (click)="colSearch.title = ''" mat-icon-button matSuffix (click)="searchHosts()" matTooltip="…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Murthy Kota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reuse Angular Material Dialog with dynamic content]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-reuse-angular-material-dialog-with-dynamic-content-4edm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rammurthykota/how-to-reuse-angular-material-dialog-with-dynamic-content-4edm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T16:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a Angular Material Dialog Component that takes Inputs and uses them in header and footer of modal. I want to pass some html elements in modal's body section from a component.
dashboard.component.html displays a 'show/hide columns' button.
dashboard.component.html
<app-modal [title]="title" [btnText]="text'>
   <section #template>
    <mat-form-field appearance="outline" *ngIf="!showForm && viewParams.length > 0 && cn_hostname_index >= 0">
      <mat-label>Search Columns</mat-label>
      <input 
        matInput
        id="columnSearchTxt"
        placeholder="Search Columns"
        name="columnSearchTxt"
        [(ngModel)]="colSearch.title"
      />
      <button *ngIf="colSearch.title" (click)="colSearch.title = ''" mat-icon-button matSuffix (click)="searchHosts()" matTooltip="…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Murthy Kota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing a Custom Provider in Terraform v0.13+]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chefgs/developing-a-custom-provider-in-terraform-v013-49l8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chefgs/developing-a-custom-provider-in-terraform-v013-49l8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T16:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Introduction and Overview


Terraform is an Infrastructure as Code technology and it is used to create immutable infrastructure. It allows infrastructure to be expressed as code in a simple, human readable language called HCL (HashiCorp Configuration Language). 
Deliver infrastructure as code with Terraform using declarative .tf configuration files.
Plan and predict changes: Terraform provides an elegant user experience for operators to safely and predictably make changes to infrastructure. It reads configuration files and provides an execution plan of changes, which can be reviewed for safety and then applied and provisioned.
Extensible providers allow Terraform to manage a broad range of resources, including IaaS, PaaS, SaaS, and hardware services.
Create reproducible infrastru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saravanan G</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Testing (TDD) for Typescript Nodejs API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inidaname/how-to-set-up-testing-tdd-for-typescript-nodejs-api-3lak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inidaname/how-to-set-up-testing-tdd-for-typescript-nodejs-api-3lak"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will see how to set up TDD for Nodejs Typescript API.
The purpose of a test case is to determine if different features within a system are performing as expected and to confirm that the system satisfies all related standards, guidelines and customer requirements. The process of writing a test case can also help reveal errors or defects within the system.
What is a Test Case? - SearchSoftwareQuality
The above is the best way to describe tests. 
TypeScript is a strongly typed programming language that builds on JavaScript.
Node.js is a JavaScript runtime built on Chrome's V8 JavaScript engine.
Jest is a JavaScript Testing Framework.
Install Nodejs https://nodejs.org

Familiarity with Typescript or JavaScript is required
node -v

You should have the below output, it varies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hassan Sani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Testing (TDD) for Typescript Nodejs API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inidaname/how-to-set-up-testing-tdd-for-typescript-nodejs-api-3lak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inidaname/how-to-set-up-testing-tdd-for-typescript-nodejs-api-3lak"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will see how to set up TDD for Nodejs Typescript API.
The purpose of a test case is to determine if different features within a system are performing as expected and to confirm that the system satisfies all related standards, guidelines and customer requirements. The process of writing a test case can also help reveal errors or defects within the system.
What is a Test Case? - SearchSoftwareQuality
The above is the best way to describe tests. 
TypeScript is a strongly typed programming language that builds on JavaScript.
Node.js is a JavaScript runtime built on Chrome's V8 JavaScript engine.
Jest is a JavaScript Testing Framework.
Install Nodejs https://nodejs.org

Familiarity with Typescript or JavaScript is required
node -v

You should have the below output, it varies…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hassan Sani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PLEASE STOP THIS!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muneebhdeveloper/please-stop-this-18l6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muneebhdeveloper/please-stop-this-18l6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T15:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLEASE STOP THIS!!!
Node.js is not a Framework or Programming Language but a runtime environment built on top of Chrome's V8 engine to execute JavaScript outside of the browser, SIMPLE!
I often read articles where the author mentions Node.js as a JavaScript Framework and even compares it with PHP Frameworks, Ruby Frameworks, C# Frameworks, and also with JavaScript frontend frameworks and libraries like Angular, React, and jQuery.
Kindly stop this and don't misguide the people as this is really confusing for beginners who are trying to understand what Node.js is under the hood as Node.js has a lot to offer than just a Web Framework or JavaScript library.
Node.js !== JavaScript in the Browser
Node.js === Runtime Environment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muneeb Hussain Modi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices, express-react app (Part 2) End it with the backend!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/omardiaa48/microservices-express-react-app-part-2-end-it-with-the-backend-2dbo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/omardiaa48/microservices-express-react-app-part-2-end-it-with-the-backend-2dbo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T15:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second article of a series of posts discussing Micro-services, how to use Docker, Kubernetes and make your own CI/CD Workflow to deploy your app with cool automation.
Part 1
You can clone the app from here, or as I strongly recommend, go along step by step
We previously discussed the required folder structure for the posts service, to have a complete backend we will need some authentication also, we need the user model who will be the owner of the post. I don't want this article to go long, So I will cut corners on the parts that I have covered previously.
inside user.ts (posts-app/auth/models)
import mongoose from "mongoose";

interface UserAttributes {
    username:string;
    password:string;
}

interface UserDocument extends mongoose.Document{
    username:string;
    passw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar Diaaeldine Elwakeel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 good posts in "Living with Kubernetes"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/5-good-posts-in-living-with-kubernetes-30mi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/5-good-posts-in-living-with-kubernetes-30mi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T15:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks a lot to AWS Justin Garrison for this good series of "Living with Kubernetes" ! Recommend read and understand more in kubernetes API versioning, Upgrade strategies, Multi-cluster management (suggest to read new EKS connector Link too), how to debug cluster and workloads/pods ! 
5 good posts below: 
API Lifecycles and You
Link

Cluster Upgrades
Link

Multicluster Management
Link

Debug Clusters in 8 Commands
Link

12 Commands to Debug Your Workloads
Link



e.g. part 1:

part 2:

part 4:

part 5:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walter Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packaging Java apps with Maven and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cvitaa11/packaging-java-apps-with-maven-and-github-actions-4gbn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cvitaa11/packaging-java-apps-with-maven-and-github-actions-4gbn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T15:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post shows how to create workflows that package Java application with Maven and then store it as an artifact or publish to GitHub Packages.
In the previous post we described GitHub Actions and how they work, so if you need a quick reminder on the jobs, steps and syntax check it out.
On the following link you can find repository with the source code. It's a simple Spring Boot application that returns students from the database. The application was bootstrapped using Spring Initializr. For the dependencies we added Spring Web which is used for building web applications using Spring MVC. This package also uses Apache Tomcat as the default embedded container. We also used Spring Data JDBC for persisting data in SQL with plain JDBC and PostgreSQL Driver that allows Java programs to connect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Cvitkovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Environment per Project: Manage Directory-Scoped envs with direnv in POSIX Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/otamm/one-environment-per-project-manage-directory-scoped-envs-with-direnv-in-posix-systems-4n3c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/otamm/one-environment-per-project-manage-directory-scoped-envs-with-direnv-in-posix-systems-4n3c"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T14:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


One of the more common practices in software projects is to keep certain information separated but accessible from the codebase which uses it. This is usually done with secrets such as passwords or private keys, but is also commonly done with user or context-specific info pieces. However, management of environment variables can be confusing. The solutions to deal with it are many, and there are even built-in ones such as bash_profile. 
direnv, a shell extension which enables the definition of a list of environment variables scoped by a directory. After installing & hooking the extension, direnv will execute every time you change directories, looking for an .envrc file in the same or in a superior directory tree level. It will then load the defined variables to the current en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otavio Monteagudo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Where does the term 'directive' come from?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ovidiu141/angular-where-does-the-directive-term-come-from-20b6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ovidiu141/angular-where-does-the-directive-term-come-from-20b6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T14:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to understand the Angular terms and philosophy. One of the most basic building blocks of Angular seems to be a directive.
The Angular glossary says that "A [directive is a] class that can modify the structure of the DOM or modify attributes in the DOM and component data model".
Seems VueJS also has the concept of directive.
directive is some special token in the markup that tells the library to do something to a DOM element."
This includes a reference to the AngularJS framework, and, yes, it seems AngularJS also has this term.
AngularJS docs:  "At a high level, directives are markers on a DOM element (such as an attribute, element name, comment or CSS class) that tell AngularJS's HTML compiler ($compile) to attach a specified behavior to that DOM element (e.g. via event listeners), or even to transform the DOM element and its children."
Ok, so it seems that the term originally comes from AngularJS, and Angular and VueJS just inherited it.
I guess, in Layman terms, a directive is a way of "teaching the HTML to do new tricks" (not mine). 
directive?
Still not sure, maybe the creators thought of this term because a directive it's like commanding (giving directives/instructions/orders) to a static technology (HTML) in order to make it smarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ovidiu Miu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditching Linux for WSL 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cryptus_neoxys/ditching-linux-for-wsl-2-2bl6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cryptus_neoxys/ditching-linux-for-wsl-2-2bl6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T14:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WSL 2 == Microsoft's love for Linux



  
  
  Development on Linux


I switched to Linux last year and shifted my development completely to the Linux ecosystem. Tried out arch, Manjaro, Pop OS!, Ubuntu, MX Linux. Development is really productive with a Linux environment.
A few months back I upgraded my potato to a gaming laptop which of course came with Windows pre-installed, I also started gaming. I ended up doing dual boot to run Ubuntu as my daily driver for development, but this eventually meant a redundant set of tools on Windows as well.
Windows released the Windows Subsystem for Linux 2 in May 2019. WSL 1 was a compatibility layer for running Linux binary executables on Windows. WSL2 built on top is built on the core technology of Hyper-V to provide better support and improved perf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dev Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good example of the flow of c / embedded systems?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yobretyo/good-example-of-the-flow-of-c-embedded-systems-2n2h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yobretyo/good-example-of-the-flow-of-c-embedded-systems-2n2h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T14:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a good outline to “think of” with steps to when you create applications? 
Such as, with creating a light to light up, on the press of a button “on screen”, 
Is that a good layout of how how things “flow” with creating interactions?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bret</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know about 10 popular open-source projects in the end of 2021!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/suchitra_13/know-about-10-popular-open-source-projects-in-the-end-of-2021-2ofp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/suchitra_13/know-about-10-popular-open-source-projects-in-the-end-of-2021-2ofp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T11:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Firefox



Technologies: C++, C, HTML, JavaScript
here

Linux is a free and open source project developed by Linus Torvald in 1991. Basically, it is an operating system kernel that is open and free for everyone.
Technologies: C, Assembly language
here

Apache Cassandra is an open source NoSQL distributed database designed to manage massive amount of structure and unstructured data across the world.
Technology: Java
here

Technologies: Python, C++
here

Django is a Python based open source web framework that follows the model template views architectural pattern. It’s design to help developers achieve their most important objective, which rapid development.
Technology: Python
here

Kubernetes is an open source container orchestration system for automating computer application deploy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchitra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReactJS vs AngularJS: Which one is better for your project?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/code2rithik/reactjs-vs-angularjs-which-one-is-better-for-your-project-2ca8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/code2rithik/reactjs-vs-angularjs-which-one-is-better-for-your-project-2ca8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T10:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya Coders! What's poppin'?
Today, I'll be talking about which is better: React or Angular. Feel free to share your opinions in the comments below!
Let's get it!

 ✨ Javascript is one of the most popular languages ​​among developers today. There are many developers, newbies, and *seasoned aficionados* who build their application or project using Javascript, but still, there is confusion when choosing the right framework or library for their design. ✨ 

Soooo Angular and React are both popular but developers can't really decide upon WHICH is good for their project. 🤷‍♂️
Most learners and students want to learn a framework that could help in getting them a good job in the market. 🤓
Alright I honestly think I'm wasting your time lets get to the point. 😂
Let's get to the BASICS.
 React 
Pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rithik Samanthula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CORS for a Twitch Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shrmpy/cors-for-a-twitch-extension-3170</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shrmpy/cors-for-a-twitch-extension-3170"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T05:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the fourth in a multi-part series to walk through the creation of a Twitch extension. For the fourth part, the goal is to refactor the CORS headers.
To go directly to the project, the source code repository is available at
 / 
        pavlok
      
    
 / 
        pavlok-panel
      
    
Requirements:
Twitch extension client ID





  
  
  § Headers



  
  
  preprocess flow







  
  
  enableCors flow







The wildcard (*) in the Access-Control-Allow-Origin header is the primary change in this refactor work. It is time to restrict the origin to the hosting server (ID.ext-twitch.tv) of the Twitch extension.
Another change that should not add extra scope, is to remove DELETE from the Access-Control-Allow-Methods header.
Start the refactor by adding the new test:
fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shrmpy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Atomic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/reimagine-atomic-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T22:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not the biggest fan of Atomic CSS myself. I don’t like all the classes. I like to express my styles in CSS because I find CSS… good. But I appreciate that a lot of people seem to like it, …
The post Reimagine Atomic CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Font Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/coding-font-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tournament bracket UI where you pick your favorite between two coding fonts and your choices are whittled down all the way to a final winner. A clever way to suss out your own taste and arrive at a choice.…
The post Coding Font Game appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Tasks with cron Jobs in Linux]]></title>
        <id>618941df8bcfae07ca4e3869</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cron-jobs-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T20:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're working in IT, you might need to schedule various repetitive tasks as part of your automation processes.  For example, you could schedule a particular job to periodically execute at specific times of the day. This is helpful for performing daily backups, monthly log archiving, weekly file deletion to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Singapore a Surveillance State?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/steelwolf180/is-singapore-a-surveillance-state-4d8c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/steelwolf180/is-singapore-a-surveillance-state-4d8c"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T20:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I stumbled across a article recommended by Google News. The article was written by Rest of World called Singapore’s tech-utopia dream is turning into a surveillance state nightmare given it's a super click baity title. 
So I took the plunge and read the article, to my horror the article was really a messy piece of writing. That is littered with a jigsaw puzzle of tech projects in Singapore to frame a narrative that Singapore is a surveillance state. While bashing local tech community efforts like better.sg in the good work they had done.
What surprises me the most were the reporter in misquoting and being shady of the article they are publishing.
I had gotten this from Facebook which the reporter had gotten one of them as their source. Nothing in this email says anything about be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Ong Zong Bao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔓 How to Add Authorization to a Rails API Following TDD]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-add-authorization-to-a-rails-api-following-tdd-36b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-add-authorization-to-a-rails-api-following-tdd-36b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T18:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to secure a Rails API with Auth0 by letting you drive by tests.



  
  
  
When you're adding authorization to an application, there are two crucial questions:
Are users that shouldn't have access actually out?
Are users that should have access actually in?
If you can't answer with certainty both questions, how can you claim to have a secure application? This is something that you can test manually, but a better alternative is test automation. Concretely, I think the best methodology to get there is using Test-Driven Development (TDD).
This piece is about adding authorization to a Ruby on Rails API by following TDD. You can check out this article to learn in detail how to secure a Rails API with Auth0. Also, you can follow this article along with this repository.
In its essence,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Someone help]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/passionate_coder/can-someone-help-dnm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/passionate_coder/can-someone-help-dnm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have some questions (may be for some these are very naive) but I am not able to find specific practical ways
1) With angular 13 now its Ivy everywhere but we have Ivy from angular 9 (by default) so what is new here.
2) For Library authors earlier it is recommended to use enableIvy: false which now not doable as we have no Ivy but we have other option compilationMode: "partial" so they both are same?
3) If a new library is published with angular version 13. then can it be consumed in an application which is non-ivy?
4) Everywhere we have benefits of Angular 13 but in practical what will be disadvantages for already developed applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Passionate Coder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux For Development?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cdthomp1/linux-for-development-1dnp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cdthomp1/linux-for-development-1dnp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've have been seeing more and more about Linux in my article feeds with topics like "Linux for the every day user", and "Linux! Can you game on it?" and in my YouTube feed there are videos about different distros and what to do on Linux. 
This got me thinking... is Linux better for development? 
Do you use Linux for development? What do you develop? How has the experience been for you? What is your best advice for someone to get into developing in Linux? Are there distros to try out? Are there distros to avoid? Why did you move to Linux from MacOS or Windows?
I welcome all comments, questions, and suggestions! I may even turn this into a series where I try out Linux and report my findings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cameron Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I implemented sticky columns in tables using directives - Angular!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/how-i-implemented-sticky-columns-in-tables-using-directives-angular-nkb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/how-i-implemented-sticky-columns-in-tables-using-directives-angular-nkb"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to create sticky columns in Angular using directives. Implementing tables with sticky columns can be tricky especially when you have to make multiple columns sticky. Using directives, we can easily implement sticky columns.
I can't emphasize more the power of directives in Angular. I've written a couple of articles showcasing how one can actually use it to implement really cool stuff. You can check some use-cases for directives here:  Angular Directive Showcase.

We make use of the position: sticky CSS property to make an element sticky. Read more about sticky positioning at  MDN.
.sticky {
  position: sticky;
  left: 0;
}

For the sticky position to work properly, at least one of top, right, bottom, or left should be specified.
Making the first column in a table sticky is super simple…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aliases - Using Linux made easier]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayushdev_24/aliases-using-linux-made-easier-3j49</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayushdev_24/aliases-using-linux-made-easier-3j49"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a lovely day, you are sitting in front of your laptop on your work desk writing some excellent code, and your terminal is full of some scripts or commands.
Now you realize I need to navigate to a directory inside another directory that is inside another. The chain continues for about 4-5 directories until you reach the required folder.
Such a mood spoiler, right! This potential move has the tendency to force you to get up from your desk and take a 5-minute break which can very quickly turn into a long break. 
See, the damaging domino effect it can have? Now you will argue, ah! You don't know, I can keep pressing the "up" arrow and find the command I need because I used it just about a few hours ago. 
But is that the most efficient way or the best we can do?
Of course not, and this is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Agarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vital Tips to Help You Create a Secure React Web Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/grapecity/vital-tips-to-help-you-create-a-secure-react-web-application-3m94</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/grapecity/vital-tips-to-help-you-create-a-secure-react-web-application-3m94"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global influx of digital transformation is creating pressure on infrastructure. All the while, threat actors are continually improving their attack techniques. If there is a vulnerability to be found, it will be exploited. 
This is why many teams are shifting security to the left, even going as far as evolving their dev methodology from DevOps to DevSecOps.
Developers still have remaining concerns, most of which focus on release time. However, you should not have to compromise fast releases in favor of security. It doesn't have to be a question of either/or.
In this article, you will learn about four methods that you can take advantage of to secure your React apps quickly. These are simple security practices that should not interrupt your workflow.
React, commonly misconstrued as a fra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Del Signore Fazio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357192</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/parallax-powered-by-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good friend Kent C. Dodds has recently dropped his new website which had a lot of work go into it. I was fortunate enough that Kent reached out a while back and asked if I could come up with some …
The post Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IRIS API Explorer Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/intersystems/iris-api-explorer-application-32gk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/intersystems/iris-api-explorer-application-32gk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T13:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background


InterSystems IRIS 2019 is going to introduce new and exciting features. One of the areas with new interesting must-to-know things is the API Management. 
OpenAPI initiative (https://www.openapis.org/) is the organization supporting a standard specification to define APIs (https://github.com/OAI/OpenAPI-Specification). The OpenAPI Specification (OAS) defines a standard, programming language-agnostic interface description for REST APIs, which allows both humans and computers to discover and understand the capabilities of a service without requiring access to source code, additional documentation, or inspection of network traffic. When properly defined via OpenAPI, a consumer can understand and interact with the remote service with a minimal amount of implementation logic. Simila…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>InterSystems Developer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 19th November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-19th-november-2021-1fc7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-19th-november-2021-1fc7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T12:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello there. Welcome to this week's review, I am your host Habdul Hazeez.
This week's review is about malware, vulnerabilities,  computer security and one article that I authored.
Let's go.
Zoom Patches High-Risk Flaws in Meeting Connector, Keybase Client


Zoom, the technology breakout star of the COVID-19 pandemic. They were in the news for all sorts of privacy-related stuff, ever since they've stepped up their security, this is another step in that direction.
Excerpt from the article:
The company released multiple security bulletins to warn of the risks and called special attention to a pair of “high-risk” bugs affecting its on-prem meeting connector software and the popular Keybase Client.
“The network proxy page on the web portal for the [affected] products fails to val…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can DevSecOps Tools Open Security Testing To Everyone?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uleska/can-devsecops-tools-open-security-testing-to-everyone-2j6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uleska/can-devsecops-tools-open-security-testing-to-everyone-2j6f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE EXPERIMENT: JAVASCRIPT SOURCE CODE SECURITY TESTING TOOLS


To begin our experiment, we chose 1,000 Javascript projects on GitHub that were recently updated and had between 50 and 200 stars in rating. Next, we went to UpWork.com and paid non-professionals £5/hour to use the Uleska Platform to automatically run three Javascript source code security testing tools. We consolidated the results generated by the platform to the project teams and made sure they didn’t have security or programming skills.
We didn’t set up any of our cyber value-at-risk enumerations, as they would apply to how an open-source library is used within the end-user application (i.e. types of data processed, quantity of data, environment etc.).
We also made the decision not to triage the results, as the Uleska Platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting with a wildcard subdomain enables your users to visit your site on any subdomain of your domain (*.example.com), and as you can imagine, we can use this to create unique user experiences which we’ll be exploring in this article through a Next.js lens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating and Configuring Eslint in Angular 11]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/migrating-and-configuring-eslint-in-angular-11-251i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/migrating-and-configuring-eslint-in-angular-11-251i"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the earlier version, Angular implements the linting with TSLint but with Angular 11 announced that the TSLint linting replaced with the ESLint.
Nx leans for some, but not for all packages from this project. It does not use the builder to execute ESLint.
The following packages are included in your project.
@angular-eslint/builder:This package is used to execute ESLint in your project using standard commands such as ng lint.
@angular-eslint/eslint-plugin: This is the ESLint specific package that contains some specific rules that are specific for the Angular projects. It can be combined with other ESLint packages.
@angular-eslint/template-parser: This is the ESLint specific parser package that allows you to written the custom ESLint rules in your Angular template.
@angular-eslint/eslint-pl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look out for these Angular App Development services while hiring Angular Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arohi/look-out-for-these-angular-app-development-services-3mjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arohi/look-out-for-these-angular-app-development-services-3mjm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T09:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is picking up the trends in the software development arena and has become one of the hot topics in the frontend development community and has broken several bars when it comes to providing result-oriented web application services through high-end performance.
Many globally renowned fortune 500 companies are outsourcing Angularjs development companies for their projects rather than hiring and maintaining an in-house team.
Furthermore, even those who already have an in-house team prefer to fill out that skill gap with expert assistance from one of the top-notch Development companies.
If you are contemplating hiring such Angularjs Development services, you should know what kind of services a web application development process would require regardless of any particular niche.
To give …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arohi7892</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers Spent 2.1 Billion Minutes (4,000 years) Using freeCodeCamp in 2021 + Other Year-End Facts]]></title>
        <id>6196aac811d3cb08287a8998</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-2021-review-budget-usage-statistics/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T05:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021 has been a big year for the global freeCodeCamp community. In this article, I will share some of the milestones we hit this year. But first, let's look at some metrics to drive home the scale at which the freeCodeCamp community is now operating. freeCodeCamp 2021 StatisticsIn 2021, freeCodeCamp's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Projects for New Developers – What to Build to Get Coding Experience]]></title>
        <id>614641bf852f4307d373021f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-projects-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a new developer, you're probably familiar with the “Experience Paradox”. It describes the frustrating cycle many of us go through when we're trying to get our first developer jobs: To get a job, you need "work experience". But to get "work experience", you need a job...! Job requires]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stress and Mental Health in Tech – What I learned from Dr. Jennifer Akullian&#x27;s freeCodeCamp Tech Talk]]></title>
        <id>619392bd11d3cb08287a6f36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stress-and-mental-health-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People in the tech industry face mental health issues like depression and anxiety every day, all around the world. But what can we do about it? In this article, I will talk about what I learned from Dr. Jennifer Akullian's freeCodeCamp Tech Talk and share her tips for reducing your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize Your Windows 10 Taskbar to Be More Productive]]></title>
        <id>6196275811d3cb08287a850e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-customize-your-windows10-taskbar-for-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On your computer desktop, you can use the taskbar to help you monitor applications, check battery life, and more.  Being able to customize what your task bar can do is crucial for boosting your productivity. And there's more to it than just monitoring applications.  In this guide, I will show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Comprehension in Python]]></title>
        <id>6193c41c11d3cb08287a70ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-comprehension-in-python-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are a helpful and frequently used feature in Python.  And list comprehension gives you a way to create lists while writing more elegant code that is easy to read.  In this beginner-friendly article, I'll give an overview of how list comprehension works in Python. I'll also show plenty of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Git Tools—Interactive Rebase, Cherry-Picking, Reflog, and more]]></title>
        <id>6196642611d3cb08287a8688</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-git-interactive-rebase-cherry-picking-reflog-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a software developer, you likely use Git all the time. But many developers don't use advanced git commands that can speed up their worflow. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use advanced git commands. Tobias Günther]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Quick Note on –  Solved for MacOS Monterey Quick Notes Hot Corner]]></title>
        <id>61971c7611d3cb08287a8d83</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/turn-off-quick-note-mac-monterey/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T04:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently updated to MacOS Monterey (Version 12.0). Sometimes software companies like Apple will add features I don't like, then enable them by default. This is what happened with the New Quick Note hot corner. Here is what the Quick Notes feature looks like when you move your cursor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Got My First Developer Job – Here&#x27;s What I&#x27;ve Learned So Far]]></title>
        <id>617a6ef033422e07df3667f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-ive-learned-at-my-first-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to share with you what I've learned so far at my first programming job as a junior full-stack developer.  Ever since my developer career began in July, 2021 I've been learning constantly. And I'm gonna share some tips from my experiences so that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Serverless Online Payments with Netlify and Stripe]]></title>
        <id>618fda8c11d3cb08287a5a51</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-online-payments/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first steps many young startups take is setting up a static web page, perhaps with an email newsletter, to help them build an audience.  As the weeks go by and the MVP is getting further along, the subject of how to handle payments will eventually emerge. From]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry-Picking Commits in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356700</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cherry-picking-commits-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 5 of this series, we looked at rebasing and merging. Although there are a couple of differences between git merge and git rebase, both commands have the same goal: they integrate changes from one branch into another.
The post Cherry-Picking Commits in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gap (Design Engineering)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357023</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-gap-design-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egor Kloos describes a situation where a (purely visual) designer asks for some changes to a component. There is a misunderstanding where the (code monkey) developer implements the change exactly as requested—but really what was required was both a bug …
The post The Gap (Design Engineering) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clever Sticky Footer Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357053</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-clever-sticky-footer-technique/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T00:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upon hearing “sticky footer” these days, I would think most people imagine a position: sticky situation where a footer element appears fixed on the screen while in the scrolling context of some parent element.
That’s not quite what I’m talking …
The post A Clever Sticky Footer Technique appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Line length revisited: following the research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356849</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/line-length-revisited-following-the-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Dyson produces nitty gritty research on the long-accepted notion that shorter line lengths are more legible than longer ones. The study finds that shorter lines do not necessarily lead to faster reading. If you’re looking for a definitive answer …
The post Line length revisited: following the research appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting late-December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate a Pull Request of Static Content With a Simple HTML Form]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356491</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/generate-a-pull-request-of-static-content-with-a-simple-html-form/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack has been in the website world for years. Static Site Generators (SSGs) — which often have content that lives right within a GitHub repo itself — are a big part of that story. That opens up the idea of …
The post Generate a Pull Request of Static Content With a Simple HTML Form appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hilman Ramadhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack TV]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jamstack-tv/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the name of Netlify’s YouTube Channel. Love that. I linked up Rich’s talk the other day, which was a part of this past JamstackConf, but now all the talks are up on there. Rich got to talk …
The post Jamstack TV appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Alpha Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356611</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/color-alpha-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T01:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my “Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage” article, I noted a situation about colors and CSS custom properties where I went “too far” with breaking up HSL color values. Breaking every single color into its H, S, and L parts …
The post Color Alpha Anywhere appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/defining-and-applying-ui-themes-using-the-mimcss-css-in-js-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Theming UI refers to the ability to perform a change in visual styles in a consistent manner that defines the “look and feel” of a site. Swapping color palettes, à la dark mode or some other means, is a good …
The post Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Michlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>