<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-18T01:04:36.805Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-18T01:04:36.805Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed up your Next.js application with Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/noahfschr/speed-up-your-next-js-application-with-redis-53lb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/noahfschr/speed-up-your-next-js-application-with-redis-53lb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T00:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a very successful web framework which brings together server side rendering and static site generation. SSG speeds up your web site thanks to CDN caching meanwhile SSR helps you with SEO and dynamic data.
Server side rendering is a great feature which helps you to write full stack applications. But if you are not careful, the performance of your Next.js website can be affected easily. In this blog post, I will explain how to leverage Redis to speed up your Next.js API calls. Before that I will br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SECURE Your Code From the Start with Snyk.io and Snyk Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/secure-your-code-from-the-start-with-snyk-io-and-snyk-code-2oj7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/secure-your-code-from-the-start-with-snyk-io-and-snyk-code-2oj7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T00:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring application security is extremely important. But usually it's also pretty tedious and definitely not fun.
The tools we use are usually slow and not very accurate, and this leads to not using them properly.
Notice that I've said "usually", because I think I've found the solution for it. Or, better, Snyk has found it.
Let's dive into it.
🌏Check out Snyk at http://snyk.co/coderdave
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SECURE Your Code From the Start with Snyk.io and Snyk Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/secure-your-code-from-the-start-with-snyk-io-and-snyk-code-2oj7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/secure-your-code-from-the-start-with-snyk-io-and-snyk-code-2oj7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T00:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring application security is extremely important. But usually it's also pretty tedious and definitely not fun.
The tools we use are usually slow and not very accurate, and this leads to not using them properly.
Notice that I've said "usually", because I think I've found the solution for it. Or, better, Snyk has found it.
Let's dive into it.
🌏Check out Snyk at http://snyk.co/coderdave
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340716</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Addy Osmani on images in HTML:
The humble <img> element has gained some superpowers over the years. Given how central it is to image optimization on the web, let’s catch up on what it can do and how it can 
…
The post The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[📈 How to Scale Quickly with Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-scale-quickly-with-identity-3baf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-scale-quickly-with-identity-3baf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📕 Learn how the right customer identity and access management (CIAM) solution helps you achieve scalability and provide consistent, reliable service.



  
  
  
In the last few years, identity has become a familiar concept to business decision-makers seeking to fortify their security, unlock efficiency gains, and outpace competitors.
Customer identity and access management (CIAM) is a set of solutions built to help organizations balance convenience, privacy, and security for every type of user who needs a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Cookies Against Common XSS Attacks on the Web?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/obetomuniz/how-to-protect-cookies-against-common-xss-attacks-on-the-web-3p39</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/obetomuniz/how-to-protect-cookies-against-common-xss-attacks-on-the-web-3p39"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T21:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can ignore Cookies danger by just not recommending its usage, but the fact is that at least 55% of all the websites use Cookies RIGHT NOW even with lots of existing cookieless strategies.
So how to protect Cookies against Common XSS Attacks?
Well, if your app really needs to use Cookies, configure each one  through Set-Cookie HTTP Header with at least the following flags:
🍪 Secure: To allow the Cookie only through HTTPS
HttpOnly: To remove the Cookie from the document.cookie
SameSite: To limit the Cooki…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beto Muniz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML vs JSX – What&#x27;s the Difference?]]></title>
        <id>60a2771762ab9107fe5ab383</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-vs-jsx-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T21:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML vs JSX Hypertext Markup Language (HTML) is the standard language for documents that determine the structure of a web page.  HTML is a very important language in web development. Your code is either in HTML originally or compiles to it so browsers can read it.  JSX, on the other]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Become a leader in VIM window and tab creation!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aminnairi/become-a-leader-in-vim-window-and-tab-creation-12c5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aminnairi/become-a-leader-in-vim-window-and-tab-creation-12c5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preface


If you are like me, a VIM user, but have never used windows, now is a great time to do it!
The main reason I didn't use windows in VIM is because I use Tmux. But this is a bad reason, and not everybody is used to use Tmux, even though you should because this is a fantastic tool.
The second bad reason why I don't use windows is because I don't really like the key combination. Since most of the keys are used for something very logical, there is no more space for using window efficiently, meaning we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Chrome DevTools tips & tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/areknawo/top-10-chrome-devtools-tips-tricks-2b8g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/areknawo/top-10-chrome-devtools-tips-tricks-2b8g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools are undoubtedly one of the most important tools in a web developer’s toolbelt. Definitely the go-to (and pretty much only) way for front-end debugging.
From all the browsers, and all the DevTools variations (most notably 3, to be precise), Chrome DevTools are the most popular. They help you debug your code across many Chromium-based browsers like Chrome, Edge, or Brave - and even more other Chromium-based projects.
So, you’re most likely familiar with the basic DevTools workflow. Click a button or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arek Nawo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Testing basado en OWASP]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atejedaautomation/api-testing-basado-en-owasp-3165</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atejedaautomation/api-testing-basado-en-owasp-3165"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En API Testing y no morir en el intento realicé una introducción sobre qué deberíamos de probar en una API, en esta oportunidad vamos a tomar en consideración el top 10 de OWASP para que agreguemos casos de pruebas de introducción a seguridad.
OWASP (Open Web Application Security Project), es un proyecto sin ánimo de lucro a nivel mundial que busca mejorar la seguridad del software en general. Para esto, la organización se ha provisto de una serie de herramientos y documentos que explican cuáles son las bre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred Tejeda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to: Use Angular Material’s Mat-Icon with local SVG Images?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/how-to-use-angular-material-s-mat-icon-with-local-svg-images-22p8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/how-to-use-angular-material-s-mat-icon-with-local-svg-images-22p8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:29:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dunkin Faulkner | ng-conf | Jan 2021
When developing an Angular application with Angular Material, there comes a point when we need to add icons on our components, or buttons etc… Angular Material has the Mat-Icon component for doing this. This component works with web fonts like Font-Awesome for instance, simply by adding the name of the image required and an image is displayed.
Note: Requires an Angular application with Angular Material installed and configured with a reference to Font-Awesome library.
Bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access Secrets in AKV using Managed identities for AKS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vivekanandrapaka/access-secrets-from-akv-using-managed-identities-for-aks-91p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vivekanandrapaka/access-secrets-from-akv-using-managed-identities-for-aks-91p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purpose of this post


The purpose of this post is to show you how to access secrets from  AKS cluster that are stored in Azure Key Vault.
In one of my previous blog posts, i have shown how to access keys from Key vault from Azure DevOps, where i have configured the release pipeline to fetch the secret from key vault and substitute it during runtime for the pipeline.
we have many other ways of accessing keys from key vault from any of the Azure resources we deploy, Using managed identities is one of the sec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivekanand Rapaka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Show Alert Message on a condition]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-show-alert-message-on-a-condition-1092</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-show-alert-message-on-a-condition-1092"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to create Alert?


You can use your custom CSS to customize your alert message or you can use Bootstrap Alert as below -
<div class="alert alert-success" role="alert">
  A simple success alert—check it out!
</div>


Now you know how to create Alert, now let's talk about how you can include bootstrap in your angular project so that bootstrap classes will work, there are two many ways to do this but I will simply use CDN style path in index.html
<link href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@5.0.1/dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing sessionStorage and localStorage with Selenium (Node)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/grouparoo/testing-sessionstorage-and-localstorage-with-selenium-node-2336</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/grouparoo/testing-sessionstorage-and-localstorage-with-selenium-node-2336"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently added a feature to the Grouparoo site that is using sessionStorage to send analytics data. Being that it's an important feature, we should write test(s) to cover the use case(s), right?
Okay, fine. Let's do it!
This website is a Next.js application that uses Jest as the test runner and Selenium WebDriver for integration test help.
What I wanted to do with Jest and Selenium was to read from sessionStorage after visiting a series of pages. After a bit of perusing, I finally uncovered a (goofy) way …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean C Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deferring Side-Effects in Node.js until the End of a Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/grouparoo/deferring-side-effects-in-node-js-until-the-end-of-a-transaction-2e8h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/grouparoo/deferring-side-effects-in-node-js-until-the-end-of-a-transaction-2e8h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Grouparoo, we use Actionhero as our Node.js API server and Sequelize for our Object Relational Mapping (ORM) tool - making it easy to work with complex records from our database. Within our Actions and Tasks, we often want to treat the whole execution as a single database transaction - either all the modifications to the database will succeed or fail as a unit. This is really helpful when a single activity may create or modify many database rows.
Take the following example from a prototypical blogging si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Tahler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DOM Explained for Beginners – How the Document Object Model Works]]></title>
        <id>60a16df162ab9107fe5ab01b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dom-explained-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-document-object-model/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I started out as a web developer, people often threw around the term "DOM" in the industry. Every JavaScript tutorial mentioned it, but I didn't know what it meant. Fast forward two years, and now that I know what it's all about, I am going to explain what the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Easiest Way to Debug Kubernetes Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/martinheinz/the-easiest-way-to-debug-kubernetes-workloads-1njg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/martinheinz/the-easiest-way-to-debug-kubernetes-workloads-1njg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging containerized workloads and Pods is a daily task for every developer and DevOps engineer that works with Kubernetes. Oftentimes simple kubectl logs or kubectl describe pod is enough to find the culprit of some problem, but some issues are harder to hunt down. In those cases you might try to use kubectl exec but even that might not be enough as some containers such as Distroless don't even contain shell that you could SSH into. So what do we have left, if all of the above fails? ...
Sometimes you n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Heinz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Easiest Way to Debug Kubernetes Workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/martinheinz/the-easiest-way-to-debug-kubernetes-workloads-1njg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/martinheinz/the-easiest-way-to-debug-kubernetes-workloads-1njg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging containerized workloads and Pods is a daily task for every developer and DevOps engineer that works with Kubernetes. Oftentimes simple kubectl logs or kubectl describe pod is enough to find the culprit of some problem, but some issues are harder to hunt down. In those cases you might try to use kubectl exec but even that might not be enough as some containers such as Distroless don't even contain shell that you could SSH into. So what do we have left, if all of the above fails? ...
Sometimes you n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Heinz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Polr on Ubuntu 20.04 with LAMP]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hostnextra/how-to-install-polr-on-ubuntu-20-04-with-lamp-3b9p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hostnextra/how-to-install-polr-on-ubuntu-20-04-with-lamp-3b9p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll explain how to install Polr on Ubuntu 20.04 with LAMP.
Polr is a quick, modern, and open-source link shortener. It allows you to host your own URL shortener, to brand your URLs, and to gain control over your data.
It has a robust API (Application Programming Interface) that allows you to create links programmatically. It is released under the GNU General Public License v2.0, and it comes with a wide range of features that allow you to customize permissions, URL forwarding, and themes.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HostnExtra Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Testing with Cypress: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/murillowelsi/api-testing-with-cypress-part-1-5coe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/murillowelsi/api-testing-with-cypress-part-1-5coe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks!!


It’s been a long time since I last wrote something here. A few days ago I was thinking about something that might be interesting to share with you about REST APIs automation testing. So the idea came to me:
Why not use Cypress to create a complete API testing project > from scratch? We can use TDD to create the test, do all the > necessary validations and put this into a CI pipeline! 
So lets go for it!
I will split this project into three parts, so that the content does not become too boring.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murillo Welsi de Souza Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Silicon Death Valleys]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pepefeliblu/apple-silicon-death-valleys-4i63</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pepefeliblu/apple-silicon-death-valleys-4i63"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sweet Apple M1


I am not an apple fan/boy. I mean, I get it. They provide this unique and friendly ecosystem of products that now are consolidating under one hardware architecture. But along those changes, their OS also changes too. On previous jobs I used the iMac 4K 27 inch display. They used intel and they were nice. And working on those machines is pretty sweet! I think it was macOS Catalina?
Personally I own an ASUS gaming machine with windows, I mostly use it for gaming! But I can tell that many work…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pepefeliblu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Lottie Library like a Pro – Lottie Resources for Designers and Developers]]></title>
        <id>609f552e62ab9107fe5aaba0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lottie-like-a-pro-resources-for-designers-and-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lottie is a library that helps render Adobe After Effects animations natively on mobile and the web. I like using Lottie for animations in my projects because: Creating an animation from scratch can be time-consuming, andGIF files can be double the size of Lottie JSON files (the files containing the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate password rotation with Github and Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-password-rotation-with-github-and-azure-412a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-password-rotation-with-github-and-azure-412a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💡 How to rotate VM passwords using Github workflows with Azure Key Vault



  
  
  Overview


Today we are going to look at how we can implement a zero-touch fully automated solution under 15 minutes to rotate all our virtual machines local administrator passwords on a schedule by using a single Github workflow and a centrally managed Azure key vault. In our use case we want to be able to rotate the local administrator password of all virtual machines hosted in an Azure subscription, trigger the rotation …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorize your routes in Angular with a simple interceptor.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elandyg/colorize-your-routes-in-angular-with-a-simple-interceptor-4kc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elandyg/colorize-your-routes-in-angular-with-a-simple-interceptor-4kc9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[live example
We know the simplest way to view traffic is using the network tab in DevTools, but sometimes you need to add another tool to your debugging arsenal. Using an interceptor will help you tap into the http request pipeline so you can work your magic and log all of your routes in a nice color-coded format so they stand out. 
If you are using the In-Memory Web API, (which is the best thing since sliced bread), all of your calls are technically not going over the wire, so nothing is written to the net…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ElAndyG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorize your routes in Angular with a simple interceptor.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elandyg/colorize-your-routes-in-angular-with-a-simple-interceptor-4kc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elandyg/colorize-your-routes-in-angular-with-a-simple-interceptor-4kc9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[live example
We know the simplest way to view traffic is using the network tab in DevTools, but sometimes you need to add another tool to your debugging arsenal. Using an interceptor will help you tap into the http request pipeline so you can work your magic and log all of your routes in a nice color-coded format so they stand out. 
If you are using the In-Memory Web API, (which is the best thing since sliced bread), all of your calls are technically not going over the wire, so nothing is written to the net…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ElAndyG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[App 101: What is a Work Queue and how to make one in Node]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zackdotcomputer/app-101-what-is-a-work-queue-and-how-to-make-one-in-node-26n0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zackdotcomputer/app-101-what-is-a-work-queue-and-how-to-make-one-in-node-26n0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of the details about building an app are mysterious, even if you've been a programmer for years. So, I'm going to bundle up some of the discussions I've had with friends who are starting their own apps into these App101 posts. Follow along and we'll bring you up to speed on the decisions that you'll have to make when building a web-based app today.
If you boil it down far enough, most internet programming follows this cycle:
Receive HTTP Request -> Do Work -> Deliver HTTP Response
This works fine 99% …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zack Sheppard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Free MongoDB Courses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/4-free-mongodb-courses-430</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/4-free-mongodb-courses-430"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I will list 4 courses on MongoDB which are completely free. These courses are provided by MongoDB University. Also, you will receive a proof of completion certificate if you achieve a grade of 65% or more depending on your performance in labs and final exam.
Link - https://university.mongodb.com/courses/M001/about
In this course, you will learn how to set up your database and start exploring different ways to search, create, and analyze your data with MongoDB. It will cover database performanc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Chilamakuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solidity Tutorial – How to Create NFTs with Hardhat]]></title>
        <id>609cb90262ab9107fe5aa026</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/solidity-tutorial-hardhat-nfts/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a developer who's mostly been writing JavaScript, so the Solidity development environment was a bit hard to learn.  About four months ago, I switched to Hardhat from Truffle. This cool new kid on the block drastically improved my coding experience. So today I want to share it with my]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automagically optimize your images with Squoosh]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/timdeschryver/automagically-optimize-your-images-with-squoosh-5fn3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/timdeschryver/automagically-optimize-your-images-with-squoosh-5fn3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitter at @tim_deschryver | Subscribe to the Newsletter | Originally published on timdeschryver.dev.
Read the TLDR on timdeschryver.dev
For my blog, I used to use the Image Optimizer Github Action to optimize my images.
The downside to this approach was that the optimization was only performed on Pull Requests. When I'm publishing a new blog post, I usually just pushed to the main branch, thus new images wouldn't be optimized. As a counter measurement, I also used Squoosh to optimize the banne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Deschryver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Table]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/angular-table-49jk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/angular-table-49jk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Table displays data in tabular format.
Refer to PrimeNG setup documentation for download and installation steps for your environment.
VirtualScrolling depends on @angular/cdk's ScrollingModule so begin with installing CDK if not already installed.
npm install @angular/cdk --save

import {TableModule} from 'primeng/table';

Table requires a value as an array of objects and templates for the presentation. Throughout the samples, a car interface having vin, brand, year and color properties is used to d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Love Letter to HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339522</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-love-letter-to-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see you. In the back there, behind JavaScript and React and PHP and all those “real” programming languages, I see you. And I appreciate you.
The post A Love Letter to HTML & CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Kolodziej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euismod]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340594</id>
        <link href="https://www.euismod.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interactive tool for learning grid syntax from Etesam Ansari. In the Learn section, it teaches you some concepts (involving multiple bits of the grid syntax) then gives you a task to complete by filling out the right syntax. I’m …
The post Euismod appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Docker image size of a Nuxt SSR application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fbjorn/reducing-docker-image-size-of-a-nuxt-ssr-application-40oe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fbjorn/reducing-docker-image-size-of-a-nuxt-ssr-application-40oe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I had to create a deployment of a NuxtJS application which is running in SSR mode. I have a separate backend that is already packed in Docker image, so it sounds pretty tempting to dockerize the frontend application as well and to run both using docker-compose. Basically, server side rendering implies that the frontend application becomes a server too, to some extent. 
To demonstrate the concept, I will show you two Dockerfiles, one is straightforward, without any optimizations, and another is what…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic Vim Commands Every Linux User Must Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/basic-vim-commands-every-linux-user-must-know-2jni</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/basic-vim-commands-every-linux-user-must-know-2jni"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is the most popular text editor and the most powerful tool in Linux. And in order to master it, one must learn its basic commands. 
Vim is one of the most interesting applications that any Linux user must learn at some point. It’s a very old text editor from the early days of UNIX, incredibly powerful and versatile, and fun to use 💻
Even if you’re not a developer or programmer, Vim is still an essential tool that you should learn if you use Linux or BSD on a daily basis.
If you are new to Vim, I recomm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git and GitHub are the same?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tannudaral/git-and-github-are-the-same-21bp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tannudaral/git-and-github-are-the-same-21bp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are they related? Yes, but are they the same? No. 
Git is a version control system that lets you manage and keep track of your source code history while GitHub is a cloud-based hosting service that lets you manage Git repositories. If you have open-source projects that use Git, then GitHub is designed to help you better manage them. 
After all, in the world of programming, naming conventions aren’t always intuitive. That’s why it’s worth recognizing the connections and the differences in the similarly named…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tannu Daral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Backup database SQL Server in docker container.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pobx/automate-backup-database-sql-server-in-docker-container-oea</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pobx/automate-backup-database-sql-server-in-docker-container-oea"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, everyone. This is first my post in dev.to and my first time for write article in second language. today I want to share some trick for backup your database from docker container. let's begin... :)
Note I assume your already running container. 
For example I use TutorialDB database for demonstrate purpose. Your can create same database click Create a database
PRINT "Start Backup process...";
DECLARE @MyFileName varchar(200)
SELECT @MyFileName=N'/tmp/Backup_' + convert(nvarchar(20),GetDate(),112)+'_'+conv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pobx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running stuff on Deno]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/running-stuff-on-deno-3e7i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/running-stuff-on-deno-3e7i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh. Hey there!
I'm happy you came back for this third post. The subject today is: "Running stuff on Deno".
This post is a transcript of a Youtube video I made.
I brushed over this on the previous post because I wanted to cover it in detail.
The first tool that I think we should explore is the REPL. It is a terminal-based interactive runtime.
To bring up the REPL, all you need to do is to execute the deno command and, you're ready to go.
ctrl+d or type close().
const message = "hello world".split("").reverse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastien Filion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running stuff on Deno]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/running-stuff-on-deno-3e7i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/running-stuff-on-deno-3e7i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh. Hey there!
I'm happy you came back for this third post. The subject today is: "Running stuff on Deno".
This post is a transcript of a Youtube video I made.
I brushed over this on the previous post because I wanted to cover it in detail.
The first tool that I think we should explore is the REPL. It is a terminal-based interactive runtime.
To bring up the REPL, all you need to do is to execute the deno command and, you're ready to go.
ctrl+d or type close().
const message = "hello world".split("").reverse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastien Filion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UML diagram for GoF design pattern examples in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/takaakit/uml-diagram-for-gof-design-pattern-examples-in-typescript-46d5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/takaakit/uml-diagram-for-gof-design-pattern-examples-in-typescript-46d5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post lists UML diagrams of GoF design pattern examples written in TypeScript.  The UML diagrams are displayed using Diagram Map. If you want to know about Diagram Map, see this post. Also, you can get UML model data and TypeScript code of the examples from here.  
Behavioral Patterns


Chain of Responsibility
Command
Interpreter
Iterator
Mediator
Memento
Observer
State
Strategy
Template Method
Visitor
Creational Patterns


Abstract Factory
Builder
Factory Method
Prototype
Singleton
Structural Patterns
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Takaaki Teshima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Node.js Event Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thawkin3/understanding-the-node-js-event-loop-242d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thawkin3/understanding-the-node-js-event-loop-242d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is single-threaded, so how does it handle asynchronous code without blocking the main thread while it waits for an action to complete? The key to understanding the asynchronous nature of JavaScript is understanding the event loop.
In the browser, the event loop coordinates the execution of code between the call stack, web APIs, and the callback queue. Node.js, however, implements its own “Node.js event loop,” which is different from the regular “JavaScript event loop.” How confusing!
The Node.js …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appointment Scheduling API for Group Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/spurwing/appointment-scheduling-api-for-group-meetings-4inn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/spurwing/appointment-scheduling-api-for-group-meetings-4inn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spurwing is for Scheduling what Stripe is for Payments. Our Appointment Scheduling API enables software teams to deliver quicker, cheaper and better scheduling features.
In this post we'll explore some of the coolest features and use cases possible with the Spurwing API.
We've updated our SDKs with Group Scheduling features from our API. These booking features were already present in the API but they weren't yet implemented in our official JavaScript, NodeJS, Python and Java Libraries.
A group appointment a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spurwing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Install LAMP stack on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eldaniz/how-to-install-lamp-stack-on-ubuntu-20na</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eldaniz/how-to-install-lamp-stack-on-ubuntu-20na"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operating System: Ubuntu 20.04


To use PHP as your local server, you have to install the LAMP stack first. Also, there is XAMPP, I'll use LAMP to show the pure server-side in Linux. Firstly, you have to install Apache2 with dpkg package management system:
sudo apt-get update
sudo apt-get install apache2

Once the installation is finished, you have to update your firewall settings to allow HTTP(HyperText Transfer Protocol) traffic. UFW(Uncomplicated Firewall) has different application profiles that you can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eldaniz Babayev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ruby Unbundled Series: Services vs. Objects - The Battle for Decomposition and Reuse]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devgraph/the-ruby-unbundled-series-services-vs-objects-the-battle-for-decomposition-and-reuse-1em1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devgraph/the-ruby-unbundled-series-services-vs-objects-the-battle-for-decomposition-and-reuse-1em1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Darren Broemmer

Before finding a home with Ruby, I was a longtime Java developer almost from the very beginning of the language. So it certainly caught my attention when I read the opening line of this article by Ilya Suzdalnitski: “C++ and Java probably are some of the worst mistakes of computer science.” Part clickbait, part theme of picking on any language to entertain readers (none are perfect), and part truth.
Despite these mixed signals, the article’s primary thesis did resonate with me to a degre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevGraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ResizeObserver in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/salimchemes/resizeobserver-in-angular-4ke2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/salimchemes/resizeobserver-in-angular-4ke2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we will review how to implement ResizeObserver in Angular applications
What is ResizeObserver?
documentation
The ResizeObserver interface reports changes to the dimensions of an Element's content or border box, or the bounding box of an SVGElement.
So, our goal is know when our component is resized.
How can implement ResizeObserver in Angular?
ng-web-apis/resize-observer
The documentation is pretty clear, so let's start with an example to see how this library works.
First thing to do is to add …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salim Chemes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helm Rollback Command | How to use Helm Rollback Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jhooq/helm-rollback-command-how-to-use-helm-rollback-command-2dd3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jhooq/helm-rollback-command-how-to-use-helm-rollback-command-2dd3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this lab session, we are going to focus on how to use the "Helm rollback command". The rollback command is very useful if you want to go back to the previous revision of your helm chart. To roll back, you simply need to type the command - helm rollback your_release_name release_version and it will simply rollback to your previous version. 
Here are the main key areas which we will target in this session on "How to use Helm upgrade command?"
What is Helm rollback command?
Syntax of Helm rollback command?
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Wagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Laravel Bootstrap admin dashboard 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codedthemes/top-10-laravel-bootstrap-admin-dashboard-2021-2i25</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codedthemes/top-10-laravel-bootstrap-admin-dashboard-2021-2i25"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last few years, Laravel has gained popularity among the developer and user. It has the ability to easily and quickly facilitate complex processes like authentication, routing, and more. It simplifies the process of web development and helps you easily build powerful web applications. 
Laravel is one of the best options when you dealing with complex web projects. Currently, Bootstrap and Laravel is one of the trending technologies and merging both of them provides a highly interactive and feature-rich websit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CodedThemes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helm Upgrade Command | How to use Helm Upgrade Command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jhooq/helm-upgrade-command-how-to-use-helm-upgrade-command-3an7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jhooq/helm-upgrade-command-how-to-use-helm-upgrade-command-3an7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this lab session, we are going to see how to upgrade your helm chart with a new revision. This command is really useful when you want to make some changes to your exiting helm chart which is already deployed inside the Kubernetes cluster. Helm upgrade command ease out the pain of doing the manual update, you can simply run the command "helm upgrade" and it will fix everything for you.
Here are the main key areas which we will target in this session on "How to use Helm upgrade command?"
What is Helm upgra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Wagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Output Values | How to use Terraform Output Values?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jhooq/terraform-output-values-how-to-use-terraform-output-values-lae</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jhooq/terraform-output-values-how-to-use-terraform-output-values-lae"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform output values are a kind of return value from the terraform modules. The output values can be used to print the information onto the terminal as well as return it to other modules within the terraform
In this session we are going to look at Terraform Output values and how to use them inside your terraform files. 
How to declare terraform output values?
What are the benefits of terraform output values?
How to use print message on terminal using terraform output values?
Print aws ec2 instance public…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Wagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Locals | How to use Terraform Locals?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jhooq/terraform-locals-how-to-use-terraform-locals-a8n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jhooq/terraform-locals-how-to-use-terraform-locals-a8n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T10:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is OpenSource infrastructure as a code software tool. 
https://aws.amazon.com/), Google Cloud(https://cloud.google.com/), Azure(https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/), DigitalOcean(https://www.digitalocean.com/), OpenShift(https://www.openshift.com/) and many more...cloud provider
In this session we are going to look on terrafrom locals and how to use it inside your terraform files.
Improve your terraform file configuration
Terraform local helps you to centralized local varible configuration, so that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Wagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS interview in 2 minutes / Closure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kozlovzxc/js-interview-in-2-minutes-closure-3hi6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kozlovzxc/js-interview-in-2-minutes-closure-3hi6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T09:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question:
closures in JavaScript.
Quick answer:
function getCounter() {
    count = 0
    return function {
        count += 1
        return count
    }
}

Longer answer:
Higher Order Functions in JavaScript, which means you can create and return functions out of the functions. 
As we also know, functions can access each of their outer scopes.
function a() {
    let variable = "hello world"
    function b() {
      console.log(variable)
    }
    b()
}
a() // hello world

So what are closures? Closures ext…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to generate thousands of usernames and halfway decent passwords with Bash💯💯]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thormeier/how-to-generate-thousands-of-usernames-and-halfway-decent-passwords-with-bash-43m9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thormeier/how-to-generate-thousands-of-usernames-and-halfway-decent-passwords-with-bash-43m9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T09:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever needed, say, an astonishing number of user names and passwords? I recently did and thought to myself: "I can automate that!"
But, first of all...
Some tools use them a lot, especially for anonymous users: Positive adjectives together with animal names. For example: "Knowledgeable ibex" or... See, it's quite hard to come up with those, especially if English isn't your first language. I was thinking for a good 5 minutes and the ibex was the only example I could come up with. To be fair, I haven'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pascal Thormeier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Upload With Multer Node.js ad Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ndohjapan/file-upload-with-multer-node-js-ad-express-f1e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ndohjapan/file-upload-with-multer-node-js-ad-express-f1e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T09:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling file input from client in the server is a very important part of both web and software development. Ranging from handling profile images of your users to handling pdf documents containing any important info about your users.
For long, anytime a project got to the stage of receiving files from the client side, I saw it as strange. 
I tried avoiding it but I found out it was something I could not just run away from as a web developer.
In the post I showed everything you must know about file upload  i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Ndoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim, the best tool for Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/vim-the-best-tool-for-programmers-2j3k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/vim-the-best-tool-for-programmers-2j3k"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T09:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is the best text editor/IDE out there. It is the "editor of choice of old-time Unix hackers". 
Vim is one of the most popular programming editors out there. It's loved by geeks for its speed, extensive feature set, and flexibility.  
Vim is very powerful, and very efficient. It is fast, lightweight. It has been around for nearly 20 years, and when I'm editing text files on a remote server I always reach for vim first .
Vim can be used anywhere. In the terminal, in GUI (gvim) and inside your IDE (Jetbrai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types Of Frontend Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bibekkakati/client-side-rendering-vs-server-side-rendering-vs-static-site-generator-447n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bibekkakati/client-side-rendering-vs-server-side-rendering-vs-static-site-generator-447n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T08:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone👋
Technology has evolved in different ways and in the same way the concepts of building products or tools. Frontend web development is one of the domains which is changing rapidly with the growing community and requirements of faster development. Many libraries and frameworks have been introduced to the developers starting from jquery to react, angular etc. Every technology, concept, library and framework have its own pros and cons but they know how to stand out as per the requirement.
In thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bibek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I handled the scalability of the SQL database in Inspector]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inspector/how-i-handled-the-scalability-of-the-sql-database-in-inspector-1ene</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inspector/how-i-handled-the-scalability-of-the-sql-database-in-inspector-1ene"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T07:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm Valerio software engineer, CTO and founder at Inspector. In this article I’ll talk about what I learned trying to increase the operational limits of the Inspector SQL database.
Before talking about read-replicas or sharded-data, it might be helpful to introduce the problem to solve and the most common strategies to improve the ability of the database to process an increasing number of queries per second, opnenig up new growth margins for the application.
Why so many performance issues are caused by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Increase Productivity with Commands and Shortcuts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/increase-productivity-with-commands-and-shortcuts-cp8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/increase-productivity-with-commands-and-shortcuts-cp8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T07:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commands and shortcuts can boost your productivity 🔥 
If you are a developer, commands and shortcuts are everywhere. Knowing the commands and shortcuts saves you a lot of time.
As a programmer, you most likely use git or will have to use git. Git is a version control system that is often used to work with code. 
Vim, a programmers editor, heavily uses commands/shortcuts. The w to jump to the next word, b to jump backwards, / to search, d2w to delete two words and so on.
You probably have to learn SQL if yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vs-form: A schema-based form generator component for React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vsform/vs-form-a-schema-based-form-generator-component-for-react-p38</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vsform/vs-form-a-schema-based-form-generator-component-for-react-p38"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you write a lot of repetitive Code or do you think your code could be more straigthforward? It’s time to look at vs-form, a Form-Generator for React to easily build UI, especially Forms with the help of a schema.
You can try it out with our Online-Designer!
Why use vs-form ?
vs-form allows you to to define Forms in a declarative way with the help of a schema.
EASY TO USE


WRITE LESS CODE


EXTENDABLE


USING TAILWINDCSS


FLEXIBLE NESTING OF COMPONENTS


RESPONSIVE LAYOUT


BUILT-IN DATATABLES


TYPESCR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Thaler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Remove Unused Imports From Your JS Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/simondosda/automatically-remove-unused-imports-from-your-js-projects-202l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/simondosda/automatically-remove-unused-imports-from-your-js-projects-202l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T04:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by The Creative Exchange.
Recently, I came across a substantial Angular project with a lot of unused imports. Not that it is a big deal but it looked quite messy, which I find to be a pity as they can easily be automatically removed.
In this article, I will show you how to do so with any node-based project using ESLint. It might sound like a very cosmetic thing and it kind of is, but I believe having too many unused imports can really hurt code readability.
And as a bonus, we will also sort our import…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A web-manjaro-ui written in Vue3!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yunyuyuan/a-web-manjaro-ui-written-in-vue3-4hcn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yunyuyuan/a-web-manjaro-ui-written-in-vue3-4hcn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T03:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys,I have build a project recently: A simulating Manjaro Linux DE,hope you like it(I just beg some stars XD)
website: https://manjaro.halberd.cn

github: https://github.com/yunyuyuan/vue3-manjaro-ui]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>云与原</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A web-manjaro-ui written in Vue3!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yunyuyuan/a-web-manjaro-ui-written-in-vue3-4hcn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yunyuyuan/a-web-manjaro-ui-written-in-vue3-4hcn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T03:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys,I have build a project recently: A simulating Manjaro Linux DE,hope you like it(I just beg some stars XD)
website: https://manjaro.halberd.cn

github: https://github.com/yunyuyuan/vue3-manjaro-ui]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>云与原</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build Crypto Tracker Chart with React 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayeprahman/how-i-build-crypto-tracker-chart-with-react-4k9h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayeprahman/how-i-build-crypto-tracker-chart-with-react-4k9h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T00:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Coders 👩🏼‍💻,
Recently, I visit a crypto tracker site to check DogeCoin prices to see whether it going to the moon 🚀

I was curious about how to build a simplified version on that site using React, other libraries, and tools out there.
Here is the link to my cool 😎 project:
https://cryptotracker.ayeprahman.com/
So I did research to find which API to use and came across a free, reliable, and comprehensive API from the team 🦎CoinGecko.
At the same time, my goal also was to focus to find a low-level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arif Rahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing table filters between components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T23:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; The logic behind this is to pass the table filters as query params when exiting the table route and when trying to re-activate the table route add the {queryParamsHandling="preserve”} directive after the routerLink so that the query params would be preserved.
Introduction

After implementing filters, another issue that arises is how to identify previously applied filters after a component containing a table has been destroyed. Here is a use case: We have a component showing a list of customers in a ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyemade Oyemaja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing table filters between components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T23:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; The logic behind this is to pass the table filters as query params when exiting the table route and when trying to re-activate the table route add the {queryParamsHandling="preserve”} directive after the routerLink so that the query params would be preserved.
Introduction

After implementing filters, another issue that arises is how to identify previously applied filters after a component containing a table has been destroyed. Here is a use case: We have a component showing a list of customers in a ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyemade Oyemaja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically forwarding ports within an existing SSH connection]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rtyler/dynamically-forwarding-ports-within-an-existing-ssh-connection-nj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rtyler/dynamically-forwarding-ports-within-an-existing-ssh-connection-nj4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working over SSH on a big beefy remote machine is a great way to extend the life of any laptop, but presents challenges when developing network-based services. Fortunately OpenSSH has a "port forwarding" feature which has been around for a number of years. Port forwarding allows the user to tunnel a port from the remote machine back to their local machine, in essence allowing you to access a remote service bound to port 8000 on your own localhost:8000. When I first learned about this, I would fiddle around …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R. Tyler Croy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with AdonisJS and Inertia.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we'll build a simple CRM app utilizing an awesome tech stack consisting of:
React - React really needs no introduction, since it's the most popular front-end framework around.
Inertia.js - Inertia allows you to create fully client-side rendered, single-page apps, without much of the complexity that comes with modern SPAs.
Typescript - A strongly typed superset of ECMAScript.
AdonisJS - A fully featured web framework focused on productivity and developer ergonomics.
If I were inclined to nam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lev Eidelman Nagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with AdonisJS and Inertia.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we'll build a simple CRM app utilizing an awesome tech stack consisting of:
React - React really needs no introduction, since it's the most popular front-end framework around.
Inertia.js - Inertia allows you to create fully client-side rendered, single-page apps, without much of the complexity that comes with modern SPAs.
Typescript - A strongly typed superset of ECMAScript.
AdonisJS - A fully featured web framework focused on productivity and developer ergonomics.
If I were inclined to nam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lev Eidelman Nagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building custom DSLs in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matechs/building-custom-dsls-in-typescript-29el</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matechs/building-custom-dsls-in-typescript-29el"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T19:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do we even need custom domain-specific languages?
First of all, we should define what do we mean by custom domain-specific languages.
In everyday programming, we have to encode real-world problems in code. We are limited by the power of expressivity of the language we are using. The programming languages are fairly low when it comes to model the real world.
Basically, we translate from a human language to a more basic form of language that a computer can understand.
While translating, and for future ref…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Arnaldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Touch Touchpad Gestures on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamst0rm/multi-touch-touchpad-gestures-on-linux-362i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamst0rm/multi-touch-touchpad-gestures-on-linux-362i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T19:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to enable multi-finger gesture support on any Linux distro, be it Ubuntu, Pop!_OS, Fedora or Arch. Supports pinch-to-zoom in Chrome, Firefox & other browsers.
Go to Touchégg's Github Repo.


Scroll down a bit and you’ll see the Installation & Configuration instructions, which will guide you through rest of the process.



Tip: Restart your PC if gestures do not work right away.
Use Touché, the desktop application to configure Touchégg, by the same developer, so less compatibility issues (I found non…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paras Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SpringBoot CRUD  DynamoDB Example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb-example-14in</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb-example-14in"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://loizenai.com/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb/
Angular SpringBoot CRUD  DynamoDB Example
In the tutorial, I introduce how to create an "SpringBoot Angular  DynamoDB CRUD Example" with POST/GET/PUT/DELETE requests to SpringBoot RestAPIs.
Design overview system by Architecture Diagram that includes: Angular Client, SpringBoot RestAPIs, and  DynamoDB database.
Implement Angular CRUD Client with Angular built-in HttpClient to communicate with server side.
Implement SpringBoot RestAPIs that gets data fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Next.js + Strapi: Security first]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rubenmarcus/getting-started-with-next-js-strapi-security-first-3380</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rubenmarcus/getting-started-with-next-js-strapi-security-first-3380"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why worry about Security?


Before starting to see about Strapi's Content-Types, before looking at Next.js' file and route structure, it's good to discuss Security.
A concern that usually is not followed up with due attention in certain teams, and that can cause a very high cost, when a project is put into production.
This article is another introductory article to the Next.js + Strapi stack, we will also cover TypeScript, Data Fetch, Layouts, CI / CD and Deploy, but first of all we will cover security.
Bel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruben Marcus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[email setup help]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dupuyinsurance/email-setup-help-3f68</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dupuyinsurance/email-setup-help-3f68"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the manager of Dupuy Insurance, the owner gave me access to his agency email. Shame to write, I'm technological savvy, however I'm having trouble setting up an email. I've done it before, it was fairly simple, however for some reason I'm having a mental block.
The business website if it matters to you is https://dupuyinsurance.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dupuy Insurance</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nullish Coalescing support in Angular template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Devs, 
I am going to explain about Nullish Coalescing (??) . Few days back while reading release details about Angular 12 I just got to know about this new word and how to write cleaner code in typescript. So, now Angular 12 view template is supporting Nullish Coalescing(??)
Let's first understand the meaning of Nullish Coalescing (??). Then how it is supported in Angular 12 version view template. 
What is Nullish Coalescing (??) ? 
Nullish - means null or undefined
Coalescing - means combine (element…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avinash Dalvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes de Pipes e Services]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T04:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes Unitários


No post anterior falamos sobre o básico de testes, neste iremos iniciar os testes unitários das estruturas do Angular.
Estruturas que iremos testar:
Pipes
Services
Como mostrado no post anterior os testes de Pipes não tem segredo.
Sempre que possível, é interessante testar todas as possíveis variações dos valores de entrada (limites do domínio de entrada) para que não tenhamos nenhum caso não tratato, pois não saberemos quem poderá utilizar nossa Pipe.
Dado a pipe abaixo no arqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Egberto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Changing Page title Dynamically]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T03:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step 1. First we need to import Title service -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";

Step 2. Using setTitle -
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }

All together -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";
@Component({
 selector: 'app',
 templateUrl: './app.component.html',
 providers : [Title]
})
export class AppComponent implements {
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }
}






  
  
  Previe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physical Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love a good caper film. When I was a wee lad my father introduced me to The Great Train Robbery. Over the years I’ve seen several memorable others Rififi, A World Without Thieves, several by David Mamet like The Spanish Prisoner. Just the other day I watched Inside Man.
Numerous vulnerabilities like Spectre, Man-in-the-middle, SQL injection, keyloggers, phishing and a legion of others have loomed over the IT sphere for decades. Seems like every month there’s a new, “largest ever”, high profile security in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeikabu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parent child communication using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T21:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's very common in modern web development to handle the communication between the nearest components. The most obvious data flow is a parent to child. In this post, I'd like to show how to share the data between such components in both directions.
Passing the data down to the children's components is very easy.
app.component.html




<p>Item clicked {{ activeElement }}</p>
<div class="box__container">
  <app-box *ngFor="let box of boxCollection"
           [details]="box"
           [isActive]="box.name ==…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michał Muszyński</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SendGrid? SMTP Email Newsletter Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>609d63e962ab9107fe5aa2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sendgrid-smpt-email-newsletter-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of the term SMTP before, and wondered what it is. SMTP is a common method for handling email messages. Today I am going to explain what SMTP is, and how to use an SMTP provider such as SendGrid to send emails from your address. What Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🆔 Identity, Unlocked... Explained: Season 2, Ep 8]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🛡 JWT Profile for OAuth 2.0 Access Tokens with Vittorio Bertocci



  
  
  
In this episode of Identity, Unlocked, the CTO and co-founder of Auth0, Matias Woloski, appears as acting host and interviews Vittorio Bertocci, principal architect at Auth0 and the regular host of Identity, Unlocked, on the JWT profiles for OAuth2 access tokens specification. 
This spec describes how to encode OAuth2 access tokens in use JWT format in an interoperable way, by giving a minimal list of claims, how to emit a JWT dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React for Beginners: Complete React Cheatsheet for 2021]]></title>
        <id>609ea83362ab9107fe5aa920</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the React for Beginners guide. It's designed to teach you all the core React concepts that you need to know to start building React applications in 2021. I created this resource to give you the most complete and beginner-friendly path to learn React from the ground up. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 14th May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time waits for no one. It feels like yesterday since the last edition of this round-up only for me to check, and it's 2 weeks already, and I am like: Are you kidding me?
What more could I say? Let's move on.
Hopefully, I can keep track of time and I will be here next week to say: "Yeah I made it this week".
Introduction


This week it's everything security.
Foxit Reader bug lets attackers run malicious code via PDFs


Foxit Reader comes pre-installed on some laptop computers. If you (or anyone else) use Fox…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps -Automate & Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is the practice of integrating a security-first mindset and methodologies into traditional DevOps CI / CD environments. Here are key best practices for organizations seeking to implement DevSecOps.
Being able to get code out the door fast, secure, and efficiently is the name of the game. In a CI/CD environment, it’s important to maintain speed as the main tenet but also to be aware of the security needed to bulk up your pipeline. Without automation, implementing security practices could be a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Bhanushali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development for Beginners – Learn Basic HTML and CSS to Build Your First Web Page]]></title>
        <id>609e8c2162ab9107fe5aa77d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-development-for-beginners-basic-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites are built and designed? Do you want to learn the art of web development but you're not that tech savvy – yet? Well, then this tutorial is for you. It's an introduction to Web Development for beginners so you can learn the basics even if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-stylesheet-feature-flags-with-sass-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[!default is a Sass flag that indicates conditional assignment to a variable — it assigns a value only if the variable was previously undefined or null. Consider this code snippet:
$variable: 'test' !default;
To the Sass compiler, this line …
The post Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Babcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Boilerplates]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340403</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-boilerplates/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzović goes line-by-line through a boilerplate HTML document. I like it. It’s a good reference and has a lot of the same type of stuff I tend to put in the main HTML template. It makes me think about …
The post HTML Boilerplates appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340490</id>
        <link href="https://chenhuijing.com/blog/devtools-for-css-layouts-2021-edition/#%F0%9F%9A%B2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Hui Jing covers some recent movement in DevTools:
Firefox’s grid inspector was pretty full-featured from the get-to and released together with CSS grid in Firefox 52. It was constantly improved upon since. Chrome added a basic grid inspector 
…
The post DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340573</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2021-design-systems-survey-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friends at Sparkbox are doing a survey on design systems, as they do each year. Go ahead and fill it out if you please. Here are the results from last year. In both 2019 and 2020, the vibe was …
The post 2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Email Newsletter [2021 Tutorial] – Design, Layout, Send]]></title>
        <id>609414f32cd0545b5e943526</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-email-newsletter-design-layout-send/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T21:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a large community, chances are you need a way to communicate updates to your members quickly and efficiently. An email newsletter can be a very effective way to do so. In this article, I am going to provide some tips and suggestions for maximizing the impact and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? The 10 Most Common Types of Tests Developers Use in Projects]]></title>
        <id>609952396008950828b3ea8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and testing go hand in hand. And in the era of agile software development, with quick releases of small iterations, you should do testing more and more frequently.  In order to perform effective testing, you need to know about the different types of testing and when you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Tutorial – How to Work with Multiple Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>609bcc6a62ab9107fe5a9f08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-multiple-checkboxes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling multiple checkboxes in React is completely different from how you use regular HTML checkboxes. So in this article, we'll see how to work with multiple checkboxes in React. You will learn: How to use a checkbox as a Controlled Input in ReactHow to use the array map and reduce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340036</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/advanced-css-animation-using-cubic-bezier/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with complex CSS animations, there is a tendency to create expansive @keyframes with lots of declarations. There are a couple of tricks though that I want to talk about that might help make things easier, while staying in …
The post Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svgator-3-0-reshapes-the-way-you-create-and-animate-svg-with-extensive-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building animations can get complicated, particularly compelling animations where you aren’t just rolling a ball across the screen, but building a scene where many things are moving and changing in concert. When compelling animation is the goal, a timeline GUI …
The post SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339960</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-disabled-buttons-more-inclusive/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about disabled buttons. Specifically, let’s get into why we use them and how we can do better than the traditional disabled attribute in HTML (e.g. <button disabled> ) to mark a button as disabled.
There are lots of …
The post Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandrina Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-pie-timer-re-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitty reflected on an ancient blog post here on CSS-Tricks on how to make an animated pie timer. The old technique is still clever. The new technique is equally clever and much easier. I particularly like the steps() animation function…
The post CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I could build this during the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340186</id>
        <link href="https://world.hey.com/joaoqalves/i-could-build-this-during-the-weekend-aa093c5e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you heard that (or even uttered it under your own breath)? I know I’ve heard it in conversations. I also know I’ve wondered the same thing about a product or two — hey, the idea here …
The post I could build this during the weekend appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Gen CSS: @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-gen-css-container/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome is experimenting with @container, a property within the CSS Working Group Containment Level 3 spec being championed by Miriam Suzanne of Oddbird, and a group of engineers across the web platform. @container brings us the ability to …
The post Next Gen CSS: @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Una Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340106</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/distributed-persistent-rendering-dpr/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Jamstack, Netlify is coining this term.
If your reaction is: great, a new thing I need to know about and learn, know that while Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) does involve some new things, this is actually a push …
The post Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>