<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-15T00:55:14.201Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-15T00:55:14.201Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Mining is Killing All Free CI/CD Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/crypto-mining-is-killing-all-free-ci-cd-platforms-4chc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/crypto-mining-is-killing-all-free-ci-cd-platforms-4chc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T23:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know that crypto mining is negatively impacting many things in the world. And now it's ruining something else in a way no one has seen coming. This is why mining crypto currencies is killing every free CI / CD platform.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/9TOJqJSHVvI
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
Today I have to talk about something I'd prefer not to, but unfortunately this is happening, and it's happening hard. So let's talk about crypto mining and its deleterious effect on free CI/CD platform.
We all know crypto mining, the process in which transactions for various forms of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design Interview Tutorial – The Beginner&#x27;s Guide to System Design]]></title>
        <id>60873d1fdd38b9088c2c0842</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/system-design-interview-practice-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System Design is an important topic to understand if you want to advance further in your career as a software engineer. Even if you are just beginning your coding journey, it's a good idea to get a head start on learning about system design.  Early in your career you will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Pagination Component in React]]></title>
        <id>60bce373acb62507dd1d9f19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-pagination-component-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often work with web applications that need to fetch large amounts of data from a server through APIs and render it on the screen. For example, in a Social media application we fetch and render users' posts and comments. In an HR dashboard we display information about candidates who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Javascript to Rust to WASM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/starsoccer/from-javascript-to-rust-to-wasm-8ci</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/starsoccer/from-javascript-to-rust-to-wasm-8ci"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a while Ive been interested in not only Rust but WASM but having limited familiarity with many of the languages that can be compiled to WASM I never really had a chance to try it out until recently. Over the last few months though I got the opportunity to learn Rust.
Rust in my opinion is very much like typescript on steroids. While Typescript may enforce types in your code if you happen to pass a string to a type expecting a number things will still compile and may even work as expected still. With Rust this is not the case. If you provide an unexpected type either things will not compile in the first place or your software will crash. 
A personal project of mine (Cryptotithe) which is an open source tax software for cryptocurrencies was something I always though would benefit from WA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>starsoccer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-tables-with-sticky-header-and-footers-got-a-bit-easier/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago when I looked at sticky headers and footers in HTML <table>s in the blog post A table with both a sticky header and a sticky first column. In it, I never used position: sticky on …
The post Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explicit ESM in Node.js with .mjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bnb/explicit-esm-in-node-js-with-mjs-3ooh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bnb/explicit-esm-in-node-js-with-mjs-3ooh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, Node.js introduced support for ECMAScript Modules (ESM). ESM is the standardized modules implementation that's been built-in to JavaScript. This differs rather significantly from CommonJS (CJS), which is the module system that Node.js has shipped with for over a decade that make them relatively incompatible.
There are a number of different components of Node.js that have been intentionally structured to allow you to use standard (as in, how the ECMAScript Specification defines it) ESM by default and extend/augment that experience if you'd like to.
Today, I want to get into one of the baisc elements of ESM in Node.js: the .mjs and .cjs extensions.
.mjs (and .cjs)?



  
  
  The Quick Answer


The straightforward answer to this is that having different file extensions allows yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tierney Cyren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Try Resurface. Get a hat.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/resurface/try-resurface-get-a-hat-10fa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/resurface/try-resurface-get-a-hat-10fa"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What every API business needs is a system of record for their API calls – someplace Devs, DevOps, DevSecOps or PMs can go to quickly answer any question they have about your API traffic, even if no one knew they would have that question when you developed your application.
Try Resurface's free-forever version and we'll send you a cool Pepper the whale hat.  https://resurface.io/join-the-pod]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davidgoossen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Routing with Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shasheeshpurohit/routing-with-express-pag</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shasheeshpurohit/routing-with-express-pag"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might be familiar with routes if you've worked with node. Routes help us to organize our app in terms of separate modules. The bigger the app gets the more the number of routes, but then that's where the magic of EXPRESS comes in play.
What is express?
Express.js, or simply Express, is a back end web application framework for Node.js, released as free and open-source software under the MIT License. It is designed for building web applications and APIs.
Express provides you with a bundle of functions that help you to organize your code better and to focus more on what to do rather than worrying about how it's being done, that's the magic of all frameworks right?
So let's begin by writing our first ever express app and see how we can use the power of Express Router to organize and mainta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ShasheeshPurohit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Roving tabindex Attribute Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c3b862d3126007592d689b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-roving-tabindex-attribute-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever used the CSS order or direction properties? You've probably used them dozens of times, but did you realize that these properties will cause a disconnect between what's being displayed and what's actually in the DOM? Using the order property will create a disconnect between the visual presentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You could have invented lenses!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/safareli/you-could-have-invented-lenses-4ohe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/safareli/you-could-have-invented-lenses-4ohe"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have a JavaScript code like this:
const someObj = { tags: [], packages: [] };
function hasValue(key, item) {
  return someObj[key].indexOf(item) !== -1;
}

And you are porting this this into TypeScript. You are trying to follow best practices, like using strict mode. And don’t want to use any and unsafe casts. so you start adding types:
type SomeType = {
  tags: (string | number)[];
  packages: string[];
};
const someObj: SomeType = { tags: [], packages: [] };

This was easy, but then you hit one issue that you can’t really write type for hasValue without using some sort of casting. This is your best attempt:
function hasValue<K extends keyof SomeType>(key: K, item: SomeType[K]) {
  return someObj[key].indexOf(item) !== -1;
  //                   ^^^^
  // Argument of type 'Som…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irakλi Safareli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips To Increase Your Programming Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rezaulkarim/5-tips-to-increase-your-programming-productivity-50m0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rezaulkarim/5-tips-to-increase-your-programming-productivity-50m0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everybody. So today we are going to discuss about 5 tips to increasing programming productivity. Tip number one
Leverage The Power of Habit is to build productive routines. I asked you guys for book recommendations on Twitter and one of the books I got was The Power of Habit now, I actually started listening to the audio book of it and I thought it was really interesting because it helped me understand how I became more productive in the past years.

And now that I can pinpoint that it was because I was building A habit out of the things I want to be productive on that. I was able to make a routine and start cranking out code videos work stuff. You name it? Now essentially what you want to do is for the next 21 days do something every day. This could be coding flossing or whatever yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rezaul karim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Backup Squarespace-Managed Styles using AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>60c794e64dc1a607ed7b25ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-squarespace-managed-styles-using-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I was doing side gig for a client who had a website hosted on Squarespace. They asked me to implement an advanced design for a page that wasn't possible with the site's current DIY tools. For an experienced and battle-tested web developer like me, this was a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Básico pra começar com o Git - Primeira Parte]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigoscferraz/basico-pra-comecar-com-o-git-primeira-parte-ea7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigoscferraz/basico-pra-comecar-com-o-git-primeira-parte-ea7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antes de mais nada, todo esse guia é baseado no livro "Pro Git"(incluindo a fonte das imagens) que pode ser baixado na versão PDF aqui e na versão EPUB aqui. O livro é GRATUITO, então se você sabe inglês e quer se aprofundar mais esse é o caminho.
O Git é um VCS(Version Control System) utilizado amplamente para o processo de desenvolvimento de software. As ferramentas VCS registram as mudanças em um conjunto de arquivos e são responsáveis principalmente pela edição de arquivos por mais de uma pessoa "ao mesmo tempo", além disso também vem com ferramentas para resolver conflitos de versões e outras mais.
De maneira bem simplória o Git é uma espécie de Google Drive com versionamento. Diferente de outros VCS de mercado o Git trabalha com o arquivo completo para cada versão diferente criada ao…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Ferraz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert Express-Generator App To Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, in this article, I'd show you how to convert an express-generator app to Typescript. It's pretty straightforward we should be done in a flash so stick with me. This is my first ever write-up 😩 😩  , I hope you find a place in your heart to forgive my grammatical errors.😔 😔  

So, I started learning Typescript recently, and honestly, my life has been a lot easier ever since. Enough said, let's jump right in and start coding, shall we? 😎 
Firstly, go to your terminal and navigate to the directory where you'd like to create your express app, type npx express-generator, hit enter you should see a structure like this automatically generated for you.
├── app.js
├── bin
│   └── www
├── package.json
├── public
│   ├── images
│   ├── Javascripts
│   └── stylesheets
│       └── style.cs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emeka Okwor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert Express-Generator App To Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, in this article, I'd show you how to convert an express-generator app to Typescript. It's pretty straightforward we should be done in a flash so stick with me. This is my first ever write-up 😩 😩  , I hope you find a place in your heart to forgive my grammatical errors.😔 😔  

So, I started learning Typescript recently, and honestly, my life has been a lot easier ever since. Enough said, let's jump right in and start coding, shall we? 😎 
Firstly, go to your terminal and navigate to the directory where you'd like to create your express app, type npx express-generator, hit enter you should see a structure like this automatically generated for you.
├── app.js
├── bin
│   └── www
├── package.json
├── public
│   ├── images
│   ├── Javascripts
│   └── stylesheets
│       └── style.cs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emeka Okwor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best African Language Datasets for Data Science Projects]]></title>
        <id>60c4b35ed3126007592d71bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/african-language-datasets-for-data-science-projects/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Africa has over 2000 languages, but these languages are not well-represented in the existing Natural Language Processing ecosystem.  One challenge is the lack of useful African language datasets that we can use to solve different social and economic problems. In this article, I have compiled a list of African language]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-chronicle-xxxx/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a little link roundup of some off-site stuff I’ve done recently. As I’m wont to do from time to time. 
DevJourney Podcast
#151 Chris Coyier from ceramics to CSS-Tricks and CodePen‘
Chris took us from playing on 
…
The post CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does any one worked dicom viewer in angular?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/b5h_bharath/does-any-one-worked-dicom-view-viewer-in-angular-459j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/b5h_bharath/does-any-one-worked-dicom-view-viewer-in-angular-459j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by Bharath Kumar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bharath Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's how 108-year-old Liberty Mutual revamped its tech strategy to cut costs and release code 200 times faster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kyliebytes/here-s-how-108-year-old-liberty-mutual-revamped-its-tech-strategy-to-cut-costs-and-release-code-200-times-faster-fip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kyliebytes/here-s-how-108-year-old-liberty-mutual-revamped-its-tech-strategy-to-cut-costs-and-release-code-200-times-faster-fip"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks! I'm going to start posting my articles here so it's easy to find, sorta like a timeline - which I do on Twitter too.
Here's my latest: Here's how 108-year-old Liberty Mutual revamped its tech strategy to cut costs and release code 200 times faster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylie Robison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RocketList: I'm planning to build a collection of cloud actions for websites and wonder about your advice!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vladdekhanov/rocketlist-i-m-planning-to-build-a-collection-of-cloud-actions-for-websites-and-wonder-about-your-advice-12ge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vladdekhanov/rocketlist-i-m-planning-to-build-a-collection-of-cloud-actions-for-websites-and-wonder-about-your-advice-12ge"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, guys! A few days ago I've got an idea to build a list of cloud-based computing functions with useful and often-used features on web development.
After deep thinking, I made up 3 features for the first version of my project:
Sending an email


Scheduling a notification or webhook call


User list collections (Subscribers, future clients, and so on).



What do you think about the potential of the idea? Is it worth to be built?
P.S. In the link below you can see a small graphical content about this platform. Also if you wonder to track the state of the project, you can follow it there.
https://www.producthunt.com/upcoming/rocketlist]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vlad Dekhanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS API Gateway Best Practices in-depth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices


Forgive me, the Bart Simpson in me couldn't resist using 'Best Practices' once again. Sure, there's a lot to say to stamp out “best practice” and I agree with most arguments in the article. Framing something as a best practice is subjective, and it could give the impression of being arrogant. But, as grown-ups, I'm convinced most of us know how to deal with the term and see why it's used. So pick the practices you agree on, which you see as 'best' practices yourself.
I have the feeling that the importance of API Gateway in a setup is sometimes overlooked. AWS wrote down the practices themselves (also using the term 'Best practices 😉). But IMHO, their documentation is a tad too brief. Also, the documentation lacks a 'WHY' in general.
Assuming the vast majority of API Gatew…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gert Leenders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS API Gateway Best Practices in-depth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices


Forgive me, the Bart Simpson in me couldn't resist using 'Best Practices' once again. Sure, there's a lot to say to stamp out “best practice” and I agree with most arguments in the article. Framing something as a best practice is subjective, and it could give the impression of being arrogant. But, as grown-ups, I'm convinced most of us know how to deal with the term and see why it's used. So pick the practices you agree on, which you see as 'best' practices yourself.
I have the feeling that the importance of API Gateway in a setup is sometimes overlooked. AWS wrote down the practices themselves (also using the term 'Best practices 😉). But IMHO, their documentation is a tad too brief. Also, the documentation lacks a 'WHY' in general.
Assuming the vast majority of API Gatew…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gert Leenders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tree in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/qainsights/tree-in-linux-mpa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/qainsights/tree-in-linux-mpa"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tree in Linux


tree command helps to recursively list the directory and its details in a tree format. In this post, we will see how you can use tree effectively to view the directory details.
tree essentials in Linux


To install tree in Ubuntu, Debian Linux distros.
sudo apt-get install tree

To install tree in CentOS:
sudo yum install tree

In Windows, you can issue tree in Windows Terminal.
tree


If you enter tree command without any arguments, it will list out everything from the current directory recursively. Suppose, if you are in your home directory, it will display everything recursively like below.

man tree

.





tree -a

tree -d

tree -f

tree -L 1


tree -P b*


tree backups -P 'SMTP*'


'*' - any zero or more characters
'?' - any single character
'[...]' - any single character listed between brackets
'[A-Z]' - for range
'[^...]'- any single character not listed in brackets
'|' - separates alternate patterns
tree backups -I 'SMTP*'


If you use -P which matches both the directories and files. If the match is found for directories, then the matching is disabled for its contents. Use it with --prune to prune it.

To not to print the file and directory report, use --noreport.
tree bin -P '*.log' --prune --noreport 

tree bin -P '*.log' --prune -J

tree bin -P '*.log' --prune -X

tree bin -P '*.log' --prune -D

tree bin/ -P '*.properties' --prune -h


-F marks directories as * and / for files.
tree -P '*.jmx' --prune -F


It displays directories first over files. To disable, use -U.
tree -P '*.jtl' --prune --dirsfirst



In this post, we have covered frequently used tree commands. Please check my blog for more such tutorials.
💙 QAInsights YouTube Channel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NaveenKumar Namachivayam ⚡</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First DEV video😊]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madhubankhatri/my-first-dev-video-4off</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madhubankhatri/my-first-dev-video-4off"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is my first DEV video.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madhuban Khatri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcement: Azure cloud cost estimates in pull requests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/infracost/announcement-azure-cloud-cost-estimates-in-pull-requests-1mfe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/infracost/announcement-azure-cloud-cost-estimates-in-pull-requests-1mfe"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to our awesome community, I'm very excited to announce that you can now use Infracost to get cloud cost estimates for Microsoft Azure in pull requests. Try it now, it's free and open source!
Cloud costs for engineering teams
Cloud costs have become so complex that the industry (ourselves included) started addressing issues around breached budgets after the bill arrived. This is not the way it should be. It is like going shopping and having no idea how much things cost till after your card has been charged.
We are on a mission to empower engineering teams to use cloud infrastructure economically and efficiently. We do this by fitting in the developer workflow via CI/CD integration, reading the Infrastructure-as-code project, picking up the parameters that have a price point, looking …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Khajeh-Hosseini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/securing-your-website-with-subresource-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you load a file from an external server, you’re trusting that the content you request is what you expect it to be. Since you don’t manage the server yourself, you’re relying on the security of yet another third party …
The post Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari McMillian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick access to my last searches on Codever]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codever/quick-access-to-my-last-searches-on-codever-567</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codever/quick-access-to-my-last-searches-on-codever-567"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When looking for bookmarks or code snippets I recently used, I often find myself use the autocompletion capability of the search box to retrieve them. So over the weekend, I figured out since I do that, why not make it easier. So I did - I added sort of quick access to my last searches directly in the side menu on the landing page. See it in action below:

One tricky part was how to show the whole content of the search query when its length passes a certain limit. That meant when hovering over it, dynamically change the content of the html anchor a element. On top of that the list is dynamically generated out of the last searches. I like challenges and I described in How to change the content of an html element on hover in Angular how I implemented this.
Another interesting aspect of the implementation was how to dynamically set the background color of the displayed search queries - this is described with the snippets and post at Set css class dynamically in Angular from expression
👉 Codever is a bookmarks and snippets manager for developers & co. Give it a try and start saving time and nerves right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Matei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective React Query Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkdodo/effective-react-query-keys-25c5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkdodo/effective-react-query-keys-25c5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Query Keys are a very important core concept in React Query. They are necessary so that the library can internally cache your data correctly and refetch automatically when a dependency to your query changes. Lastly, it will allow you to interact with the Query Cache manually when needed, for example when updating data after a mutation or when you need to manually invalidate some queries.
Let's quickly have a look what these three points mean before I'll show you how I personally organize Query Keys to be able to do these things most effectively.
Internally, the Query Cache is just a JavaScript object, where the keys are serialized Query Keys and the values are your Query Data plus meta information. The keys are hashed it in a deterministic way, so you can use objects as well (on the top le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominik D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a lo-fi cafe for your Discord Server in 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heyayush/build-a-lo-fi-cafe-for-your-discord-server-in-5-minutes-1e4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heyayush/build-a-lo-fi-cafe-for-your-discord-server-in-5-minutes-1e4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog was originally published at my personal website 
I decided to have a chill voice channel where we all could sit together (virtually) and co-work while listening to a lo-fi audio stream and maybe have some occasional talks too.
We will be learning how to create a bot that automatically joins a voice channel whenever someone joins, starts broadcasting music & leaves after 5 minutes of inactivity. 
Do you need something cool like this in your own server?
TL;DR
here's the github code with one click deploy button for heroku, ready.
Less gooo 🥳
Prerequisites
NodeJS LTS  and VScode or IDE of your choice.
Pen
Pineapple
Apple
pen
Just kidding, let's setup the project now,
git init
npm init -y 
npm i -s discord.js dotenv ytdl-core-discord lodash

Go to Discord Developer Portal and create …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up Gulp On Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oyedeletemitope/setting-up-gulp-on-node-js-1082</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oyedeletemitope/setting-up-gulp-on-node-js-1082"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gulp is a cross-platform, streaming task runner that lets developers automate many development tasks. At a high level, gulp reads files as streams and pipes the streams to different tasks. The set tasks are code-based and use plugins.
If you’ve previously installed gulp globally, run npm rm --global gulp before following these instructions. For more information, read this
To verify that you have node.js installed, run
node --version

If it's not, follow the instructions here
You can choose to install gulp globally on your PC by running:
npm install --global gulp-cli

The above command will install gulp-cli globally and you will be able to run the gulp command anywhere, directly from your CLI/terminal.
To install gulp as a one-time dev-dependency in your project:
Let's go ahead and create a new project. The mkdir command creates a new folder: my-project, and the cd command navigates to this directory.
mkdir my-project
cd my-project

To get started, we will need to generate a new package.json which will contain basic information about our project, to do this run:
npm init

This will guide you through giving your project a name, version, description, etc.
npm install --save-dev gulp

gulp --version

Using your text editor, create a file named gulpfile.js in your project root with these contents.
function defaultTask(cb){
// place code for default task here
 cb();
}
exports.default= defaultTask

From your project directory, run the following command:
gulp

This command will automatically locate your gulpfile.js file and execcute it as a gulp task.
You can also run multiple task with gulp simultaneously by running:
gulp <path/to/task1> <path/to/task2>

In this article, we've been able to cover the basics of gulp and how to install it both globally, and also as a one-time devDependency.
Kindly share if you found this helpful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oyedeletemitope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor your Python application with full stack open source APM tool - SigNoz]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/signoz/monitor-your-python-application-with-full-stack-open-source-apm-tool-signoz-10n8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/signoz/monitor-your-python-application-with-full-stack-open-source-apm-tool-signoz-10n8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to check our Github repo before diving in 👇

The cost of a millisecond.
TABB Group, a financial services industry research firm, estimates that if a broker's electronic trading platform is 5 milliseconds behind the competition, it could cost $4 million in revenue per millisecond.
The cost of latency is too high in the financial services industry, and the same is true for almost any software-based business today. For Google, half a second delay in search results caused a 20% drop in traffic. Half a second is enough to kill user satisfaction to a point where they abandon an app's service.
While a user sees a screen, there are thousands of services in the background taking care of a user's request. In a microservices architecture, the challenge for engineering teams is to constan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Nayan ⚡</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS vs. PHP]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/nodejs-vs-php-3g54</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/nodejs-vs-php-3g54"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will start with the fundamentals for getting everything clear from the very beginning. First, we will talk about the basics of PHP and Node.js before comparing these 2. So, let us not waste time and go through this article from start to finish.
What exactly is Node.js?
Node.js, created and published by the reputed software engineer named Ryan Dahl in 2009, was initially compatible with only several selected OS like Mac OS X and Linux. At present, the latest version of Node.JS, 10.16.0, has been released.
Node.js happens to be amongst one of the most well-known and in-demand open-source back-end development environments, which have been written in C++, C#, plus JavaScript programming language, which has been built on the V8 JavaScript engine of Chrome. It is usually known to execute Java…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Benefits Of Taking Azure DevOps Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/christy129/top-10-benefits-of-taking-azure-devops-certification-20li</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/christy129/top-10-benefits-of-taking-azure-devops-certification-20li"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is the combination of two terms -Development and Operations. This is the prime requirement of the developers today due to its features comprising both the benefits. 
Microsoft Azure is a cloud based platform that provides testing, deploying, building and managing applications and services.
Azure DevOps is the platform that is Software as a Service(SaaS) platform that offers end-to-end DevOps toolchain in order to develop and deploy software. By using right mix of DevOps technologies, culture and process to get continuous software delivery and hence customer satisfaction. 
Microsoft's Azure DevOps course is available for professionals who are willing to learn and grow in their career in DevOps expertise. There are many benefits of doing this certification course in Azure DevOps. 
Azure pipelines- To implement CI/CD continuously build, test 
and deploy 
Azure artifacts
Azure boards- For Planning ,tracking and discussing among team
Azure repos
Azure test plans
1.You will learn basics of Azure DevOps.
2.Lern virtual networking skills and implementation through Azure 
3.You will get acceleration in your career. There opens many 
4.Career flexibility: Its very important for a person working in 
5.Better security : As the demand for cloud computing and Azure 
6.High salary and great perks: As per the reports a Azure 
7.Expert in DevOps skills : Along with Azure ,Candidate also get 
Better integration with .NET platform: As .NET platform is 
widely used by the programmers and also opensource, integrates 
easily with Azure, so developers need not go for any other 
cloud service provider to offer cloud integration for their 
coding platform.
Getting certified in Microsoft Azure DevOps platform will get you innumerable benefits as above and also it is a futuristic investment in your career. It is not going to diminish anytime soon as it is rapidly growing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christy129</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up React + TypeScript app from scratch without create-react-app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alekseiberezkin/setting-up-react-typescript-app-without-create-react-app-oph</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alekseiberezkin/setting-up-react-typescript-app-without-create-react-app-oph"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why bother if there is create-react-app?


Good question! In fact, if you are happy with create-react-app — just use it 🙂 But if you want to figure out how everything works together, let's combine all parts ourselves! 
/hello-react
  /dist
    index.html
    main.css
    main.js
    main.js.LICENSE.txt
  /src
    index.css
    index.tsx
  index.html
  package.json
  tsconfig.json
  webpack.config.js

Node.js installation steps depend on your system — just proceed to a download page and follow instructions.
npm doesn't need any installation because it comes with Node. If you wish to check that everything is properly installed on your system, follow these instructions.
Sidenote: npm is not the only package manager, there's also Yarn. If uncertain, I'd recommend staying with npm.
Create the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksei Berezkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitations on config updates]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohithv07/limitations-on-config-updates-1mc1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohithv07/limitations-on-config-updates-1mc1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sample Scenario


Is it possible to make any change to the config file which is having a kind: Pod and use kubectl to that file, well lets see what happens if we try to change the container port.
We are having a config file named client-pod.yml file.
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
metadata:
  name: client-pod
  labels:
    component: web
spec:
  containers:
    - name: client
      image: some image name
      ports:
        - containerPort: 3000

Now I update the containerPort field to 9999
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
metadata:
  name: client-pod
  labels:
    component: web
spec:
  containers:
    - name: client
      image: some image name
      ports:
        - containerPort: 9999

After changing the port and if we feed this config into kubectl, kubectl apply -f client-pod.yml, the output will be as follows :

Yes we will be getting an error saying we can't change the fields other than the fields mentioned in the terminal, so in our case we cannot change the container port.

    
Limitations on Updating Config file
    
Can only change spec.containers[*].image
    
Can only change spec.initContainers[*].image
    
Can only change spec.activeDeadlineSeconds
    
Can only change spec.tolerations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohith V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Terraform to make my many side-projects 'pick up and play']]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thundergolfer/using-terraform-to-make-my-many-side-projects-pick-up-and-play-aca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thundergolfer/using-terraform-to-make-my-many-side-projects-pick-up-and-play-aca"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform is an infrastructure-as-code technology providing a way to describe cloud infrastructure like AWS S3 buckets and SQS queues as code objects and manage the full lifecycle of that AWS infrastructure programmatically. It has very recently reached the 1.0 version milestone. Like git, learning Terraform is not easy and using Terraform is not fun, but it's so obviously better than alternatives that it has become a 'no-brainer' choice in my software engineering toolkit. I had to learn Terraform for work and use it extensively there, but I also now also put in the effort to use it from day one in any side project that runs in the cloud. 
thundergolfer/example-bazel-monorepo is a public repository where I have an infrastructure/ top-level folder with all the project's Terraform, and there…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathon Belotti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[☑️ HIPAA/HITECH: A Compliance Guide For Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/hipaa-hitech-a-compliance-guide-for-businesses-3c1m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/hipaa-hitech-a-compliance-guide-for-businesses-3c1m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📓 HIPAA and HITECH both provide legal guidelines for managing protected health information in the United States. Here is what businesses need to know to comply.


If your business processes protected health information (PHI) in the United States, you’ll need to familiarize yourself with both the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) and the Health Information Technology for Economic and Clinical Health (HITECH) Act.
Both pieces of legislation provide legal guidelines for managing PHI in the United States and come with strict penalties for violations. For example, two health care networks were fined $5.5M each in two of the worst violations in recent history.
However, each law manages and protects health data in different ways (and for different reasons). Below is a summary of what each law could mean for your business if it processes PHI in any format.

HIPAA and HITECH are two separate laws with two different goals:
HIPAA was passed in 1996 and was the first U.S. law to regulate how protected health information was managed. It introduced a set of security controls and privacy rights aimed at reducing fraud and waste in health care. HIPAA defined who was required to comply with its regulations (which HIPAA called “covered entities”) and how they were required to do so in order to protect health data.
The HITECH Act was passed in 2009 as part of the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA) to encourage HIPAA-covered entities to adopt electronic health records (EHRs) for managing PHI. It offered financial incentives from 2011 to 2015 to transition to EHRs and to improve the delivery of healthcare. The HITECH Act also introduced new technical security standards (in addition to a few other things below) that complement and enhance HIPAA as well.

Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up Vim for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrdestructive/setting-up-vim-for-python-ej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrdestructive/setting-up-vim-for-python-ej"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Vim is quite a powerful text editor which can add performance to the already fast typed language Python. Vim can be highly customizable and efficient to use as it has the power of adding custom plugins and plugins managers, key mappings, and the most critical weapon of vim - Access to the terminal straight away.
So let us start making Vim, the text editor suitable for a python programmer. Firstly we'll need the vim plugin manager. There are different plugin managers out there, each of them has the same purpose to install, upgrade and manage the plugins for vim. You can install any one of them and get up and running.
 Vim Plug 
 Vundle 
 Pathogen 
These are some of the finest and well-supported plugin managers in vim. You can use any of these plugin managers, and get started …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MeetGor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔴 TechTalk - How to become a Secure Developer in 2021 with Liran Tal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/destrodevshow/techtalk-how-to-become-a-secure-developer-in-2021-with-liran-tal-51gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/destrodevshow/techtalk-how-to-become-a-secure-developer-in-2021-with-liran-tal-51gf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 👋
I have started a LIVE TechTalk show on my channel.
And on the episode, Liran Tal joined as a Guest.
Liran is working as a Director of Developer Advocacy at Snyk and is a member of Node.js Foundation Security Working Group.
He shared some of the tips developers can use to make more secure software.
Topic: How to become a Secure Developer in 2021.
You can Watch on YouTube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1hczYOdrA_o




Enjoy 🌸
Also SUBSCRIBE to YouTube Channel - https://www.youtube.com/c/TheDestroDevShow?sub_confirmation=1
LIKE FB Page - https://www.facebook.com/the.destro.dev.show/
Follow on Twitter - https://twitter.com/destro_mas
Follow on DEV - https://dev.to/destro_mas
Made with ❤️ in Berlin!
Cheers!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahjada Talukdar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔴 TechTalk - How to become a Secure Developer in 2021 with Liran Tal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/destrodevshow/techtalk-how-to-become-a-secure-developer-in-2021-with-liran-tal-51gf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/destrodevshow/techtalk-how-to-become-a-secure-developer-in-2021-with-liran-tal-51gf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! 👋
I have started a LIVE TechTalk show on my channel.
And on the episode, Liran Tal joined as a Guest.
Liran is working as a Director of Developer Advocacy at Snyk and is a member of Node.js Foundation Security Working Group.
He shared some of the tips developers can use to make more secure software.
Topic: How to become a Secure Developer in 2021.
You can Watch on YouTube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1hczYOdrA_o




Enjoy 🌸
Also SUBSCRIBE to YouTube Channel - https://www.youtube.com/c/TheDestroDevShow?sub_confirmation=1
LIKE FB Page - https://www.facebook.com/the.destro.dev.show/
Follow on Twitter - https://twitter.com/destro_mas
Follow on DEV - https://dev.to/destro_mas
Made with ❤️ in Berlin!
Cheers!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahjada Talukdar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SCS-C01 Security Specialty Certification Recap Jun 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/talkncloud/aws-scs-c01-security-specialty-certification-recap-jun-2021-5c0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/talkncloud/aws-scs-c01-security-specialty-certification-recap-jun-2021-5c0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am fresh off the AWS Security Specialty exam for 2021 having successfully sat for the exam last week. What a doozy! I've 4 other AWS certifications and for me, personally I found this one to be the most challenging. I do practice security in my day to day to ensure I am building secure systems and enjoy discussing designs with security professionals but I'm not in a dedicated security team or SysOps role so I'm not living and breathing security everyday.
In this post I'll give you a run down on the exam, what you can expect on the day and what materials I used to prepare for the exam.
As usual the official AWS doco gives you the best info on the exam. It's basically an exam for security professionals (shocker), so, think security in transit, rest, shared responsibility model, users, desi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Web Development Frameworks to Use in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/agilecp/top-10-web-development-frameworks-to-use-in-2021-2ij7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/agilecp/top-10-web-development-frameworks-to-use-in-2021-2ij7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T08:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction:


There are multiple frameworks being invented for the purpose of simplifying the web development process. It helps increase flexibility and reduces launch time. Without frameworks, modern web development would not be possible as they need to create databases, security options, and various other things from the start.
In this blog, we are talking about, 

Angular was released in 2016 by Google. It is one of the most popular frameworks, and it is best suited for high-performance web and mobile apps as well as complex e-commerce projects. It is not a complete stack platform and can be used for front-end development for client-side applications. Angular uses Typescript front-end technologies, a JavaScript framework superset, along with HTML and CSS. 
It is used by companies like…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chandresh Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Recover Data from RAID 5 Based on NAS QNAP TS-412]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-data-from-raid-5-based-on-nas-qnap-ts-412-1cm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-recover-data-from-raid-5-based-on-nas-qnap-ts-412-1cm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T08:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you accidentally deleted some information, formatted the hard disk or realized your NAS device is out of order? Read this article to find out how to recover data from a RAID system based on NAS QNAP TS-412.

A QNAP NAS storage system consists of several hard disks. To improve resilience and data safety, such devices enable you to create RAID systems of various types. However, even the most reliable storage systems may encounter emergencies like accidental deletion of files, formatting or damaging the hard disk, system errors, controller failures and other hardware issues, which may result in loss of important data.

If NAS works properly and you just removed some important files by accident, you can try restoring them from the Network Recycle Bin.
YouTube: 



You can configure the Ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced TypeScript: A Generic Function to Merge Object Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fullstackchris/advanced-typescript-a-generic-function-to-merge-object-arrays-18ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fullstackchris/advanced-typescript-a-generic-function-to-merge-object-arrays-18ja"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is mirrored on my blog, chrisfrew.in
I just can't stop writing these generic functions! This is another powerful generic function that follows my previous post on building a generic function to update an array at a specific key according to a specific test value. As I try and maintain the cleanest codebase as possible for ReduxPlate, I continue to find new use cases for these easy-to-use yet powerful generic functions.
Often when doing state modifications, you want to merge or add some properties to an object that you get from an API or some other source. You could explicitly write key / value assignments for the keys that you want to update... or you can leverage JavaScript's built in Object.assign function and TypeScript's generic capabilities to only write one such function fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Frewin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mocking with MSW and Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/foxandxss/mocking-with-msw-and-nx-28ab</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/foxandxss/mocking-with-msw-and-nx-28ab"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are sitting in front of our new project and we need to start coding some new screens but the backend is just not ready yet. Isn't that familiar?
It is a good practice to have some sort of mocking mechanism so we can start coding as soon as we can and also make our unit testing less error prone by using well known data.
Yes, but that sounds overly complicated to achieve. We need to turn off and on the backend, swap modules around to enable or disable the mocking and be careful to not deploy any of that the production.
Well, not anymore.
MSW as they say, is the API mocking of the next generation. Right, but what does that mean? It works by intercepting requests on the network level or in other words, by using a service worker.
The interesting part is that it is invisible for us, developer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesús Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ways to convert String to Number in JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pankajpatel/ways-to-convert-string-to-number-in-js-4hdl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pankajpatel/ways-to-convert-string-to-number-in-js-4hdl"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Converting from one type to another (or simply called typecasting) is needed very frequently in any programming language. So is in JavaScript.
Today we are going to take a look at some of the ways to Typecast Strings to Number.
As the name suggests, parseInt the function parses the argument as Integer. Though parseInt is made to parse to String to different kinds of Integers like Decimal, Binary, Octal etc
With the above definition, parseInt accepts two parameters:
string: The value that needs to be converted to an integer
integer: The radix base number between 0 and 32



Examples:
parseInt('123', 10) // 123
parseInt('111', 2) // 7
parseInt('111', 8) // 73
parseInt('111', 9) // 91
parseInt('111', 10) // 111
parseInt('111', 16) // 273
parseInt('111', 32) // 1057
parseInt('111', 36) // 1333…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pankaj Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash the full power of angular-i18next]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adrai/unleash-the-full-power-of-angular-i18next-4b7o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adrai/unleash-the-full-power-of-angular-i18next-4b7o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk about internationalization (i18n) for Angular (not AngularJS, not Angular 2, just Angular 😉).
When it comes to JavaScript localization. One of the most popular frameworks is i18next. One of the most famous Angular extension for i18next is angular-i18next.
Sergey Romanchuk.
So first of all: "Why i18next?"
Let's get into it...


Prerequisites
Getting started
Language Switcher
Separate translations from code


How does this look like?
save missing translations
👀 but there's more...
🎉🥳 Congratulations 🎊🎁



i18next was created in late 2011. It's older than most of the libraries you will use nowadays, including your main frontend technology (angular, react, vue, ...).
➡️ sustainable
Based on how long i18next already is available open source, there is no real i18n case that coul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adriano Raiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux adding a timestamp to the bash history]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/linux-adding-a-timestamp-to-the-bash-history-4eej</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/linux-adding-a-timestamp-to-the-bash-history-4eej"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:07:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Linux systems, by default, the history does not include a timestamp, which can be annoying when you want to see when a command was executed to determine an update or some kind.
So today, I'll be showing you how to enable timestamps for the bash history in Linux.
Before we get started, let's look at how the history works and which files are attached.
The bash history is kept so we can retrieve whatever actions some user did.
To retrieve this history, we can type the following command.
history

It should come back with something that looks like this.

To find where this file is located you can run the following command.
echo $HISTFILE

It will generally come back with a location like:
/root/.bash_history

However, to change the history output, we have to make a change in the configuration settings.
These configuration settings are set in a file called .bashrc.
We need to add the HISTTIMEFORMAT config settings, which will change the output.
There are two ways to include this in your .bashrc file.
Manually open the .bashrc file and paste it in.
Echo it into the file.




# method 1
nano ~/.bashrc
# now paste:
export HISTTIMEFORMAT="%F %T "

# method 2
echo 'export HISTTIMEFORMAT="%F %T "' >> ~/.bashrc

The format we are using includes the %F and %T variables which stand for:
%F: full date (year-month-day)
%T: time (hour:minute:seconds)
Now you won't see the change yet. We have to enable it, which we can do by rebooting or simply running this command:
source ~/.bashrc

Now when we run the history command, we should see something like this.

As you can see, we now have timestamps in front of our history!
Thank you for reading my blog. Feel free to subscribe to my email newsletter and connect on Facebook or Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django Defense Against Bot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-defense-against-bot-42ib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-defense-against-bot-42ib"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T05:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post, I talked about how we could implement a simple trick to stop bot from continuing to submit a form in our web app. However like I told you, this might not be enough to keep all the bot from doing harm to our website. How to make it better? well another simple way is to implement a ReCaptcha. ReCaptcha is a relatively simple tool to identify if a web form in our site is being submitted by a human being or a robot. For this implementation ReCaptcha, a package called django-recaptcha.
Before we can start using google ReCaptcha Api, first we need to register our application with google. I would propose to use Google ReCaptcha V3.
click on this link Google ReCaptcha Admin, and fill in the required information

click the submit button and copy your public and private api key…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashrafZolkopli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Checklist 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codecrafttechnologies/security-checklist-1-14k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codecrafttechnologies/security-checklist-1-14k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T05:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agile methodologies and DevOps are widely adopted by many software service providers and consulting companies. The primary driver for this adoption being, faster delivery of products, independent teams, and generally better all-around synergy between the engineering and operations team.
In this DevOps and Agile world, the traditional modes of quality assurance, like manual testing, are not as effective when it comes to quality assurance. Granted, risk analysis, test planning, and test management are still important, but to ensure the same level of quality in an Agile world as before, or even better, organizations are using new skills such as test automation, data analytics, and AI technologies amongst others.
In this two-part blog(IInd part coming soon), we provide an example of such an ad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Codecraft Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google sheets API and Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/siddharth151199/google-sheets-api-and-node-js-3558</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/siddharth151199/google-sheets-api-and-node-js-3558"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T04:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Everyone! 
First create new folder node-googlesheets and open terminal in that directory and write a command
npm init
Hit the enter to given questions. Now install the packages that we need.
npm i googleapis google-auth-library express
Now create a new file named index.js and require the packages
const express = require('express');
const app = express();
const {GoogleAuth} = require('google-auth-library');
const {google} = require('googleapis');

app.get("/",(req,res) =>{
    res.send("hello world")
})

app.listen(3000,(req, res) =>{
    console.log("running on server");
})

Now its time to enable google sheets api. click on this Link. Sign in using your google account. you will redirect to this home page.

Now click on select project on top left corner.


Now you need to enable google…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siddharth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working With DynamoDB, AWS NoSQL Workbench, and Node.JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/josuebustos/working-with-dynamodb-aws-nosql-workbench-and-node-js-42eh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/josuebustos/working-with-dynamodb-aws-nosql-workbench-and-node-js-42eh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T03:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this tutorial, I will show you how to set up a locally-hosted DynamoDB server, use the AWS NoSQL Workbench to insert data into DynamoDB, and finally, create a simple Node.JS project that will query sample data provided by AWS NoSQL Workbench.
This tutorial assumes you're comfortable executing terminal commands, navigating, and modifying the macOS and Ubuntu Linux file system. 
My setup is a hybrid environment consisting of a Host, macOS Catalina, and a Guest Ubuntu VM instance. But You can set up everything on one host, macOS, Ubuntu, or Windows.
To follow along, you will need the following already installed:
On Ubuntu (Guest) or Host:
Docker
Docker Compose
Node.js
On MacOS (Host):
Ubuntu 20.04.2 VM instance
Okay, let's get started! :) 
Let's get the simple stuff out of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josue Bustos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Common Causes of Partition Loss and Data Recovery Methods to Use]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/most-common-causes-of-partition-loss-and-data-recovery-methods-to-use-42am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/most-common-causes-of-partition-loss-and-data-recovery-methods-to-use-42am"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T20:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we list the most common causes of partition loss and suggest how to avoid it. Also, we will tell you what to do if a partition is lost, and how to recover important files and folders.

Reinstalling your favorite operating system or changing to another one, accidentally removing a partition from the hard disk, taking a wrong step while working in a partition manager utility, hardware issues, bad blocks – these are only a few things that may cause partitions to become unreadable. The main cause behind partition loss is logical errors in partition tables.
A partition table is a special system file containing settings that contain information about the hard disk drive’s partitions, including the beginning and the end of the disk, the file system, the name, size and many other …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate React Native Boilerplate with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joeygoksu/the-ultimate-react-native-boilerplate-with-typescript-3778</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joeygoksu/the-ultimate-react-native-boilerplate-with-typescript-3778"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T18:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The template for React Native that includes all you need to build amazing projects 🔥
📱 React Native — version 0.64.0
🎉 TypeScript - Type checking
📏 ESLint — Pluggable JavaScript linter
💖 Prettier - Opinionated Code Formatter
🌘 Dark Mode - Support dark mode
🌆 UI Kit - Beautiful UI
⚙️ RN Dotenv Environment variable with RN env

👉 Let's try: https://github.com/joeygoksu/LightReactNative
🌸 Built with template
Vocabulary Builder App
Animal Finder Game]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Goksu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create simple voice chat app with nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-simple-voice-chat-app-with-nodejs-1b70</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hosseinmobarakian/create-simple-voice-chat-app-with-nodejs-1b70"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T17:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm Hossein in this article we will build a simple voice chat web application with nodejs and socketIo.
npm init -y

After installing dependencies, create and open index.js file and put codes below into it:
const express = require("express");
const app = express();
const handlebars = require("express-handlebars");
const http = require("http").Server(app);
const io = require("socket.io")(http);

//To holding users information 
const socketsStatus = {};

//config and set handlebars to express
const customHandlebars = handlebars.create({ layoutsDir: "./views" });

app.engine("handlebars", customHandlebars.engine);
app.set("view engine", "handlebars");

//enable user access to public folder 
app.use("/files", express.static("public"));

app.get("/home" , (req , res)=>{
    res.render("inde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>h_mobarakian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshoot — Cannot reach Destination server (Permission Denied)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/troubleshoot-cannot-reach-destination-server-permission-denied-2jml</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/troubleshoot-cannot-reach-destination-server-permission-denied-2jml"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T16:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scenario
You are using nginx and trying to call the downstream application but it returns http 502.
Cause
The reason could be because SELINUX would have blocked certain port. You can check the logs for more details.
Steps
The following example is from a sample repo whereby the downstream application uses port 801 and 802.
1) Check the ngnix logs — /var/log/ngnix/error.log
From here you will be able to see the error “permission denied”

2) Check the audit log — /var/log/audit/audit.log
Command:
sudo cat /var/log/audit/audit.log | grep nginx | grep denied


3) Check the ports that are allowed.
Command:
semange port -l | grep http


4) You can allow them for testing if it’s a legit request. 
Command:
semanage port -a -t http_port_t -p tcp 801]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ng-magical directives series (ng-template)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T16:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic is just science that we do not understand yet
...Arthur C. Clarke
This article is part of what I call the magical directives series. In this series, we will unravel the mystery behind some interesting Angular directives. Afterwards, we can add this little magic to our tool box. I call them magical directives because they play a very important role in building reusable components across our Angular applications.
Below are the directives that we will be looking at in this series.
ng-template
ng-container
ng-content
*ngTemplateOutlet
The ng-template directive simply represent an Angular template. Angular uses the ng-template under the hood in our structural directives( *ngIf, *ngFor) and ngSwitch. The ngSwitch controls the structural directives (*ngSwitchCase and *ngSwitchDefault ) and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Awe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ng-magical directives series (ng-template)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T16:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic is just science that we do not understand yet
...Arthur C. Clarke
This article is part of what I call the magical directives series. In this series, we will unravel the mystery behind some interesting Angular directives. Afterwards, we can add this little magic to our tool box. I call them magical directives because they play a very important role in building reusable components across our Angular applications.
Below are the directives that we will be looking at in this series.
ng-template
ng-container
ng-content
*ngTemplateOutlet
The ng-template directive simply represent an Angular template. Angular uses the ng-template under the hood in our structural directives( *ngIf, *ngFor) and ngSwitch. The ngSwitch controls the structural directives (*ngSwitchCase and *ngSwitchDefault ) and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Awe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install python37 on RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aklm10barca/install-python37-on-rhel-3kc0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aklm10barca/install-python37-on-rhel-3kc0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T16:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Setup
Check the enabled repos.




yum repolist all

Make sure the below two are enabled.




yum-config-manager — enable ‘rhel-7-server-rhui-optional-rpms*’
yum-config-manager — enable ‘rhel-server-rhui-rhscl-7-rpms*’

Install python3.7




yum install rh-python37

(note: currently RHEL 7.7 only got rh-python36)
The pip package will be installed on the following location




/opt/rh/rh-python36/root/usr/bin/pip

Reference:
https://developers.redhat.com/blog/2018/08/13/install-python3-rhel/#full-install]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Commands/Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/useful-commands-solutions-19ch</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/useful-commands-solutions-19ch"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T15:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1). Simulate external response using shell2http
If you need a quick way to simulate / fake external server response, then shell2http is an easy way to simulate the response.
Example:
shell2http -cgi /call1 'cat 1.json' /call2 'pwd'

Reference:
[https://github.com/msoap/shell2http]
(2). DNS server issues in RHEL
Problem Statement
When adding static DNS servers in /etc/resolv.conf file, entries disappear after a server reboot or network service restart.
Solution
After adding static DNS servers entries in /etc/resolv.conf, do the following which will make file immutable.




> chattr +i /etc/resolv.conf

The below also might work as per the below reference.
Adding PEERDNS=no in /etc/sysconfig/network-scripts/ifcfg-eth0

Adding RESOLV_MODS=no in /etc/sysconfig/network-scripts/ifcfg-eth0

Refe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a GraphQL API with TypeScript, AWS AppSync, and CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/build-a-graphql-api-with-typescript-aws-appsync-and-cdk-1jbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/build-a-graphql-api-with-typescript-aws-appsync-and-cdk-1jbg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T15:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What We’re Building


Previously, I had used AWS SAM to build a CRUD app for notes. Recently, I wanted to learn more about the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK), GraphQL, and AWS AppSync, so I decided to refactor my original project.
Disclaimer that at the time of writing the CDK v2 is in developer preview. This blog post will use CDK v1.
If you want to skip ahead, take a look the finished project here.
If this is your first time using the CDK, bootstrap your AWS account. The Prerequisites section in this guide has the steps.
Start by installing the CDK npm package and running the cdk init command. This is helpful because it gives you a directory structure along with a very minimal stack to get started.
On top of the initial scaffolding in /lib/note-service-stack.ts let’s add some extra impo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danielle Heberling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cariddi released!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/edoardottt/cariddi-released-2j51</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/edoardottt/cariddi-released-2j51"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T14:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://github.com/edoardottt/cariddi
Take a list of domains and scan for endpoints, secrets, api keys, file extensions, tokens and more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gilfoyle97</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More .NET Core Apps on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobrundle/more-net-core-apps-on-linux-323i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobrundle/more-net-core-apps-on-linux-323i"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T14:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my first post on this subject, I demonstrated how to develop a simple console app on windows and get it running on Linux with unit tests.  In this post I will expand on the previous post and show how Linux-specific and Windows-specific code can be developed and unit tested.  In addition I will take a look at xUnit test fixtures, Windows ACLs and Linux file permissions.
As in the last post, the approach is to develop code on Windows and test in Linux containers.  So on your windows dev box the set up you need is Hyper-V and Docker. 

Also needed are the dotnet CLI and VS Code for this optimum (in my view) setup.

All the code for this tutorial can be found at https://github.com/bobrundle/dotnettolinux2
What I want is to create an API to test read and write access of files and folders.  T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Rundle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to enable SELinux boolean values]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-enable-selinux-boolean-values-5h8g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-enable-selinux-boolean-values-5h8g"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T14:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem:
If Apache DocumentRoot is not the default /var/www/html, it could be a NFS/EFS share. 


Then you might encounter “Permission denied for Apache HTTPD” error when accessing the site.



Solution:
Check your DocumentRoot setting to confirm it is not the default by running below command.




grep -i ‘DocumentRoot’ /etc/httpd/conf/httpd.conf

In output, you might see the DocumentRoot location as “/data/docs/demo” (this is a NFS share)


By default NFS share access will be denied. This can be confirmed by running below command.




getsebool -a | grep httpd_use_nfs

It will give result “httpd_use_nfs → off”


To enable it, run the command,




sudo setsebool -P httpd_use_nfs 1

You can see now "httpd_use_nfs →.on"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install Qualys Cloud Agent on Linux/Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-install-qualys-cloud-agent-on-linux-windows-3gjg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/how-to-install-qualys-cloud-agent-on-linux-windows-3gjg"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T14:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) / Amazon Linux
Download the latest Qualys Cloud Agent installer from below.
[https://qualysguard.qualys.com/am/help/sensors/cloud_agent.htm]
Perform installation with the following command:




sudo rpm -ivh qualys-cloud-agent.x86_64.rpm

Activate Qualys Cloud Agent with the following command:




sudo /usr/local/qualys/cloud-agent/bin/qualys-cloud-agent.sh ActivationId=1032h37-dd20-4fde-93c8-2q3dwedae34 
CustomerId=aa9845nb0-6643-5564-8045-1234wsDDAS

Update Qualys Proxy setting and restart the service.




echo "qualys_https_proxy=\"http://<proxy-url>:1080\"" > /etc/sysconfig/qualys-cloud-agent
systemctl restart qualys-cloud-agent

For troubleshooting -> log path in Linux environment




/var/log/qualys/qualys-cloud-agent.log

Ubuntu
Download the latest Qu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patching Vulnerable Instances]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/patching-vulnerable-instances-1lkj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/patching-vulnerable-instances-1lkj"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T14:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Useful commands
Run the below command at instance level to check security vulnerabilities




yum check-update — security — sec-severity=important,critical

Note:
The below command will fetch different results (‘I’ instead of ‘i’)
yum list-security — security — sec-severity=Important 

Run the below command to update the missing packages in the instance or Run the AWS-RunPatchBaseline document using SSM Run Command




sudo yum update-minimal — sec-severity=critical,important — bugfix

Again check for vulnerability of the instance by running the below command.




yum check-update — security — sec-severity=important,critical

To check for missing updates and patches/Vulnerability on the target managed instance.




yum list-security — security — sec-severity=important,critical — bugfix

How Patch manager works:
[https://docs.aws.amazon.com/systems-manager/latest/userguide/patch-manager-how-it-works-installation.html]
Running patch using cli:
[https://docs.aws.amazon.com/systems-manager/latest/userguide/sysman-patch-cliwalk.html]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django-Honeypot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-honeypot-3p93</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-honeypot-3p93"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T10:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made it so we can catch bad guys that try to access our Admin site, but not how about we make so that all of our site form able to catch the bad guy? Sound like a cool proposal right.
Usually, attacker will use a bot to try and crack our web app. One solution is to also include a honeypot everywhere there is a form. This will not deter all of the bot but adding that extra layer of security will not hurt right. Honestly, so far we made it so that we have incremental security measure in place. 
I think this is where I should say that, in security terms, there is nothing that is truly secure but we need to just slowdown the attack as much as we can to the point it doesn't make any sense for the attacker to continue. 
pipenv install django-honeypot
pipenv lock -r > requirements.txt

INSTALLED_APPS = [
    #...

    # django-honeypot
    'honeypot',
    #...
]

if you want to activate the honeypot web app wide, the easiest way was to use a middleware provided by django-honeypot
MIDDLEWARE = [
    #...

    # Django-honeypot
    # https://pypi.org/project/django-honeypot/
    'honeypot.middleware.HoneypotMiddleware',

    #...
]

lastly add this variable to your settings.py file
# Django-honeypot
# https://pypi.org/project/django-honeypot/
HONEYPOT_FIELD_NAME = "secret_key"

As of right now I feel that we made our web app a bit safer. I'm not gonna say that our code is safe from any bot attack but at least the normal to medium type bot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashrafZolkopli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Development on VS code and Docker using Remote Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srinivasarajui/angular-development-on-vs-code-and-docker-using-remote-containers-5a1a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srinivasarajui/angular-development-on-vs-code-and-docker-using-remote-containers-5a1a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code  with Remote Containers extension will help us develop with in container. More details are here
I decided to try angular development using VS Code Docker containers. This is my Journey Hope it helps others.
prerequisite:
Docker
VS Code with Visual Studio Code Remote - Containers
Start VS code in a brand new folder(say AngularOnRC). Open Command palette by pressing F1. Follow this naviation.

Select Remote-Containers: Add Development Container Configurations Files..
Select Nodejs & Typescript
Select node version as 16.
This will add files in .devcontainer and the VS code will prompt to restart in Docker Container. Restart in docker container.(If you miss the prompt you use command Palette for the same)
Once the Project starts in Container(starting may take some time). Open the termi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srini Raju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi 4 : quick review]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/8bitsouvik/raspberry-pi-4-quick-review-59o7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/8bitsouvik/raspberry-pi-4-quick-review-59o7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T09:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the month of June of 2019 raspberry Pi foundation introduced a new model of SBC(single board computer) named 'Raspberry Pi 4 (model B)',  which was 50% more powerful and 30% more efficient than its previous version. this was one of among most powerful ARM devices in the first two decades of 21st century.
Spec.: 

         RAM: 1GB/2GB/4GB/8GB (DDR4)
         CPU: 4 cores (64-bit ARM cortex A72)
         GPU: VideoCore VI
         Clock Speed: 1.5gHz
         Storage type: micro SD card, USB(external)
         Wireless connectivity: bluetooth 2.4/5 gHz, Wifi 802.11ac

 I/O: 
 


         2x USB type-A (3.0)
         2x USB type-A (2.0)
         1x USB type-C 
         1x Ethernet port (RJ-45)
         2x micro HDMI
         1x headphone jack (3.0)
         1x CSI connector
         1x DS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Souvik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to implement an inline styles Content Security Policy with Angular and Nginx]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferdiesletering/how-to-implement-an-inline-styles-content-security-policy-with-angular-and-nginx-2ke2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferdiesletering/how-to-implement-an-inline-styles-content-security-policy-with-angular-and-nginx-2ke2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T09:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


We want to make our applications as safe as possible, so we implement a content security policy(CSP) to mitigate Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attacks or Click Jacking.
The demo application contains an ngx-bootstrap toggle and a Angular Material slider component.
application

Let's implement a CSP header. More information about CSP.
<meta http-equiv="Content-Security-Policy" content="default-src 'self'">

The result is that our application doesn't look the same anymore.
application

Due to our CSP policy, the browser blocks all inline styling that comes from an untrusted source.
console.log

Angular Material and ngx-bootstrap styles are added with the styleUrls property. Angular will parse the component's styling and add them to the 
 of the page. Based on the ViewEncapsulation proper…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ferdie Sletering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to implement an inline styles Content Security Policy with Angular and Nginx]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferdiesletering/how-to-implement-an-inline-styles-content-security-policy-with-angular-and-nginx-2ke2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferdiesletering/how-to-implement-an-inline-styles-content-security-policy-with-angular-and-nginx-2ke2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T09:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


We want to make our applications as safe as possible, so we implement a content security policy(CSP) to mitigate Cross Site Scripting (XSS) attacks or Click Jacking.
The demo application contains an ngx-bootstrap toggle and a Angular Material slider component.
application

Let's implement a CSP header. More information about CSP.
<meta http-equiv="Content-Security-Policy" content="default-src 'self'">

The result is that our application doesn't look the same anymore.
application

Due to our CSP policy, the browser blocks all inline styling that comes from an untrusted source.
console.log

Angular Material and ngx-bootstrap styles are added with the styleUrls property. Angular will parse the component's styling and add them to the 
 of the page. Based on the ViewEncapsulation proper…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ferdie Sletering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to version control Cloud?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heldsteel7/do-you-version-control-cloud-28ah</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heldsteel7/do-you-version-control-cloud-28ah"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T07:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arguably version control is among the biggest innovations in software engineering. 
Version control or revision control as it is called gives an immense power to the developers while developing the complex systems. Version control allows developers to keep the working pieces of the system available. Specifically version control allows critical capabilities such as reproducibility, traceability. 
Reproducibility is like a magical wand which helps to create identical systems no matter how complex the system itself is. 
Traceability helps developers to pick up any environment and track its dependencies. Traceability also helps to pick up any two versions of the environment and find out differences, if any. 
Advantages offered by reproducibility and traceability are already well understood by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>heldsteel7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Core types]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/debugger333x/core-types-23lo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/debugger333x/core-types-23lo"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T06:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey peeps!



  
  
  The following is a blog on core types in typescript that are not there in JavaScript for beautiful devs. You should have  a proper knowledge of 'vanilla' JavaScript.



  
  
  The following are the steps to setup the dev environment {


• install node 
to compile the file and automatically you should have a JavaScript file created 
• enables you to add multiple values in one variable


• allows you to add multiple core types


 • enum helps you delaring set of named constants


}


  
  
  Nice!



  
  
  Now you know all the core types!



  
  
  So yeah that's it for now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>debugger333X</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[deploying node.js on digital ocean with pm2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ajcwebdev/deploying-node-js-on-digital-ocean-with-pm2-4hhm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ajcwebdev/deploying-node-js-on-digital-ocean-with-pm2-4hhm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T01:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless deployment is becoming easier and easier every year, but there will always be a subset of use cases that require a persistent, running server.
Projects with stricter requirements around performance, computation, storage, concurrency, and isolation may opt for a more traditional deployment strategy and host a Linux server.
In this tutorial we will deploy a Node.js application on Digital Ocean with PM2.
Create a Node.js app
Configure Node.js app for PM2
Deploy Linux server on Digital Ocean droplet
Setup SSH keys
Install Node.js, Git, and PM2
We will generate a simple Node.js application.
mkdir ajcwebdev-pm2
cd ajcwebdev-pm2
yarn init -y
touch index.js

If we look at our package.json file in the root of our project we will see:
{
  "name": "ajcwebdev-pm2",
  "version": "1.0.0",
  "…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anthony-campolo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typing effect in React with typed.js and hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shareef/typing-effect-in-react-with-typed-js-and-hooks-5bl2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shareef/typing-effect-in-react-with-typed-js-and-hooks-5bl2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Developers 🤩🤩🤩


Let's admit it typing effect looks cool and the good news is we can achieve it without any pain 😜.
    npm install typed.js
    or
    yarn add typed.js
    or
    bower install typed.js

Let's dive into the code.





import Typed from "typed.js";
import { useEffect, useRef } from "react";

export default function App() {
  // Create Ref element.
  const el = useRef(null);

  useEffect(() => {
    const typed = new Typed(el.current, {
      strings: ["Handy", "Mandy", "Candy", "More Strings"], // Strings to display
      // Speed settings, try diffrent values untill you get good results
      startDelay: 300,
      typeSpeed: 100,
      backSpeed: 100,
      backDelay: 100
    });

    // Destropying
    return () => {
      typed.destroy();
    };
  }, []);

  return (
    <div>
      <h1>Hello Developers</h1>
      {/* Element to display typing strings */}
      <span ref={el}></span>
    </div>
  );
}


Kaboom🔥🔥🔥 with just some lines of codes we achieve a lot thanks to typed.js
Custom cursor.
Loop.
Smart backspace





    ...
  useEffect(() => {
    const typed = new Typed(el.current, {
      strings: ["Handy", "Mandy", "Candy", "More Strings"], // Strings to display
      // Speed settings, try diffrent values untill you get good results
      startDelay: 300,
      typeSpeed: 100,
      backSpeed: 100,
      backDelay: 100,
      smartBackspace: true,
      loop: true,
      showCursor: true,
      cursorChar: "!"
    });

    // Destropying
    return () => {
      typed.destroy();
    };
  }, []);
    ...


For TypeScript lovers it provide types by default.
Closing here 👋👋👋.
Typed.js examples
Typed.js docs
This is Shareef.
Live demo
GitHub repo of this blog
GitHub
Portfolio
ShareefBhai99
Linkedin
Cover photo by Firmbee
 from Pixabay]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammed Nadeem Shareef</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Node.js][TypeScript][Windows] Play with child process]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masanori_msl/node-js-typescript-windows-play-with-child-process-114e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masanori_msl/node-js-typescript-windows-play-with-child-process-114e"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


When I call another software from Node.js, I use "child_process" like this.
[Windows][Node.js][TypeScript] Get installed printer driver names
"child_process" has four kind of methods(exclude "Sync" mehtods).
exec
execFile
fork
spawn
Because I wanted to know how to use them properly, I will try them.
Node.js ver.16.3.0
ts-node ver.10.0.0
TypeScript ver.4.3.2
According to the documents, they are based on "child_process.spawn()".
import { exec, execFile, fork, spawn } from "child_process";
import path, { resolve } from "path/posix";

function start() {
    spawnSample('powershell',['node', '-v']);
}
function spawnSample(command: string, args: string[]) {
    const execProcess = spawn(command, args);
    console.log('spawn');
    console.log(execProcess.spawnfile);
    execProcess.on('…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masui Masanori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Copy to Clipboard on a Website]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bibekkakati/how-to-implement-copy-to-clipboard-on-a-website-1p0l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bibekkakati/how-to-implement-copy-to-clipboard-on-a-website-1p0l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T12:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we are going to see how we can implement a copy to clipboard functionality on our website. On clicking the Copy button, the content/text of a paragraph tag should be copied to the clipboard which we can paste anywhere in our system.
Let's directly jump onto the code part.
I am assuming you have some basic knowledge of HTML, JavaScript and DOM manipulation.
We will write a very simple HTML code to display the paragraph content and a copy button.
index.html
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">

<head>
    <meta charset="UTF-8">
    <meta http-equiv="X-UA-Compatible" content="IE=edge">
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0">
    <title>Copy To Clipboard</title>
</head>

<body align="center">
    <p id="content">The text to be copied.</p>
    <bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bibek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce load time for Angular Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gourav_gunjan/reduce-load-time-for-angular-apps-2gg0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gourav_gunjan/reduce-load-time-for-angular-apps-2gg0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T11:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi All


Hi Guys, I have created the second post in the series where I talk about boosting performance in Angular. I would really appreciate if your one like or comment can help me reach those who require to know about these topics. Happy Coding!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gourav Gunjan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple but customizable accordion component in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/a-simple-but-customizable-accordion-component-in-angular-ck0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/a-simple-but-customizable-accordion-component-in-angular-ck0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T06:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a super simple accordion component in Angular. Using the power of content projection in Angular, we are going to build an accordion/expansion panel that can be customized in multiple ways.
Accordions in general are vertically stacked lists of headers when clicked reveals some content. Accordions or expandable sections are seen as part of almost all the UI libraries out there.
If we take a look at Angular material, we have Expansion Panel (ref) and in Ng Bootstrap its called simple Accordion (ref).
What we are gonna build is a much simpler version of these. And as always, the whole idea behind this is to help you explore some possibilities of Angular. This blog post would be mostly about how we can use Content Projection (ref) in Angular to create reusable and customizable UI …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Discussion] Use a template engine with backend integration instead of a fully-JS UI framework like react or angular?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pazvanti/discussion-use-a-template-engine-instead-of-a-fully-js-ui-4k84</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pazvanti/discussion-use-a-template-engine-instead-of-a-fully-js-ui-4k84"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T05:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let me start by saying that I am a back-end developer. I do have some experience with front-end technologies, but I can't say that I am capable of a full-stack dev session. With that being said, let me rant a bit.
I find all the JS UI frameworks confusing. There are so many of them, each has its own syntax and structure, many components, and doesn't use "traditional" JS/TS, but many placeholders that get "replaced" later on. I reached this conclusion recently when I started a new project (with a new company) and the UI part was done purely in Angular and the UI communicated with the BE using REST calls. The project had less than a month since it started, so I wasn't quite from the start so I could not impose my view :D
This brings me to my next rant. The UI does soo many calls to the backe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pazvanti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Disaster Recovery Plan? How to Use RTO and RPO to Protect your Business]]></title>
        <id>60b72d5facb62507dd1d777b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/disaster-recovery-plan-what-are-rto-and-rpo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T22:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're in the world of tech, you will inevitably run into a work-related disaster now and then. These setbacks come in many forms such as cyber-attacks, theft, leaks, and corruption. And every business must be ready to face these things and plan for them. Sir Benjamin Franklin famously said,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342429</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-new-ui-theme-colors-and-a-css-tricks-cameo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a 33-minute video (and resources) over on apple.com covering the upcoming Safari changes we saw in the WWDC keynote this year in much more detail. Look who’s got a little cameo in there:
Perhaps the most noticeable thing there …
The post Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Possibilities of Syndication]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-possibilities-of-syndication/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the one word that isn’t an adjective in the acronym RSS. 
Really Simple Syndication.
Update: Lol there are literally two mistakes there. RSS is an initialism not an acronym, and “Really” is an adverb not an adjective. 
RSS …
The post The Possibilities of Syndication appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Center Anything in CSS Using Flexbox and Grid ✨]]></title>
        <id>6063b9189618b008528a9d81</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-center-objects-using-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T20:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm gonna show you how you can center and align your content with CSS. Along the way, we'll look at various alignment techniques. So, let's get started! 🥇 Table of Contents -> How to Use Flexbox to center anything horizontally center anything vertically center both horizontally & Vertically How]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Keyboard Accessibility for Complex React Experiences]]></title>
        <id>5f9c97e9740569d1a4ca1768</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/designing-keyboard-accessibility-for-complex-react-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can design an inclusive and accessible org chart experience and solutions to common development challenges you will face.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ask Good Technical Questions – the Ultimate Guide]]></title>
        <id>60bc0444acb62507dd1d9a31</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-ask-good-technical-questions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T17:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to ask effective technical questions is an essential skill every software engineer should have.  You may be stuck with a bug, unable to figure out why your program isn't working correctly, or you might be having trouble learning how to implement a certain algorithm. In all of these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Level Up Your React Conditionals]]></title>
        <id>60c24cf8d3126007592d61d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-conditionals/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T16:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you write conditionals correctly within your React applications?  Good conditionals are an essential part of any React application. We use conditionals to show or hide elements or components in our applications.  In short – to be an effective React developer, you must know how to write good conditionals. Let's go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342164</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-shadows-to-svg-icons-with-css-and-svg-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T14:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would we need to apply shadows to SVG?
Shadows are a common design feature that can help elements, like icons, stand out. They could be persistent, or applied in different states (e.g. :hover, :focus, or :active) 
…
The post Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put a Background on Open Details Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/put-a-background-on-open-details-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that can be just a smidge funky about the <details> element is that, when open, it’s not always 100% clear what is inside that element and what isn’t. I’m not saying that always matters or that it’s a …
The post Put a Background on Open Details Elements appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/equal-columns-with-flexbox-its-more-complicated-than-you-might-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As awesome as flexbox is, what it’s doing under the hood is actually a little strange because, by default, it is doing two things at once. It first looks at the content size which is what we would get if by declaring width: max-content on an element. But on top of that, flex-shrink is also doing some work allowing the items to be smaller, but only if needed.
Let’s break those two down and see how they work together.
The post Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Powell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342182</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-headless-cms-with-fauna-and-vercel-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn and use headless CMS, Fauna, and Vercel functions to build a blogging platform, Blogify After that, you can easily build any web application using a headless CMS, Fauna and Vercel functions.
The post Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikeh Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cornucopia of Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340967</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-cornucopia-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T20:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know about y’all, but my feeds have been flooded with articles about CSS Container Queries these past few weeks. The buzz about container queries actually started back in December after Miriam Suzanne posted a proposal (picking up on …
The post A Cornucopia of Container Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[target=blank]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341916</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/targetblank/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T14:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does that make your eye twitch a little bit? Like… it’s a typo. It should be target="_blank" with an underscore to start the value. As in…
<a target="_blank" href="https://codepen.io"Open CodePen in a New Tab
</a
Welp, that’s correct syntax!…
The post target=blank appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341982</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/looking-at-wcag-2-5-5-for-better-target-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T18:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever experienced the frustration of trying to tap a button on a mobile device only to have it do nothing because the target size is just not large enough **and it’s not picking up on your press? Maybe …
The post Looking at WCAG 2.5.5 for Better Target Sizes appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Libby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341884</id>
        <link href="https://alex.party/posts/2021-05-31-css-trickz-an-experiment-with-netlify-s-on-demand-builders/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T14:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress sites have an API by default. Wanna see this site’s most recent posts, with just a specific set of data… in JSON format? Here ya go. Alex Riviere made a joke site using that.
At first, the site …
The post CSS-Trickz: An Experiment with Netlify’s On-Demand Builders appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T19:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Show/Hide password accessibility and password hints tutorial — Nicolas Steenhout goes deep on <input type="password"> accessibility. For one thing, being able to toggle it to type="text" should be possible, while announcing, politely, the change. But also, put the password hints 
…
The post Links on Accessibility appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions for HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340390</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/vs-code-extensions-for-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T14:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s look at some extensions for VS Code that make writing and editing HTML (and languages that are basically HTML with extra powers) better. You may not like all of them. Maybe some of them don’t appeal to you, solve …
The post VS Code Extensions for HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>