<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-16T01:06:25.994Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-16T01:06:25.994Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Time "Truth Dare & Stare" game with video and audio chat functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ishanextreme/real-time-truth-dare-stare-game-with-video-and-audio-chat-functionality-10ek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ishanextreme/real-time-truth-dare-stare-game-with-video-and-audio-chat-functionality-10ek"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T22:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Link to the game
Game Teaser
Truth Dare & Stare is a Web Application where users can play the famous Truth Dare and Stare game with video and audio chat with their friends. Due to corona and lock down in many countries we are facing a serious mental health issues, specially the students who at this time enjoy the summer vacations with their friends are locked inside their houses. And the only thing we can do is to wait for the situation to improve. To contribute towards improving mental health I have made t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishan Mishra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A visual guide to how my brain understands INTERFACES]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ingriddorioschulze/a-visual-guide-to-how-my-brain-understands-interfaces-58hg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ingriddorioschulze/a-visual-guide-to-how-my-brain-understands-interfaces-58hg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T21:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sketching note was the result of my process understanding Interfaces with visual input, practical and simple examples and comparisons with events in my day to day life.
Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid do Rio Schulze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Technology - outsourcing company founded in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/istef94/global-technology-outsourcing-company-founded-in-2021-4p3c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/istef94/global-technology-outsourcing-company-founded-in-2021-4p3c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T21:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2021 seems to be the year of the IT industry that has developed a lot during the pandemic. New opportunities have emerged for entrepreneurs who have managed to attract many projects.
Thus was born a new start-up for outsourcing companies, namely Global Technology Innovation which provides software services.
Global Technology is an outsourcing company founded in 2021 that works with clients from several industries such as:
Manufacturing
Healthcare
Automobile
Banking
Real Estate
Logistics
Insurance
C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Ionel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upload and handle file in ReactJs and NodeJs using FormData.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sakshamcoder/upload-and-handle-file-in-reactjs-and-nodejs-using-formdata-2ekh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sakshamcoder/upload-and-handle-file-in-reactjs-and-nodejs-using-formdata-2ekh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T19:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upload and handle file from ReactJs and NodeJs using FormData.



  
  
  Introduction


You may not have ever handled file uploads in React or any other technologies, but there is a high possibility you’ll encounter the need for it, whether tor update profile photos of users, CSV files, or PDFs, to mention but a few. In this guide, you’ll learn how to upload files in your React apps(Frontend) to NodeJs(Backend).
To get started, run the following command in your terminal or visit React to get a fully config…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saksham Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VimGore : an interactive game to learn vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ps173/vimgore-an-interactive-game-to-learn-vim-10kn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ps173/vimgore-an-interactive-game-to-learn-vim-10kn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T18:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I wanted to try MERN stack and thus started out with this idea of creating a game that will provide you with snippets of code which will be corrected by the user using vim mode. So this idea was enough to give me motivation to jump into the project state.

So below is the link to the app. It is not fully featured and I think that it is missing lot of stuff but will be happy to get a overall feedback. 
If you have any issues then report in repo :)
For now this is vimgore
source code
live site
(also this w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pratham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Package CI/CD with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jidicula/go-package-ci-cd-with-github-actions-350o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jidicula/go-package-ci-cd-with-github-actions-350o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T18:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, I wrote about how I implemented CI/CD checks and autoreleases for the Python implementation of my random-standup program. I also developed some similar workflows for the Go implementation, so I thought I'd also write a Go-flavoured post about packaging CI/CD using GitHub Actions. This post may seem very familiar if you read that previous post - as I described in my comparison between the Go and Python implementations of this program, my CI/CD goals are the same: PR checks and autorelease…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johanan Idicula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My most used Bit commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emilygracekz/my-most-used-bit-commands-2ehl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emilygracekz/my-most-used-bit-commands-2ehl"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T17:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bit is a tool where you can upload components to the cloud ☁️ 🌈 so you can use them in other codebases, or import them to several files in one codebase. With Bit's built in version control uploading and editing components across several codebases and machines is easily manageable. 
Although I love Bit, I experienced a learning curve with the commands. As a result here's an explanation of my most used Bit commands as a library metaphor. 
or check out a book
bit import seattle.seattle-public-library/harry-po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Kondziola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expense Manager - SpringBoot and ThymLeaf (Dockerized)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vijai021096/expense-manager-springboot-and-thymleaf-dockerized-56e2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vijai021096/expense-manager-springboot-and-thymleaf-dockerized-56e2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T17:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXPENSE MANAGER


Pull the image using  the below command:
 docker pull vijaim/expensemanager:latest 

Use the below as docker compose file.

 version: "3.7"
services:
  mysql-service:
    image: mysql:5.7
    networks:
      - spring-boot-mysql-network
    restart: always
    environment:
      - MYSQL_ROOT_PASSWORD=1234
      - MYSQL_DATABASE=testapp
  expensemanager: 
    image: {id of the pulled image }
    ports:
      - "4000:4000"
    networks:
      - spring-boot-mysql-network
    depends_on:
      …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parse shell commands in javascript with tagged templates]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vonheikemen/parse-shell-commands-in-javascript-with-tagged-templates-1g5a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vonheikemen/parse-shell-commands-in-javascript-with-tagged-templates-1g5a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T16:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm here now to share something that I think you might find useful, as well as asking for help to improve my code.
I want to parse commands using javascript's tagged templates. Something like this.
$`dep deploy --branch=${branch}`

example taken from zx.
This isn't anything new, I've seen others try to do this before, but the thing that bothers me is that they use an actual shell to execute the commands. They have their methods to sanitize inputs and whatnot but it still bothers me. For that particular case…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js tips for more robust and secure apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anilkaundal/node-js-tips-for-more-robust-and-secure-apps-6b2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anilkaundal/node-js-tips-for-more-robust-and-secure-apps-6b2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T16:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js tips and tricks to deliver more secure and robust applications.
You should use tools like npm audit or snyk to check for vulnerable dependencies. You can also use dependabot to keep yourself updated.
You should name all the functions, closures and callbacks. This will help you easily understand what you are looking for from memory snapshots while profiling your application.
Libuv is an open-source library that handles the thread-pool which is used by node for many asynchronous operations like file I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anil Kaundal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux beginner to pro Commands Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/linux-beginner-to-pro-commands-part-2-3jb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/linux-beginner-to-pro-commands-part-2-3jb5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to another blog of Linux beginner to pro series.
1.1 We use cp command to copy file. Syntax to copy file goes like cp path_of_file path_of_target_file  . In below example we are going to copy the file hello.txt to hello2.txt
$ cp hello.txt hello2.txt

In above command content of hello.txt is copied to hello2.txt regardless to the existence of file. If file does not exist file will get generated.
1.2 If you want to copy all the files from the folder to another location use -r option as shown in follo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Rawas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali linux + Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gabby1024/kali-linux-windows-2di</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gabby1024/kali-linux-windows-2di"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to install Kali linux and windows on same computer without using any virtual machine!? And how is it done?(if it possible!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabby Mturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongoose Unique Not Working]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akshatsinghania/mongoose-unique-not-working-16bf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akshatsinghania/mongoose-unique-not-working-16bf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have a user schema and you want the email field to be unique
import { Schema } from 'mongoose';

const userSchema = new Schema({
    password: { type: String, required: true },
    email: { type: String, required: true, unique: true },
});

export default user schema;

but it doesn't work! , here are some reasons because which this wouldn't work
You might have already added some duplicate data in the database so mongoose and MongoDB simply doesn't check unique field because it's already messed up
Delete…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akshat Singhania</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A boilerplate for node TS packages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johnb8005/a-boilerplate-for-node-ts-packages-26d3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johnb8005/a-boilerplate-for-node-ts-packages-26d3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T14:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I make use of NPM packages extensively since they provide a convenient and nice way to encapsulate modules and manage versions independently from the rest of the codebase.
However, I found myself copying code from other repo over and over to get to an acceptable boilerplate. So I decided to write a github templates so I could create a new package in a matter of seconds (at least get a decent boilerplate).
It is available here: https://github.com/Nexysweb/boilerplate-node-package
I would love feedbacks or co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A boilerplate for node TS packages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johnb8005/a-boilerplate-for-node-ts-packages-26d3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johnb8005/a-boilerplate-for-node-ts-packages-26d3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T14:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I make use of NPM packages extensively since they provide a convenient and nice way to encapsulate modules and manage versions independently from the rest of the codebase.
However, I found myself copying code from other repo over and over to get to an acceptable boilerplate. So I decided to write a github templates so I could create a new package in a matter of seconds (at least get a decent boilerplate).
It is available here: https://github.com/Nexysweb/boilerplate-node-package
I would love feedbacks or co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCP DevOps Certification - Pomodoro Twelve]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eggsy84/gcp-devops-certification-pomodoro-twelve-4nhn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eggsy84/gcp-devops-certification-pomodoro-twelve-4nhn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T13:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System Complexity


The Coursera SRE programmes shifts on to discussing system complexity and the introduction of the initial Service Level Indicators. Google recommend that around 1 to a maximum of 3 SLI's per user journey should be enough.
Thoughts behind limiting the number to a maximum of 3 SLI's:
Not all metrics make could SLIs
Each SLI increases the cognitive load on the operations team
More SLIs lower the signal-to-noise ratio (which can impact resolution time)
You may also have lots of user journey'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Heggs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔥Understanding the Events Reactivity System of Node.js and The Event Emitter Class [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenerdydev/understanding-the-events-reactivity-system-of-node-js-and-the-event-emitter-class-2h1g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenerdydev/understanding-the-events-reactivity-system-of-node-js-and-the-event-emitter-class-2h1g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T13:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, we will learn about the Events Core Module in Node.js and then we will also understand the Event Emitter class of Node.js and the methods that we can use on the event emitter instances that we create to listen for an event ( on method ) and to fire an event, we have the emit method that is used to emit an event name to which you can optionally pass a payload  as well







Follow me on:
https://twitter.com/The_Nerdy_Dev
https://instagram.com/thenerdydev
https://youtube.com/thenerdydev
PS - M…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Nerdy Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔥Node.js Architecture - Understanding its Internal Components [video]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenerdydev/node-js-architecture-understanding-its-internal-components-video-41bi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenerdydev/node-js-architecture-understanding-its-internal-components-video-41bi"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T13:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, we will understand the Node.js Architecture namely the Application, V8 JavaScript Engine, Node.js Bindings, Libuv, Event Loop and Worker Threads








Follow me on:
https://twitter.com/The_Nerdy_Dev
https://instagram.com/thenerdydev
https://youtube.com/thenerdydev
PS - Make sure to subscribe to my YouTube Channel for FREE content on Web Development and loads of other technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Nerdy Dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes: part 42 – Tools - Encrypt your Secret with kubeseal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-part-42-tools-encrypt-your-secret-with-kubeseal-1l1l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-part-42-tools-encrypt-your-secret-with-kubeseal-1l1l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T13:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes can be difficult or time-consuming. In order to spread knowledges about Cloud technologies I started to create sketchnotes about Kubernetes. I think it could be a good way, more visual, to explain Kubernetes (and others technologies).
We continue the serie of Sketchnotes about Kubernetes, with some useful tools to know.


If you are interested, I published all the sketchnotes on Kubernetes (and new ones!) to make a "book" of 165 pages: "Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way".
As …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurélie Vache</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is resilience engineering? A lightning talk with background information]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pietvandongen/what-is-resilience-engineering-a-lightning-talk-with-background-information-3n27</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pietvandongen/what-is-resilience-engineering-a-lightning-talk-with-background-information-3n27"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The coronavirus pandemic has taught us two things: all online systems will fail eventually, and they will fail in unpredictable ways. But have no fear; resilience engineering is here!
Building and maintaining event-driven, highly scalable, and quickly adaptable systems are a pain in the neck. Resilience engineering embraces this complexity and helps you manage it.
In the TEQnation lightning talk below, I will explain what resilience engineering is, why every software person should know about it, and how you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piet van Dongen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rest API Boilerplate for Node.js 🤖🔥]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/webdeasy/rest-api-boilerplate-for-node-js-30kc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/webdeasy/rest-api-boilerplate-for-node-js-30kc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T12:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you also tired of writing the same code for every project? 😔
I am, anyway. That's why I created a Rest API boilerplate for Node.js!
Only 3 simple steps to use them 🔥
Rest API Boilerplate Repo (GitHub)





I know that there are already such boilerplates, however, they are simply much too large and extensive for most purposes.
My boilerplate is as small as possible, but still offers you a meaningful structure for your projects.
Dynamic creation of routes
Preinstalled nodemon for faster development
REST…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>webdeasy.de</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restart Policies Docker Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohithv07/restart-policies-docker-compose-2c14</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohithv07/restart-policies-docker-compose-2c14"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T12:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are mainly 4 different restart policies.
It means never attempt to restart the container if it stops or crashes. 
restart: 'no' in our docker-compose.yml file. 
Remember to give single quotes 'no' because in yaml file, if we give no without quotes, it is treated as false.
version: '3'
services: 
  redis-server:
    image: 'redis'
  node-app:
    restart: 'no'
    build: .
    ports: 
      - "4001:8081"

If our container stops for any reason, always attempt to restart the stopped container.
restart: a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohith V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image Compression with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/image-compression-with-node-js-4d7h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/image-compression-with-node-js-4d7h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T12:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, I feel that the market is increasingly oriented towards the use of third-party services to make part of our pipeline. One of the most common is to compress images.
However, I will show that with a simple Express.js api we can upload an image, change the Mime Type and still decrease its size.
I don't think I need to talk about Express.js because everyone who uses Node.js has used this framework at some point. Today I'm going to focus on multer and sharp.
Nowadays uploading images is one of the mos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REACT SIDE NOT SERVING]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/react-side-not-serving-2ig4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/react-side-not-serving-2ig4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Development 101: Architectures, Approach, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bari_parth/software-development-101-architectures-approach-and-more-1hnd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bari_parth/software-development-101-architectures-approach-and-more-1hnd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T11:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software is often written in response to real-world problems that organizations discover through market analysis. It may seem an easy task for many people to read a set of requirements and interpret them in technology. But, on the contrary, it takes much planning and a synchronized development approach to deliver high-end software solutions.

Source: Worldwide IT enterprise software spending 2009-2022 | Statista
According to Statista, IT spending on software development is bound to grow at 10.8% to reach $5…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parth Bari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tagged Unions and ReScript Variants]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ryyppy/tagged-unions-and-rescript-variants-5e4d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ryyppy/tagged-unions-and-rescript-variants-5e4d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T10:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript there are many situations where we want to express certain shapes of an object based on the conditions of its attributes, e.g.
// Plain JS - Typical Redux Action types
if(action.type === "addUser") {
  const user = action.user;
  createUser(user);
}

if(action.type === "removeUser") {
  const userId = action.userId;
  removeUser(userId);
}

You can find this pattern in many other scenarios, such as representing the method of a request (req.method === "POST" -> req.body != null), representing U…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Ecker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting to DevOps from Build and release background]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prasanna/shifting-to-devops-from-build-and-release-background-3e8f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prasanna/shifting-to-devops-from-build-and-release-background-3e8f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T10:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone!
I just wanted to share my journey from working in build and release profile and shifting to DevOps.
In my first few years of my professional career, I was working in Build and release engineer profile. The tools and technologies included were
SCM : IBM Rational ClearCase
You could imagine these IBM Rational tools were popular earlier. But already the new open source tools started become popular and tools like Jenkins, Git etc are widely adopted.
So it was necessary to start working on new ag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasanna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T09:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do we build our own OS or not?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/askneilpatel/do-we-build-our-own-os-or-not-1po5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/askneilpatel/do-we-build-our-own-os-or-not-1po5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T07:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are considering to fork Android or create our own OS with Linux for our open source metaverse. 
I’m looking for opinions from the community to help me understand the pros and cons of making this decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a todo list in React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/achukka/create-a-todo-list-in-react-4mp4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/achukka/create-a-todo-list-in-react-4mp4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T05:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to create a todo list in React using Typescript.

Before we create the application, let’s set up our development environment.
Download and install the latest stable version of Node
Though Node is not really required to use React, it bundle react applications into a neat packages that can be used relatively easy by other clients. See this stack over flow post for more details
Section 1: Create a react application
Open your terminal and run
npx create-react-app todolist — te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Chukka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes de Pipes e Services]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T04:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes Unitários


No post anterior falamos sobre o básico de testes, neste iremos iniciar os testes unitários das estruturas do Angular.
Estruturas que iremos testar:
Pipes
Services
Como mostrado no post anterior os testes de Pipes não tem segredo.
Sempre que possível, é interessante testar todas as possíveis variações dos valores de entrada (limites do domínio de entrada) para que não tenhamos nenhum caso não tratato, pois não saberemos quem poderá utilizar nossa Pipe.
Dado a pipe abaixo no arqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Egberto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Changing Page title Dynamically]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T03:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step 1. First we need to import Title service -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";

Step 2. Using setTitle -
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }

All together -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";
@Component({
 selector: 'app',
 templateUrl: './app.component.html',
 providers : [Title]
})
export class AppComponent implements {
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }
}






  
  
  Previe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 software for your Homelab in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T02:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have lots of reasons for what you run your lab but there is an always growing list of new things to try in your homelab or server. Check out this quick list of 10 apps that you can try out and see if you can get some new functionality for free through self-hosting.
Portainer



Docker is a powerful tool that can allow you to host and run apps easily on your servers. Now, docker's main interface is a command-line tool but with an application like Portainer you get a nice GUI interface to manage your …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Berry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 software for your Homelab in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T02:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have lots of reasons for what you run your lab but there is an always growing list of new things to try in your homelab or server. Check out this quick list of 10 apps that you can try out and see if you can get some new functionality for free through self-hosting.
Portainer



Docker is a powerful tool that can allow you to host and run apps easily on your servers. Now, docker's main interface is a command-line tool but with an application like Portainer you get a nice GUI interface to manage your …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Berry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physical Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love a good caper film. When I was a wee lad my father introduced me to The Great Train Robbery. Over the years I’ve seen several memorable others Rififi, A World Without Thieves, several by David Mamet like The Spanish Prisoner. Just the other day I watched Inside Man.
Numerous vulnerabilities like Spectre, Man-in-the-middle, SQL injection, keyloggers, phishing and a legion of others have loomed over the IT sphere for decades. Seems like every month there’s a new, “largest ever”, high profile security in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeikabu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Clear a Redux Toolkit State That's Using redux-persist With Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bionicjulia/how-to-clear-a-redux-toolkit-state-that-s-using-redux-persist-with-typescript-4360</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bionicjulia/how-to-clear-a-redux-toolkit-state-that-s-using-redux-persist-with-typescript-4360"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got into a bit of a pickle with the user experience for my app last week. Prior to this issue coming up in my React app, I had been:
Using Redux Toolkit to store state in localForage.
Using redux-persist to persist and rehydrate state if the user closes, or refreshes / uses the navigation buttons on their browser.
Generating a unique user id for each new visitor who comes to the app for the first time i.e. if their redux state was empty. This was for purposes of identification in the backend database.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bionic Julia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parent child communication using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T21:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's very common in modern web development to handle the communication between the nearest components. The most obvious data flow is a parent to child. In this post, I'd like to show how to share the data between such components in both directions.
Passing the data down to the children's components is very easy.
app.component.html




<p>Item clicked {{ activeElement }}</p>
<div class="box__container">
  <app-box *ngFor="let box of boxCollection"
           [details]="box"
           [isActive]="box.name ==…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michał Muszyński</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SendGrid? SMTP Email Newsletter Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>609d63e962ab9107fe5aa2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sendgrid-smpt-email-newsletter-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of the term SMTP before, and wondered what it is. SMTP is a common method for handling email messages. Today I am going to explain what SMTP is, and how to use an SMTP provider such as SendGrid to send emails from your address. What Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript enum guide: get started in 5 minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/typescript-enum-guide-get-started-in-5-minutes-4447</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/typescript-enum-guide-get-started-in-5-minutes-4447"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enumerations (or enums) are a supported data type in TypeScript. Enums are used in most object-oriented programming languages like Java and C# and are now available in TypeScript too. They are one of the few features of TypeScript which isn’t a type-level extension of JavaScript. Enums allow you to define a set of named constants. Using them makes it easier to document intent or create a set of distinct cases. Today, we’ll explore the basics of TypeScript enums along with use cases, various enum types, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erin Schaffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🆔 Identity, Unlocked... Explained: Season 2, Ep 8]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🛡 JWT Profile for OAuth 2.0 Access Tokens with Vittorio Bertocci



  
  
  
In this episode of Identity, Unlocked, the CTO and co-founder of Auth0, Matias Woloski, appears as acting host and interviews Vittorio Bertocci, principal architect at Auth0 and the regular host of Identity, Unlocked, on the JWT profiles for OAuth2 access tokens specification. 
This spec describes how to encode OAuth2 access tokens in use JWT format in an interoperable way, by giving a minimal list of claims, how to emit a JWT dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React for Beginners: Complete React Cheatsheet for 2021]]></title>
        <id>609ea83362ab9107fe5aa920</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the React for Beginners guide. It's designed to teach you all the core React concepts that you need to know to start building React applications in 2021. I created this resource to give you the most complete and beginner-friendly path to learn React from the ground up. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 14th May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time waits for no one. It feels like yesterday since the last edition of this round-up only for me to check, and it's 2 weeks already, and I am like: Are you kidding me?
What more could I say? Let's move on.
Hopefully, I can keep track of time and I will be here next week to say: "Yeah I made it this week".
Introduction


This week it's everything security.
Foxit Reader bug lets attackers run malicious code via PDFs


Foxit Reader comes pre-installed on some laptop computers. If you (or anyone else) use Fox…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live Dev: How to set up a Node project with Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adamcoster/how-to-set-up-a-node-project-with-typescript-d5c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adamcoster/how-to-set-up-a-node-project-with-typescript-d5c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning how to code is a long process. Structured coursework and tutorials are a great way for most people to learn, especially at the beginning, but at some point you start to wonder... what does the actual work of development look like? How do you go from identifying a problem to a deployable project that solves that problem?
I had a (relatively) small side project I wanted to tackle for fun, and decided to do it live on video so that people could see the whole process from start to finish.
If you:
Love …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Coster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes OpenID Connect Integration with Resource Owner Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nuculabs_dev/kubernetes-openid-connect-integration-with-resource-owner-flow-ban</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nuculabs_dev/kubernetes-openid-connect-integration-with-resource-owner-flow-ban"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello 😄,
In this article I will demonstrate how to configure Kubernetes (minikube) to use OpenID Connect as an authentication strategy.
We will cover the Resource Owner Password flow. Feel free chose the right authentication flow depending on your application’s needs.
Please refer to this diagram in order to choose the flow:

Note that the Client Credentials flow is not supported by Kubernetes. According to the officials docs:
“To identify the user, the authenticator uses the id_token (not the access_token…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nucu Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps -Automate & Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is the practice of integrating a security-first mindset and methodologies into traditional DevOps CI / CD environments. Here are key best practices for organizations seeking to implement DevSecOps.
Being able to get code out the door fast, secure, and efficiently is the name of the game. In a CI/CD environment, it’s important to maintain speed as the main tenet but also to be aware of the security needed to bulk up your pipeline. Without automation, implementing security practices could be a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Bhanushali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps -Automate & Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is the practice of integrating a security-first mindset and methodologies into traditional DevOps CI / CD environments. Here are key best practices for organizations seeking to implement DevSecOps.
Being able to get code out the door fast, secure, and efficiently is the name of the game. In a CI/CD environment, it’s important to maintain speed as the main tenet but also to be aware of the security needed to bulk up your pipeline. Without automation, implementing security practices could be a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Bhanushali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Lofi Club - Enjoy Hip hop beats to Relax or Code! 🎧]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saviomartin/introducing-lofi-club-enjoy-hip-hop-beats-to-relax-or-code-11ij</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saviomartin/introducing-lofi-club-enjoy-hip-hop-beats-to-relax-or-code-11ij"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Devs 👋


This is Savio here. I'm young dev with an intention to enhance as a successful web developer. I love building web apps with React. I have proved my superiority in frontend technologies. Today, I'd like to share my latest project Lofi Club
I'm a big fan of lofi music, In fact, many of us are. Lo-fi is a music or production quality in which elements usually regarded as imperfections of a recording or performance are audible, sometimes as a deliberate aesthetic choice. Hearing to lofi music mak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Savio Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorization mechanisms in Rust web applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ddtkey/authorization-mechanisms-in-rust-web-applications-27ag</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ddtkey/authorization-mechanisms-in-rust-web-applications-27ag"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To ensure application security, we use mechanisms such as authentication and authorization. I think many of you are familiar with these concepts and in this article we will focus on the concept of authorization and related access control models.

Definitions of terms used in the article
  
It's important to understand the difference between authorization and authentication:
Authentication – a process of verifying your identity and proving that you are a user of the system (by means of a password, token or a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Medvedev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development for Beginners – Learn Basic HTML and CSS to Build Your First Web Page]]></title>
        <id>609e8c2162ab9107fe5aa77d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-development-for-beginners-basic-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites are built and designed? Do you want to learn the art of web development but you're not that tech savvy – yet? Well, then this tutorial is for you. It's an introduction to Web Development for beginners so you can learn the basics even if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH Azure Linux VM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mohan023/how-to-ssh-azure-linux-vm-4k9l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mohan023/how-to-ssh-azure-linux-vm-4k9l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm glad to write this post about my experience in connecting linux vm. Below are the number of steps to be taken. Keeping this short and simple.
Create Linux VM on Azure


Enable SSH connectivity 

You must enable port 22 for SSH connectivity and create VM with default options.


Download Private Key as prompted. It will be .pem file.


Once downloaded, VM will be created for you. Go to Virtual Machine-->Settings-->Connect




Now here is a twist. People don't know how to use that .pem file downloaded as g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohan Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular forms - NEVER rely on a disabled "submit" button!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're just writing some Angular code.
A form.
That form has some required fields, like email and password.
Your "submit" button is disabled until the form is valid, by using <button type="submit" [disabled]="myForm.invalid">, which you can find in many stackoverflow answers.
You're safe - the feature is working, a user isn't able to submit an invalid form.
Actually, you're not.
Now, try opening the dev console in your browser and manually removing the disabled attribute from the "submit" button.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Manista</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular forms - NEVER rely on a disabled "submit" button!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're just writing some Angular code.
A form.
That form has some required fields, like email and password.
Your "submit" button is disabled until the form is valid, by using <button type="submit" [disabled]="myForm.invalid">, which you can find in many stackoverflow answers.
You're safe - the feature is working, a user isn't able to submit an invalid form.
Actually, you're not.
Now, try opening the dev console in your browser and manually removing the disabled attribute from the "submit" button.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Manista</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[😫 Tired Of Relative Imports? Time To Get Rid Of Them!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamludal/tired-of-relative-imports-time-to-get-rid-of-them-1n48</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamludal/tired-of-relative-imports-time-to-get-rid-of-them-1n48"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in your Javascript developer journey, you've certainly encountered these types of imports:
import Car from '../../../vehicles/car'
import House from '../../../buildings/house'

And you were probably bothered by the ugliness of them...

But guess what? I'm here as a savior to show you how to get rid of them! (really) 😎
Ready? Let's go! 🏁
The simplest way to get rid of these awful imports is by simply editing your jsconfig.json file. If you don't already have one, you can just create it at the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ludal 🚀</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Line filter program that removes digits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gonzalezlrjesus/line-filter-program-that-removes-digits-3005</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gonzalezlrjesus/line-filter-program-that-removes-digits-3005"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📌 A filter is a program that gets data from standard input, performs some manipulation of the data, and then writes its results to standard output.
📌 Most common functions:
▶️ Convert data to a different format
📌 Unix has many filter programs, most common are: cat, cut, grep,
Go Playground: https://play.golang.org/p/s8FwQRkZXdr]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Gonzalez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple arrow operators in a single function]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/multiple-arrow-operators-in-a-single-function-551d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/multiple-arrow-operators-in-a-single-function-551d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We may have come across arrow functions in javascript and are almost saturated learning about the difference between normal functions and arrow functions, the difference between ES5 and ES6 and everything that is connected to it. But everytime we come across multiple arrows in a single function, we keep struggling - or it could just be a "me" problem. Here goes, what multiple arrows in a function mean.
A simple ES6 function that demonstrates it:-
const add = x => y => x + y

This can be written in ES5 funct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muzammil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Getting through that pesky company proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-getting-through-that-pesky-company-proxy-fp5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-getting-through-that-pesky-company-proxy-fp5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are attempting to get an Angular site running on your Windows work computer at XYZ Company the chances are that you are having problems getting through the company proxy.
There are (at least) two package managers that need to get through the proxy:
NPM
Typings
For NPM you need to add the following lines to the .npmrc file:
proxy=http://[DOMAIN]%5C[USER]:[PASS]@[PROXY]:[PROXYPORT]/
https-proxy=http://[DOMAIN]%5C[USER]:[PASS]@[PROXY]:[PROXYPORT]/

For Typings you need to add the following lines to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting Left of Bang to Improve Your DevOps Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nextlinklabs/shifting-left-of-bang-to-improve-your-devops-security-bok</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nextlinklabs/shifting-left-of-bang-to-improve-your-devops-security-bok"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early 2000s, the US Marine Corps' Combat Hunter training program introduced, among many other concepts, the ‘left of bang’ idea as a way to improve situational awareness and save lives.
The way ‘left of bang’ works is simple.
Any critical event that causes significant disruption, loss, or other negative outcome -- an attack, injury, or breach of security -- can be mapped out and analyzed on a timeline. The actual occurrence of the event -- the thing that happened -- falls directly in the middle of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nextlink Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-stylesheet-feature-flags-with-sass-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[!default is a Sass flag that indicates conditional assignment to a variable — it assigns a value only if the variable was previously undefined or null. Consider this code snippet:
$variable: 'test' !default;
To the Sass compiler, this line …
The post Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Babcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Boilerplates]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340403</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-boilerplates/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzović goes line-by-line through a boilerplate HTML document. I like it. It’s a good reference and has a lot of the same type of stuff I tend to put in the main HTML template. It makes me think about …
The post HTML Boilerplates appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Video] Introduction to Git and GitHub Crash Course + Giveaway ⭐]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/video-introduction-to-git-and-github-crash-course-giveaway-3jjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/video-introduction-to-git-and-github-crash-course-giveaway-3jjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello everybody! Welcome to this Introduction to Git and GitHub video series, where you will learn the basics of Git and start using it for your day-to-day tasks.
My name is Bobby and I've been working as a Linux system administrator for the past 7 years and a few months ago I wrote an opensource eBook on how to get started with Git and GitHub.
You can find a link to the GitHub project where you can Download the eBook for free here:
Opensource eBook on how to get started with Git and GitHub
I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Shopify Themes Development with Nx-Shopify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/trafilea/modern-shopify-themes-development-with-nx-shopify-31ho</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/trafilea/modern-shopify-themes-development-with-nx-shopify-31ho"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR


Nx-Shopify is an Nx plugin for developing Shopify themes with performance, modern tooling, and ergonomics in mind.
Check the Getting Started guide and the full docs at the Nx-Shopify official website.
 / 
        nx-shopify
      
    




  Nx-Shopify











🔎 An Nx plugin for developing performance-first Shopify themes 🚀
Be it you need to build a custom Shopify store theme, develop a generic theme or even maintain multiple stores/themes with shared code across them, this Nx plugin helps you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastián Duque G</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five tips about React hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/le_humch/five-tips-about-react-hooks-fik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/le_humch/five-tips-about-react-hooks-fik"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T13:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, when you use React and functional components, you need hooks.
Work with hooks is easier than lifecycle methods in class components, but I've encountered some issues and today, I want to share my solutions with you.
I like to cut my code in small pieces for a better understanding. I make four blocks in reading's order. Usually, I use the same layout between functional and class components. In this article, I will only get into functional components.
The first block is for all the hooks and variables. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabien Schlegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Vs Bootstrap- A Comparison Of Frontend Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ltdsolace/angular-vs-bootstrap-a-comparison-of-frontend-frameworks-2gig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ltdsolace/angular-vs-bootstrap-a-comparison-of-frontend-frameworks-2gig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T13:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this competitive market, a creative and responsive UI plays a vital role in the success of web solutions. So for developers, it is important to choose the best frontend framework for app development. Angular and Bootstrap are the two popular frameworks used by developers, but choosing the best one for a project is not an easy task. Angular is a TypeScript based framework with immense codes and vast tools for app development whereas Bootstrap is an HTML/CSS/JS framework with ready-made components. The fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solace Infotech Pvt. Ltd.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript and why should you use it?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coderslang/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-use-it-3mfd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coderslang/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-use-it-3mfd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is TypeScript?


TypeScript is a programming language developed and maintained by Microsoft. It introduces additional features like strict type binding (variables are bound to specific data types) to JavaScript and can also be compiled down to JavaScript as well.
TypeScript is an Open Source Project, and the source code for it is available on GitHub.
TypeScript introduce?


TypeScript adds several additional features to JavaScript. The most important one is strict typing (it is turned on by default, bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Coderslang: Become a Software Engineer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are your tools for keeping dependencies and plugins versions up-to-date?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cfecherolle/what-are-your-tools-for-keeping-dependencies-and-plugins-versions-up-to-date-126g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cfecherolle/what-are-your-tools-for-keeping-dependencies-and-plugins-versions-up-to-date-126g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone!
I rarely post here but today I decided to ask the community about some tooling.
One thing that I find daunting in today's web dev ecosystem is how to keep track of dependencies and plugin versions in all layers of our apps and, say, not miss a lot of versions for one tool or the other.
For example, in the project I'm working on, we have a front-end app made with React, a Java/Spring Boot back-end, a Keycloak authentication system, and so on.
So I was asking myself: is there some kind of tool to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cécile Fécherolle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do you need CIAM?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-do-you-need-ciam-28pa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-do-you-need-ciam-28pa"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how customer identity and access management (CIAM) helps you balance security, privacy, and experience for all users.



  
  
  
Customer experiences happen primarily online. If this wasn’t completely true for your business before 2020, it’s probably true now. Companies have come to understand that a seamless digital experience is no longer a competitive differentiator; it’s a baseline requirement.
Moreover, pressure-cooker economic conditions during the pandemic have shown that companies that unders…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Google Social Login or Sign In Tutorial using angularx-social-login]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/angular-11-google-social-login-or-sign-in-tutorial-using-angularx-social-login-55of</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/angular-11-google-social-login-or-sign-in-tutorial-using-angularx-social-login-55of"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, We at Bacancy Technology, shared a tutorial about how you can implement the Google Social Login with the use of the angular-social-login library which is available in angular. In Angular 9+, you can easily implement this technique. But if you want to implement this in older versions of Angular, it asks for a few modifications in the code(especially in the module.ts file). 
Do you know about the benefits or we can say what is the magic in this tutorial of social login, here you can sign in to the appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bacancy Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : conditional class with *ngClass]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-conditional-class-with-ngclass-3kf2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-conditional-class-with-ngclass-3kf2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is NgClass?


Adds and removes CSS classes on an HTML element.
Angular provides several ways to add classes conditionally:
[class.my_class] = "step === 'step1'"

[ngClass]="{'my_class': step === 'step1'}"

[ngClass]="{'my_class': step === 'step1', 'my_class2' : step === 'step2' }"

[ngClass]="{1 : 'my_class1', 2 : 'my_class2', 3 : 'my_class4'}[step]"

[ngClass]="step == 'step1' ? 'my_class1' : 'my_class2'"

Based on the Official Documentation 
The CSS classes are updated as follows, depending on the ty…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Angular HttpClient to POST, PUT, DELETE data on SpringBoot Rest APIs – Angular 4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-use-angular-httpclient-to-post-put-delete-data-on-springboot-rest-apis-angular-4-34ai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-use-angular-httpclient-to-post-put-delete-data-on-springboot-rest-apis-angular-4-34ai"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/use-angular-httpclient-post-put-delete-data-springboot-rest-apis-angular-4
How to use Angular HttpClient to POST, PUT, DELETE data on SpringBoot Rest APIs – Angular 4
With previous posts, we had done 2 important things: fetching data from remote server by Angular HttpClient, and navigate among views by Angular Routing.
In this tutorial, we'll go to next step - work with Rest APIs: How to use Angular HttpClient to POST, PUT & DELETE data on SpringBoot RestAPI Services.
Related Articles:
H…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/how-to-use-vim-g1o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/how-to-use-vim-g1o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a powerful text editor used by programmers and system administrators as a command line interface. Vim is widely used by Linux users. It is also available in Windows, Mac OS X and every other Unix system.
The reason why it is that popular is that vim allows the programmer to code efficiently without leaving the editor. When coding, you don't need to use your mouse. This sounds simple, but this is exactly what any programmer wants from an editor.
Most of its commands are robust and cryptic enough to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JS interview in 2 minutes / Currying 🥘]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kozlovzxc/js-interview-in-2-minutes-currying-2hko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kozlovzxc/js-interview-in-2-minutes-currying-2hko"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T09:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Question:
Quick answer:
Longer answer:
Higher Order Functions. It is an application of JavaScript's ability to return functions from other functions.
We are replacing a function that takes n arguments with a set of n functions, which applied one by one gives exactly the same answer as original functions.
We can learn it by example right away. Btw it feels like this one is the most common one.
// regular implementation
function add1(a, b) {
  return a + b;
}

console.log(add1(2,5)) // 7

// curried implement…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking wireless access points]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rootsec1/hacking-wireless-access-points-598j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rootsec1/hacking-wireless-access-points-598j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T07:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know how to hack WiFi access points -- just read this step by step aircrack-ng tutorial, run the verified commands and crack passwords easily.
With the help a these commands you will be able to hack WiFi AP (access points) that use WPA/WPA2-PSK (pre-shared key) encryption.
The basis of this method of hacking WiFi lies in capturing of the WPA/WPA2 authentication handshake and then cracking the PSK using 'aircrack-ng'.
 Download and install the latest aircrack-ng

 Start the wireless interface …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse engineering binaries using gdb]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rootsec1/reverse-engineering-binaries-using-gdb-2bhc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rootsec1/reverse-engineering-binaries-using-gdb-2bhc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T07:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General note on compiling for debugging:


Normally, to enable the debugger to use the source code, you would compile a program using the -g flag:
$ gcc -g program.c -o program (for lowest level of optimization), or

$ gcc -g -O2 program.c -o program (for optimization level 2)

The -g -O2 combination is valid and enables one to to debug the optimized executable. However the compiler will have generated a lot of optimizations, which will make it more difficult to step through the code. Using -g with no optim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How long lived is your Linux, before next clean install?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/patarapolw/how-long-lived-is-your-linux-before-next-clean-install-37gc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/patarapolw/how-long-lived-is-your-linux-before-next-clean-install-37gc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T05:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I mean, how often do you want to wipe everything away and clean install?
Even in macOS, I clean installed every once in a while.
But for Ubuntu, new version came out, and I might want to clean install.
Hopefully, for Arch, there would be no real need to clean install again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pacharapol Withayasakpunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : How to use *ngIf else? [Including NgIf, ngIfThen and ngIfElse with Live Demo]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-use-ngif-else-5gcp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-how-to-use-ngif-else-5gcp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T04:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simple form with shorthand syntax:
<div *ngIf="condition">Content to render when condition is true.</div>

Simple form with expanded syntax:
<ng-template [ngIf]="condition"><div>Content to render when condition is
true.</div></ng-template>

Form with an "else" block:
<div *ngIf="condition; else elseBlock">Content to render when condition is true.</div>
<ng-template #elseBlock>Content to render when condition is false.</ng-template>

Shorthand form with "then" and "else" blocks:
<div *ngIf="condition; then t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to transfer data from your Existing Server to Aws S3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bawa_geek/how-to-transfer-data-from-your-existing-server-to-aws-s3-4p8g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bawa_geek/how-to-transfer-data-from-your-existing-server-to-aws-s3-4p8g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T03:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 is a pretty good and inexpensive choice for website data storage. You can save a lot of money uploading website data such as user uploads to S3 instead of your hosting server.
I found it a little difficult to understand how s3 migration works and did not find any simple tutorial on that. So here I am sharing the steps that can help you to migrate data to the S3 bucket.
Steps:
Install Aws Cli on your existing Server




curl "https://awscli.amazonaws.com/awscli-exe-linux-x86_64.zip" -o "awscliv2.zi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lakhveer Bawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memory of Hiny Umoren - a podcast episode on security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/raped-and-murdered-4hn3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/raped-and-murdered-4hn3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T03:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm hurt. I'm sorry guys if today I'm not posting anything related to codding. I feel hurt and bad about the recent happenings in Nigeria. Although not peculiar to Nigeria only. So I've decided to write instead about security. Please follow up with the podcast link below.
https://anchor.fm/dami-okoro/episodes/RAPED-AND-MURDERED-in-memory-of-Hiny-Umoren-e10rj7q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Angular 13]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/michelledev3/the-future-of-angular-13-18ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/michelledev3/the-future-of-angular-13-18ja"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular did it again, on May 12, 2021, the newest major version of Angular arrived a stable Angular v12.0.00. 

Angular version 12.0.0 released May 2021. The Angular v12 major release is getting closer to “Ivy Everywhere”. The newest version enables the transition of the Angular ecosystem to the Ivy compiler.
Angular v12 includes stylish improvements, nullish coalescing allowing developers to write cleaner code in TypeScript and Angular templates, Webpack 5 support and TypeScript v4.2, and a stick model ena…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michelledev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340490</id>
        <link href="https://chenhuijing.com/blog/devtools-for-css-layouts-2021-edition/#%F0%9F%9A%B2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Hui Jing covers some recent movement in DevTools:
Firefox’s grid inspector was pretty full-featured from the get-to and released together with CSS grid in Firefox 52. It was constantly improved upon since. Chrome added a basic grid inspector 
…
The post DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340573</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2021-design-systems-survey-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friends at Sparkbox are doing a survey on design systems, as they do each year. Go ahead and fill it out if you please. Here are the results from last year. In both 2019 and 2020, the vibe was …
The post 2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Email Newsletter [2021 Tutorial] – Design, Layout, Send]]></title>
        <id>609414f32cd0545b5e943526</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-email-newsletter-design-layout-send/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T21:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a large community, chances are you need a way to communicate updates to your members quickly and efficiently. An email newsletter can be a very effective way to do so. In this article, I am going to provide some tips and suggestions for maximizing the impact and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? The 10 Most Common Types of Tests Developers Use in Projects]]></title>
        <id>609952396008950828b3ea8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and testing go hand in hand. And in the era of agile software development, with quick releases of small iterations, you should do testing more and more frequently.  In order to perform effective testing, you need to know about the different types of testing and when you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Tutorial – How to Work with Multiple Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>609bcc6a62ab9107fe5a9f08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-multiple-checkboxes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling multiple checkboxes in React is completely different from how you use regular HTML checkboxes. So in this article, we'll see how to work with multiple checkboxes in React. You will learn: How to use a checkbox as a Controlled Input in ReactHow to use the array map and reduce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Lawyer to Engineer at Google – How to Switch Careers and Learn New Skills]]></title>
        <id>609ccb0d62ab9107fe5aa0ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-lawyer-to-google-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a corporate lawyer for 12 years. I never thought I'd be working at Google as a software engineer, but that's what I have been doing for the past year. I'm working remotely until COVID subsides and we can move to San Francisco.  In this article I'm going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340036</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/advanced-css-animation-using-cubic-bezier/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with complex CSS animations, there is a tendency to create expansive @keyframes with lots of declarations. There are a couple of tricks though that I want to talk about that might help make things easier, while staying in …
The post Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svgator-3-0-reshapes-the-way-you-create-and-animate-svg-with-extensive-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building animations can get complicated, particularly compelling animations where you aren’t just rolling a ball across the screen, but building a scene where many things are moving and changing in concert. When compelling animation is the goal, a timeline GUI …
The post SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Portfolio with Vue.js Axios, the GitHub REST API, and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>5fde208ae6787e09839407c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-portfolio-with-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this free book, we will build two simple projects and deploy them on Netlify. We will use Vue.js as our front-end framework, and use different technologies to build our projects.  If you follow this tutorial to the end, you will build a simplified version of Twitter and a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the Kivy Python Library to Create Games and Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>609c215862ab9107fe5a9fa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-the-kivy-python-library-to-create-games-and-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kivy is a free and open source Python framework for developing mobile apps and games with a natural user interface. We just released a 5-hour Kivy course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this Kivy course, you will learn to create games and applications with Python for every platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339960</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-disabled-buttons-more-inclusive/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about disabled buttons. Specifically, let’s get into why we use them and how we can do better than the traditional disabled attribute in HTML (e.g. <button disabled> ) to mark a button as disabled.
There are lots of …
The post Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandrina Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Selenium and Python to Scrape Websites More Effectively]]></title>
        <id>6096aafe2cd0545b5e944430</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-web-scraping-with-selenium/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're scraping data from the web with Python, Selenium will often come up as an helpful tool to use. It was originally designed for automated testing, but its scraping capabilities are impressive, too. This is because Selenium can do things that other libraries or frameworks often can't when collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-pie-timer-re-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitty reflected on an ancient blog post here on CSS-Tricks on how to make an animated pie timer. The old technique is still clever. The new technique is equally clever and much easier. I particularly like the steps() animation function…
The post CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I could build this during the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340186</id>
        <link href="https://world.hey.com/joaoqalves/i-could-build-this-during-the-weekend-aa093c5e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you heard that (or even uttered it under your own breath)? I know I’ve heard it in conversations. I also know I’ve wondered the same thing about a product or two — hey, the idea here …
The post I could build this during the weekend appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Gen CSS: @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-gen-css-container/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome is experimenting with @container, a property within the CSS Working Group Containment Level 3 spec being championed by Miriam Suzanne of Oddbird, and a group of engineers across the web platform. @container brings us the ability to …
The post Next Gen CSS: @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Una Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340106</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/distributed-persistent-rendering-dpr/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Jamstack, Netlify is coining this term.
If your reaction is: great, a new thing I need to know about and learn, know that while Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) does involve some new things, this is actually a push …
The post Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topframe]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/topframe/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is extremely fun. Jeff Lindsay has created Topframe, and writes:
Anybody that knows how to mess around with HTML can now mess around with their desktop computing experience. Topframe is an open source tool that lets you 
…
The post Topframe appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340208</id>
        <link href="https://benfrain.com/migrating-from-parcel-to-snowpack-build-tool-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find build tooling endlessly interesting, especially right now as we’re in a juicy next-gen transitional period with players like Vite, wmr, Snowpack, and esbuild. Hugh Haworth has a good run-down of the new players, and we’ve chatted on …
The post Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339203</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/variable-aspect-ratio-card-with-conic-gradients-meeting-along-the-diagonal/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across an interesting problem. I had to implement a grid of cards with a variable (user-set) aspect ratio that was stored in a --ratio custom property. Boxes with a certain aspect ratio are a classic problem in …
The post Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.6]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: The output website didn't have favicon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Item description didn't use the description property from feed item.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>