<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-09T01:03:19.566Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-09T01:03:19.566Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding timing attacks with code examples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/propelauth/understanding-timing-attacks-with-code-examples-32e6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/propelauth/understanding-timing-attacks-with-code-examples-32e6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T23:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerable login example


The following code snippet has a subtle security issue with it. Can you tell what's wrong?
// Returns true if the email/password pair is valid
async function isValidCredentials(emailAddress, password) {
    // Fetch the password hash from the DB by email address
    const passwordHashOrNull = await fetchPasswordHash(emailAddress);

    // If there was no match, return false
    if (!passwordHashOrNull) {
        return false;
    }

    // Bcrypt is "a library to help you hash passwords"
    // Here we use the compare function to check that the
    //   provided password matches the hashed password in the DB
    const doesPasswordMatch = await bcrypt.compare(password, passwordHashOrNull);
    return doesPasswordMatch;
}

// Fetches the password hash from the DB
a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>propelauthblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript Example #2.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baenencalin/typescript-example-2-42n1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baenencalin/typescript-example-2-42n1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[// An example of using generics in a type union.
// A compact version of my Option<T> type from
// "Typescript Example #1." (https://dev.to/baenencalin/typescript-example-1-ia3).
type Option<T> = T|null;]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Calin Baenen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing Just One False Positive in Brakeman]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/presidentbeef/fixing-just-one-false-positive-in-brakeman-4060</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/presidentbeef/fixing-just-one-false-positive-in-brakeman-4060"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, I came across a Brakeman false positive that I wanted to fix.
For a single false positive, it became a bit of an epic journey.
The code looked something like this:
class Task < ApplicationRecord
  enum status: {
    pending: 0,
    success: 1,
    failed: 3,
  }

  NOT_FAILURES = ['pending', 'success'].freeze
end

class TaskRunner
  def get_failures
    start_time = Date.beginning_of_quarter
    end_time = Date.end_of_quarter

    no_failure_enums = Task.statuses.values_at(*Task::NOT_FAILURES)

    query = <<~QUERY
      SELECT COUNT(*)
      FROM `tasks`
      WHERE `tasks`.`status` NOT IN (#{no_failure_enums.join(',')})
      AND `tasks`.`time_end` BETWEEN #{start_time} AND #{end_time}
    QUERY

    # Line below triggers a SQL injection warning
    Task.connection.select_al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VSCode project-wide TS checks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/beeinger/vscode-project-wide-ts-checks-2c7m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/beeinger/vscode-project-wide-ts-checks-2c7m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a coder I have never limited myself to one language, one framework and I didn’t want to have a milion code editors each specialised in different thing so I have always used VSCode. Keeping the theme, the look and feel of the editor with power of an IDE one plugin away no matter which language I want to jump into is the key factor that guided my choice.
However, I have tried JetBrains’ WebStorm before and just couldn’t get rid of one huge thing haunting me, the project-wide type checking.
In VSCode the typescript plugin works great but it only checks files that are currently opened in the editor! Other files inside the project are not being checked until opened 😕 Now this is a huge bump, having to run the check manually through console or build the whole app in order to check if one type alternation hasn’t influenced anything else? Madness…
This is when I decided to research this problem — and there really is no out of the box solution! After trying every way on the internet I have finally pieced together the final solution for this problem:
{
    "version": "2.0.0",
    "tasks": [
      {
        "label": "tsc-watch project",
        "type": "typescript",
        "tsconfig": "tsconfig.json",
        "option": "watch",
        "problemMatcher": ["$tsc-watch"],
        "group": "build",
        "runOptions": {
          "runOn": "folderOpen"
        },
        "presentation": { "reveal": "never" }
      }
    ]
  }

This is an automated task for VSCode — it runs when the project folder is opened and keeps on running, checking the whole repo real-time based on the changes you make! Finally! 🎉
Put it in

.vscode/tasks.json




Re-open the project folder and accept the popup asking whether Automatic Folder Tasks should be allowed
If the popup isn’t there do:
⌘⇧p
-> Manage Automatic Tasks in Folder
-> Allow Automatic Tasks in Folder



  
  
  🎉 All done! Enjoy your VSCode with TypeScript better than ever! 🎉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Sułecki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five common causes for flaky tests and what you can do about them]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sprihatucker/five-common-causes-for-flaky-tests-and-what-you-can-do-about-them-2ej7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sprihatucker/five-common-causes-for-flaky-tests-and-what-you-can-do-about-them-2ej7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flaky tests are non-deterministic tests in your test suite. They may be intermittently passing or failing, making test results unreliable.
Why are flaky tests bad?
Developer productivity goes down as test results become inaccurate and trust in the test-suite decreases.
Multiple, unrelated commits cause similar errors, making maintenance difficult.
Legitimate issues may get ignored due to a high number of false positives.
Repetitive work is required to determine if bugs exist at all.
Diagnostics time increases as errors can be in the test or code.
User dissatisfaction due to bugs ending up in production.
Let's look at five common causes for flaky tests showing up in your build pipeline and what you can do about them.
One of the common reasons why tests do not find bugs is concurrency. They …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spriha B. Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Monitoring Commands 📈💻]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linuxseb/system-monitoring-commands-4gc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linuxseb/system-monitoring-commands-4gc9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! I am back with another Linux article!😊
Today I will be going over basic commands you can use to monitor system performance! 📈📉💻
The 'top' command is used to display active processes and how much they are using system resources.

lsof stands for list of open files- basically shows you list of files and the processes

'tcpdump' is used to analyze network traffic
'htop' is a lot like top - It's just allows you to monitor system resources or processes. As you can see, it's a bit more fancy than top

'iostat' is a command that is used to monitor input/output devices, by telling you how long the devices have been active.

Displays the processes

Tells you how long the system has been up

'free' shows you the amount of available memory you have.

Used to monitor individual tasks. Great for troubleshooting issues.

'w' tells you information about users logged on and their processes

These commands can be vital for you to monitor your system, so I will be releasing a part 2 soon, as well!😆
For future Linux and security content, please give me a follow 
@linuxseb
 


  
  
  Thank you again!😊]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of the OWASP Serverless Top 10 [videos]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/miguelacallesmba/overview-of-the-owasp-serverless-top-10-videos-1e25</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/miguelacallesmba/overview-of-the-owasp-serverless-top-10-videos-1e25"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T22:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This YouTube video series provides quick overviews of the top 10 cybersecurity risks for serverless applications. Each video covers the risk and some recommendations on how to address it.
In this video, I discussed the reasons why the OWASP Serverless Top 10 cybersecurity risks for a serverless application are important to consider.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wWDzqrvt73A]
In this video, I discussed what is the injection attack.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QhmAs30-b_k]
In this video, I discussed what is broken authentication and authorization.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDO4n3HrvQw]
In this video, I discussed the sensitive data exposure risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q8j8Cu0jhqc]
In this video, I discussed the XML external entities risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wtgTtYXenyM]
In this video, I discussed the broken access control risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nqBQdAiTOb8]
In this video, I discussed the security misconfiguration risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yDyYqDGph8c]
In this video, I discussed the cross-site scripting (XSS).
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jyLOBsHg-7c]
In this video, I discussed the insecure deserialization risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RlV79AmI6Yw]
In this video, I discussed the risk of using components with known vulnerabilities.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ij6xU48K11k]
In this video, I discussed the insufficient logging and monitoring risk.
%[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Alu17kfNQA]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel A. Calles MBA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Estude TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jonatanlima/estude-typescript-486a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jonatanlima/estude-typescript-486a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T20:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post original: link
Bom dia amigos, gostaria de citar alguns benefícios de aprender e utilizar TypeScript em JavaScript.
Alguns motivos:
Temos a possibilidades de trabalhar com tipagem, algo muito útil para nós desenvolvedores JavaScript.
Orientação a Objetos, sim, vamos poder usufruir de todo o poder desse paradigma (Class, Interface, Abstract), somando com a programação funcional nativa.
Melhora seu código, seu código vai se tornar mais coeso, bem divido, claro, se você usufruir de interfaces, classes abstratas e da boa e velha herança.
Muitas tecnologias utilizam ou dão suporte ao TypeScript: Angular, React, Graphql, Graphcool e etc.
Lembre-se TypeScript é um supertest de JavaScript, ou seja, você pode implementar ele sem precisar usar esses frameworks citados acima.
Comece agora a utilizar TypeScript e eleve seu JavaScript para o próximo nível. Vou deixar alguns links legais pra você estudar TypeScript:
O próprio site dará todo o suporte que você precisará: https://lnkd.in/dC4bbuX


No próprio site tem uma área pra você começar do zero: https://lnkd.in/dB8pTuj



Agora só depende de você, estude, pratique e use TypeScript em seus novos projetos.
Fiquem com Deus e até a próxima.
Nunca desista de correr atrás dos seus sonhos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonatan Lima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Przegląd wybranych ataków na polskich internautów (25.10–7.11.2021 r.)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gizamichal/przeglad-wybranych-atakow-na-polskich-internautow-2510-7112021-r-4p4j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gizamichal/przeglad-wybranych-atakow-na-polskich-internautow-2510-7112021-r-4p4j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T20:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://sekurak.pl/przeglad-wybranych-atakow-na-polskich-internautow-25-10-7-11-2021-r/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michał Giza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Grid Can Do Auto Height Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356204</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-grid-can-do-auto-height-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T19:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bonafide CSS trick alert! Nelson Menezes figured out a new way (that only works in Firefox for now) that is awfully clever.
Perhaps you know that CSS cannot animate to auto dimensions, which is super unfortunate. Animating from …
The post CSS Grid Can Do Auto Height Transitions appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Give Developers Secure Access to Kubernetes Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eionel/how-to-give-developers-secure-access-to-kubernetes-clusters-4j26</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eionel/how-to-give-developers-secure-access-to-kubernetes-clusters-4j26"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T18:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Lens


Navigate to the Lens website (https://k8slens.dev/) and download the latest version of Lens for your preferred OS. Once you have downloaded and installed, open the application, Lens IDE will automatically add your Kubeconfig (if done correctly, you will see a cluster icon on the left-hand-side). Lens works with any certified CNCF Kubernetes distro. 
Now that your cluster has been added, you have full situational awareness of your Kubernetes cluster. Users can easily monitor all objects and resources within their cluster.  
In order to share a cluster with a team or team member, you will first need to create a Lens Spaces account:
https://app.k8slens.dev/signup)
Click “Create an account” and follow the process to sign up for a Lens Spaces account. Once you have registered …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eionel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migração de serverless framework v1 para v2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thiagofelippi/migracao-de-serverless-framework-v1-para-v2-1je</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thiagofelippi/migracao-de-serverless-framework-v1-para-v2-1je"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T18:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recentemente em alguns projetos que participei tive alguns desafios com relação a mudança do serverless framework de v1 para v2. No projeto utilizei NodeJS com Typescript, toda infra na AWS.
Estava utilizando a versão 1.83.2 juntamente com a imagem do docker softinstigate/serverless:1.83.0
Link da imagem: Docker Hub
Queríamos utilizar a imagem: Docker Hub
Que no momento era a mais atual. Porém tivemos alguns desafios e é sobre isto que falarei hoje
Primeiramente, porque quisemos mudar? Simplesmente porque queríamos mexer com tecnologias mais modernas, usar features novas e nos atualizarmos afim de não termos um projeto depreciado ao longo do tempo.
Queriamos estar disponíveis para testar novas features da versão v2, aumentar a versão do node, que estava a 10 e iria começar a parar de ter s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thiago Crespo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching Anaconda environments in GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/epassaro/caching-anaconda-environments-in-github-actions-5hde</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/epassaro/caching-anaconda-environments-in-github-actions-5hde"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most time-consuming tasks in my GitHub workflows is the solving, download and installation of Anaconda environments.
Some of my pipelines runs on Linux and Mac, so I usually need to set up matrix to handle the different installation paths of Miniconda.
jobs:
  build:
    strategy:
      matrix:
        include:
          - os: ubuntu-latest
            label: Linux
            prefix: /usr/share/miniconda3/envs/carsus

          - os: macos-latest
            label: macOS
            prefix: /Users/runner/miniconda3/envs/carsus

At the step level, install Miniconda without specifying a YAML environment file.
I choose the Mambaforge variant, which is basically a custom Miniconda build shipped with the lightning-fast mamba package manager and the conda-forge channel enabled.
- name: Setup Miniconda
  uses: conda-incubator/setup-miniconda@v2
  with:
      miniforge-variant: Mambaforge
      miniforge-version: latest
      activate-environment: <your-env-name>
      use-mamba: true

The cache task work with keys. When the task is executed, looks for a saved cache that matches the key and retrieves the data.
Cache is specific for every OS. Also, I set up the key in a way that will update the cache every 24 hours or if the environment has changed.
- name: Set cache number
  run: echo "::set-output name=number::$(date +'%d%m')"
  id: cache-number

- uses: actions/cache@v2
  with:
    path: /usr/share/miniconda3/envs/carsus
    key: ${{ runner.os }}-conda-${{ hashFiles('<your-env-yaml-file>') }}-${{ env.CACHE_NUMBER }}
  env:
    CACHE_NUMBER: ${{ steps.cache-number.outputs.number }}
  id: conda-cache

Finally, if the cache is not available, update the environment according to the YAML environment file.
- name: Update environment
  run: mamba env update -n <your-env-name> -f <your-env-yaml-file>
  if: steps.conda-cache.outputs.cache-hit != 'true']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>epassaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[C/C++] How to get scope_id of IPv6 Link local Address on Linux.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fmtweisszwerg/cc-how-to-get-scopeid-of-ipv6-link-local-address-on-linux-7c4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fmtweisszwerg/cc-how-to-get-scopeid-of-ipv6-link-local-address-on-linux-7c4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-known way is to use getaddrinfo() such like:
#include <arpa/inet.h>
#include <cerrno>
#include <cstring>
#include <iostream>
#include <netdb.h>
#include <string>
#include <sys/socket.h>
#include <sysexits.h>

int main(void)
{
    struct addrinfo hints;
    memset(&hints, 0, sizeof(struct addrinfo));
    hints.ai_family = AF_INET6;
    hints.ai_socktype = SOCK_DGRAM;
    hints.ai_protocol = IPPROTO_UDP;

    struct addrinfo* result_addrinfo = nullptr;
    auto result = getaddrinfo("fe80::dabb:c1ff:fe0a:17f2%enp39s0", std::to_string(12345).c_str(), &hints, &result_addrinfo);
    if( result != 0 ){
        std::cout << "`getaddrinfo()` failed: " << gai_strerror(errno) << std::endl;
        return result;
    }

    for(
        struct addrinfo* info = result_addrinfo;
        info != nullptr;
        info = info->ai_next
    ){
        char ipv6addr_human_readable_form[INET6_ADDRSTRLEN] = {0, };
        inet_ntop(info->ai_family, &((struct sockaddr_in6*)(info->ai_addr))->sin6_addr, ipv6addr_human_readable_form, info->ai_addrlen);
        auto ipv6_scope_id = ((struct sockaddr_in6*)(info->ai_addr))->sin6_scope_id;

        std::cout << "IPv6 address = " << ipv6addr_human_readable_form << std::endl;
        std::cout << "Scope-ID = " << std::to_string(ipv6_scope_id) << std::endl;
    }

    freeaddrinfo(result_addrinfo);
    return EX_OK;
}

Of course, the Scope-ID can also be obtained as previously. But is there an easier and shorter?
if_nametoindex()


Fortunately, Linux provides a function called if_nametoindex (). It returns the index number of the network interface, which is currently equal to the Scope-ID.
#include <net/if.h>
#include <iostream>
#include <sysexits.h>

int main(void)
{
    auto scope_id = if_nametoindex("enp39s0");
    std::cout << scope_id << std::endl;

    return EX_OK;
}

Now, the code became much shorter and easier. Also, there is no need to care to free memory!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fomalhaut Weisszwerg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remove Protected Data with No-code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/frizzled/remove-protected-data-with-no-code-2cng</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/frizzled/remove-protected-data-with-no-code-2cng"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[remove-pii is a no-code solution that creates shareable CSVs while removing protected data, PII and PHI with just a few clicks.
Working with third parties, contractors and partners who need access to files containing protected data means walking a tightrope between providing useful data without violating privacy, HIPAA or GDPR. 
Let's remove protected data from a CSV without writing any code using an example file.

This walk-through will use remove-pii.com. Although we're working with a website, no data is transmitted to any server; all processing is handled in the browser. An offline version is also available.
Now, we'll provide our CSV to the website. This will parse the headers and allow us to replace any data within the file.  Any unset columns pass through to the final file. 

Let's s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vlad Loscutoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Subscribe to and Receive Push Notifications from YouTube’s API using Typescript and Nodejs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/algodame/how-to-subscribe-to-and-receive-push-notifications-from-youtubes-api-using-typescript-and-nodejs-2gik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/algodame/how-to-subscribe-to-and-receive-push-notifications-from-youtubes-api-using-typescript-and-nodejs-2gik"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Youtube’s API provides developers with a way to get push notifications for when specific changes occur on a youtube channel. Youtube’s API sends out these notifications through a PubSubHubbub webhook protocol.
Webhooks are used to send near-real-time data to applications. 
Let’s say you have an application that sends out emails to a mailing list and you only want to send out these emails whenever Beyonce posts a video on her channel. To do this, you can use Youtube’s webhooks to subscribe to push notifications on Beyonce’s channel. Whenever Beyonce posts a video, Youtube will tunnel down a request to your server to inform you of this event.
In order to get the push notifications from Youtube’s webhook, you need to provide Youtube with a URL which you will use to receive the data for whenev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chiamaka Ojiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thing to know before developing your cyber security solution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/thing-to-know-before-developing-your-cyber-security-solution-2onk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/thing-to-know-before-developing-your-cyber-security-solution-2onk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency(CISA)," Cybersecurity is the art of protecting networks, devices, and data from unauthorized access or criminal use and the practice of ensuring confidentiality, integrity, and availability of information.". A few terms to know before going ahead,
Privacy means maintaining confidentiality.
Anonymity means no body knows who you are?
Pseudonymity means using an alias.
How much of your daily life relies on technology? How much of your personal information is stored on a device or a server?
There are many risks, some more serious than others. Among these dangers is malware erasing your entire system, an attacker breaking into your system and altering files, an attacker using your computer to attack others, or an attacker stealin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hridyesh bisht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: An Exploration in Triggering Validation and Transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-an-exploration-in-triggering-validation-and-transformation-5g4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-an-exploration-in-triggering-validation-and-transformation-5g4k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I came across an intriguing article about (Dynamic self-registered FormControl in Angular)(https://medium.com/@toha.marko/dynamic-self-registered-reactive-formcontrol-in-angular-bf2342b7f14d).
Everything about this article was well done and very interesting.
There was one point in the article that spiked my interest: the author triggered the "creation" of the Form Controls dynamically within the Angular HTML.
So, I decided to experiment and see if I could use this as a means to trigger data validation and transformation.
This is an experiment, simple to see if I can do something. Personally, I see some benefit in the pattern. But, this does not mean I am endorsing this as a good pattern or a better means than any other way of doing something.
The working code ...
REPO
PAGE
Here's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.ts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: An Exploration in Triggering Validation and Transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-an-exploration-in-triggering-validation-and-transformation-5g4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-an-exploration-in-triggering-validation-and-transformation-5g4k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I came across an intriguing article about (Dynamic self-registered FormControl in Angular)(https://medium.com/@toha.marko/dynamic-self-registered-reactive-formcontrol-in-angular-bf2342b7f14d).
Everything about this article was well done and very interesting.
There was one point in the article that spiked my interest: the author triggered the "creation" of the Form Controls dynamically within the Angular HTML.
So, I decided to experiment and see if I could use this as a means to trigger data validation and transformation.
This is an experiment, simple to see if I can do something. Personally, I see some benefit in the pattern. But, this does not mean I am endorsing this as a good pattern or a better means than any other way of doing something.
The working code ...
REPO
PAGE
Here's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.ts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install Dropbox on ArchLinux with paru]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shawon/install-dropbox-in-archlinux-with-paru-2nen</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shawon/install-dropbox-in-archlinux-with-paru-2nen"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever encountered ERROR: One or more PGP signatures could not be verified! this error during the installation of Dropbox in Arch based distro ? If yes then this guide is for you. 
Dropbox has their own PGP key because they upload it directly to the AUR that key is for linux@dropbox.com (if you don't know what PGP keys are it's basically a complex math formula that proves that this app is being uploaded and managed on the AUR by somebody at dropbox)
if you use a tool like yay or paru it can handle the functions of pacman and downloading stuff from the AUR and it's dead simple to use, I recommend paru because it's more modern and faster
To install paru run these commands
sudo pacman -S --needed base-devel

git clone https://aur.archlinux.org/paru.git

cd paru

makepkg -si

After succesfully installing paru now it's time to install Dropbox. To do that first run
paru dropbox

Now you'll be prompt with a list of packages from AUR to choose from. You have to choose aur/dropbox which should be the first one... So press 1 and hit enter

If you want to review hit Y and enter

To close the review hit q on the the keyboard
Now you must prompt with installation confirmation. Hit Y and enter. You may need to enter your password for installation. 
After completion of you installation run dropbox on your terminal or search on the GUI

That's it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shawon Saha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a Default Value to an Existing Column in MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/how-to-add-a-default-value-to-an-existing-column-in-mysql-28dk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/how-to-add-a-default-value-to-an-existing-column-in-mysql-28dk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this quick tutorial, you will learn how to add a default value to an existing column in MySQL.
You always need to be careful, when changing the structure of an existing column in your database. Make sure to always have backups of your database before making such changes. 
For MySQL, you could use the following script to generate a backup of your database:
Script to backup a MySQL/MariaDB database
When making changes to a column in your database, you can use the ALTER TABLE statement followed by the ALTER COLUMN statement.
The syntax is the following:
ALTER TABLE name_of_the_table ALTER name_of_the_column SET DEFAULT your_new_default_value;

Let's say that we had a table called users and a column called is_admin. We want all new users to have the is_admin value set to 0. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evitando conflitos na infraestrutura]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bernardo/evitando-conflitos-na-infraestrutura-3f4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bernardo/evitando-conflitos-na-infraestrutura-3f4k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform State é uma das coisas mais legais da ferramenta por facilitar a gestão do codígo com times distribuídos evitando conflitos desnecessários na esteira. 
Sempre que você executa o Terraform, ele registra informações sobre a infraestrutura que criou em um arquivo de estado do Terraform. Por padrão, quando você executa o Terraform na pasta /foo/bar, o Terraform cria o arquivo /foo/bar/terraform.tfstate. Este arquivo contém um formato JSON personalizado que registra um mapeamento dos recursos do Terraform em seus arquivos de configuração para a representação desses recursos no mundo real. Por exemplo, digamos que sua configuração do Terraform contenha o seguinte:
resource "aws_instance" "example" {
  ami           = "ami-0c55b159cbfafe1f0"
  instance_type = "t2.micro"
}

Depois de exe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luiz Bernardo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIM Card Based Mobile Authentication with iOS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tru-id/sim-card-based-mobile-authentication-with-ios-11n6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tru-id/sim-card-based-mobile-authentication-with-ios-11n6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tru.ID SubscriberCheck offers both mobile phone number verification and SIM swap detection. SubscriberCheck achieves this by combining the workflows of PhoneCheck, which confirms the ownership of a mobile phone number by verifying the possession of an active SIM card with the same number, with SIMCheck, which provides information on when a SIM card associated with a mobile phone number was last changed. SubscriberCheck can be used when augmenting existing 2FA or anti-fraud workflows.
If you'd prefer to go directly to the completed code, it's in the sim-card-auth-ios Github repository.
For development you'll need:
Xcode 12
An Apple developer account via the Apple Developer Portal

An iPhone or an iPad with a SIM card with an active data connection
Node.js installed for the tru.ID CLI
With t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg Holmes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know your Azure environment better with Grafana]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kutsyk/know-your-azure-environment-better-with-grafana-3o8o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kutsyk/know-your-azure-environment-better-with-grafana-3o8o"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originaly posted here
Monitoring of production environment is an essential part of any products not depending on the size. But monitoring big production environments efficiently is the essential difference between good quality of service and bad service.
Brief prehistory — our product is delivered to a few different clients. It means we have a multi-tenant environment and each of them requires proper monitoring. Every tenant has its own production subscription and independent infrastructure.
At the start all our monitoring was organized on native Azure Cloud resources, meaning all data go into Application Insight (Log analytics) and dashboards were built in the same environment. But as a result when we needed to investigate the root cause of the issue in our environment we were spending ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vasyl Kutsyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram notification with Github Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/telegram-notification-with-github-actions-69m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/telegram-notification-with-github-actions-69m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🇧🇷 Versão em português
Use the following script to receive Telegram notifications always your Github Actions is running.
    - name: Send Telegram Message Ok
        uses: appleboy/telegram-action@master
        env:
          GITHUB_CONTEXT: ${{ toJSON(github) }}
        with:
          to: ${{ secrets.TELEGRAM_ID }}
          token: ${{ secrets.TELEGRAM_TOKEN }}
          format: markdown
          message: |
            *1st line of your message with bold*
            *2nd line of your message with bold, too*
            Application: *Write something to be put inside your message*. The below lines still are part of your message.          
            Branch: *${{ github.ref }}*
            Repository: *${{ github.repository }}*
            Owner: *${{ github.repository_owner }}*

If you want to go deeper into this component, go to project's github repository
As we can see, to use this component we need two important informations, the TELEGRAM_ID and the TELEGRAM_TOKEN.
To get your TELEGRAM_TOKEN, you will need to create a telegram's bot, do that starting a conversation with BotFather. Start a new conversation and search for @botfather.

You can start the conversation sending a /help message to see all options allowed. But if you want to skip this step, just send /newbot and follow the instructions. When finish bot's creation, you will receive a message with your bot's token, as show below:

Good job! Now you got your TELEGRAM_TOKEN, in this example it is 2063069520:AAE7Gcummn9fSp_xLQH7dBGihpzOyWQCm9g.
Now, let's find out your TELEGRAM_ID. Just search for @userinfobot and start a conversation with /star message. The result message will be like that:
@your_telegram_username
Id: 12345678
First: <Your Firstname>
Last: <Your Lastname>
Lang: en-US

Your TELEGRAM_ID is the number in second line, right between your username and firstname.
In this point you have all information to start sending notification messages at any pipeline in Github Actions.
Just add these information to repository secrets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Protect Against Ransomware In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-protect-against-ransomware-in-2021-130m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/how-to-protect-against-ransomware-in-2021-130m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👾 Ransomware attacks are among the most profitable for criminals and remain  the most prominent malware threat today.



  
  
  
As digital assets increase in value (in some cases, being the most valuable assets a company owns), threats become more profitable to criminals too. The largest ransomware payout made by an insurance company ($40 million) to date happened in 2021, and the trend doesn’t show any signs of slowing down.
The major problem with attacks like these is that computers today are so fast and interconnected that malware can harness those resources to spread itself throughout the network and encrypt an enormous amount of files before the victim can respond.
Unfortunately, after the files have been encrypted, there is not much that can be done. Most modern ransomware has goo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Go!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joetags/lets-go-1b41</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joetags/lets-go-1b41"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I finish the last week of my software engineering bootcamp, it is time to start focusing my energy on the job hunt. One of the companies I’m interested in working with lists a particular technology as a Nice to have’. So, this week, I decided to write my blog on golang, the Go language. Let the endless journey of learning continue.
The Go language was developed by computer scientists Robert Griesemer, Rob Pike, and Ken Thompson at Google and released in 2009. The mission was to address deficiencies in other programming languages used at Google. A few issues the trio sought to address was to create a language that was easy for a programmer to use. That meant having a minimal set of strict rules. They also wanted a language that would compile quickly and could scale to large codebases tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JoeTags</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Icon Glassmorphism Effect in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=322098</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/icon-glassmorphism-effect-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a cool effect known as glassmorphism in a Dribble shot. My first thought was I could quickly recreate it in a few minutes if I just use some emojis for the icons without wasting time …
The post Icon Glassmorphism Effect in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does the Next Generation of Static Site Generators Make Building Sites Better?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356134</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/does-the-next-generation-of-static-site-generators-make-building-sites-better/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just ran across îles, a new static site generator mostly centered around Vue. The world has no particular shortage of static site generators, but it’s interesting to see what this “next generation” of SSGs seem to focus on or …
The post Does the Next Generation of Static Site Generators Make Building Sites Better? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best 3 Youtube channel for Learning DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/star_trooper/best-3-youtube-channel-for-learning-devops-51m0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/star_trooper/best-3-youtube-channel-for-learning-devops-51m0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1.TechWorld with Nana

TechWorld with Nana
TechWorld with Nana youtube channel is focused on Cloud and DevOps founded by @techworld_with_nana
 . 
You can find beginner friendly crash course in which you will learn concepts of Docker , Kubernetes , Github Actions , AgroCD , Terraform etc from scratch.

2.DevOps Directive

DevOps Directive
DevOps Directive youtube channel also focuses on Cloud and DevOps concepts, founded by @sidpalas
  . 
You can find beginner friendly tutorial in which you will learn concepts of Docker , Github Actions and Cloud platforms like AWS from scratch. 
 Sid also shares tips and best practices about how to build small size docker images.

On DevOps Directive youtube channel you will also find talks and podcast with professionals working in Tech Industry which are hundred percent insightful to watch.

3.FreeCodeCamp

FreeCodeCamp
On Freecodecamp youtube channel you will find numereous Devops and Cloud related tutorials and complete crash course t

 It doesn't focus only on DevOps and Cloud but reason to add the youtube channel in this blog is for getting started with DevOps you need to have basic knowledge of Web Development for which Freecodecamp have covered you.
I guess every web languages and framework tutorial are present on FreeCodeCamp.

 Freecodecamp also has amazing blogs written by amazing professional folks which you will find on there official website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atharva Shirdhankar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js GitHub Authentication using Passport.js and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joshuajee/nodejs-github-authentication-using-passportjs-and-mongodb-2lfd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joshuajee/nodejs-github-authentication-using-passportjs-and-mongodb-2lfd"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you will learn how to authenticate with GitHub using Passport.js in a Nodejs express app. 
You can get the source code for this project here, this project can be used as a boilerplate code when setting up an express app that uses Passportjs for authentication.
Basic Knowledge of NodeJS
Node JS should be installed on your system.
## What is Passport.js?
Passport is authentication middleware for Node.js. It is very flexible and modular. A comprehensive set of strategies supports authentication using a username and password, Google, Facebook, Apple, Twitter, and more. Find out more about Passport here.
Before using passport-github2, you must have a Github account and register an application with Github. If you have not done this, You can do that here.

To start, create a Node…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Evuetapha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The top 10 Linux Commands that Every Data Engineer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-top-10-linux-commands-that-every-data-engineer-should-know-mbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-top-10-linux-commands-that-every-data-engineer-should-know-mbg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


No matter if you are a data analyst or a system administrator when working with unstructured files in Linux there are a set of commands that would help you a lot in your daily tasks.
In this tutorial, you will learn the basics of the following commands and how to combine them using a pipe (|) and analyze some raw data files.
The list of the commands that we will go over are:
cat
head and tail
pipe (|)
wc
grep
awk
sort
uniq
sed
tr
Here is a very simple example file that I will be using to go over each of the commands:
Username    ID  Name    Orders
rachel  9012    Rachel  2
laura   2070    Laura   3
craig   4081    Craig   4
mary    9346    Mary    1
jamie   5079    Jamie   2
bobby   1456    Bobby   3
tony 5489 Tony  6
devdojo 9874 DevDojo    3
tom 2589 Tom    2
rachel  9012 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The top 10 Linux Commands that Every Data Engineer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-top-10-linux-commands-that-every-data-engineer-should-know-mbg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/the-top-10-linux-commands-that-every-data-engineer-should-know-mbg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


No matter if you are a data analyst or a system administrator when working with unstructured files in Linux there are a set of commands that would help you a lot in your daily tasks.
In this tutorial, you will learn the basics of the following commands and how to combine them using a pipe (|) and analyze some raw data files.
The list of the commands that we will go over are:
cat
head and tail
pipe (|)
wc
grep
awk
sort
uniq
sed
tr
Here is a very simple example file that I will be using to go over each of the commands:
Username    ID  Name    Orders
rachel  9012    Rachel  2
laura   2070    Laura   3
craig   4081    Craig   4
mary    9346    Mary    1
jamie   5079    Jamie   2
bobby   1456    Bobby   3
tony 5489 Tony  6
devdojo 9874 DevDojo    3
tom 2589 Tom    2
rachel  9012 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to upload a file to Azure Blob using Spring Boot?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohan2596/how-to-upload-a-file-to-azure-blob-using-spring-boot-3c3a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohan2596/how-to-upload-a-file-to-azure-blob-using-spring-boot-3c3a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello👋, Its Rohan Kadam😊
Today cloud is becoming come standard for the development of any software. We used the cloud in every aspect of the programming cycle be it uploading our code to Github or Gitlab or be it using Google Drive or Dropbox or uploading our personal files. In the article, we are going to understand how we can implement file** upload to Azure Blob Using Spring Boot**.

Blob storage is a feature in Microsoft Azure that lets developers store unstructured data in Microsoft’s cloud platform. This data can be accessed from anywhere in the world and can include audio, video and text. Blobs are grouped into “containers” that are tied to user accounts. Blobs can be manipulated by using any programming language. Blobs are widely used by streaming companies with high volumes of a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ROHAN KADAM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate deployment in simplest way by SilvenLEAF]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/silvenleaf/automate-deployment-in-simplest-way-by-silvenleaf-17p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/silvenleaf/automate-deployment-in-simplest-way-by-silvenleaf-17p"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahoy there! Let's automate deploying our Web App! We'll be using React for this. Don't worry, because react or angular or vue, that's not important. The core concept is same for all! Also we'll be going from level 0. So even if you don't know React or any of these, just hop on!!
It is a part of my future DevOps and automation blogs. So stay tuned for more amazing stuff!!
To deploy an app, we need an app, right? So let's create one. But if you don't like React, go with Angular, Vue or whatever you like.
First create a github repo (assuming you have a github account, if not, create one and then create a github repo) and then clone it onto your computer. Open it in your favorite text-editor (mine VS Code). Then type the following command to create a react app.
npx create-react-app client --te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SilvenLEAF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Kubernetes Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/semaphore/securing-kubernetes-deployments-3bg7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/semaphore/securing-kubernetes-deployments-3bg7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T13:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent survey by Red Hat found that more than half of the Kubernetes environments are misconfigured. Even worse, about 90% of respondents had at least one security incident last year, leading to the very first wave of Kubernetes-native malware. In this tutorial, we present three tools to validate and secure your Kubernetes deployments.
Kubernetes main selling point is in its declarative nature — we write a manifest describing the desired final state of a deployment and let the platform figure out the rest. But the fact of the matter is that these manifests are easy to get wrong, breaking stuff in the process.
Continuous delivery with Kubernetes is only viable when we test at every stage. For example:
 First, test the code in the build stage.
 Then, build the container image and check its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Fernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Features and Advantages of Google Kubernetes Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/key-features-and-advantages-of-google-kubernetes-engine-2jf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/key-features-and-advantages-of-google-kubernetes-engine-2jf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T13:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Overview
It is an extensible and portable open-source platform used to manage containers. It was created by Google, also known as K8s, which makes many computers or machines work in one unit. Through Kubernetes, several people can utilize containerized apps that work together, whether the apps are on various platforms.
Why To Opt For GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine)?
GKE helps a lot in app development services as it manages containerized applications. There are many reasons to select GKE, and some of them are mentioned below.
Google developed both GKE and Kubernetes. So, there is an excellent team, and GKE provides easy integration with plentiful Google services.

It offers nodes auto-scaling that Amazon Kubernetes and Azure container Services lack.

Any new tool or feature releas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Performance Monitoring For SREs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/application-performance-monitoring-for-sres-475e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/application-performance-monitoring-for-sres-475e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T12:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of monitoring systems and applications has been around for years. Ensuring that a system and application are performing the way they're supposed to isn't anything new. It's simply a component that's been changing drastically, specifically with application performance and load using a practice called Application Performance Monitoring (APM).
So why is APM important now and why should you care? In this blog post, you're going to learn about APM, why it's important, and how to get started.
In the early days of software, tools started to come out for understanding how much load a system running an application could take. A notable tool is Apache JMeter, which is a load testing tool for analyzing and measuring performance. The first release of JMeter was in 1998, which means the idea o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Levan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of AWS: Quantum, Robotics, Satellite, Security, Identity, Compliance, and Storage Services |AWS WhitePaper Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/overview-of-aws-quantum-robotics-satellite-security-identity-compliance-and-storage-services-aws-whitepaper-summary-2ahi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/overview-of-aws-quantum-robotics-satellite-security-identity-compliance-and-storage-services-aws-whitepaper-summary-2ahi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T12:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum Technologies



Amazon Braket is a fully managed quantum computing service that helps researchers and developers get started with the technology to accelerate research and discovery. Amazon Braket provides a development environment for you to explore and build quantum algorithms, test them on quantum circuit simulators, and run them on different quantum hardware technologies.

AWS RoboMaker is a service that makes it easy to develop, test, and deploy intelligent robotics applications at scale. RoboMaker extends the most widely used open-source robotics software framework, Robot Operating System (ROS), with connectivity to cloud services. This includes AWS machine learning services, monitoring services, and analytics services that enable a robot to stream data, navigate, communicate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>‪Karim Negm‬‏</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conduct A Web Application Penetration Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/khalilpreview/conduct-a-web-application-penetration-testing-27f5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/khalilpreview/conduct-a-web-application-penetration-testing-27f5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T10:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this digital age when everything is being done online, web applications have become an integral part of all businesses. Since today’s web applications usually store or send out sensitive data, they attract malicious hackers and script kiddies, at an unprecedented level, to find and exploit vulnerabilities in them for their personal gain or just to have fun.
To secure your web application, security testing is the best way to identify security loopholes and misconfiguration flaws in your application before malicious hackers do. This is achieved by simulating attacks in order to find the potential vulnerabilities in your application.
Web application penetration testing a.k.a web app pentesting is essential as it helps in determining the security posture of the entire web application includ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalil Preview</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Security Vulnerabilities to Fix Without any Programming Skill]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smartscanner/5-security-vulnerabilities-to-fix-without-any-programming-skill-37in</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smartscanner/5-security-vulnerabilities-to-fix-without-any-programming-skill-37in"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T10:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We usually think security and hacking are complicated—at least it's super geeky in movies—but you will be surprised to see how easy you can fix some security problems even without programming knowledge. Let's review and fix them right away.
Do you use 123456 to login into your website? Change it now! Easy passwords can be guessed and cracked in minutes.
passphrase.
Outdated applications are like open doors for hackers to break in. Hackers search the whole Internet for outdated applications of any kind (web server, CMS, router, etc.). If you're using outdated software, you've already become a target for hackers.
Does your website display a list of files and folders when the URL ends with a slash (/)? If yes, you have a directory listing issue you need to fix.
A universal and easy fix for th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SmartScanner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Node.js admin panel]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/forestadmin/how-to-build-a-nodejs-admin-panel-379b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/forestadmin/how-to-build-a-nodejs-admin-panel-379b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T09:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is great about Node.js is that it allows for building even complex applications that can handle a plethora of real-time data. In the last couple of years, many well-known established companies like Netflix, eBay, or Uber have rewritten their microservices using Node.js. LinkedIn, in turn, has successfully migrated a part of the code that has been written in Ruby on Rails to Node.js. It shouldn’t come as a surprise that robust applications need robust internal tools.
Node.js doesn’t have a default admin panel solution like Django Admin for Django or Active Admin for Ruby on Rails. However, there are quite a few options for building an admin panel for a Node.js application:
Build all internal tools in-house from scratch. This option gives you the maximum flexibility but it also comes wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monika Ambrozowicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[😎 How to convert a normal React form to use react-hook-form?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxprogramming/how-to-convert-a-normal-react-form-to-use-react-hook-form-26g9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxprogramming/how-to-convert-a-normal-react-form-to-use-react-hook-form-26g9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T09:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone!


Nice to see you all around again! Today you'll find out how easy it is to use the  react-hook-form  library for forms instead of the normal method of forms in React.

So, the first thing is first, normally, in React we use state, and whenever the value of an input changes, we change the state. This method's good but there is a lot of code. Here's how the code looks like in this case.
import { useState } from 'react';

export default function LoginForm() {
  const [email, setEmail] = useState('');
  const [password, setPassword] = useState('');

  const onSubmit = (e) => {
    e.preventDefault()
    // Submit logic
  }

  return (
    <div>
      <form onSubmit={onSubmit}>
        <input
          type='email'
          value={email}
          onChange={e => setEmail(e.targe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Programming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React doesn't need state management tool, I said]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tolgee_i18n/react-doesnt-need-state-management-tool-i-said-31l4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tolgee_i18n/react-doesnt-need-state-management-tool-i-said-31l4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T08:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From time to time someone still tells me that is using REDUX or similar tool in their project. I usually respond, that I wouldn't use it as now with hooks and context API you don't need it.
But context API usually brings performance problems and is also a bit awkward to use it properly, so today I'll try to show how to avoid common problems, and also build your own (micro) state management tool, without any compromises.
Basic idea is to manage state in one component and pass the whole it by context so it's accessible from all child components, so we can avoid props drilling.
export const StateContext = createContext(null);
const Provider = () => {
  return (
    <StateContext.Provider value={state}>
      <ChildComponent />
    </StateContext.Provider>
  )
}

However you also need some way…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stepan662</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Login with Session Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/angular-login-with-session-authentication-noi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/angular-login-with-session-authentication-noi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T08:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this article, we'll look at how to handle the login process with Session Authentication. We'll verify if the user is logged in or not, and if he is not, then the route will simply be blocked.
Let’s go through the following Angular principles for better understanding.
Angular Routing module
Manage the user authentication permission for the Angular path.
Angular Auth Guard
This Angular function helps a lot when it comes to handling authentication. This is an interface that instructs the router whether or not to enable navigation to a specific route. We're using the 'canActivate' guard form in this case.
Angular localStorage
In an Angular program, there are three ways to store data on the client-side.
Memory
Session storage
Local Storage.
We're using localStorage in this cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring Symfony 2.7 App with Apache 2.4 HTTP Server on Ubuntu 20.04]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jsv1280/configuring-symfony-27-app-with-apache-24-http-server-on-ubuntu-2004-35b1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jsv1280/configuring-symfony-27-app-with-apache-24-http-server-on-ubuntu-2004-35b1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T04:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, when we are configuring legacy applications is difficult to find accurate documentation about the used tools (Dependencies, Libraries, Environment).
Currently, Symfony's version is 5.3.10 thus actual documentation points out towards these newer versions from the framework even though previous documentation is still accessible since version 2.7

Avoid looking for hundred sites and freaking out whether any solutions work or work partially, in this post we are going a step to step to configure a Symfony 2.7 app in Apache 2.4 HTTP Server running in Ubuntu 20.04.
I don't recommend editing etc/apache2/apache2.conf because it is the main configuration file of Apache so if you broke that file probably your Apache will not work.
Add the next code in etc/apache2/sites-available/000-default…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jairo Salazar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Manipulate Files on the Command line]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dolamu/7-easy-tips-to-manipulate-files-on-the-linux-command-line-2glf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dolamu/7-easy-tips-to-manipulate-files-on-the-linux-command-line-2glf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T00:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found the linux command line quite intimidating when I first started learning to code. It seemed to require extensive and comprehensive knowledge and understanding of commands and keyboard shortcuts. However, as I read more about it and practiced what I learned, I realized that it isn't as scary as it seemed; that It only requires a lot of constant practice. I also discovered that others feel the same way, which made me realise that I wasn't alone.
The other thing I discovered during this period is that we are all beginners and sharing is helpful, since no one is an island. So I decided to share my experience with others starting out as well. As we all know, learning is never-ending. There will always be new tools and new commands to learn, especially when you're a beginner. The followin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dolamu Asipa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get or access the properties and methods of h6 HTML element tags without errors in TypeScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/melvin2016/how-to-get-or-access-the-properties-and-methods-of-h6-html-element-tags-without-errors-in-typescript-443</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/melvin2016/how-to-get-or-access-the-properties-and-methods-of-h6-html-element-tags-without-errors-in-typescript-443"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally posted here!
To get or access the properties and methods of the h6 HTML element tags without having errors or red squiggly lines in TypeScript, you have to assert the type for the h6 HTML element tag using the HTMLHeadingElement interface in TypeScript.
The errors or warnings are shown by the TypeScript compiler since the compiler doesn't know more information on the h6 HTML element tag ahead of time. But we know that we are referencing the h6 HTML tag and thus we can tell the compiler to use the HTMLHeadingElement interface which contains the declarations for properties and methods.
// get reference to the first 'h6'
// HTML element tag in the document
// with type assertion using the HTMLHeadingElement interface
const h6Tag = document.querySelector("h6") as HTMLHeadingElement;…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MELVIN GEORGE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlight active menu item with scrollspy hook ⚛]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rgolawski/highlight-active-menu-item-with-scrollspy-hook-1gpp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rgolawski/highlight-active-menu-item-with-scrollspy-hook-1gpp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T21:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is scrollspy?


Scrollspy is a mechanism that highlights an active menu item based on current scroll position to indicate which section is currently visible in the viewport. It's available in Bootstrap (see the docs), but right now let's implement it from scratch using React and TypeScript.
Before we start, let's add some helper functions that we will use for computations in our hook. Also, this way we keep logic separated and make our code look cleaner.
// Restrict value to be between the range [0, value]
const clamp = (value: number) => Math.max(0, value);

// Check if number is between two values
const isBetween = (value: number, floor: number, ceil: number) =>
  value >= floor && value <= ceil;

Once we're ready with helpers, we can jump to the hook code.
const useScrollspy = (ids…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafał Goławski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding view count to your Nextjs Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/adding-view-count-to-your-nextjs-blog-55lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/100lvlmaster/adding-view-count-to-your-nextjs-blog-55lj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T20:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alright lads, this will be a quick one. I want to add the views count functionality on my personal portfolio website's blog section.

Expected behavior:
  Blogs Page : List of blogs -> Show count.
 Blog Page : Particular Article -> Show count and  Increment count.
How to achieve:
Use supabase to store count by slug
Stored procedure to increment count
Tools that I'll need:
supabase : open source firebase alternative 
swr : data fetching
Create a table views with schema like such:
slug -> text -> primary key
created_at -> timestamp -> now()
count ->  int2 
count:



Fetch count
Increment one
Fetch count again
Now we can reduce this to one db call using stored procedures:

create function increment (slug_text text)
returns void as
$$
update views
set count = count + 1
where slug = slug_text;
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Navin Kodag</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building More Than Just a YouTube Video Downloader]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/benank/building-more-than-just-a-youtube-video-downloader-1ko7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/benank/building-more-than-just-a-youtube-video-downloader-1ko7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T17:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the dance game I'm making, I want players to be able to use any YouTube video and dance to it. To put it simply, they'll paste a YouTube link into the game and it'll analyze it for them and they'll be able to dance to it, being scored in realtime as they dance along. (take a look at the previous blog posts if you need more context!)
I don't want to embed YouTube videos in my game. There's a few reasons for this:
TensorFlow.js (the machine learning platform that I'm using) can't analyze an embedded YouTube video. The video needs to be inside of an accessible <video> (or similar) element on the webpage and cannot be embedded.
Improving the editor user experience - to create new dance charts from YouTube videos, a player needs to go to the Create tab and make a new project, using a YouTub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Technical Side Of Fitness]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/haileyhahnnnn/the-technical-side-of-fitness-4k5b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/haileyhahnnnn/the-technical-side-of-fitness-4k5b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building my Dream Application


For those who are fitness gurus like me, I never quite found an app that track everything in one app without the prescription fee. Even when it comes with a prescription fee, I still am not fully satisfied with what it entails. I have tried using a few different apps throughout the last few years like MyFitnessPal, the apple watch health and even Kayla Itsines "Sweat" app. But in the end, fitness is really about having a truly healthy lifestyle and not just working out. 
Food: cooking, baking, meal prepping 
Athletics: Tracking Calories, progress, workouts 
lifestyle: motivation and a safe community
What you eat is just as important as how you exercise. Meaning that you have to track what you eat no matter what your goals are. I want this app to give people …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>haileyhahnnnn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js error-handling gotcha: synchronous errors from an asynchronous function]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shalvah/nodejs-error-handling-gotcha-synchronous-errors-from-an-asynchronous-function-3d8f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shalvah/nodejs-error-handling-gotcha-synchronous-errors-from-an-asynchronous-function-3d8f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T16:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing to look out for in Node.js: functions that may throw an error either synchronously or asynchronously (which, technically, is any function that does async work). You may think you've got pretty good error-handling, but they complicate things.
For instance, here's a basic example:
function getAdditionalData(input) {
  const url = getRequestUrl(input);

  return makeHttprequest(url).then(response => {
    return response.data;
  });
}

app.get('/data', (req, res) => {
  const input = calculateInput();
  return getAdditionalData(input).then(result => {
    return { input, result };
  });
});

This is a simple endpoint that calls getAdditionalData() to get some data and return to the user. The function does an asynchronous thing (HTTP request), so it returns a promise.
Let's think abo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shalvah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load-Balanced MEAN-Stack by AWS CloudFormation & Docker 🐳]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tgotwig/load-balanced-mean-stack-by-aws-cloudformation-docker-3pj9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tgotwig/load-balanced-mean-stack-by-aws-cloudformation-docker-3pj9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T16:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short article I will show how to deploy a Mean-Stack app by AWS-CLI and CloudFormation using a v1 load-balancer 😃
All the code regarding our deployment you can also find here:
https://github.com/TGotwig/devops
We take usage of an very nice and simple MEAN-Stack project which comes from Brad Traversy 🤗
Download the sample repo and cd into it:
git clone git@github.com:TGotwig/devops.git
cd aws-cloudformation/solutions/advanced/mean-stack

Install the awscli from somewhere and login:
aws configure --profile <YOUR_AWS_ACCOUNT_NAME>

You will be asked for two IDs, you can get them through:

 

Create a file called parameters.json:
[
  {
    "ParameterKey": "KeyName",
    "ParameterValue": "<KeyName>"
  }
]

Replace <KeyName> by your SSH key under EC2 / Key Pairs:

Create a file called .env for the Makefile:
stack-name=simple-mean-stack
profile=<YOUR_AWS_ACCOUNT_NAME>
region=<YOUR_AWS_REGION>

Start it by running make up, an EC2 machine should boot up:

After some time we can reach the app, run make getUrl to get the url:

After refreshing the page few times you should see another IP:

You can remove the entire stack by running make rm! 🔥 
Awesome! Now we have finished our load-balanced Mean-Stack app 😎🎉]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Gotwig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Node.js to the latest version on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mdmarufsarker/how-to-update-nodejs-to-the-latest-version-on-ubuntu-3md6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mdmarufsarker/how-to-update-nodejs-to-the-latest-version-on-ubuntu-3md6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T14:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1st of all you need to download the latest version of Nodejs from the official Nodejs website
Go to the correct path using command line or GUI.
cd Downloads/node-v17.0.1-linux-x64.tar.xz/
tar -xf node-v17.0.1-linux-x64.tar.xz

Check Current Node version
node --version
v14.17.0

To upgrade
sudo n latest

Check Updated Node version
node --version
v17.0.1


If you are using graphical interface then go to the destination path. Click right button and select extract here. Open the bin folder.

sudo n latest

Check Updated Node version
node --version
v17.0.1


Playlist]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Maruf Sarker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Update Node.js to the latest version on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mdmarufsarker/how-to-update-nodejs-to-the-latest-version-on-ubuntu-3md6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mdmarufsarker/how-to-update-nodejs-to-the-latest-version-on-ubuntu-3md6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T14:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1st of all you need to download the latest version of Nodejs from the official Nodejs website
Go to the correct path using command line or GUI.
cd Downloads/node-v17.0.1-linux-x64.tar.xz/
tar -xf node-v17.0.1-linux-x64.tar.xz

Check Current Node version
node --version
v14.17.0

To upgrade
sudo n latest

Check Updated Node version
node --version
v17.0.1


If you are using graphical interface then go to the destination path. Click right button and select extract here. Open the bin folder.

sudo n latest

Check Updated Node version
node --version
v17.0.1


Playlist]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Maruf Sarker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node version and Nextjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yobretyo/node-version-and-nextjs-11d7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yobretyo/node-version-and-nextjs-11d7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T13:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can a out dated node version cause next not to work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bret</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I structured my first Express App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zisan34/how-i-structured-my-first-express-app-20ik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zisan34/how-i-structured-my-first-express-app-20ik"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T13:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pretty much a beginner dev, working for 2years as a developer. During this period most of the time, I’ve used PHP as backend but recently my company assigned me to a project in which I had to use Node(Express) as backend. So here’s the story about my first MERN stack app.
TLDR

During this short period of my career, I got the opportunity to work with several technologies. As I’m working as a Full-Stack dev so previously I had hands-on experience with Laravel, React, Vue, Mysql other related techs. I was very excited when my company assigned me to a MERN stack app. That was a huge transition. I took that as a challenge and decided that I’d prepare myself for larger apps built with the MERN stack. So that’s why even the purpose of the app is simple but the structure is not. Basically, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fazlul Kabir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[ytdl-s3bucket]: Uploading Video Files to s3 Bucket with Python Using Youtube_dl]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/munazhe/ytdl-s3bucket-uploading-video-files-to-s3-bucket-with-python-using-youtubedl-341g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/munazhe/ytdl-s3bucket-uploading-video-files-to-s3-bucket-with-python-using-youtubedl-341g"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T13:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source Code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>munazhé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Connect Your Server To Your Phone.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emanuelone/how-to-connect-your-server-to-your-phone-ikg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emanuelone/how-to-connect-your-server-to-your-phone-ikg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T08:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's is Needed



Mobile Hotspot
A running Server.
Let begin.
Firstly, Turn on your mobile Hotspot
npx create-react-app new_react_project
cd new_react_project
npm start

localhost:3000


3000 is the PORT number
ipconfig 

ip a

192.168.43.198
localhost
192.168.43.198:3000
Congratulations, you can now serve your contents to your phone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Ifeanyi MECHIE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Developer environment setup for a new Ubuntu/ Ubuntu based distro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_mohanmurali/web-developer-environment-setup-for-a-new-ubuntu-ubuntu-based-distro-bpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_mohanmurali/web-developer-environment-setup-for-a-new-ubuntu-ubuntu-based-distro-bpn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T05:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I will share the common developer environment setup steps once you have a new Ubuntu/Ubuntu based distro setup. This can be a clean OS installation or a Windows subsystem for Linux setup.
So the first thing we need to do is update the existing packages currently present. To do that we need to run the following command in the terminal. This will make sure that you have the latest security patches updated in your instance.
sudo apt-get update
sudo apt-get upgrade

Now we will install NodeJs. We will install NodeJs using the apt package manager which is the default package manager for Ubuntu. We need to use the following command on the terminal to install the latest LTS version of NodeJs.
sudo apt install nodejs

Verify that node is installed using the below command
node -v

Node…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohan Murali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Moderno #3 | Objetos Literales.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jleondev/javascript-moderno-3-objetos-literales-50pf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jleondev/javascript-moderno-3-objetos-literales-50pf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T02:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En esta serie de posts repasaremos features modernas del lenguaje de programación JavaScript que harán de tu vida como programador mucho más fácil, pero antes te dejo las otras entregas de esta serie:
#1 Variables y Constantes


#2 Template String



Vayamos al tema de hoy. Lo primero que tenemos que entender, es que no hay una sola forma de utilizar objetos en JavaScript, en este post vamos a ver cómo utilizar objetos literales y cómo estos nos permiten trabajar con POO de manera muy rápida y nada verbosa.
Crear un objeto literal es muy sencillo, se comienza con la definición e inicialización de una variable o constante (mi post anterior trata sobre esto), así:
const desarrollador = {} // Si, eso es todo 👀

Esto es muy parecido a lo que en otros lenguajes se le llama diccionario, mapa o …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph León</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Free Fully Functional Blog in Angular and Firebase]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jdgamble555/a-free-fully-functional-blog-in-angular-and-firebase-e4j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jdgamble555/a-free-fully-functional-blog-in-angular-and-firebase-e4j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T22:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I've decided to release my source code on github for my Fireblog.io fully functional blog written in Angular, using Firestore as the database, and hosted on Cloud Run.
--- scroll down for screenshots, or Fireblog.io ---
I was originally hosted on Firebase Functions, but I wanted it to be a little bit faster, and the ng deploy to Firebase Functions also stopped working as expected. In fact, I wonder what the Angular Firebase Team is doing at all these days. The documentation for Angular Firebase 9 is still not up-to-date, and it seems like they are behind on updating to Angular 13 (to be fair, it has only been a few days at this point).
Before I get into anything, I have to recommend you check out Fireship.io, as it is the reason I have become proficient in these technologies. 
I have r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Gamble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An online shop API Node js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devtips3/an-online-shop-api-node-js-4l38</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devtips3/an-online-shop-api-node-js-4l38"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T20:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[onlineshop-api
Features:
Technology Stack:
Github : https://github.com/saidMounaim/onlineshop-api
Follow me on github : https://github.com/saidMounaim/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dev tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : RxJS concatMap operator]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dipteekhd/angular-rxjs-concatmap-operator-4614</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dipteekhd/angular-rxjs-concatmap-operator-4614"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T14:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Angular, we use HTTP to get data from backend,HTTP methods always return an observable.Generally we subscribe to that observable and assign response data to class variables to use it in our component.
But using RxJS operators we can compose multiple observables(data streams) or process  observable data  before subscribing to it.
RxJS concatMap operator
Observable emits observable).
concatMap operator
Takes each value from the outer observable and maps that value  to observable(called as inner observable) 
Concat all inner observables into a single observable in order  and subscribe to inner observables and emit data of each inner observable into output observable in sequential manner.
concatMap never subscribes to the next inner observable until the previous one completes.
Example:

Run live
Here we have 2 API’s
In the above case we need to take all roll numbers from the first API  and pass it to the second API.

So solution to this problem is use concatMap RxJS operator instead of nested subscription.

First contactMap operator -
getToppers_rollNum() this method returns an Observable of type number[] , conactMap  maps Observable<number[]> to Observable <number>(inner observable) then subscribes to inner observable and emit data into output observable(top_3_rollNum$).
Second  concatMap operator -
top_3_rollNum$ as outer observable.concatMap takes each roll number from the outer observable and hits http request sequentially(here we have 3 inner observables return by 3 http requests) & emits http response data into output observable(topper_marks$).
concatMap never hits the next http request until the previous one completes.
Shorthand syntax for above code

So,concatMap is used where sequence of execution matters.
Thanks for reading! If you found this helpful please share!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>diptee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how to use secondary entrypoints in your Angular Libraries in Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kauppfbi_96/why-and-how-to-use-secondary-entrypoints-in-your-angular-libraries-in-nx-3bb2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kauppfbi_96/why-and-how-to-use-secondary-entrypoints-in-your-angular-libraries-in-nx-3bb2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T09:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Sangga Rima Roman Selia on Unsplash
Nx Devtools recently released version 13.1, which came with a very handy generator for Angular libraries, which creates secondary entrypoints for your Angular Libraries with ease. In this blog post we will cover why and how we should make use of this new function.
By adding secondary entrypoints, we basically split our Angular libraries into multiple chunks, just like Angular Material does.
// One entrypoint: 
import { MatButtonModule, MatCardModule } from '@angular/material';

// With secondary entrypoints:
import { MatButtonModule } from '@angular/material/button';
import { MatCardModule } from '@angular/material/card';

The idea behind it is not new at all, this option already exists since the beginning phase of ng-packagr. By leveraging seco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kauppfbi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favicons: How to Make Sure Browsers Only Download the SVG Version]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355780</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/favicons-how-to-make-sure-browsers-only-download-the-svg-version/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T20:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Šime Vidas DM’d me the other day about this thread from subzey on Twitter. My HTML for favicons was like this:
<!-- Warning! Typo! --<link rel="icon" href="/favicon.ico" size="any"<link rel="icon" href="/favicon.svg" type="image/svg+xml"
The attribute size is a typo there, …
The post Favicons: How to Make Sure Browsers Only Download the SVG Version appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, Design Systems Do Improve Developer Efficiency and Design Consistency]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355888</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/yes-design-systems-do-improve-developer-efficiency-and-design-consistency/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T19:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the toughest things about being someone who cares deeply about design systems is making the case for a dedicated design system. Folks in leadership will often ask you to prove the value of it. Why should we care …
The post Yes, Design Systems Do Improve Developer Efficiency and Design Consistency appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git and GitHub Tutorial – Version Control for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>617acb5b33422e07df366c9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T18:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git and GitHub are two technologies that every developer should learn, irrespective of their field.  If you're a beginner developer, you might think that these two terms mean the same thing – but they're different.  This tutorial will help you understand what Git and version control are, the basic Git commands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Key Not Working? Here&#x27;s How to Fix It [Windows 10 PC Guide]]]></title>
        <id>61850c138bcfae07ca4e245f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/windows-key-not-working-heres-how-to-fix-it-windows-10-pc-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T17:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On your Windows machine, the Windows key launches the Start menu, and from there you can access anything on your computer.  When you press it in combination with other keys, it also acts as a useful shortcut to utilities you don't get easily through your computer's graphic user interface (GUI)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript String Contains – How to use JS .includes()]]></title>
        <id>6182162c8bcfae07ca4e0737</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-string-contains-how-to-use-js-includes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T16:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In JavaScript you can use the .includes() method to see if one string is found in another. But how does it work exactly? In this article, I will walk you through a few code examples of the JavaScript string method called .includes().  Basic .includes() SyntaxHere is the basic syntax for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basics of CURL command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mr_destructive/basics-of-curl-command-20nc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mr_destructive/basics-of-curl-command-20nc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T16:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


We all might have used the curl command but might be unaware of it. It's super old
Curl or cURL command is the utility or tool to access the internet from the command
Before we talk about how to use the curl command let's talk about why might we need
curl or Client URL is a command-line utility that helps in accessing/posting
 It basically serves as a
curl URL arguments 

The above is a basic structure of the curl command. We see the argument
curl "https://github.com"   

From this query to github.com, you are literally going to GitHub.com and getting a response as the entire HTML source code of the page.
curl "https://github.com" >temp.html

With this command, we store the output of the command in the file temp.html, it can be any other file you like. 
It turns out that you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meet Gor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Animated Chart of Nested Squares Using Masks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355623</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-an-animated-chart-of-nested-squares-using-masks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have many well-known chart types: bar, donut, line, pie, you name it. All popular chart libraries support these. Then there are the chart types that do not even have a name. Check out this dreamt-up chart with stacked (nested) …
The post How to Create an Animated Chart of Nested Squares Using Masks appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mészáros Róbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[enterkeyhint]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355902</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/enterkeyhint/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only just recently learned the enterkeyhint attribute on form inputs was a thing! It seems like kind of a big deal to me, as crafting HTML form markup is a decent slice of a front-end developer’s life, and this …
The post enterkeyhint appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add Google Adsense code in angular 9 application?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/indiantrain/how-to-add-google-adsense-code-in-angular-9-application-3gjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/indiantrain/how-to-add-google-adsense-code-in-angular-9-application-3gjh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have added Google Adsense to my angular site. It shows ads on some pages and doesn't on some pages. I will show the example of pages which doesn't shows ads, suppose we go to this page "https://www.indiantrain.in/train-time-table", in the search box we have filled the train number and hit get schedule button. It will redirect to other page. Almost all the features of my site is in this manner only. I think angular block the Adsense script and that's why it doesn't load all the time. As we already know, outside script need to sanitize in order to run in angular. So, I just want to know the proper way to add Google Adsense to my site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Indian Train</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in @this-dot@route-config v1.2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/whats-new-in-this-dotroute-config-v12-f3k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/whats-new-in-this-dotroute-config-v12-f3k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, we introduced our first open source library to have easier access to RouterModule config's data property. If you haven't read about it yet, I recommend reading my colleague’s introductory blog post.
Since the first release, we received great feedback from the community, and we've been working on improving the developer experience using it. In this article, I'd like to share with you the new features we've introduced, and how to use them.
*tdRouteData)


One of the new features we've introduced is a directive for directly accessing the current route data property from within the component's template. This is a structural directive that binds the whole data property to the local variable we define. To use it, we need to add a *tdRouteData directive attribute to a tag that we want i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Linux Dot Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/opfour/common-linux-dot-files-3b55</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/opfour/common-linux-dot-files-3b55"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T09:16:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, dotfiles are simply configuration files where software programs store their configuration settings in plain, text-based files or directories.
Syntax: 
Dot File Name 
    Format Purpose

.bash_history 
    File History of commands typed at a Bash command prompt.

.bash_logout 
    File Script that's run when logging out of a text-mode Bash shell.

.bash_profile 
    File Script that's run when starting up a text-mode Bash shell.

.bashrc
    File Script that's run when starting up a text-mode Bash shell.

.DCOPServer_*
    Filename varies with the computer's name; status file for the Desktop Communication Protocol (DCOP), which is used by KDE to help manage interprogram communications.

.dmrc 
    File KDE Display Manager (KDM) configuration file; specifies what desktop 
    envi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opfour</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 50 Linux Commands You Must Know as a Regular User]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kiransethu46/top-50-linux-commands-you-must-know-as-a-regular-user-9bo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kiransethu46/top-50-linux-commands-you-must-know-as-a-regular-user-9bo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T05:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top 50 Linux Commands You Must Know as a Regular User are
ls - view contents of directory (list)


pwd - path of the current directory


cd -  change directory


mkdir - make new directory 


mv - move files / rename files


cp - copy files 


rm - remove files


touch - create blank new file


rmdir - delete directory


cat - list content of file to terminal


clear - clear terminal window


echo - move data into a file


less - Read text file one screen at a time


man - show manual of Linux commands 


sudo - enables you to perform tasks that require administrative or root permissions


top - task manager in terminal


tar - used to archive multiple files into a tarball


grep - used to searching words in specific files


head - view first lines of any text file


tail - view last l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiran Sethumadhavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Svelte, and Comparing Svelte with React and Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355937</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/introducing-svelte-and-comparing-svelte-with-react-and-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T21:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Collingsworth is clearly a big fan of Svelte, so while this is a fun and useful comparison article, it’s here to crown Svelte the winner all the way through.
A few things I find compelling:
One of the 
…
The post Introducing Svelte, and Comparing Svelte with React and Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code extensions NOT only for Frontend developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/smetankajakub/vscode-extensions-not-only-for-frontend-developers-30aj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/smetankajakub/vscode-extensions-not-only-for-frontend-developers-30aj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prettier - Code formatter


It is code formatter with support of many languages. It can automatically format the code right after save which save your time and increase productivity. 

This extension is used for more friendly comments, you are able to customize tags by your own. Very easy configurations with support to plenty of programming languages.

Snippets for Angular, Typescript, HTML.

Extension to autocomplete filenames.

This extension take care of completion of CSS class in HTML.

Javascript Linter extension.

This extension provide to you useful information from git on hovering of each line. Easy to explore repository, with possibility to be fast redirected to requested file in your Source Control Client (GitHub, BitBucket, ...).

Is lightweight Rest API Client. It is alternative to Postman not that heavy but still useful.

Helps to launch local development server with live reloading of static and dynamic pages as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Smetanka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C vs C++ – What&#x27;s The Difference?]]></title>
        <id>618180828bcfae07ca4e03d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-vs-cpp-whats-the-difference/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T20:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The C and C++ programming languages power a large part of the world's products, applications, and websites.  Each helped lay the foundation for the creation of many popular programming languages, such as Java. They also support many languages that you might use regularly for your programming projects, such as Python.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I was invited to Adventures in Angular podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomaszs2/i-was-invited-to-adventures-in-angular-podcast-286b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomaszs2/i-was-invited-to-adventures-in-angular-podcast-286b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T19:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately I was invited to Adventures in Angular podcast by Charles Max Wood. We were talking about a method to improve Angular development with Visu Studio Code
check it out]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Smykowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Break and Continue Statements – Loop Control Statements in C Explained]]></title>
        <id>61751bafd48e1707b6d7aa12</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-break-and-continue-statements-loop-control-statements-in-c-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the C programming language, there are times when you'll want to change looping behavior. And the continue and the break statements help you skip iterations, and exit from loops under certain conditions. In this tutorial, you'll learn how break and continue statements alter the control flow of your program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing the Drift in Shape Rotations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356047</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fixing-the-drift-in-shape-rotations/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T17:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Ruiz calls this post an “extra-obscure edition of design tool micro-UX,” but I find it fascinating! If you select a bunch of elements in a design tool, then rotate then, then later select those same elements and try to …
The post Fixing the Drift in Shape Rotations appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Replit – A Beginner&#x27;s Guide]]></title>
        <id>6182d4c28bcfae07ca4e0d18</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-replit/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T15:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Replit is a popular free online IDE that you can use to create your projects with very little setup. This editor supports over 50 languages and many programming courses use it, including freeCodeCamp.  In this article, I will show you how to get started with Replit and show you how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desktop Icons Missing – How to Fix Windows 10 PC Icons that Have Disappeared]]></title>
        <id>6183a45e8bcfae07ca4e1470</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/desktop-icons-missing-how-to-fix-windows-10-pc-icons-that-have-disappeared/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T15:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Desktop icons are a convenient way to launch apps and open folders. They've actually become the de facto way of opening apps because many apps create them automatically when installed.  So what happens when you can't find your desktop icons on your computer anymore? Well, you might have mistakenly hidden]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scroll-Linked Animations With the Web Animations API (WAAPI) and ScrollTimeline]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355060</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scroll-linked-animations-with-the-web-animations-api-waapi-and-scrolltimeline/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scroll-linked Animations specification is an upcoming and experimental addition that allows us to link animation-progress to scroll-progress: as you scroll up and down a scroll container, a linked animation also advances or rewinds accordingly.
We covered some use cases …
The post Scroll-Linked Animations With the Web Animations API (WAAPI) and ScrollTimeline appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bramus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Lead Generation Tips for Freelance Developers]]></title>
        <id>616e581dd48e1707b6d77deb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lead-generation-freelancers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a freelancer, targeting your desired clients requires time and effort, and sometimes money.  While spending money to generate leads can be a good thing, in this article I want to focus on the free lead generation tips to get clients as a freelance developer, all in a quick and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vcruntime140.dll Was Not Found [Solved on Windows 10 PC]]]></title>
        <id>61839bcd8bcfae07ca4e1422</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vcruntime140-dll-was-not-found-solved-on-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever tried to open an app on your computer only to see the error "The program can't start because vcruntime140.dll is missing from your computer. Try reinstalling it to fix this problem."?  This is a common issue with Windows 10 and it can be quite]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Applications for Everybody - Dr. Chuck Teaches HTML, JavaScript, PHP, SQL, and More]]></title>
        <id>6183db8b8bcfae07ca4e15f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-applications-for-everybody-dr-chuck/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T13:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of diverse skills required to create a modern web application can be intimidating to beginners. But with the right teacher and the right mindset, everybody can learn to create complex web applications. We just published Web Applications for Everybody on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. This 14-hour course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 13 ya esta disponible]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/macaoblog/angular-13-ya-esta-disponible-2oce</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/macaoblog/angular-13-ya-esta-disponible-2oce"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T08:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Articulo original de Angular Blog por Mark Thompson
ng update en su proyecto. También tenemos una guía de actualización disponible en update.angular.io para ayudar a los equipos a obtener instrucciones sobre cómo actualizar sus proyectos.
Con cada nuevo lanzamiento  nuestro objetivo es encontrar maneras de mejorar Angular. En esta versión, lo hemos logrado mediante la expansión de las funciones y optimizaciones basadas en Ivy, asociándonos con nuestra excelente comunidad Angular y continuando brindando un proceso de actualización estable y fluido para sus equipos y proyectos.
En la versión v12 de mayo de 2021 hablamos sobre "Ivy Everywhere" y mencionamos que habría algunos cambios importantes en Angular para respaldar esta iniciativa. Hemos sido diligentes en la búsqueda de esto y estamos …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Cardenas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ToDo app with Sifu code generator]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vesindusko/todo-app-with-sifu-code-generator-179a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vesindusko/todo-app-with-sifu-code-generator-179a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T07:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of promoting DRY (don't repeat yourself), MDD (model-driven development), and code generator, I would like to show its full power on a real-life example.
We will implement a simple ToDo app with backend and client app. Let's start.
First we will define the project with basic informations.
todo project[
    url www.todo.com 
    namespace com.todo
    version 1 . 0 . 0 . 0
    environments prod
    developer(duskovesin)
]( 

Now we will define the #backendpart of the app.
backend server[
        owners(duskovesin)
        template springboot(tests fabut)        
    ]

We are starting with the definition of User and Todo #models, with a few fields and Todo Status #enums.
        UserRole enum(
            ADMIN
            MEMBER
        )

        Status enum(
            NOT_START…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vesin Dusko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 10: Browser Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-10-browser-wars/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T15:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June of 1995, representatives from Microsoft arrived at the Netscape offices. The stated goal was to find ways to work together—Netscape as the single dominant force in the browser market and Microsoft as a tech giant just beginning to …
The post Chapter 10: Browser Wars appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proxying Third-Party JavaScript as First-Party JavaScript (and the Potential Effect on Analytics)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354619</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/proxying-third-party-javascript-as-first-party-javascript-and-the-potential-effect-on-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T22:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, check out how incredibly easy it is to write a Cloudflare Worker to proxy another URL:
addEventListener("fetch", (event) ={
  event.respondWith(
     fetch("https://css-tricks.com")
  );
});
It doesn’t have any error handling or anything, but hey, it works:
Now imagine how …
The post Proxying Third-Party JavaScript as First-Party JavaScript (and the Potential Effect on Analytics) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355016</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/gui-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T21:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I keep bookmarking Adam’s GUI Challenges posts/videos and, before I even have a chance to review and link them up, another one is already published! Fortunately, the homepage for them on web.dev is a nice roundup. 
For example, a recent …
The post GUI Challenges appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebase vs. Merge: Integrating Changes in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354734</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/rebase-vs-merge-integrating-changes-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T14:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is part of our “Advanced Git” series. Be sure to follow us on Twitter or sign up for our newsletter to hear about the next articles!
Most developers understand that it’s important to use branches in Git. In …
The post Rebase vs. Merge: Integrating Changes in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355395</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsible-javascript-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T14:17:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High five to Jeremy on the big release of Responsible JavaScript on A Book Apart. There is a lot of talk about how the proliferation of JavaScript has had a negative impact on the web, but now we have …
The post Responsible JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Quasar Framework: Building Cross-Platform Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar is an open-source Vue.js-based cross-platform framework that allows you, as a developer, to easily build apps for both desktop and mobile using technologies such as Cordova and Electron and writing your code once. The app we’ll build will store and get its data from Firebase, meaning that we will also be seeing how to use Firebase in Quasar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joel Olawanle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The SSG I’ve Always Wanted: An 11ty, Vite And JAM Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, Ben Holmes set out to do what just about every web developer does each year: rebuild his personal site. In this article, he shares his story of how he set out to build his own build pipeline from absolute ground zero and created “Slinkity”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Holmes)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An API With Gatsby Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Paul Scanlon explains how to build an API by using Gatsby Functions and what you need to keep in mind when deploying it to Gatsby Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 42 With Jeff Smith: What Is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about DevOps. What is it, and is it a string to add to your web development bow? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeff Smith to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving CLS Issues In A Next.js-Powered E-Commerce Website (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cumulative Layout Shift is one of the hardest core web vital to debug. In this article, we go through different tools to investigate CLS, when to use them(and when not), and solutions to some of the CLS issues we faced in our Next.js-based e-commerce website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arijit Mondal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple But Effective Mental Health Routine For Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look at why taking care of our work-life balance is important, how to develop a simple and effective mental health routine, and the most common and efficient techniques you can use to make your custom routine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dave Oscar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: broken links in documentation
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @hirdot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips And Tricks For Evaluating UX/UI Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers may start using your app because you offer a unique product, but user experience is what makes them stay. For that, you need excellent UX designers, and the know-how to spot them when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nataliya Sambir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart CSS Solutions For Common UI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS has probably never been more fun and exciting than it is today. In this post we’ll take a look at common problems and use cases we all have to face in our work and how to solve them with modern CSS. If you’re interested, we’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Live Workshops On Front-End & UX (Oct 2021&ndash;Jan 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like a good interface design challenge? What about accessibility testing and design systems? Or maybe Next.js and advanced CSS? With our new online workshops on front-end & design, we cover all of it. Ah, and [here's what our workshops are like](https://vimeo.com/616485526).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React APIs For Building Flexible Components With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React with JSX is a fantastic tool for making easy-to-use components. Typescript components make it an absolute pleasure for developers to integrate your components into their apps and explore your APIs. Learn about three lesser-known React APIs that can take your components to the next level, and help you build even better React Components in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gaurav Khanna)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging The Gap Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UXPin has recently launched a new feature called “Merge”. This tool aims to break through the chasms of design and development, all while improving the agility and quality our teams expect. This new technology may cause some rethink on how the whole design team and engineering team collaborates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>