<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-26T01:17:49.221Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-26T01:17:49.221Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.8.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can you send automated messages via WhatsApp with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/carlosvldz/how-can-you-send-automated-messages-via-whatsapp-with-node-js-5387</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/carlosvldz/how-can-you-send-automated-messages-via-whatsapp-with-node-js-5387"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T23:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can use Node.js to send messages via WhatsApp with Twilio's API.



  
  
  First, here the things that you need:



Node and npm installed
Create an account with  Twilio  (it's free)
And finally, Twilio and dotenv library
Once you sign up for the Twilio account, activate the Sandbox for Whatsapp. This enable you a shared phone number and allows you to test with WhatsApp service. 
Then you have to opt in sending a message to the phone number provided from the sandbox. The message should say "join mass-there", if everything is ok you will receive a confirmation response. 

Once you are in the directory where is created the project, in the terminal run the following commands:
npm init -y

npm install twilio@3.30.0 dotenv

The first one to iniciate a package.json and the second one for install the dependencies.
The next step is create the file index.js with the following code:
const { config } = require('./config');

const accountSid = config.sid;
const authToken = config.token;
const client = require('twilio') (accountSid, authToken);

client.messages.create({
    from: 'whatsapp:+14155238886',
    body: 'Hello world this is CarlosVldz!!!',
    to: 'whatsapp:+5215555555555'
}).then(message => console.log(message.sid));

(Don't forget replace the phone numbers in this example with your sandbox number and a personal number.)
Finally I used dotenv to configure the environment variables TWILIO_ACCOUNT_SID and TWILIO_AUTH_TOKEN with their values from the account credentials. You can find both in your Twilio console. 
.env.example
TWILIO_ACCOUNT_SID = "Your account sid"

TWILIO_AUTH_TOKEN = "Your auth token"

In your terminal run this last command to send the WhatsApp message:
node index.js

In your phone check WhatsApp and you should have a new chat like this.

Hope you liked! (:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Simple Secure API REST with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/carlosvldz/building-a-simple-secure-api-rest-with-node-js-3576</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/carlosvldz/building-a-simple-secure-api-rest-with-node-js-3576"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T23:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time we learn to create a secure API REST with CRUD operations like Create, Read, Update and Delete.
This development include a public and private API, for security we use JWT for authentication and Bcrypt for hashing our passwords. The database engine is run by MongoDB.
REST API: it's an interface between systems that use HTTP protocol for obtain data and perform operations. In this case we will use the most important operations: POST, GET, PUT and DELETE.
Node.Js: it's a runtime environment based in JavaScript for the server side, is asynchronous and event oriented architecture. Based on Google's V8 engine.
JWT: it's an open standard ( RFC-7519 ) based in JSON to create a token that serves to send data between applications and services, guaranteeing that is authentic.
Bcrypt: is a p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up ESLint and Prettier with pre-commit hooks (with Typescript)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-set-up-eslint-and-prettier-with-pre-commit-hooks-with-typescript-h0a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-set-up-eslint-and-prettier-with-pre-commit-hooks-with-typescript-h0a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source code: Github





  
  
  The baseline project


This post assumes you are following along with the baseline project tutorial, but the concepts apply to any Typescript project.
As our codebase expands, so does the risk of introducing bugs and inconsistent styling. We are going to use two tools to help enforce some Typescript best practices and general code formatting guidelines:
ESLint
eslint is a linter, which is a static code analysis tools that can scan our codebase and throw errors and warnings if there are any issues in our codebase.
Prettier
prettier is an automatic code formatter that automatically formats our code with consistent styling.
We can manually run these tools to lint and format our codebase, but we are also going to enforce these rules by setting up git hooks - sc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up ESLint and Prettier with pre-commit hooks (with Typescript)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-set-up-eslint-and-prettier-with-pre-commit-hooks-with-typescript-h0a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-set-up-eslint-and-prettier-with-pre-commit-hooks-with-typescript-h0a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source code: Github





  
  
  The baseline project


This post assumes you are following along with the baseline project tutorial, but the concepts apply to any Typescript project.
As our codebase expands, so does the risk of introducing bugs and inconsistent styling. We are going to use two tools to help enforce some Typescript best practices and general code formatting guidelines:
ESLint
eslint is a linter, which is a static code analysis tools that can scan our codebase and throw errors and warnings if there are any issues in our codebase.
Prettier
prettier is an automatic code formatter that automatically formats our code with consistent styling.
We can manually run these tools to lint and format our codebase, but we are also going to enforce these rules by setting up git hooks - sc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Valentine]]></title>
        <id>60ac3a2711ffb70827ef6aec</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-valentine/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Valentine machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[425show @ Build 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/425show/425show-build-2021-2a7e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/425show/425show-build-2021-2a7e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T21:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks for joining us at Build! We'll be updating this post throughout the week with code samples, docs and other info after our sessions.
This session kicks off a 5-week series every Monday through June, where Christos & I will take you through the Implement Microsoft identity - Associate learning path. Join us each Monday from June 7th - July 12th as we'll go into the why behind the how.
Find the code samples from this session, complete with CodeTour!
Single-page applications
Web app that signs in users and calls APIs
Headless/daemon apps
Stay tuned, more to come throughout the week! Join us on discord]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Patrick Dandison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No-code AWS Lambda Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sentry/no-code-aws-lambda-monitoring-1fbd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sentry/no-code-aws-lambda-monitoring-1fbd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T21:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-instrumenting AWS Lambda Monitoring didn’t originate through a focus group or business plan. It started as a hackathon project that addressed the tedium of removing manual code instrumentation. Developer environments often include hundreds of AWS Lambda functions. And our existing instrumentation required initialization code to be manually placed on every single function. So to fix this, our growth team used Amazon CloudWatch to build a prototype that could instrument AWS Lambda functions.
This prototype began by using AWS CloudFormation stack to automatically create resources in a customer environment. Then we streamed Amazon CloudWatch Logs to Sentry through the Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose. This made it so all you had to do was put in your AWS account ID and create the stack using …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Lam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up ESLint + Prettier]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saulodias/setting-up-eslint-prettier-4802</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saulodias/setting-up-eslint-prettier-4802"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T21:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This is not intended as a step-by-step tutorial. It's just a draft of a solution me and my team are still discussing for our TypeScript projects. 
npm install prettier --save-dev
Create the .prettierrc file.
{
  "printWidth": 140,
  "singleQuote": true,
  "useTabs": false,
  "tabWidth": 2,
  "semi": true,
  "bracketSpacing": true
}

Name: Prettier - Code formatter
https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=esbenp.prettier-vscode
On VSCode, open your settings.json file and add the following configurations.
"editor.defaultFormatter": "esbenp.prettier-vscode",
"[javascript]": {
    "editor.defaultFormatter": "esbenp.prettier-vscode"
}

eslint-config-prettier


Turns off all rules that are unnecessary or might conflict with Prettier.
npm install --save-dev eslint-config-prettier
npm install --save-dev eslint
npm install --save-dev @typescript-eslint/eslint-plugin@latest @typescript-eslint/parser@latest
Create the .eslintrc.json file.
{
  "env": {
    "browser": true,
    "es2021": true
  },
  "extends": [
    "eslint:recommended",
    "plugin:@typescript-eslint/recommended",
    "prettier"
  ],
  "parser": "@typescript-eslint/parser",
  "parserOptions": {
    "ecmaVersion": 12,
    "sourceType": "module"
  },
  "plugins": [
    "@typescript-eslint"
  ],
  "rules": {
    "indent": ["error", 2, { "SwitchCase": 1 }],
    "linebreak-style": ["error", "windows"],
    "quotes": ["error", "single"],
    "semi": ["error", "always"],
    "curly": ["error", "multi-line"]
  }
}

Name: ESLint
https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=dbaeumer.vscode-eslint
The ESLint plugin requires permission to execute the local ESLint installation from your node_modules. Open the command palette (F1 or Ctrl + Shift + P) and select ESLint: Manage Library Execution to open the dialog for your project and confirm with 'Accept'.
ESLint not working in VSCode? Help build a troubleshooting checklist!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React-Hook-Form to Build Beautiful Forms with Chakra UI]]></title>
        <id>60a93b0011ffb70827ef5b0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-hook-form-with-chakra-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T20:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, it’s the default behavior for forms to redirect to a new page whenever they're submitted. So in order to provide dynamic functionality, React uses a strategy called controlled components. If you have recently gone through a React course, you probably didn't like this part, because there are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Face detection with Tensorflow【React + TypeScript】]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yuiko/face-detection-by-using-tensorflow-react-typescript-3dn5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yuiko/face-detection-by-using-tensorflow-react-typescript-3dn5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T20:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys,
I have developed an application with face detection, that applies a mask automatically to your face in real time.

In this article, I will explain how to develop this application.
DEMO→https://mask-app-one.vercel.app/
https://github.com/YuikoIto/mask-app
If the mask does not show up even after some seconds, please reload it.
$ npx create-react-app face-mask-app --template typescript
$ yarn add react-webcam @types/react-webcam

Then, try setting up web camera.
// App.tsx

import { useRef } from "react";
import "./App.css";
import Webcam from "react-webcam";

const App = () => {
  const webcam = useRef<Webcam>(null);

  return (
    <div className="App">
      <header className="header">
        <div className="title">face mask App</div>
      </header>
      <Webcam
        audi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yui_travel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media App Using MERN Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/safak/social-media-app-using-mern-stack-4ic6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/safak/social-media-app-using-mern-stack-4ic6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T19:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to be a full-stack web developer and stuck at just beginner projects, here is the chance to improve your skills and create something real. I decided to share my 9 hours tutorial series on YouTube for free.
We are going to create a social media application from scratch. And this project is not going to include just a basic couple of methods and an unpleasant design, it's going to include a complete web API, impressive React components, and chat functionality.
Let's dive into it!
In this section, we are going to create an Express server and the MongoDB connection. You are going to learn how to create Models and Routes. And after the section, you will be able to create your own web API, login and register operations, and CRUD for users and posts.





  
  
  Designing React Components


In this section, we are going to design Facebook like website using reusable React components and React Hooks.





  
  
  Creating MERN Stack Social Media App


In this 3rd section, we are going to combine our Rest API and React UI design. You are going to learn real-world usage of a MERN application.





  
  
  React Chat App Using Socket.io


In the final section, we are going to design a React messenger component and some additional routes in Node.js to get and post chat messages. And finally you are going to learn how to use Socket.io to send instant messages and notifications.




I hope it was useful. If you want to learn more about web development and practice with real-world projects, you can check my channel out.
🔥 Lama Dev Youtube Channel
Lama Dev Facebook
Source Code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Safak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB find() e findOne()]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emanuelferreira/mongodb-find-e-findone-5c6b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emanuelferreira/mongodb-find-e-findone-5c6b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Métodos


Para fazer uma busca por documento no MongoDB utilizamos os métodos find() e findOne(), que recebem dois tipos de parâmetro: a query, que irá fazer a busca no nosso banco de dados e o segundo parâmetro, que dizemos o que será retornado.
Nosso Documento
{
    "name": {
        type: String,
        required: true
    },
    "password": {
        type: String,
        required: true
    },
    "email": {
        type: String,
        required: true
    }
}

Exemplo do Comando
const query = { name: "Emanuel"}
const retorno = { name: 1, email: 1, password: 1}
const users = User.find(query, retorno)

O Método find retorna uma array com todos os documentos que foram encontrados utilizando o campo name. 
Query
const users = User.find({ name: Emanuel })

Retorno
[{ "_id": 12345678, "name…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emanuel Ferreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoying an Haskell like Type System in Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iquardt/enjoying-an-haskell-like-type-system-in-javascript-42fa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iquardt/enjoying-an-haskell-like-type-system-in-javascript-42fa"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[scriptum is a type validator and a functional library build upon it. A type validator is distinguished by a static type checker like Typescript by operating at runtime. Besides it doesn't infere types from terms but only checks applications.
Doing without type inference sounds like a silly idea but fortunately the validator can resort to Javascript's introspection means, so the developer only has to annotate function types.
Technically speaking scriptum is based on the Hindler-Milner type system extended by higher-kinded/rank types and row polymorphism. 
A runtime type system can never attain the soundness of a static one. You can think of it more as a tool for gradual typing. Here is a complex, real world example that should give an intuition how expressive this approach is.
Javascript is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iven Marquardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoying an Haskell like Type System in Javascript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iquardt/enjoying-an-haskell-like-type-system-in-javascript-42fa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iquardt/enjoying-an-haskell-like-type-system-in-javascript-42fa"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[scriptum is a type validator and a functional library build upon it. A type validator is distinguished by a static type checker like Typescript by operating at runtime. Besides it doesn't infere types from terms but only checks applications.
Doing without type inference sounds like a silly idea but fortunately the validator can resort to Javascript's introspection means, so the developer only has to annotate function types.
Technically speaking scriptum is based on the Hindler-Milner type system extended by higher-kinded/rank types and row polymorphism. 
A runtime type system can never attain the soundness of a static one. You can think of it more as a tool for gradual typing. Here is a complex, real world example that should give an intuition how expressive this approach is.
Javascript is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iven Marquardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make a basic discord bot in discord.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/integratergithub/make-a-basic-discord-bot-in-discord-js-37i2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/integratergithub/make-a-basic-discord-bot-in-discord-js-37i2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T18:28:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating the bot


Go to the discord developer portal and click on create new application. Now choose the name and click create. Now click on Bot and click add bot, next click yes, do it. 
To invite the bot, click on oauth2, then choose the bot scope now scroll down and give the bot the admin permission. Now copy the link and paste it into your browser and you will be able to invite it to any server you own. 
Open up your text editor of choice and execute

npm init -y && npm i discord.js 


Explanation: npm init -y creates our package.json and npm i discord.js installs the discord.js libary in order to interact with the discord api. 
index.js and paste in the following code:

var discord = require("discord.js"); // imports the discord.js libary
var client = new discord.Client(); // this is the main way we interact with the discord api   
client.on('ready', () => { // executes when the bot is online
    console.log("Bot online")
})
client.on("message", (msg) => { // executes on a new message
    if(msg.content === "!ping"){
        msg.reply("pong")
    }
})
client.login("your-token") // replace "your-token" with your bot token from https://discord.com/developers/applications


Now replace "your-token" with your bot token from the discord developer portal. Next, run the following command:

node index.js


You should see in the console: Bot online and if you send  !ping in your discord server with the bot you'll see the bot reply with pong.
More tutorials coming soon!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IntegraterGithub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebdriverIO - Part1: A Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sadabnepal/webdriverio-part1-a-journey-39dj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sadabnepal/webdriverio-part1-a-journey-39dj"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebdriverIO is a testing framework that uses NodeJS to provide an extensive API to write automated tests. 
Unforgettable year 2020, new company and new team. I remember, with Selenium and Java in resume joining new work place. The rationale for switching to WebdriverIO started with a project member saying “Start exploring WEBDRIVERIO” in call. A quick search on the YouTube and I landed on channel called Naveen Automation Labs where I started the playlist and I was able to write my first test. I recommend everyone to check it out as you will gain enough knowledge to start your journey.
Not sufficiently convinced (that bond with selenium being obvious reason), I continued on practicing (no other option as project requirement). After couple of weeks I started realizing that I am falling in lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MD SADAB SAQIB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebdriverIO - Part1: A Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sadabnepal/webdriverio-part1-a-journey-39dj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sadabnepal/webdriverio-part1-a-journey-39dj"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebdriverIO is a testing framework that uses NodeJS to provide an extensive API to write automated tests. 
Unforgettable year 2020, new company and new team. I remember, with Selenium and Java in resume joining new work place. The rationale for switching to WebdriverIO started with a project member saying “Start exploring WEBDRIVERIO” in call. A quick search on the YouTube and I landed on channel called Naveen Automation Labs where I started the playlist and I was able to write my first test. I recommend everyone to check it out as you will gain enough knowledge to start your journey.
Not sufficiently convinced (that bond with selenium being obvious reason), I continued on practicing (no other option as project requirement). After couple of weeks I started realizing that I am falling in lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MD SADAB SAQIB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using JSON Web Tokens with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/using-json-web-tokens-with-node-js-22c6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/using-json-web-tokens-with-node-js-22c6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe you have been developing Apis to be consumed by a website, mobile or desktop application. And one of the points that you need to learn in a quick and simple way is how to implement authentication and authorization in your Api.
Obviously, there are several strategies, from the most popular, such as cookies, sessions and JWT. However, in recent years there has been a huge popularity in the use of third party services like OAuth. However, I am always reticent about whether or not I will give the sensitive data of my users to another company.
I would also add that implementing OAuth can be challenging, at least on the server side. However, in this article I will talk about JWT and I will give a simple example of its implementation.
A JSON Web Token, or JWT, is a method used to securely t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need help in reactjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pradeep_murugan/need-help-in-reactjs-4gc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pradeep_murugan/need-help-in-reactjs-4gc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T17:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[here is my question posted on stackover flow this is bothering me for last two days 😭😭
https://stackoverflow.com/a/67680014/5730749]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pradeep murugan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check out the latest .Net core Developer Hourly rate in 2021!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexisdevs/check-out-the-latest-net-core-developer-hourly-rate-in-2021-348o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexisdevs/check-out-the-latest-net-core-developer-hourly-rate-in-2021-348o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The demand for .Net core expert developers has been increasing steam fast. And the experts predict this demand will keep on increasing with time.
One of the advantages of .Net core is if you know c language or Javascript, learning .Net core is not a big task to accomplish.
Its vital base class directories and shared binaries within multiple frameworks and platforms make the language more robust when it comes to web development.
If we look at the current trends hiring the professional or globally leading .Net core Development company is quite popular these days.
So basically, how this works, you can Hire any .Net core development company, and they will connect you with their well-versed expert .Net core team.
This .Net core developer team will lead your project from that and gives you profo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexis Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Best Practices for New Developers – How to Create Portfolio-Worthy Work]]></title>
        <id>608706aedd38b9088c2c012c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-design-best-practices-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner developer, it can be difficult to find ways to use your limited knowledge to support yourself. And at the same time, you won't be able to hone your skills if you aren't using them full time.  It's a precarious spot that I remember being in when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp Privacy Policy: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afifa83248486/whatsapp-privacy-policy-everything-you-need-to-know-4lfh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afifa83248486/whatsapp-privacy-policy-everything-you-need-to-know-4lfh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WhatsApp is an instant messaging application that Facebook owns. It is the third most used messaging application, according to Messenger People. Although it uses end-to-end encryption, it still collects more metadata on its users than other messaging applications like Signal. 
In January 2021, news circulated that WhatsApp planned to roll out in-app notifications to users, informing an update in its Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. It was up to the user to accept the new WhatsApp Privacy Policy and Terms of Service to continue to use the messaging application.
The company tweaked its terms of service and privacy policy which notified users once they entered the application. Users had to accept these updates to continue to use the application, and these changes were scheduled to be implemented on February 8th, 2021. The following were the updates made in terms of service and privacy policy:
WhatsApp’s service and how we process your data
How businesses can use Facebook hosted services to store and 
manage their WhatsApp chats
How they partner with Facebook to offer integrations across the 
Facebook Company Products
Read the full article here:WhatsApp Privacy Policy: Everything You Need to Know]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afifa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-site Request Forgery: protection against CSRF attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ra1nbow1/cross-site-request-forgery-protection-against-csrf-attacks-a6o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ra1nbow1/cross-site-request-forgery-protection-against-csrf-attacks-a6o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSRF (cross-site request forgery) is a type of attack on a site that is carried out using a fraudulent site or a script that causes the user's browser to perform an undesirable action on a trusted site where the user is logged in.
Usually, to do this, the user must click on a fraudulent link (which can be changed using a link shortener).
For example, Jane, who is logged in to the bank's website, checks her email. They may click on a phishing link that includes a request to transfer money to the fraudster's account.
Due to the fact that it is authorized on the bank's website, the bank will process the transfer request.
The GET, HEAD, OPTIONS, and TRACE methods are not subject to CSRF, because they are intended only for retrieving information and do not change the server state.
The POST, PUT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matvey Romanov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edit remote files with Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/edit-remote-files-with-vim-24k9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/edit-remote-files-with-vim-24k9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T15:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a text editor with a huge following. It's installed by  default on every Linux system and even on Mac OS X.
Vim is a tool that wants you to succeed. if you want something to happen, you can make it happen. It works completely by keyboard shortcuts. 

It gives you the power to manipulate text at a fundamental level. you can operate on individual characters, words or lines of text this gives vim a really powerful interactive feel.
If you are new to vim, I recommend these exercises
I am often connecting to remote machines and editing config files. 
This was cumbersome, as I would have to use SFTP to copy files, manually updating the buffer when the file was modified on the remote machine. 
It was too easy to get distracted and lose track of what I was doing.
If you want to edit files on a remote server, try this command:
vim scp://you@remote_ip//path/file.txt

and change username to your username, your remote ip, the path and the filename.
vim scp://frank@192.168.2.7//home/frank/hello.txt

If you have vim open, you can also do :e scp://you@remote_ip//path/file.txt
You can use sftp too:
vim sftp://user@remote_ip//path/file

Change it with your username, remote ip and path to the file.
vim sftp://frank@192.168.2.7//home/frank/hello.txt

If you want to use the old unencrypted ftp protocol
:e ftp://[user@]machine/path/

Vim is relentlessly awesome. It does everything an editor should do and nothing it shouldn't. There are no gimmicks, no silly settings, no bloat. It just works. all the time. no exceptions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want to compress your pdf files ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/burakcank/want-to-compress-your-pdf-files-5ff9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/burakcank/want-to-compress-your-pdf-files-5ff9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you tired of scanning images and trying to shrink them under 25 mbs just so you can send them via email ? Look no further, I am here to save you from this trouble. (that kinda rhymed.)
This basic shell script uses ghostscript to compress your scanned pdfs significantly. Just yesterday I scanned 100 pages of documents and it was over 90 mbs. I searched for a way to compress them under 25 mbs and voila. Here I was with only 6 mbs of pdfs. Much wow. Such compression.
Why we need it,
Fast.
Ez.
No need to go online. Especially no need to upload company top-secret documents to any website you see on the Internet.
Possible huge compression without notable loss.
Command usage:
./shrinkpdf.sh in.pdf out.pdf
ghostscript.





If you are in a situation exactly like me where there are 100 pdf files under one folder that you want to compress altogether, a simple for loop will suffice.
import os
import subprocess
import sys

infolder = sys.argv[1]
outfolder = "compressed_" + infolder
os.mkdir(outfolder)

for f in os.listdir(infolder):
    subprocess.run(["./shrinkpdf.sh", os.path.join(infolder, f), os.path.join(outfolder, f)])

Run this python script,
python shrink.py pdfs/
and all of your pdfs will be put under compressed_pdfs/.
http://www.alfredklomp.com/programming/shrinkpdf/
All the relevant details and more, inside. I humbly wanted to let you know such a useful tool exists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Burak Can Kahraman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The bpmn-visualization project celebrates its 1st anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tbouffard/the-bpmn-visualization-project-celebrates-its-1st-anniversary-4ae2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tbouffard/the-bpmn-visualization-project-celebrates-its-1st-anniversary-4ae2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate the first year of our work on the bpmn-visualization library, here's a look back about what has been achieved.
bpmn-visualization is an open source TypeScript library for visualizing process execution data on BPMN diagrams.
From its first public release in March 2020 to the introduction of diagram interactions in January 2021, here it is: an overview of the first year achievements.

Template from Simple Blackboard Background
Below are some examples of what can be done with bpmn-visualization.
dedicated GitHub repository if you want a more complete overview of the available capabilities.
BPMN diagrams are at the foundation of the bpmn-visualization capabilities.
This animation shows the evolution of BPMN support over time. It uses the B.2.0 diagram of the BPMN Model Interchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Bouffard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-i-learned-building-a-word-game-app-with-nuxt-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell in love with coding the moment I created my first CSS :hover effect. Years later, that initial bite into interactivity on the web led me to a new goal: making a game.
Table of contents
What’s the game 
…
The post What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Angular: The Most Impactful RxJs Best Practice Tip Of All Time (Medium Dev.to auto import)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomastrajan/practical-angular-the-most-impactful-rxjs-best-practice-tip-of-all-time-3kc3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomastrajan/practical-angular-the-most-impactful-rxjs-best-practice-tip-of-all-time-3kc3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This easy to follow tip can help YOU and your teammates to simplify and hence improve your projects significantly!
Continue reading on Medium »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Trajan 🐻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Angular: The Most Impactful RxJs Best Practice Tip Of All Time (Medium Dev.to auto import)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomastrajan/practical-angular-the-most-impactful-rxjs-best-practice-tip-of-all-time-3kc3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomastrajan/practical-angular-the-most-impactful-rxjs-best-practice-tip-of-all-time-3kc3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This easy to follow tip can help YOU and your teammates to simplify and hence improve your projects significantly!
Continue reading on Medium »]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Trajan 🐻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 (+/-) Linux skills for landing a Linux job]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/asciiden/top-10-linux-skills-for-landing-a-linux-job-1i5m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/asciiden/top-10-linux-skills-for-landing-a-linux-job-1i5m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hey now, you have probably went through numerous job-hunting websites and you memorized all the buzzwords (Junior Sysadmin; Junior Site Reliability Engineer; NOC Engineer; System support; etc.) that can get you in IT with zero experience, or even zero education. Well, let me tell you - you are on the right track! However, there are some insights that a lot of you don't know as you haven't got a real Linux job. Well now, except you are on the right track, you are on the post, as well!
I am going to note down & explain the top 10 Linux skills (in the opinion of a person who had a Linux job as a first) that you should have before rushing into the interview.
Linux skills? But I know a lot of commands already!
It is not up to the commands you know but the ability to imply them at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denislav Gavrilov 👨‍🚀🤖🤷‍♂️</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Não use node.js 10, Angular 12 lançado, Bootstrap 5, Deno 1.1, Playwright, TS 4.3 e muito mais]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wilsonnetodev/nao-use-node-js-10-angular-12-lancado-bootstrap-5-deno-1-1-playwright-ts-4-3-e-muito-mais-3393</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wilsonnetodev/nao-use-node-js-10-angular-12-lancado-bootstrap-5-deno-1-1-playwright-ts-4-3-e-muito-mais-3393"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Não use mais o node 10! Node 10 chega ao End Of Life, Angular 12 lançado, Bootstrap 5, Deno 1.1, Playwright, TS 4.3, CloudFront Functions, Azure Static WebApp e muitas outras novidades!
As principais novidades da semana, no mundo da tecnologia e do javascript.
Leia a edição desta semana da newsletter em:
https://novidadesjs.substack.com/p/nao-use-nodejs-10-angular-12-lancado
Para se inscrever e receber semanalmente as principais novidades, cadastre-se em:
https://novidadesjs.substack.com/welcome]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wilson Neto B.R.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Command Line for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/linux-command-line-for-beginners-16n8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/linux-command-line-for-beginners-16n8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux command line is for power users. It is not for the faint of heart or for people who are afraid to take a risk. 
If you are new to Linux and are afraid to take the plunge into using the command line interface, then this tutorial is a good start. 
Linux is an open source operating system that is used on everything from smart phones to main frame computers. 
Linux provides a command line interface (CLI) that provides a quick and powerful way to control and manipulate your computer. Once mastered, the Linux CLI can save you time and provide a powerful tool to aid in your daily tasks.
The command line can be intimidating but learning the basics will give you access to a world of scripts and automation tools that will make your life a lot easier and more productive.
The Basics: You will be using the command line to type various commands and tasks. Commands are what Linux runs. In Linux, the Command Line can be used for various things.

To start, open up a terminal. Now, let's try using some basic Linux commands! 
Most of these commands are applicable for all Linux distributions. Linux is case sensitive (capitalization matters).
Navigation
ls    List directory
cd DIR Change the current directory to the DIR directory
cd ~  Change to home directory
cd /      Change the current directory to the root directory
cd ..     Go one directory lower
pwd   Show name of current working directory 
File Commands
mkdir -p DIR Create directory DIR 
rm FILE Remove FILE
rm -r DIR Remove DIR and its contents recursively
rm -f FILE Force remove FILE 
System Info
date  Print or set the system date and time
cal   Displays a calendar
uptime Tell how long the system has been running
w     Show who is logged on and what they are doing
whoami  Print effective userid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.JS - Foal framework - version 2.4 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.4 of Foal has been released! Here are the improvements that it brings.
$data references for validation


Version 2.4 allows you to enable the AJV $data option so that you can use the verified data values as validators for other values.
config/default.json
{
  "settings": {
    "ajv": {
      "$data": true
    }
  }
}

Example of auth controller
import { Context, Post, ValidateBody } from '@foal/core';

export class AuthController {
  @Post('/signup')
  @ValidateBody({
    type: 'object',
    properties: {
      username: { type: 'string' },
      password: { type: 'string' },
      // "password" and "confirmPassword" should be identical.
      confirmPassword: {
        const: {
          $data: '1/password',
        },
        type: 'string',
      },
    }
    required: [ 'username', 'password', 'confirmPassword' ],
    additionalProperties: false
  })
  signup(ctx: Context) {
    // Do something.
  }
}


Starting from version 2.4 the Disk.createHttpResponse method accepts an optional parameter to specify the value of the Cache-Control header.
import { Context, dependency, Get } from '@foal/core';
import { Disk } from '@foal/storage';

import { User } from '../entities';

export class ProfileController {
  @dependency
  disk: Disk;

  @Get('/avatar')
  async readProfileImage(ctx: Context<User>) {
    return this.disk.createHttpResponse(ctx.user.avatar, {
      cache: 'no-cache'
    });
  }

See issue #930.
@ZakRabe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loïc Poullain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.JS - Foal framework - version 2.4 is here]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loicpoullain/node-js-foal-framework-version-2-4-is-here-dhh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.4 of Foal has been released! Here are the improvements that it brings.
$data references for validation


Version 2.4 allows you to enable the AJV $data option so that you can use the verified data values as validators for other values.
config/default.json
{
  "settings": {
    "ajv": {
      "$data": true
    }
  }
}

Example of auth controller
import { Context, Post, ValidateBody } from '@foal/core';

export class AuthController {
  @Post('/signup')
  @ValidateBody({
    type: 'object',
    properties: {
      username: { type: 'string' },
      password: { type: 'string' },
      // "password" and "confirmPassword" should be identical.
      confirmPassword: {
        const: {
          $data: '1/password',
        },
        type: 'string',
      },
    }
    required: [ 'username', 'password', 'confirmPassword' ],
    additionalProperties: false
  })
  signup(ctx: Context) {
    // Do something.
  }
}


Starting from version 2.4 the Disk.createHttpResponse method accepts an optional parameter to specify the value of the Cache-Control header.
import { Context, dependency, Get } from '@foal/core';
import { Disk } from '@foal/storage';

import { User } from '../entities';

export class ProfileController {
  @dependency
  disk: Disk;

  @Get('/avatar')
  async readProfileImage(ctx: Context<User>) {
    return this.disk.createHttpResponse(ctx.user.avatar, {
      cache: 'no-cache'
    });
  }

See issue #930.
@ZakRabe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loïc Poullain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Use Vim for Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/why-use-vim-for-programming-467h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/why-use-vim-for-programming-467h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is the most famous text editor many programmers use for coding on the Linux terminal.
Vim is a text editor for Linux. Many people have grown up using Vim, that and its ubiquitous nature means it can be found on any Unix/Linux system. 
Many “power users” swear by the power and functionality of Vim, however many people see it as intimidating and complicated. If you are new to vim, I recommend these exercises
Vim can be downloaded and installed from a software repository. Vim is often installed by default on Linux systems and even on Mac OS X.
You can install vim with your package manager
sudo apt-get install vim

The reasons for this are simple: it's fast, it's powerful, and it comes in both a terminal emulator and a GUI version. 
You can use it locally or over an ssh connection. It can even be used inside IDEs as a plugin.
Vim allows programmers to edit text quickly and efficiently. You can jump to the end of file using G, top of file using gg and to line 10 using 10G. Vim allows you to record and replay keystrokes and has many many more features.

Vim 8 comes with built-in support for Python, PHP, Perl, Ruby and Tcl programming languages.
Vim as a code editor but it's much more powerful than you may think. Before you do anything else, you should know that:
Vim is not a text editor that uses a mouse. It's a program that uses keyboard shortcuts to perform all of the tasks.
Vim is hard to learn. You will have to spend a lot of time practising and mastering your skills before using it effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧩 What is Caching and How It Works]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/what-is-caching-and-how-it-works-4gg0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/what-is-caching-and-how-it-works-4gg0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🖥 Let’s see why caching has become one of the most crucial concepts in computer science. We will dive into the concept of caching, understanding what it is, how it works, and what are the most important types of caching.



  
  
  
Over the past few years, information technology has been improving whatever kind of business drastically. Meanwhile, software architectures have become increasingly complex, and the number of their users has grown exponentially. This has represented a performance challenge for any application. Slow performance can undermine the strategic goals of any company, which is why finding smart ways to improve it is critical. As a consequence, avoiding overhead and reducing data retrieval and processing time has become imperative. This is where caching comes into play …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Role-Based Security using Entity Framework (Part 1) | Dear Coder]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/piaomu/role-based-security-using-entity-framework-part-1-dear-coder-4d6h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/piaomu/role-based-security-using-entity-framework-part-1-dear-coder-4d6h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Coder,
If you're working on an application that allows users to register an account, you've likely encountered the issue of role-based security.
What is role-based security and why do we need it?
Say you're working on an application that allows users to share webcomics with each other. You've already built in the features that allow the user to securely upload photos to your database, and you've implemented features that allow users to register an account and log in.
But now you need to ask what features should be accessible to any user regardless of if they've registered an account, what features should be accessible to registered users, and what features should be available to privileged users.
This is where role-based security comes in.
For the sake of my illustration, let's catego…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasey Wahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for non-profit or open-source projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dinhhuyams/looking-for-non-profit-or-open-source-projects-3119</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dinhhuyams/looking-for-non-profit-or-open-source-projects-3119"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🏋️‍♂️I am looking for a non-profit or an open-source project that I can contribute to.
The motivation behind this is that I would love to find a place I can practice coding. Normally, if I want to learn something, I will try to write a blog or create some small projects.
👉 Example of my projects:
awesome-react-typescript-boilerplate
awesome-node-boilerplate
👉 Blogs
10 tips to improve readability in Javascript
Introduction to React.memo, useMemo and useCallback
It would be good to do something meaningful, and I would like to work in a team 
🪄 I have 3-year experience in coding. 
I work mostly with React and I am quite familiar with these tech:
JavaScript
TypeScript
React
NextJS
NodeJS
My ideal project is a non-profit or an open-source project built with these tech:
JavaScript
TypeScript
React
NextJS
NodeJS
AWS
I would love to work in a team who is passionate about tech
I can contribute about 3-7 hours/week
Feel free to contact me so we can discuss if you have any interesting non-profit projects that need help.
Twitter
LinkedIn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TrinhDinhHuy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Startups Are Thriving, With More on the Way]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/india-startups-are-thriving-with-more-on-the-way-33cf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/india-startups-are-thriving-with-more-on-the-way-33cf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bolstered by a 42% increase in unicorns, India’s technology startup scene is powered by developers focusing on new core products.



  
  
  
Have you noticed the number of Indian startups making international news lately? Well, the world media and investors sure have, and with good reason. The startup scene in India has not only weathered the last year of global uncertainty, it’s managing to thrive by staying focused on core offerings. According to a report from KPMG and Pitchbook, that worked out to 2019 Q3 returns in the $3.6 billion range. 
Fortune India reports that as of the end of 2019, India was home to 26 unicorns. And according to Inc42, by the end of 2020, 11 more were added to the ranks. That’s an increase of 42%, during a global pandemic no less. The keys to this success are v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Academy - Help me out!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appsecmonkey/hacking-academy-help-me-out-35pm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appsecmonkey/hacking-academy-help-me-out-35pm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys,
I'm building an online e-learning platform for hackers (you can see some screenshots/videos here), and two of the demographics I'm trying to reach are: 
Experienced developers who already know how to create backend or full-stack applications but don't necessarily know about all of the security hazards or how to exploit them as an attacker.


Beginner developers who know what a variable or a function is but don't yet understand how the HTTP protocol or browsers or web applications in general really work.



Because it's difficult to really put oneself in someone else's shoes, I humbly ask for your help. If you belong to either of the two demographics, and are interested in the topic, what would be most important to you in an e-learning platform that aims to teach about hacking and defending against the attacks?
Feel free to suggest specific content, features, or anything at all. The page I linked above should give a pretty good overview of the current idea that I have about what it could look like.
Thanks in advance! And sorry I know this is a bit of a plug but there is no better place to ask (:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Teo Selenius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-powerful-websites-with-serverless-driven-cms-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right tools to build a website for your organization is essential, but it can be tough to find the right fit. Simple site builders like Wix and Squarespace are easy for marketers to use, but severely limit developers …
The post Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Bouchefra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't throw the infra baby out with the bathwater]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tinydevops/don-t-throw-the-infra-baby-out-with-the-bathwater-4bnb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tinydevops/don-t-throw-the-infra-baby-out-with-the-bathwater-4bnb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of The Tiny DevOps Podcast, Jonathan talks with guest Patric Conant about an often-overlooked aspect of our technology stack: the physical infrastructure.  Patric talks about some common problems he sees, and some simple tips to make sure your team doesn't fall into the common trap of throwing the "infrastructure baby" out with the bathwater.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Connect - Standalone React WebRTC Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/huseyn0w/fast-connect-standalone-react-webrtc-application-4n44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/huseyn0w/fast-connect-standalone-react-webrtc-application-4n44"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19 Changed the world...


Since the year 2020 world is different. The majority of people change the way of workflow from Office to Remote mode.
By using our application you DO NOT NEED to download anything to your device or pay for anything.
ABSOLUTELY FREE and without registration ;)
All you have to do is to take 2 steps:
Create a unique ID for the conference, send it to all your colleagues.
Enter that ID on the homepage and start your conference. 
Github
Demo
My Linkedin profile
Application features:
No registration and NO "PREMIUM" accounts
Realtime video/audio conference with unlimited number of users
Different rooms creating an option for conversations
Chat for sending messages
Screen Sharing option
Technologies that used in the creation of this app:
React JS
TypeScript
Material UI
Node / Express js
Socket IO
Peer JS
Like it ? Please star the project and share in return ;)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elman Huseynov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type-check your JavaScript with JSDoc]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ncribt/type-check-your-javascript-with-jsdoc-e7i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ncribt/type-check-your-javascript-with-jsdoc-e7i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSDoc refers to JavaScript documentation through comment blocks, it is similar to the JavaDoc. With it, it is possible to type-check your JavaScript code and avoid setting up a build/compilation step in your project. This method still requires TypeScript, but only for developing, not to ship your code.
Why would anyone want to use JSDoc instead of TypeScript for type-checking?
If you're building a frontend application using a library like React, you will probably use a tool such as Webpack (or Vite) to bundle/compile your code into JavaScript that browsers can understand. In that case you might as well use TypeScript because you already have a build step. Though, if you think the Hot Reloading or the build step are too slow, JSDoc could still be of help.
Now if you're building a library, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Kubernetes on Ubuntu 21.04 | Install Kubernetes on Ubuntu | Install kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jhooq/how-to-install-kubernetes-on-ubuntu-21-04-install-kubernetes-on-ubuntu-install-kubernetes-5379</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jhooq/how-to-install-kubernetes-on-ubuntu-21-04-install-kubernetes-on-ubuntu-install-kubernetes-5379"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T08:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this lab session we will focus on how to setup your Kubernetes cluster on Ubuntu 21.04. 
Benefits of local k8s cluster - 
You do not need to pay cloud services for learning purpose
You can destroy and rebuilt everything as many times as you can using virtual machine
You know what you are doing.
Read more detailed blog post at - https://jhooq.com/14-steps-to-install-kubernetes-on-ubuntu-18-04-and-16-04/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul Wagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React VS Angular: Which framework is the best choice for app development?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abbasmurtza/react-vs-angular-which-framework-is-the-best-choice-for-app-development-4lhg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abbasmurtza/react-vs-angular-which-framework-is-the-best-choice-for-app-development-4lhg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T08:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React vs Angular – which framework is best app development? This blog is extensively written to present entire knowledge and benefits.
Read full article here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MURTZA ABBAS RIZVI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Node Environment Variables with a DotEnv File for Node.js and npm]]></title>
        <id>60abc6d011ffb70827ef630f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-node-environment-variables-with-a-dotenv-file-for-node-js-and-npm/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Environment variables are variables that are set outside of a program, often through a cloud provider or operating system.  In Node, environment variables are a great way to securely and conveniently configure things that don't change often, like URLs, authentication keys, and passwords. How to Create Environment VariablesEnvironment variables are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Nibbles]]></title>
        <id>60626dc29618b008528a9589</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-nibbles/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Nibbles machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts about productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/burakcank/some-thoughts-about-productivity-308k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/burakcank/some-thoughts-about-productivity-308k"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last couple of years, I have been in the Linux space and mostly tried to find the best distro, best file manager, best terminal etc. I was caught up in the loop of finding the best programs to handle a job. This approach, unless controlled, usually leads to low productivity in the long term.
How so you might ask ? Well, this behavior is really relatable for some people. When I am talking about this subject, some of you might probably say, "Oh yes I have been there". In Linux world, there is even a term for this. Ricing.
Ricing means tweaking the configuration of your working environment to suit your personal needs. At particular level, one might consider this useful, and it indeed is. There are some workflow approaches, shortcuts and others that helps the developer access files and folders faster, learn by muscle memory and perform some set of actions quicker. Past that particular level and you are now in the over-ricing zone. Where you are essentially tweaking every aspect of each program, work environment to your needs, but at the same time you are never satisfied so you keep tweaking and changing settings, configs and what not. It reduces your productivity and at the end of the day when you look back, you realize you have done nothing but tweaking some stuff to find the best work environment.
This is what I call the loop (referring to the Bandersnatch here). You are in the loop. You need to get out and you need to get sh*t done. Don't worry about using the best tool out there, don't try to find the absolute efficient program. Just get it done.
This is in actuality a paradox. The paradox goes as such, "The more choices you have, the less satisfied you are". Seems about right when you think for a bit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Burak Can Kahraman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340808</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making GitHub’s new homepage fast and performant — Tobias Ahlin describes how the scrolling effects are done more performantly thanks to IntersectionObserver and the fact that it avoids the use of methods that trigger reflows, like getBoundingClientRect. Also, 
…
The post Links on Performance appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I love Linux ... and AppImages <3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sjustesen/i-love-linux-and-appimages-3-2f77</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sjustesen/i-love-linux-and-appimages-3-2f77"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T21:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using Ubuntu/Debian/Nitrux/Manjaro ARM as my main go-to OS' for several years now. I absolutely love being part of this vast community of great individuals.
"Linux is difficult" - "Packaging is hard" was once the most predominant ways for software companies to tell users, why they didn't support Linux. 
But these days we got things like AppImages[1], which I think is very underappreciated within the community (just a feeling, no figures to back it up). Actually I'm unaware why AppImages aren't already part of all Linux distros out there. I guess it's because everyone is trying to roll their own distribution formats?
Anyway, An AppImage is a container format much akin to Mac Applications. You just download an AppImage from e.g. AppImageHub[2], set the execute permission on the file and off you go. No installation required - you can even place the AppImage file where ever you'd like. If you want to skip the "set execute bit" step and need tighter GUI integration there's a daemon called appimaged[3] that you can run beforehand which will take care of all this.
[1] https://appimage.org/
https://www.appimagehub.com/
https://github.com/probonopd/go-appimage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Justesen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to avoid Meltdown, Spectre and CSRF Attacks on Web with CORP, CORB, and CORS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/obetomuniz/how-to-avoid-meltdown-spectre-and-csrf-attacks-on-web-with-corp-corb-and-cors-1944</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/obetomuniz/how-to-avoid-meltdown-spectre-and-csrf-attacks-on-web-with-corp-corb-and-cors-1944"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T21:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A brief and useful content about the mechanics on Cross-Origin Read Blocking, Cross-Origin Resource Policy and Cross-Origin Resource Sharing against Meltdown, Spectre and CSRF Attacks.
By design, Cross-Origin Read Blocking validates browser requests before they even reach the server using their MIME type as a validation rule.
To enable it, send the HTTP header X-Content-Type-Options: nosniff  from the server.
Cross-Origin Resource Policy is a complementary CORB mechanism for validation applied to requests flagged with no-cors to invalidate them if they came from different domains or origin.
Send the header Cross-Origin-Resource-Policy from the server with values same-origin or same-site to invalidate no-cors requests from different domains or origin.
Cross-Origin Resource Sharing is a logical context mechanism that ensures minimal security in the way that users consume web content using browsers instructing how the browser will validate the origin of the requests.
To define rules about how the origin of the request will be identified, send the HTTP header Access-Control-Allow-Origin using values like <exact_request_origin> and even a more generic approaches using *.
Hope that now you understand a bit better why to use these Cross-Origin Resource features
Try don't disable or ignore them in your web applications. Spectre, CSRF, and Meltdown attacks are really dangerous.
💌 If you liked this content, subscribe to my newsletter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beto Muniz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Small and Sustainable Habits to Get Your First Dev Job]]></title>
        <id>60aaba5911ffb70827ef5ffc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-small-sustainable-habits-to-get-your-first-dev-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T21:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving a big goal like transitioning into a new career can be extremely challenging and overwhelming. The amount of information isn't the problem. We have access to more information than we ever have. The problem is knowing how to effectively execute on the information available to us. The more I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ngx-awesome-popup Interactive modals on steroids 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/ngx-awesome-popup-interactive-modals-on-steroids-2ej3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/ngx-awesome-popup-interactive-modals-on-steroids-2ej3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T20:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is it?


It's the npm library made for the Angular 9+
It provides:
Evoking dynamic components in popup
Toast Notifications
Alert Box
Confirm Box
Cookie GDPR banner
It has:
Clean API
Better documented than others
Easy to use
d.ts files
Awesome snippet generator
Ability of global or local configuration
Predefined styles
Easy to change colors 
Button generator
Simple and powerful Dependency Injection 
Okay
toastNotification() {
        const newToastNotification = new ToastNotificationInitializer();
        newToastNotification.setTitle('Title!');
        newToastNotification.setMessage('Message!');
        newToastNotification.setConfig({
            LayoutType: DialogLayoutDisplay.INFO // SUCCESS | INFO | NONE | DANGER | WARNING
        });
        newToastNotification.openToastNotification$();
    }

confirmBox() {
        const confirmBox = new ConfirmBoxInitializer();
        confirmBox.setTitle('Title!');
        confirmBox.setMessage('Message!');
        confirmBox.setButtonLabels('Button1', 'Button2'); 
        confirmBox.setConfig({
            LayoutType: DialogLayoutDisplay.SUCCESS // SUCCESS | INFO | NONE | DANGER | WARNING
        });
        const subscription = confirmBox.openConfirmBox$().subscribe(resp => {
            // button response
            subscription.unsubscribe();
        });
    }

dialog() {
        const dialogPopup = new DialogInitializer(AnyAngularComponent);
        dialogPopup.setCustomData({myData}); 
        dialogPopup.setConfig({
            Width     : '500px',
        );

        dialogPopup.setButtons([
            new ButtonMaker('Submit', 'submit', ButtonLayoutDisplay.SUCCESS),
            new ButtonMaker('Cancel', 'cancel', ButtonLayoutDisplay.SECONDARY)
        ]);

        const subscription = dialogPopup.openDialog$().subscribe(resp => {
            // button response
            subscription.unsubscribe();
        });
    }

Here's how!



Toast - playground
Toast - StackBlitz
Confirm box - playground
Confirm box - StackBlitz
Dialog - playground]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Jenicek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Media Queries to Create Responsive Websites]]></title>
        <id>60ac07ec11ffb70827ef66e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-media-queries-to-create-responsive-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T20:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Media Queries allow you to create responsive websites that look good on all screen sizes, from desktop to mobile. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to create CSS Media Queries. After learning the basics, you will learn how to use media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate a Code Coverage Report with CodeCov and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>60aa161211ffb70827ef5f2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-code-coverage-report-with-codecov-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software testing is an important part of the software development process. You run tests at different stages of the software development life cycle, and you'll want to make sure that you have good test coverage.  Here are some key reasons for writing software tests:  Testing prevents you from introducing breaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[proxy-www]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341153</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/justjavac/proxy-www"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a good trick. What if… a URL was…  a promise… that fetched said URL?
www.codepen.io.then((response) ={
  console.log(response);
});
That’s what @justjavac did with JavaScript Proxys. A clever trick, that. Don’t @ me about the practicality. Trick…
The post proxy-www appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create New VM in CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/how-to-create-new-vm-in-cli-4f6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/how-to-create-new-vm-in-cli-4f6f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KVM to Create New VM using CLI Commands, Tested in ubuntu 16.04 its working fine





sudo virt-install \
--virt-type=kvm \
--name centos7 \
--ram 6144 \
--vcpus=8 \
--os-variant=rhel7 \
--hvm \
--cdrom=/RootPartitions/CentOS-7-x86_64-DVD-1810.iso \
--network network=default,model=virtio \
--graphics vnc \
--disk path=/RootPartitions/centos7-0.1.img,size=30,bus=virtio


# Spin a New VM with Bridge Network

sudo virt-install \
--virt-type=kvm \
--name centos7 \
--ram 6144 \
--vcpus=8 \
--os-variant=rhel7 \
--hvm \
--cdrom=/RootPartitions/CentOS-7-x86_64-DVD-1810.iso \
--network bridge=br0,model=virtio \
--graphics vnc \
--disk path=/RootPartitions/centos7.img,size=30,bus=virtio

sudo virsh list --all. # to all the VM in the Host Machine 
sudo virsh destroy <vm-nam> # Stopping or Shutting down the VM
sudo virsh dumpxml vm-name > vm-name.xml # Export the VM setting in XML Formate
sudo cat vm-name.xml | grep source # to list the attached Partition
sudo lvremove /partition/name # remove the LVM Partition 
sudo rm -rf /RootParition/Centos.img # To remove the .img and .qcow2 partitions
sudo virsh undefine <vm-name> # Removing the VM from the Host Machine, before execute
sudo virsh vncdisplay # to display the VNC port number

Host Machine should have the Public and Private Network and VM should configured via bridge network from Privat network. 
Using SSH tunnel we can connect the VM, before pls install VNC viewer in your local - https://www.realvnc.com/en/connect/download/viewer/
From Local Machine
ssh -L localhost:5900:VM-IP:VNC-Port-Number username@hostmachine.com

For Example
HostMachine: dhanesh.vm-test.com (Public IP)
ssh -L localhost:5900:192.168.100.100:5912 dhanesh@dhanesh.vm-test.com

Finally open the VNC viewer and type localhost:5900 you can able to see the VM from your local machine. 
Ensure that all the Network settings are working fine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create New VM in CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/how-to-create-new-vm-in-cli-4f6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhanupreeth/how-to-create-new-vm-in-cli-4f6f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KVM to Create New VM using CLI Commands, Tested in ubuntu 16.04 its working fine





sudo virt-install \
--virt-type=kvm \
--name centos7 \
--ram 6144 \
--vcpus=8 \
--os-variant=rhel7 \
--hvm \
--cdrom=/RootPartitions/CentOS-7-x86_64-DVD-1810.iso \
--network network=default,model=virtio \
--graphics vnc \
--disk path=/RootPartitions/centos7-0.1.img,size=30,bus=virtio


# Spin a New VM with Bridge Network

sudo virt-install \
--virt-type=kvm \
--name centos7 \
--ram 6144 \
--vcpus=8 \
--os-variant=rhel7 \
--hvm \
--cdrom=/RootPartitions/CentOS-7-x86_64-DVD-1810.iso \
--network bridge=br0,model=virtio \
--graphics vnc \
--disk path=/RootPartitions/centos7.img,size=30,bus=virtio

sudo virsh list --all. # to all the VM in the Host Machine 
sudo virsh destroy <vm-nam> # Stopping or Shutting down the VM
sudo virsh dumpxml vm-name > vm-name.xml # Export the VM setting in XML Formate
sudo cat vm-name.xml | grep source # to list the attached Partition
sudo lvremove /partition/name # remove the LVM Partition 
sudo rm -rf /RootParition/Centos.img # To remove the .img and .qcow2 partitions
sudo virsh undefine <vm-name> # Removing the VM from the Host Machine, before execute
sudo virsh vncdisplay # to display the VNC port number

Host Machine should have the Public and Private Network and VM should configured via bridge network from Privat network. 
Using SSH tunnel we can connect the VM, before pls install VNC viewer in your local - https://www.realvnc.com/en/connect/download/viewer/
From Local Machine
ssh -L localhost:5900:VM-IP:VNC-Port-Number username@hostmachine.com

For Example
HostMachine: dhanesh.vm-test.com (Public IP)
ssh -L localhost:5900:192.168.100.100:5912 dhanesh@dhanesh.vm-test.com

Finally open the VNC viewer and type localhost:5900 you can able to see the VM from your local machine. 
Ensure that all the Network settings are working fine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K Dhanesh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data-Driven Components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/data-driven-components-fcl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/data-driven-components-fcl"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | Feb 2021
Runtime Templates Using String Identifiers
Many of the applications I develop for clients most often involve mathematical sciences, ranging from physics and engineering to financial modeling to data analytics. These applications regularly employ components in which the majority of the component’s runtime display is driven by external data. We are all familiar with using binding to alter some portion of a component. A fully data-driven component will also have other aspects of its display controlled by external data.
For example, it is common in the utility industry to display, analyze, and even edit load profiles. Each profile contains one or more time series such as ‘raw data,’ ‘cleansed data’, ‘gross’, ‘AMI’, etc. Each of these series has some meaning t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to self-host Plausible Analytics on Ubuntu with SSL for Free!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/adisreyaj/how-to-self-host-plausible-analytics-on-ubuntu-with-ssl-for-free-32a5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/adisreyaj/how-to-self-host-plausible-analytics-on-ubuntu-with-ssl-for-free-32a5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-host the open-source alternative to Google Analytics, Plausible using Oracle Cloud Free VM instance. Set up Plausible Analytics on an Ubuntu machine with these simple steps. Follow them one by one and then you can get yourself a simple and easy-to-use analytics tool.
Simple and privacy-friendly alternative to Google Analytics
This is what their website says. What makes it better you may ask? For starters, it's open-source. Here are some other features that make it stand out from others:
Lightweight script (<1KB)
Simple and easy to use
Privacy-friendly
Read more about it here: https://plausible.io |  Demo 
Plausible is open-source. According to their website, there is only one version of it and both the managed version and the self-hosted version are completely equal. 

If you go with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Code Generation in Angular CLI workspaces with Nx Devkit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nx/better-code-generation-in-angular-cli-workspaces-with-nx-devkit-3m09</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nx/better-code-generation-in-angular-cli-workspaces-with-nx-devkit-3m09"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schematics in Angular provide a way to automate common tasks, such as generating files, reading, and updating configuration files, and modifying your codebase. Angular Schematics are built using the Angular Devkit, which consists of many lower-level APIs, along with a few concepts to learn such as the Virtual Filesystem, Trees, Rules, Actions, Context and more. Learning these concepts and APIs can be challenging for developers looking to write schematics for Angular applications and libraries.
The Nx Devkit is an underlying part of the Nx build framework that provides utilities for building generators and executors. The Nx Devkit provides a way to build generators with a more straightforward approach using only JavaScript language primitives and immutable objects (the tree being the only e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Azure Role Based Access Control (RBAC) using Github]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-azure-role-based-access-control-rbac-using-github-2349</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/automate-azure-role-based-access-control-rbac-using-github-2349"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Azure Roles and Custom Definitions?


When you start working more and more with Azure permissions you will undoubtedly have used Azure RBAC (also known as IAM) and have most likely used some of the great built-in roles that have been created and provided by Microsoft, but sometimes you may come across a requirement or a need to have a very specific role tailored with a set of permissions that are more granular than what comes out of the box in a standard Azure (RBAC) built-in role.
Luckily Azure offers a great deal of flexibility when it comes to defining your own custom roles vs built-in roles. This is where Custom Role Definitions comes into play.
Today we will look at how we can utilize Github actions in creating and also maintaining our Azure (RBAC) custom role definitions fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I found the best text editor for basic code fixing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/souviktests/i-found-the-best-text-editor-for-basic-code-fixing-4bfm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/souviktests/i-found-the-best-text-editor-for-basic-code-fixing-4bfm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a couple of days, I was looking for a simple terminal-based text editor for taking simple code notes or basic code fixing kinds of stuff.
As an aspiring developer, I really like the concept of coding without touching the mouse.
So I downloaded the king of CLI text editors, Vim.
Now, guess what happened.
Yeah, you're right. I stuck inside vim and couldn't even quit from there.
Then, I started watching a bunch of tutorials and started reading vim's documentation.
This tutorial from Ben Awad helped me to get started.
But then I realized, I have to learn a lot of things only to operate vim and it's a pretty lengthy process.
At that time, I really needed a very simple text editor for doing basic stuff.
But, vim is not simple... you know :)
So, I had to come back to 'nano' & I was not happy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Souvik Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best No-Code Tools for Developers in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60a5248c906c5207e3a7e54b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-no-code-tools-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code tools let people across the world build different products and applications without writing code.   Before no-code tools, building simple websites or mobile applications took weeks or months and only experienced software developers could do it.  But that's not the case anymore. Now, you can spin up blogs, websites, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Azure SignalR +Azure App Service - Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jayendran/securing-azure-signalr-azure-app-service-part-1-bko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jayendran/securing-azure-signalr-azure-app-service-part-1-bko"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I start to explore the Azure SignalR Service for one of my chat based web wpplication.
Azure SignalR Service simplifies the process of adding real-time web functionality to applications over HTTP. This real-time functionality allows the service to push content updates to connected clients, such as a single page web or mobile application. As a result, clients are updated without the need to poll the server or submit new HTTP requests for updates.
To put more simple word Azure SignalR is a PaaS helps us to update the Client (UI) without refreshing the Page - So Cool😎 Is it?
For that I need to come-up with a architecture, So I start doing a POC - "How to securely connect a Azure SignalR Service from a simple ChatBased Application" ?
You can find more asp.net sample code for Azuresig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jayendran Arumugam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340626</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wrangling-control-over-pdfs-with-the-adobe-pdf-embed-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By our last estimate, there are now more PDFs in the world than atoms in the universe (not verified by outside sources) so chances are, from time to time, you’re going to run into a PDF document or two. Browsers …
The post Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raymond Camden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the full stack demands in the next few years?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/what-are-the-full-stack-demands-in-the-next-few-years-5daf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/what-are-the-full-stack-demands-in-the-next-few-years-5daf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, Today is full stack developers are great demand for app development. So, Let’s know here Top 7 reasons which is the the know as a full stack developer’s future is great in the next few years.
Fewer resources for a business
Besides being a specialist in front-end and back-end development, a full-stack developer is likewise proficient in several other fields. Full-stack programmers will be able to play the role of web developers and mean-stack developers
plus DevOps developers. They need to be theoretically sound in just about all aspects of development and technology.
Some programming languages which full-stack developers must get better at happen to be JavaScript, React.js, MongoDB, node, in addition to Python. The future of the majority of the full-stack developers is great because o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is opinionated and that’s great]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stephenradams/angular-is-opinionated-and-that-s-great-3ldn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stephenradams/angular-is-opinionated-and-that-s-great-3ldn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of Angular, I’ve been using it for years now, for a variety of projects. I’ve written about it and helped others learn it. One thing that I have noticed that a lot of developers who start using Angular who have come from a different technology stack, is that they try to apply the style and approach they have in another framework or language to Angular. This can lead to extremely messy code or Angular code that is hard to maintain as a project grows.
The reason I feel this happens is Angular is an opinionated framework, there is an approach you take to write Angular apps. If you try to ‘build’ an Angular app in a way that goes against this approach, then things can start to go wrong.
In Angular there are some things you should do:
Split your functionality into modules
Use serv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[👤 5 Ways Your Login Box Is Not Living Its Best Life]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/5-ways-your-login-box-is-not-living-its-best-life-26i3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/5-ways-your-login-box-is-not-living-its-best-life-26i3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T12:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📌 Here are five ways in which your login box is turning your customers away from your brand.



  
  
  
Blame Netflix or Spotify.
In fact, take your pick of any of the digital brands that have made seamless and beautiful UX a staple part of daily life. From one-click checkouts on Amazon to Single Sign-On across all of Google’s services, consumers have never had it better for digital experiences….and they are now expecting it everywhere they go online. 

Login boxes are the first thing many people engage with on a website. Yet, the importance of them can sometimes be relegated to “as long as it works, it works.”
The challenge is consumers don’t just want things that work; they want things that work so well they never even notice it. 
And so here are five ways in which your login box is turning your customers away from your brand.
Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with IRC and Weechat]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skorotkiewicz/getting-started-with-irc-and-weechat-5f66</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skorotkiewicz/getting-started-with-irc-and-weechat-5f66"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T12:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, first of all I would like to tell you what IRC is, I will explain it in simple words so that even non-technical people can start playing with IRC.
Today I will describe how to start chat with IRC with my favorite IRC Weechat client, it's a terminal client, but don't worry, it's very easy to configure and use on a daily basis, and if you have your own server you can even set it up in screen -S weechat :)
Shall we get started? Here we go!
First we need to install our new IRC client, there are many ways to install it, depending on which system you use.
pacman -S weechat and on macOS brew install weechat.
No worries as you saw the word compile, weechat is very easy to compile :)
You can skip the compilation step and download the finished weechat from weechat.org. But what fun is that?
For …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Korotkiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Custom Resource using CDK `AwsCustomResource` construct]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikhilzadoo/aws-custom-resource-using-cdk-awscustomresource-construct-5emn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikhilzadoo/aws-custom-resource-using-cdk-awscustomresource-construct-5emn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prerequisite



Understanding of AWS CDK (Cloud development kit)
Understanding of AWS Custom resources
All through the blog I will be mentioning terms custom resource lambda and custom resource. Both terms look similar but actually are different. Custom resource lambda refers to the lambda that is responsible for implementing the logic. Custom resource is the resource itself that is created by invoking the custom resource lambda.
In this blog I am covering a niche scenario related to AWS custom resources when all your custom resource lambda needs is to call an AWS API. Usual use case of doing so would be when cloudformation does not support a resource and it is only available with an API.
For all other use cases, please refer to my earlier blog Custom Resources with AWS CDK.
CDK Construct …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Zadoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 4 - Wordpress EC2 instance in ASG with RDS database and ALB- Awesome AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emmanuelnk/part-4-wordpress-ec2-instance-in-asg-with-rds-database-and-alb-awesome-aws-cdk-3cij</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emmanuelnk/part-4-wordpress-ec2-instance-in-asg-with-rds-database-and-alb-awesome-aws-cdk-3cij"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T10:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Abbreviations
Setup


Setup AWS configuration and CDK
Create a new project
Project structure
Config
VPC


Setup
RDS


Setup
Application Load Balancer


Important Load Balancer concepts
Setup
EC2 via Autoscaling Group


Setup
User script
EC2 instance in ASG
Deployment


Local machine
Github Actions
Destroying the stack
Final result
Conclusion


Debugging
Homework Assignments
Hot off the heels (more than one month ago lol) of the last post, we're going to provision better infrastructure for our Wordpress powered website using the AWS CDK!
In this tutorial, you will learn how to:
setup a Wordpress EC2 instance in an Autoscaling Group (ASG) that is attached to an Application Load Balancer (ALB)
setup AWS RDSMySQL database using the CDK
place your RDS MySQL database in an isolated …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel N Kyeyune</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HashiCorp Vault with Octopus Deploy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/octopus/using-hashicorp-vault-with-octopus-deploy-e88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/octopus/using-hashicorp-vault-with-octopus-deploy-e88"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T10:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storing sensitive values in Octopus Deploy solves many problems. If your organization has standardized on a secrets manager though, that might mean storing sensitive values twice, making secrets management more complicated.
Octopus has supported the concept of sensitive variables since Octopus 2.0, but customers often ask about support for secret managers. One in particular is HashiCorp Vault.
In this post, I walk through a number of new HashiCorp Vault step templates designed to retrieve secrets from Vault for use in your deployments or runbooks.
Introduction
Authentication



LDAP login step


LDAP login parameters
Using the LDAP login step
AppRole login step


AppRole login parameters
Using the AppRole login step
AppRole best practises
AppRole Get Wrapped SecretID step


AppRole Get Wra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scheduling API for Service Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/spurwing/scheduling-api-for-service-providers-56de</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/spurwing/scheduling-api-for-service-providers-56de"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T10:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing multiple offices with a high influx of client appointments can be complicated and error-prone. Tracking the appointments with client's payments makes it even more cumbersome. That is where a system like what Spurwing provides becomes a crucial element of daily office life.
Spurwing's Scheduling API has been used by a variety of companies from health-related offices to engineering and development teams. It has several scheduling tools to keep appointments organized and convenient to clients. Custom time management solution systems can be designed around your specific use cases, for instance:
Allow clients to maintain choice in who they are seeing during their appointment.


Keep track of scheduling of multiple staff members with various services in several locations.


Maintain all…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spurwing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Guide to the Vim Text Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/a-quick-guide-to-the-vim-text-editor-3e2b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/a-quick-guide-to-the-vim-text-editor-3e2b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T10:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a  text editor which is highly efficient. It is an improved variant of the vi editor, that is distributed with UNIX systems. 
Vim is often called a "programmer's editor," and so useful for programming that many consider it an entire IDE. It's not just for programmers, though. Vim is perfect for all kinds of text editing, from composing email to editing configuration files.
The vim text editor is an extremely powerful tool for developers, but it can be difficult to master.  If you are new to vim, I recommend these exercises
If you're using a Mac or a Linux machine, it's likely that your terminal has vim built in, so it's worth being familiar with to work on those systems. 
If not, you can install vim with your package manager or test if vi is installed.
To install vim for Ubuntu, follow these instructions.
1: Open a terminal window and type sudo apt-get install vim
sudo apt-get install vim

2: If you want to get updated version of vim, open a terminal window and type sudo apt-get update
sudo apt-get update

3: Then type sudo apt-get install vim
sudo apt-get install vim

The installation process will take some time, after which all the commands of vim will be available.

To start vim, just type vim in the command line
vim

Then you can type ESC followed by :e filename to open filename.
To open a vim directly from the command line, type:
vim filename

Press ZQ to quit vim without saving. Press ZZ to save and exit.
To move the cursor, you can press ESC and use the keys h,j,k,l.  You can also use the arrow keys in vim.

Vim has modes. To switch to writing mode, press the i key or the insert key. To switch to command mode, press the ESC key.
To save your file press ESC followed by :w.
Press :Explore to open the file explorer. Use the j and k keys and press enter to open the file. You can also use :LExplore]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Testing Essentials of Cloud-based Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cigniti/security-testing-essentials-of-cloud-based-applications-1d8j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cigniti/security-testing-essentials-of-cloud-based-applications-1d8j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T09:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a consistent focus on scalability, an interconnected ecosystem, and seamless operation, businesses are deploying their applications in the Cloud environment. Naturally, Cloud-based application security testing is emerging as an essential exercise. 
In this blog, we will outline the key aspects of Cloud application testing. Before that, let’s take a brief look at the concept and importance of Cloud security testing.
Cloud testing focuses on securing an application hosted on Cloud infrastructure. The latest techniques are employed to ensure data safety and prevent stealing & omission. Some of the advantages of Cloud testing include: 
Regulatory Compliance - Cloud computing security solutions help to manage and maintain an enhanced architecture for compliance.
Limited Expenditure - There…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hemanth Yamjala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring InnoDB Cluster members using Prometheus and MySQL Exporter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nirgilboa/monitoring-innodb-cluster-members-using-prometheus-and-mysql-exporter-1c1l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nirgilboa/monitoring-innodb-cluster-members-using-prometheus-and-mysql-exporter-1c1l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T08:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The high-availability features of MySQL InnoDB Cluster in its open source (Community) edition have come a long way, and in recent years the 8.x versions have delivered immense improvements in this area over the veteran 5.7 versions. I've found that monitoring such a cluster with OSS tools to be more involved, and through this post I hope to shed some light and share what has worked for me and my team.
TL;DR



8.x InnoDB Clusters (single Primary) are more tolerant to network failures (Auto Rejoin)

5.7.x InnoDB Clusters can also be managed using MySQL Shell from the 8.x series, although you will miss some of the newest management features (e.g. Clone)
Prometheus  and MySQL Exporter will enable you to monitor cluster members as reported in the replication_group_members table.
Let me start o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nir Gilboa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Commands For Everyday Life]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/linux-commands-for-everyday-life-5e5f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/linux-commands-for-everyday-life-5e5f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T08:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Linux commands is one of those things that help you in your everyday life as a programmer, systems administrator or IT professional. So today I compiled a list of everyday linux commands that you might find useful in real life.
Linux is solid, but you don’t realize how much you depend on it until something goes wrong. Whether it’s a simple fix or you have no idea what’s going on. We’ll start with the basics:
ls : List contents of directory
$ ls
public_html

$ ls -l
-rw-r--r-- 1 owner group 0 Jan 23 13:09 index.html

$ ls -l /tmp/
total 616
drwxrwxrwt 27 root root 4096 Oct 22 14:09 .

cd : Change directory
user@hostname:~$ cd /etc
user@hostname:/etc

user@hostname:~$ cd /usr/local/bin
user@hostname:/usr/local/bin

pwd : Show current directory
user@hostname:/usr/local/bin$ pwd
/usr/local/bin
user@hostname:/usr/local/bin$ 

sudo : run command as root (admin)
$ sudo ls
[sudo] password for user: 

run a program
$ ./app

As a Linux user, you have more commands than you can count at the tip of your fingers.
In fact, you have enough commands to do every day tasks, including:
Using git version control for your project
Connecting to your web server over ssh
Controlling your file system
Searching for files containing a particular word in the file path
Backup databases or interact with them
See your web server logs for security attacks
Opening up a terminal-based text editor either locally or remotely
To get to a Linux pro level quickly, I recommend this tutorial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is computer vision? And how it works.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rishabh062/what-is-computer-vision-and-how-it-works-5789</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rishabh062/what-is-computer-vision-and-how-it-works-5789"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T07:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer Vision(CV) is a field of Artificial Intelligence(AI) that enables computers and systems to derive meaningful information from digital images, videos and other visual inputs- and make recommended output based on that.


If AI enables computers to think, computer vision enables them to see, observe and understand.
CV trains their machine to do such work but it should do those work in lesser time with the use of cameras or algorithms as compare to retina or nerves.
48.6 billion by 2022.



  
  
  How does Computer vision works?


Computer vision requires lots of data for getting good accuracy.
openCV 
There are many research has done in this field, but apart from it there are many uses of CV in business, entertainment, transportation, healthcare and everyday life.
Image Classification:
It sees an image and can classify it (a dog, an apple, a person’s face).
Object detection:
It can use image classification to identify a certain class of image and then detect and tabulate their appearance in an image or video.
Object Tracking:
It follows or tracks an object once it is detected. This task is executed by with image capturing in sequence or real-time.
Content-based image retrieval:
It uses computer vision to browse, search and retrieve images from large data stores, based on the content of the images rather than metadata tags associated with them.(PS:This is most useful application of CV)
You can check out my github repository where I have made many projects based on CV.
OpenCV-Tutorial
Projects
Now it's time to explore friends.
Linkedln
Twitter
Thanks for reading.
Rishabh Dwivedi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Dwivedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which one should I do first?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pavithrasp1194/which-one-should-i-do-first-2oe5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pavithrasp1194/which-one-should-i-do-first-2oe5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T07:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am planning to upgrade my angular application to version 10 and migrate Tslint to Eslint which one should I do first?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavithra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When should I use NgRx (or Redux)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/3zsforinsomnia/when-should-i-use-ngrx-or-redux-5dk9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/3zsforinsomnia/when-should-i-use-ngrx-or-redux-5dk9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T02:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When should I use NgRx or Redux?


"When should I use NgRx" is a question whose answers have changed several times over the years, and personally I find a lot of the guidance available online to be a little too "does it feel right" and “can something else handle what you are doing”. While informative and a great way to learn about some new libraries, this is largely not helpful for deciding when to say “yes, I would benefit from using NgRx for this project”. Over the last several years I’ve tried to come up with a mental framework for deciding whether or not a project would benefit from NgRx, and decided to share what I’ve come up with and see what others think.
Obviously this is subjective and I would love to hear what others have to say and see what the community would add or remove to t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary Levine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live Q&A on DevOps, GitHub and Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/live-q-a-on-devops-github-and-azure-devops-o5h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/live-q-a-on-devops-github-and-azure-devops-o5h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T01:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got any questions about DevOps, GitHub and/or Azure DevOps?
Join me for this live Q&A and I will try and answer all your questions!




To celebrate the 2,000 subscribers on my YouTube channel CoderDave I will host a live Q&A/AMA next Tuesday (see below the time schedule)
Prepare your questions, and I hope to see y'all live! And if you can't make it, post your questions either here or in the comments of the video so I can address them during the live!
Thanks so very much again for your support!
TIME OF THE LIVE:
Tuesday 25, 9.30 pm UTC+8
Tuesday 25, 7.00 pm IST
Tuesday 25, 1.30 pm UTC
Tuesday 25, 9.30 am ET
Tuesday 25, 6.30 am PT
Like, share and follow me 🚀 for more content:
📽 YouTube
Buy me a coffee
Patreon
Merch
Facebook page
GitHub
Twitter
LinkedIn
Podcast]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditsmod - new NodeJS webframework writen in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T22:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivation to create Ditsmod


Before creating Ditsmod, of course, I was looking for: "Are there ready-made solutions for my purposes?".
I believe that the set of the following features is unique at the moment:
The framework is written in TypeScript (and under the hood there is no ExpressJS or Fastify ;).
Modular architecture with decorators.
Has a hierarchical Dependency Injection that allows you to use classes as a search token, rather than their names.
Clearly delineated providers arrays for DI injectors at the application, module, route, or request level.
Built-in support for nested routes, such as /api/posts/:postId/comments/:commentId.
Check for collisions when importing providers. This feature allows you to detect situations where you import two or more modules that export providers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Костя Третяк</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SELECT PATH OF FOLDER OR DIRECTORY USING JAVASCRPT OR ANGULAR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/biq12/select-path-of-folder-or-directory-using-javascrpt-or-angular-40p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/biq12/select-path-of-folder-or-directory-using-javascrpt-or-angular-40p4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T16:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i like to select a path in local drive , the probleme if i choose a directory if it s empty the code nto work if it not empty it work fine 
//  input type="file"   name="currentselectedFile"  (change)="onFileSelected($event)"   webkitDirectory directory multiple 
onFileSelected(event){
 var theFiles = event.target.files;
 var relativePath = theFiles[0].webkitRelativePath;
}
// if the path it s not empty all it s ok]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>biq12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Developer discovers Redux-Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/angular-developer-discovers-redux-toolkit-3bn8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/angular-developer-discovers-redux-toolkit-3bn8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T15:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an Angular developer, one of my biggest challenges was shifting my thought process from mutable-, to immutable state.
In an Angular service, you can simply assign a new value to a property, and like magic - the change detection would kick in and update any component using the property. 
Switching over to React, suddenly immutable state is the way to go! Then, suddenly Redux - actions, reducers, middleware, dispatchers, and the list goes on. 
The first time I saw Redux toolkit, the very first thing that hit me, in Reducers:
...
reducers: {
    increment: state => {
        state.value += 1;
    }
}
...

Assignment operator in a Reducer? For a brief moment I thought I somehow ended up in the Vuex documentation, this is how you update state in mutations. But No, it was Redux Toolkit. 
I fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dewald Els</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>