<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-17T00:50:43.182Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-17T00:50:43.182Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Winston Logger; A beginner's guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jobizil/getting-started-with-winston-logger-a-beginner-s-guide-7j3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jobizil/getting-started-with-winston-logger-a-beginner-s-guide-7j3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T23:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging Definition




Logging is the process of recording application actions, activities and state to a secondary interface.


Logging is the process of recording application activities into log files. Data saved in a log file are called logs and are usually identified with the .log extension (some people use other extension preferences)



In this article, you will discover how to use - Winston to log your application activities into files instead of logging to the console.
Why do we need to Log application activities you may ask;
Helps us know when something or an issue occurs with our app, especially when it's in production mode.
Helps monitor and Keep track of your system activities.
Helps persist data so you can view this data for analysis later
In this tutorial, we will need an Exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ugbem Job</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird rants of a new Devops + Backend engineer 😤 [17 June 21]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uds5501/weird-rants-of-a-new-devops-backend-engineer-17-june-21-57l4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uds5501/weird-rants-of-a-new-devops-backend-engineer-17-june-21-57l4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T22:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the weird notes of a new DevOps and Backend engineer. This is my (quite open) notebook on what was all the stuff I read and learnt. Not necessarily tech, you can just read on and understand what I am rambling on about.
Opentelemetry's sentry exporter is pretty cool, even thought it's specifically for traces right now, it does its job well.
The sidecar architecture for opentelemetry-collector will work the best for a scenario. The engineers thought out the agent, collector interface pretty good. 
The Traces specification and the TraceID stuff is good too, I just hope there was more sync between the published package and the github repository.
Need to show the instrumentation demo to the lead.
Probably will need to checkout Elastic APM exporters for these traces.
See if sentry can support any logging :)
Checking how opentelemetry trace back the traces by the ID.
WTF is going on with those spans? Why do they provide us with new contexts?
Thanks for listening to the rant.
Uddeshya Singh,
Signing off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uddeshya Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring 2FA on your Linux Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended Setup


Update your server to the latest packages.
sudo apt update && apt upgrade && reboot

Add a non-root user with sudo privileges.
adduser username
usermod -aG sudo username
su username

First, install the Google Authenticator PAM module.
sudo apt install libpam-google-authenticator

Run the google-authenticator binary to create a new secret key (keep this one safe).
google-authenticator

After completing the process, you can scan/enter the code in an Authenticator App.
I've chosen the following settings for this example.
Do you want authentication tokens to be time-based (y/n) y

Do you want me to update your "/home/username/.google_authenticator" file? (y/n) y

Do you want to disallow multiple uses of the same authentication
token? This restricts you to one login about ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florentin / 珞辰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring 2FA on your Linux Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ecklf/configuring-2fa-on-your-linux-server-2fjm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended Setup


Update your server to the latest packages.
sudo apt update && apt upgrade && reboot

Add a non-root user with sudo privileges.
adduser username
usermod -aG sudo username
su username

First, install the Google Authenticator PAM module.
sudo apt install libpam-google-authenticator

Run the google-authenticator binary to create a new secret key (keep this one safe).
google-authenticator

After completing the process, you can scan/enter the code in an Authenticator App.
I've chosen the following settings for this example.
Do you want authentication tokens to be time-based (y/n) y

Do you want me to update your "/home/username/.google_authenticator" file? (y/n) y

Do you want to disallow multiple uses of the same authentication
token? This restricts you to one login about ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florentin / 珞辰</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Split – How to Split a String into an Array in JS]]></title>
        <id>60c088e5d3126007592d56f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-split-how-to-split-a-string-into-an-array-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In general, a string represents a sequence of characters in a programming language.  Let's look at an example of a string created using a sequence of characters, "Yes, You Can DO It!". In JavaScript, we can create a string in a couple of ways: Using the string literal as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inline Styles as Classes (lol)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inline-styles-as-classes-lol/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re abhorred by using inline styles, just move that style to the class attribute! And then make sure you have CSS in place that, ya know, does what it says on the box. 
I've revolutionized CSS. pic.twitter.com/1AWCldyCwP
— Sam 

…
The post Inline Styles as Classes (lol) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comandos básicos que debes conocer para dominar LINUX. ​💻​]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gdcodev/comandos-basicos-que-debes-conocer-para-dominar-linux-1emi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gdcodev/comandos-basicos-que-debes-conocer-para-dominar-linux-1emi"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En la informática saber usar la consola de comandos Linux es fundamental, es por eso que les comparto una serie de comandos básicos para que aprendas y logres dominar el terminal.
A continuación vamos a ver algunos de los comandos con los que se puede empezar.
Sirve para encontrar la ruta del directorio (carpeta) de trabajo actual en el que te encuentras
pwd

Crear un nuevo directorio
mkdir <nombre-directorio>

Sirve para navegar por los archivos y directorios
cd Fotos/  entrar en el directorio Fotos 
cd .. (con dos puntos) retroceder un nivel
cd ../.. retroceder dos niveles
cd para ir directamente a la carpeta de inicio (raíz)
cd - (con un guión) para ir al directorio anterior

Crear ficheros
touch index.html

Si necesitas eliminar un directorio, pero solo te permite eliminar directorios …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gastón Danielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skewness and Kurtosis – Positively Skewed and Negatively Skewed Distributions in Statistics Explained]]></title>
        <id>60b8cb0aacb62507dd1d82ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/skewness-and-kurtosis-in-statistics-explained/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll explain two important concepts in statistics: skewness and kurtosis. And don't worry – you won't need to know very much math to understand these concepts and learn how to apply them. What are Density Curves?Let's first talk a bit about density curves, as skewness and kurtosis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Better React Apps with These Simple Tricks]]></title>
        <id>60ca25704dc1a607ed7b408c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-better-react-apps-with-these-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a list of amazing tricks that you can use to improve your React applications instantly. These tips will not only make your code cleaner and more reliable, but they also aim to make your development experience easier and overall more enjoyable.  Give these techniques a try in your React]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Examples of DevOps Remediation with Datadog and WayScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jorshman/3-examples-of-devops-remediation-with-datadog-and-wayscript-3c5k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jorshman/3-examples-of-devops-remediation-with-datadog-and-wayscript-3c5k"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a scaling software company, we experience periods of unpredictable platform usage spikes which can come from all over the world. This volatility fosters complexity around instance scaling and other core dev infrastructure. If our instances don’t scale properly, our users experience a less performant product. If our servers are too large, it is a waste of dollars.
Hooking into Datadog gave our company newfound and much-needed insights into our AWS infrastructure. Moreover, the alerting functionality built into Datadog’s event monitoring unlocked the ability for us to monitor, investigate, and ultimately resolve issues with our infrastructure. However, although Datadog alerted us to issues, we still had to manually manage our AWS infra. Our goal was to build a platform that could remediat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Orshan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla Use Reducer with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fangoh/vanilla-use-reducer-with-typescript-4f9p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fangoh/vanilla-use-reducer-with-typescript-4f9p"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I was recently doing a project for my portfolio, a React Project with a slightly complex state. Personally, I really love TypeScript and the Redux/Reducer patterns, because they give me a great Developer Experience with TypeScript and a lot of autocompletion available, quite useful in order to not get bit by a bug caused by a typo, and really convenient as I don't have to explore files constantly in order to know what are the properties that a certain object should have.
I always prefer to use TS over vanilla JS, so, it makes a lot of sense to try to make use of strict typing, even in a concept app. Also, while vanilla useReducer might not be what most projects use, I still want to share how I found it to be pretty useful in this context.
My application is a Social Media-like platform,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hector Osuna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start a SPA and it's API in one click]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/binarypatrick/start-a-spa-and-it-s-api-in-one-click-5cg3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/binarypatrick/start-a-spa-and-it-s-api-in-one-click-5cg3"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using start or jump scripts for a long time to start up my API and SPA at the same time. With project TYE on the horizon, I thought I would share more about my more simplistic, "poor man", implementation.
It is important to note, a lot of configuration information is specified ahead of time in different files to make this work. For ASP.Net, the ports are configured in the launch.json and for node, proxy information is set up in a proxy.config.json file. Below is a simple example of the proxy config I use most often to route api requests to the ASP.Net port. It is also good to remember both apps are running locally under localhost.
// proxy config
{
  "/api": {
    "target": "http://localhost:5000",
    "secure": false,
    "logLevel": "debug",
    "changeOrigin": false
  }
}

it'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful and Useless Code Comments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342630</id>
        <link href="https://blog.jim-nielsen.com/2021/useful-and-usless-code-comments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nielsen: 
If somebody says a comment isn’t adding any value, I would ask: to whom?
Personally, I’ve never liked the advice that writing obvious comments is bad practice—probably because I write obvious comments all the time.
Jim showed …
The post Useful and Useless Code Comments appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what are the  best npm packages you like ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/visurockerr/what-are-the-best-npm-packages-you-like-41p8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/visurockerr/what-are-the-best-npm-packages-you-like-41p8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T19:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[what are the  best npm packages which can make my express Js project a good one.
ex: swagger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>visurockerr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ngModel - Type 'Event' is not assignable to type 'string'.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mateuszto/ngmodel-type-event-is-not-assignable-to-type-string-f2n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mateuszto/ngmodel-type-event-is-not-assignable-to-type-string-f2n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T18:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://stackblitz.com/edit/angular-ivy-ws1lhp?file=src%2Fapp%2Fapp.component.ts What am I doing wrong? Somebody help?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mateusz Tomczyk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Just Want to Download You!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jneuhaus20/i-just-want-to-download-you-fo2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jneuhaus20/i-just-want-to-download-you-fo2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T18:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have software that people download from your site, there is a finite set of versions people actually care about.  Yes, some people want all of them, and you should satisfy that.  But honestly, no one should have to actually read to get the "right" version.  We have plenty of other shit to read, and so do you.
The latest version (or current major)
All the currently supported Long-Term Stable versions (explicit LTS, or latest of all supported majors)
Latest plus all LTS
Here we have pgAdmin. Not the most egregious, but this is also the update process when the running app has already informed you of the latest version.





 


  
  
  Done Well


Contrast this with Node.js. This is the first page off Google search results:



There are no other screens, because those buttons immediately trigger the download.
It's the Golden Rule, and just good citizenship! Respect others' time and effort as you would like yours to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Neuhaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach Yourself Data Analytics in 30 Days]]></title>
        <id>60ca30af4dc1a607ed7b4197</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/teach-yourself-data-analytics-in-30-days/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T17:19:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn the basics of Data Analytics with 30 days of practice.  We just released a Data Analytics course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. The course includes a 40-minute video, as well as a website and Jupyter notebooks. If you follow the plan laid out in these course]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Podcast] Statuspal Running in Production]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/statuspal/podcast-statuspal-running-in-production-5dh4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/statuspal/podcast-statuspal-running-in-production-5dh4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T16:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our CEO Eduardo Messuti in the ▶️ Running in Production podcast, where he and host Nick Janetakis talk about the different challenges that go behind the curtains in running a hosted status page & monitoring platform using Elixir and Phoenix since 2017.
Some of the subjects discussed are:
How picking Elixir as the backend impacted the project early on as it was maturing.
Hosting the platform in DigitalOcean and Heroku.
How we manage to serve ~500k requests/day.
How we created a Restful API to send batch email through our customer's SMTP servers.
How we use Docker and docker-compose together with Github actions for deployment.
What's our experience with hiring Elixir developers.
For this and much more interesting insights listen to the podcast at:
▶️ The Running in Production podcast ▶️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduardo Messuti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Most Interactive Shell On A Linux Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nirupamvas/how-to-install-most-interactive-shell-on-a-linux-machine-36ko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nirupamvas/how-to-install-most-interactive-shell-on-a-linux-machine-36ko"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T16:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Guys, I am Nirupamvas and I am back again with an other awesome Linux tutorial. So let's get started.
Before getting into it, let's understand some of the things 
A shell is an interface to the underlying operating system. It allows you to execute operations using text and commands, and it provides users with advanced features like being able to create scripts.
So, everytime you want to execute a command you need to type entire command, I think this is one messy thing we need to do each and every time. To boost productivity and to save time for our lazy squad we have something called Fish. So let's see what is it all about.
Fish, or the “Friendly Interactive Shell,” is the most user-friendly and interactive shell, in my opinion.
Let's start our installation,
Step 1 : Download Fish


…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nirupamvas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scout APM Launches Error Monitoring for Ruby Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahowescoutapm/scout-apm-launches-error-monitoring-for-ruby-applications-j44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahowescoutapm/scout-apm-launches-error-monitoring-for-ruby-applications-j44"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T16:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scout APM, a leading provider of Application Performance Monitoring (APM), announced the release of Scout Error Monitoring for Ruby applications on June 1, 2021. Scout APM provides developers and application administrators software performance insights by delivering key web application performance metrics. 
Traditionally an APM tool, Scout has expanded its service offerings to now include error monitoring of web applications for more cohesive and actionable observability insights within a single platform. This new feature supports an overall better user experience by eliminating the need for multiple web-application monitoring services; Scout APM with Scout Error Monitoring offers performance and error insight and alerting within a single, integrated dashboard.
“Scout’s industry-leading performance and, now, error monitoring solutions are essential for developers building performant, cloud-native applications,” says Jason Hable, Scout’s CEO. “We wanted to expand our services to build a more holistic performance and exception monitoring tool to help our customers solve issues quickly and efficiently. By connecting error reporting and performance monitoring data in one platform we provide our customers with the insights they need without paying for the features they don’t.”
Multiple trends and factors have contributed to the growth of both the APM and error monitoring markets in recent years. Companies are experiencing an increased reliance on advanced data analytics and automation as cloud computing and containers become progressively mission-critical. 
About Scout APM
ScoutAPM.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ahowe-scoutapm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's why you should use Kubernetes!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pghildiyal/here-s-why-you-should-use-kubernetes-g9l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pghildiyal/here-s-why-you-should-use-kubernetes-g9l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is a portable, extensible, open-source platform for managing containerized applications and services that facilitates both declarative configuration and automation. Kubernetes provides a platform to configure, automate, and manage:
Intelligent and balanced scheduling of containers
Creation, deletion, and movement of containers
Easy scaling of containers
Monitoring and self-healing abilities
Challenges with Previous Technologies


Before Kubernetes there were containers, which became popular because they simplified going from application development to deployment without having to worry about portability or reproducibility. Developers can package an application and all its dependencies, libraries, and configuration files needed to execute the application into a container image. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prashant Ghildiyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implicit ESM in Node.js with "type": "module"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bnb/implicit-esm-in-node-js-with-type-module-np</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bnb/implicit-esm-in-node-js-with-type-module-np"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing the Node.js ESM content, I'd like to talk about the comparitively straightforward alternative to using .mjs to get your Node.js applications to run as ECMAScript Modules (ESM) rather than CommonJS: including "type": "module" in your package.json.
"type": "module"


Let's assume we've started with the following package.json for a zero (production) dependency application:
{
  "name": "apollo-lunar-module",
  "version": "0.0.1",
  "description": "A simple, fast, nice lunar lander module",
  "main": "index.js",
  "scripts": {
    "lint": "standard"
  },
  "author": "Tierney Cyren <hello@bnb.im> (https://bnb.im/)",
  "license": "MIT",
  "devDependencies": {
    "standard": "^16.0.3"
  }
}

To have implicit ESM - that is, have our .js files parsed as ESM - we' need to make the followi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tierney Cyren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342353</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-i-used-the-waapi-to-build-an-animation-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Web Animations API lets us construct animations and control their playback with JavaScript. The API opens the browser’s animation engine to developers and was designed to underlie implementations of both CSS animations and transitions, leaving the door open to …
The post How I Used the WAAPI to Build an Animation Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okiki Ojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a self-sequential pipeline in Jenkins]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/taikedz/creating-a-self-sequential-pipeline-in-jenkins-1aij</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/taikedz/creating-a-self-sequential-pipeline-in-jenkins-1aij"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(header image derived from image by Wikipedia user Inductiveload)
So I had the absolute pleasure this fortnight of implementing what we call in my company a "lifecycle pipeline" in Jenkins. Essentially, running a script over and over and over again to flex the mechanics of our physical product, through means of our CI pipeline infrastructure. It produces a lot of log data, and for something that stands to be running for weeks, even months, we wanted to be sure that
We didn't max out the storage on the little Raspberry Pi that was powering the process and
That we had the extracted data being uploaded at intervals
To do this, we used to have a standard Jenkins job that would run, and then check how many runs it hand done, and if not yet at maximum, it would call itself again for a new run, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tai Kedzierski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Helm plugin in minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/datreeio/how-to-build-a-helm-plugin-in-minutes-47i0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/datreeio/how-to-build-a-helm-plugin-in-minutes-47i0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Helm is a great addition to the Kubernetes ecosystem; it simplifies complex Kubernetes manifests by separating them into charts and values. 
Sharing charts has never been easier especially since all the customizable parameters are located separately (values.yaml). The downside of this is that there’s no single place to see the resulting manifest, as it’s usually compiled and installed in a single step - helm install. 
Helm alleviates this with a plugin system that allows you to seamlessly integrate with the Helm flow and easily run custom code that’s not part of the Helm core code which, as we’ll see in the next section, can be written in any language, even Bash.
Let's build a simple plugin that prints out some useful information and environment variables that Helm provides.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Labunsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize Angular Webpack config]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dontry/customize-angular-webpack-config-4be6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dontry/customize-angular-webpack-config-4be6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[add customWebpackConfig to angular.json
{
    "projects": {
        "architect": {
            "build": {
                "options": {
                  "customWebpackConfig": {
          "path": "./custom-webpack.config.js",
          "replaceDuplicatePlugins": true
        },
                }
            }
        }
    }
}

add the extra webpack plugin config in the custom-webpack.config.js
module.exports = {
    module: {
        rules: [
            {
                test: /\.js$/,
                loader: 'babel-loader',
                query: {
                    presets: ['@babel/preset-env'
                    ]
                }
            }
        ]
    }
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build quality forms with React 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alarid/build-quality-forms-with-react-9nk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alarid/build-quality-forms-with-react-9nk"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by  Kelly Sikkema
☕️ Read this article on my blog
When it comes to building forms with React, there are tons of possibilities out there in the React Ecosystem. Many libraries have emerged to answer specific needs, and it can be a little bit overwhelming at first: which one to choose? what strategy to adopt? 
Even without using a library, just using pure React, you can basically go two ways: controlled or uncontrolled. We will briefly discuss this, so if you're new to React, you might want to start there. 
If you already know all about controlled VS uncontrolled forms, you can skip the first part and jump right to the second one, where I will show you how I like to build my forms today: using react-hook-form, yup and TypeScript. Those tools allow me to quickly build any type of form w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yohann Legrand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Export Bear Notes to Markdown Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/seancdavis/export-bear-notes-to-markdown-files-5aal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/seancdavis/export-bear-notes-to-markdown-files-5aal"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love Bear. The only other writing experience I've had that rivaled it was Ulysses. It's an absolute joy to use to author content with markdown.
The biggest issue I have with Bear is that it's not easy to do anything with the content outside of the application. But in the end, what you're authoring within Bear is just markdown (or it can be), and that content should be portable to wherever you can make it most actionable.
Here's a guide to get you started in building a workflow around your Bear notes by exporting them to markdown files.
We're going to write a single Node.js script that will export notes from Bear into markdown files with frontmatter metadata elsewhere on your machine.
In this specific example, we're going to target active notes (i.e. not trashed). And in the frontmatter, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean C Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Website Scraper | NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/knolcoder/website-scraper-nodejs-3fp4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/knolcoder/website-scraper-nodejs-3fp4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Download a website by it's url .



  
  
  Requirements


To download all the resources from a website, we are going to use the website-scraper module. This module allows you to download an entire website (or single webpages) to a local directory (including all the resources css, images, js, fonts etc.). 
Install the module in your project executing the following command in the terminal:
npm install website-scraper

Dynamic websites (where content is loaded by js) may be saved not correctly because website-scraper doesn't execute js, it only parses http responses for html and css files.
Visit the official Github repository for more information here.
The scrape function returns a Promise that makes requests to all the providen urls and saves all files found with sources to directory. The r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prince Jaiswal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What JS frameworks fail at that makes the new ones being developed so often?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrisczopp/what-js-frameworks-fail-at-that-makes-the-new-ones-being-developed-so-often-2o73</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrisczopp/what-js-frameworks-fail-at-that-makes-the-new-ones-being-developed-so-often-2o73"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any thoughts? Aren't we in some sort of limbo?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chris-czopp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como ter janelas em seu terminal usando tmux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itexto/como-ter-janelas-em-seu-terminal-usando-tmux-g46</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itexto/como-ter-janelas-em-seu-terminal-usando-tmux-g46"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Muitas vezes você lida com ambientes que possuem apenas uma interface de linha de comandos e precisa executar mais de uma ação ao mesmo tempo. Como resolver esta necessidade tendo uma única sessão/janela? Nesta receita apresentamos o tmux. 
Esta receita lhe fornecerá o essencial para que possa dar os primeiros passos com esta super ferramenta de produtividade que não é tão conhecida como deveria por usuários Linux. 
Ingredientes

Linux (mas você pode substituir pelo WSL no Windows ou mesmo pelo macOS).
tmux.
Habilidade e memória manual mínima.
Um pouco de paciência e persistência pois o primeiro contato pode não ser tão fácil assim.
Ingrediente principal: tmux

A melhor maneira de entender o problema é vendo-o em ação, sendo assim vamos a um caso real. Preciso iniciar dois processos, acomp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henrique Lobo Weissmann (Kico)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go from Zero to Cypherpunk]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blahblahman9/go-from-zero-to-cypherpunk-3h5a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blahblahman9/go-from-zero-to-cypherpunk-3h5a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We live in a post-Snowden world. For many, that means assuming none of your digital assets are safe from surveillance.
There are ways, however, to use the internet with insane mathematics in your favor to ensure that no one can see whatever it is that you’re sending to someone else.
Cryptography is an ancient mathematical science that was originally used for military communications, and designed to conceal the contents of a message should it fall into the hands of the enemy. Recent developments in cryptography have added additional uses, including mechanisms for authenticating users on a network, ensuring the integrity of transmitted information and preventing users from repudiating (i.e. rejecting ownership of) their transmitted messages.
Today, encryption is an integral part of many of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blahblahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PrimeNG v12.0.0 is here!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/primeng-v12-0-0-is-here-5cge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/primeng-v12-0-0-is-here-5cge"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T12:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PrimeTek is thrilled to announce the PrimeNG 12.0.0 release to bring first class Angular 12 support with new gray scheme along with numerous improvements and responsive updates to the components.
Angular 12
PrimeNG v12.0.0 depends on Angular 12 and is fully compatible with it. As it is always suggested, use the PrimeNG whose major version matches your Angular version e.g. PrimeNG 12 with Angular 12.
Responsive Updates
PrimeNG v12.0.0 focuses on improving the responsiveness of components so that they can be used within a responsive layout seamlessly. Latest additions to the set are:
Responsive Toast
Responsive TabMenu
Responsive BreadCrumb
Changelog
changelog for more details.
Download
PrimeNG is licensed under MIT and free to download at NPM.
Roadmap
Always Bet On Prime!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crazy case of Embedding Git Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nabheet/crazy-case-of-embedding-git-repositories-297</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nabheet/crazy-case-of-embedding-git-repositories-297"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Situation


We were having multiple projects in a folder and all pointing to its own remote git repo. we thought of making our parent folder also available on GitHub,so that all projects are  available at one place. We went ahead with our typical regular follow as mentioned below 
Initializing the parent folder with below mentioned command
git init

Then as usual staging all content and commiting using below mentioned command
Git add .
Git commit  -m “Main Project”

Created a repo on Github and added the remote connection uploaded the stuff.
git branch -M main
git remote add origin <url>
git push -u origin main

We were expecting everything to be available on remote repo but sadly that is where the real problem starts. If you look at screenshot below we can see two projects but none of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nabheet Madan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use node version manager (nvm for windows) to handle different node-versions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elischei/how-to-use-node-version-manager-nvm-for-windows-to-handle-different-node-versions-5a35</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elischei/how-to-use-node-version-manager-nvm-for-windows-to-handle-different-node-versions-5a35"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T09:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This is about nvm for windows. If you are on mac/linux follow this link to find the correct version.
Have you ever experienced difficulties with a project because you are on the wrong node version? I have! A lot of projects break, or won't build,  if you don't have the required version. Previously I used to uninstall/install the correct version manually. And it was a pain everytime. And what if you are working on multiple projects that all uses different node versions? This is where NVM comes in handy.
With nvm you can have multiple versions of node installed at the same time, and easily switch between them! In this blogpost I will show you how to install and use nvm.
Installing nvm for windows
Go to nvm-windows github repo and download the zip-file containing the installation …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli H. Schei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Azure API Management Instance using Bicep Lang via Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/willvelida/creating-a-azure-api-management-instance-using-bicep-lang-via-azure-devops-7o5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/willvelida/creating-a-azure-api-management-instance-using-bicep-lang-via-azure-devops-7o5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T09:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The more I use Bicep, the more I love it. This is what ARM Templates should have been. When it comes to IaC, I usually use Terraform. It's the IaC tool we used at my last gig and I like that it has support for multiple clouds.
However, I've recently changed jobs and I'm finding that I'm using ARM templates more. With this in mind, I've been wanting to learn Bicep and use it in my own personal projects so when the day comes that I have to convert ARM templates to Bicep code, I'll be prepared 😂
Coming back to this article, I'm working on a personal health application that has a bunch of APIs (Built using Azure Functions ⚡) that interacts with my data. Ideally, I'd like to integrate this within Azure API Management. I deploy these APIs using Azure DevOps so to be consistent, I want to deploy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Velida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cschotte/azure-devops-dashboard-2lfh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cschotte/azure-devops-dashboard-2lfh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T09:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


When you are managing Azure DevOps in a large enterprise organization, and you are still using only one Azure DevOps organization account, you are probably hitting some limits or have potential performance issues. Microsoft's recommendation is to have around 300 projects in a single Azure DevOps organization account. I have seen Azure DevOps organizations with more than 600 projects that still work.
The solution is to set up a multi-organization structure. Move all the inactive projects to an archive or boneyard Azure DevOps organization account and add an extra Azure DevOps organization account per department.
Next, you need some insights and automation on which projects have no activity anymore. The Azure DevOps Dashboard gives you the basic insights and an API to automate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clemens Schotte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write a VS Code extension in JavaScript, not TypeScript ^]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robole/write-a-vs-code-extension-in-javascript-not-typescript-727</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robole/write-a-vs-code-extension-in-javascript-not-typescript-727"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T08:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[^ Write an extension in TypeScript or JavaScript or CoffeeScript - whatever script you prefer! This is not meant to be contentious. 
The official docs for the VS Code API are oriented towards TypeScript and all of the examples are written in TypeScript. Microsoft is behind VS Code and TypeScript, so that is not unexpected. If you read the docs, it may not be apparent that you can build an extension in JavaScript. 
If you are more experienced, you may be saying "duh", that's obvious it's an electron app. But not everyone has the experience to make this corollary, and I think it would be a shame if that fact passes people by. Being able to hack your code editor in a language that you know already is a great opportunity. Customizing something you use a lot can be enormously rewarding. 🏆
So, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob OLeary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Rogue]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daveclarke/going-rogue-5fc4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daveclarke/going-rogue-5fc4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T07:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time I was at University doing a maths and computer science degree (and presumably provided subject matter for the BOFH but that's a different story). The University had a shiny DEC VAX 11/780 running VMS. The computer lab was an underground bunker with a bunch of physical terminals. Second year students were allowed a key to access it after hours. Yes a physical key. What did comp-sci students do after hours back in 1984? We played Rogue on a VAX 11/780. 
While Rogue was not the first dungeon-crawling game with procedural generation features, it introduced the subgenre of roguelike RPG procedurally generated dungeon crawlers with Dungeons-and-Dragons-like items (armor, weapons, potions, and magic scrolls) that also had permadeath (permanent death) and an overhead graphical vie…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daveclarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Custom Algorithm in AWS Sagemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/running-custom-algorithm-in-aws-sagemaker-4jdf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/running-custom-algorithm-in-aws-sagemaker-4jdf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T07:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this part, you will see how to run an algorithm of your own, instead of using SageMaker’s built-in algorithms. Although SageMaker provides built-in algorithms for almost any kind of problem statement, many times we want to run our own custom model utilizing the power of SageMaker. We can do so effectively if we have
We will create a custom random forest model for our Big Mart dataset. We will deploy the container in ECR and then train the model using SageMaker. Then we will use the model to do real-time inference as well as understand how batch transformation is done.
The problem statement is that we will try to predict the sales of an e-commerce firm using the random forest algorithm (one of the supervised learning ensemble tree algorithms). As it is a regression problem, we will be us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salah Elhossiny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Choosing The Best Web Template Is Important?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/designappweb/why-choosing-the-best-web-template-is-important-h84</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/designappweb/why-choosing-the-best-web-template-is-important-h84"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T07:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designing websites from scratch is hard, costly, and most significantly time-consuming but luckily nowadays we can get pre-design (readymade) templates that are available at no cost similarly as we can get a premium design with modern, creative features & layout.
So, let’s see which kind of a template you must choose and its benefits and downfalls.
To choose the most effective web template you would like to grasp what reasonable website you're starting.
The first thing to think about before you decide on a template, is to know what type of website you would like to start, is it something to sell or to share, what reasonable audience you wish to draw in, and how important is creativity within the design and how important is informative design.
As, you would possibly be knowing that there are both free & paid templates available, and no doubt both of them is amazing, but if you're a newbie and don’t want to spend because it's your portfolio website or blog website then it's fine to urge free template but with a free template, there's always specific amount compromise attached.
There are certain things or elements that everyone who is trying to find a template should know and must consider.
Pre-design (Readymade) templates can benefit you and your website in many ways.
Let’s Take a glance at what and where pre-design templates fall.
Picking the best web template is vital because your online business website has to be the most effective and inventive to draw in and stand out as best for your audience or customers.
best web template depends on many factors and during this blog you have seen a number of the foremost important factors that anyone who is looking to purchase or looking to acquire a free template must consider.
There are loads of websites available in the market which sell free and premium, basic and modern website templates. All of them offer you certain things and you must consider the best one for you and your website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Klaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Js Node (NodeMailer)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/feco2019/js-node-nodemailer-31ic</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/feco2019/js-node-nodemailer-31ic"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T06:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there guys,i hope my post finds you well and with appetite for programming during the week.
Today my subject is NodeMailer a module which stands for transporting email in javascript logic.
It is a node  module so you can easily install it with yarn or 
So, first things first just simple open up your CLI and  type
npm install nodemailer
Node.js v6.0.0 or newer. That’s it.
Nodemailer is a module for Node.js applications to allow easy as cake email sending. The project got started back in 2010 when there was no sane option to send email messages, today it is the solution most Node.js users turn to by default.
To send an email you need a transport object which will include some additions about the email,the recipient,the adress and some other stuff like that.
So we are creating our objec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dimitris Chitas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Reasons To Choose Node.js For Server-Side Programming]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ltdsolace/top-5-reasons-to-choose-node-js-for-server-side-programming-4ji1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ltdsolace/top-5-reasons-to-choose-node-js-for-server-side-programming-4ji1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T06:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is one of the Javascript technologies that made Javascript so trendy. But why? This is because it builds high-performing, real-time web apps easily. It can be used for client side programming and server side programming. If you wonder what’s the superpower of this technology for server side programming, or maybe you don’t know what Node.js actually is, then this blog is for you. Here we’ll see the reasons of why you should choose Node.js for server side programming. But before digging to it, let us see the overview of Node.js.
Node.js is an application runtime environment that allows you to write server-side apps built on Chrome’s V8 Javascript engine. It uses event-driven, non-blocking I/O model that make sit lightweight and efficient. And it’s ability to use Javascript on both frontend and backend adds one more benefit for development. Node.js package ecosystem, npm is the largest ecosystem of open-source libraries. Lots of big companies have adopted Node.js in the production environment. 
Know the amazing tips and tricks to make node.js app faster at- Tips And Tricks To Make Your Node.js Web App Faster
1. Javascript-
2. Event Driven Architecture-
3. Asynchronous Events-
4. NPM Package Manager-
https://solaceinfotech.com/blog/top-5-reasons-to-choose-node-js-for-server-side-programming/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solace Infotech Pvt. Ltd.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing a basic Slack app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chriscmuir/dockerizing-a-basic-slack-app-pdc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chriscmuir/dockerizing-a-basic-slack-app-pdc"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T05:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog I wrote about creating a basic Slack app using NodeJS, Slack's Bolt JavaScript framework, and ngrok.  In this blog I will extend this to include deploying the application to Docker.
Like the previous blog, this blog is just capturing my notes on how to do this so I don't have to remember all the steps.
The main inspiration for the Dockerfile in this post comes from Kathleen Juell's post How to Build a Node.js Application with Docker.  All credit goes to Kathleen for summarizing these steps so neatly.
On the assumption we already have Docker installed on our local machine, within the application we create a Docker configuration file literally called the Dockerfile.  
(1) In the previous application's root directory, in our favourite text editor, create a new file Dockerfi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you wanted to know about the Security+ SY0-601 but were afraid to ask]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kiarasmith/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-the-security-sy0-601-but-were-afraid-to-ask-4p7j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kiarasmith/everything-you-wanted-to-know-about-the-security-sy0-601-but-were-afraid-to-ask-4p7j"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T04:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CompTIA Security+ is the pinnacle cyber protection certification. Security+ certification is in high demand and maintains to serve as a fundamental certification for experts beginning an IT career or others looking to construct a profession in cybersecurity. On top of that, Security+ certification is also authorized using the Department of Defense (DoD) to satisfy Directive 8570.01 -M requirements.

If you’re looking for employment within the government, then it's far a required certification. CompTIA Security+ SY0-501 is the present-day Security+ examination and maybe to be had to take till the Spring of 2021. However, the Security+ SY0-601 is scheduled to be launched in October of 2020. If you’re an IT security professional and you’re seeking to decide which certification is nice for you or if you’re simply trying to research extra about every examination, check out the statistics under:
The SY0-501 examination specializes in these talent regions:
• Threats, attacks, and vulnerabilities
The SY0-601 Exam will cover the equal talent regions pondered within the SY0-501. However, some of these areas will consist of extra information. Expect to see changes in the following regions:
• Threats, assaults, and vulnerabilities
• Cloud assist
Also, expect to peer extra overall performance-based questions (PBQs) on SY0-601.
Professionals need to determine to take every examination based on their man or woman's needs and timeline. Both assessments will train you on how to recognize and manipulate security threats, but if you’re equipped properly now SY0-501 is the most effective examination to be had until October.
If you can wait till October, the SY0-601 will include updates based totally on the nature of the current cyber protection environment and troubles that cyber protection specialists are combating these days. If you decide to put together for SY0-601 make certain that your examination education is appropriate to that exam!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiara Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Custom Form Validators In Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karvel/exploring-custom-form-validators-in-angular-52fb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karvel/exploring-custom-form-validators-in-angular-52fb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T04:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that the reactive form library in Angular is one of the most powerful tools in the framework. Developers can create performant and reactive forms that provide great UI/UX. One part of the reactive form toolkit that I think people often overlook is creating custom validators. In this article I show how to create a custom password field validator and how to use it.
Reactive forms create objects that all inherit from the same AbstractControl. The AbstractControl has an errors object property, which is where I can get or set validation errors for the form or particular control. This errors object contains key value pairs. When using the default built-in validation, these key value pairs are predefined with specific (often boolean) values. That means that I would need to evaluate the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elanna Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 14 Angular mistakes you should Avoid]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devdefinitive/top-14-angular-mistakes-you-should-avoid-i6h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devdefinitive/top-14-angular-mistakes-you-should-avoid-i6h"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T04:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a survey of Libscore in 2016, almost 12,000 websites out of 1,000,000 have been using angular. These additionally consist of a few setup corporations like Wolfram Alpha, Sprint, ABC News, Walgreens, and Intel. It aims to disentangle each the trying out and improvement of such programs with the aid of presenting a framework for a client-aspect version-view-ViewModel (MVVM) architecture and version-view-controller (MVC).
With its growing call for withinside the improvement of front-cease net utility framework, an increasing number of builders are looking to ace it. Angular JS is an entirely practical framework. It is the 0.33 maximum starred repository GitHub. However, it isn't always tough to begin using the dreams that it's far meant to perform a call for comprehension. No lon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devdefinitive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to send mail using nodemailer in Angular 11?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arahman092/how-to-send-mail-using-nodemailer-in-angular-11-347c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arahman092/how-to-send-mail-using-nodemailer-in-angular-11-347c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T03:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to send form data to mail using nodemailer in Angular 11?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>a-rahman092</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish Websites Using Airtable With 21YunBox]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/21yunbox/publish-websites-using-airtable-with-21yunbox-2h7o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/21yunbox/publish-websites-using-airtable-with-21yunbox-2h7o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T02:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will walk through the steps of publishing websites using Airtable with 21YunBox. 
 


  
  
  Steps to deploy publish websites using Airtable with 21YunBox:



Sign up on 21YunBox

Use this Airtable base to start, click the Copy base button located in the top right corner.
Fork this Airtable starter on Github
Use the following values during creation:



Runtime
Static Site




Build Command
yarn && yarn build


Publish Directory
./public



 

Click Advanced Configuration to add below environment variables:



KEY
VALUE




AIRTABLE_BASE_ID
You can find it on your base -> "Help" -> "API documnetation"


AIRTABLE_API_KEY
You can find it on Airtable Dashboard -> "Account" -> API


AIRTABLE_TABLE_NAME

Destinations for this starter. If you use a custom base, you can find the name of the base on the tab (top left)



 

...
To read the full content of this post, go to: https://launch-in-china.21yunbox.com/cms/publish-websites-using-airtable-with-21yunbox.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>21YunBox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Luxarg" Text Editor ! liberty + pure python3 !]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-text-editor-liberty-pure-python3-5754</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amzy0/luxarg-text-editor-liberty-pure-python3-5754"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T02:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/ 
        luxarg
      
    
LUXARG is another keyboard friendly text editor.
This project started at August 2019 and restarted at 2021 TODAY!
Easy to use and userfriendly !
LUXARG support :
Fedora, CENTOS and RedHat,
Debian and Ubuntu,
OpenSUSE,
Arch and Manjaro, ...


INSERT MODE : <F1>
SAVE   MODE : <F2>
OPEN   MODE : <F3>



INSTALLATION
$ python<3X> installer.py



dependencies
$ pip3 install -r requirements.txt



update method
$ cd ~/.luxarg
$ python<3X> update.py



Install pip
pip.txt








  
View on GitHub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amzy 0 |  محمد امین عظیمی</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect Unused Classes in… HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342198</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/detect-unused-classes-in-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T23:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Usually, when “unused” comes up in conversation regarding CSS, it’s about removing chunks of CSS that are not used in your site or, at least, the styles not currently in use on a specific page. The minimal amount of CSS …
The post Detect Unused Classes in… HTML appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Engineering Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60c91b2b4dc1a607ed7b389a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/devops-engineering-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps is becoming an in-demand role at many software companies. We just released a DevOps Engineering course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Learn all about DevOps in this comprehensive course for beginners with three technical tutorials. Colin Chartier created this course. He is the co-founder and CEO at LayerCI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data driven game with phaser 3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/habiblila/data-driven-game-with-phaser-3-1elb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/habiblila/data-driven-game-with-phaser-3-1elb"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jun 15 '21
            Comments: 1
            Answers: 0
        
well i'm working on an e-learning platform for kids that contain courses and each course contain lessons and some games
games will be programmed in phaser 3
so the admin in the dashboard will have a form to add new course (add  the lesson which is a video and also…
Open Full Question
    
  
well i'm working on an e-learning platform for kids that contain courses and each course contain lessons and some games games will be programmed in phaser 3 so the admin in the dashboard will have a form to add new course (add the lesson which is a video and also a link to the phaser game since the admin is not a developer so i wanted to transform my phaser game to a link or something like that ) my question is how to get a game set up to use data from json objects from a URL [sort of Data-driven game ] ps: to develop this platform i'm using spring boot and angular]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>💞💞LiLa HaBiB 💞💞</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does &#x27;this&#x27; Mean in JavaScript? The this Keyword Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c72a0ad3126007592d7e2a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-this-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand what this truly means in JavaScript, let's take a look at a very similar concept in the English Language: Polysemy. Let's consider the word "run". Run is a single word which could mean many different things depending on the context. “I will run home” – means to move quickly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Charge as a Freelance Developer – and Why You Should Avoid Being the Cheapest]]></title>
        <id>60c8912c4dc1a607ed7b2fff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-to-charge-as-a-freelance-developer-dont-be-the-cheapest/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a freelance developer, knowing how much to charge for a project can often feel like a gamble. It's easy to wonder "Am I setting my price too high?" This is normally the first question that comes to mind. And your brain will probably meet this question with a resounding]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Fraudulent POS ~cybersafety]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dammyreginal/beware-of-fraudulent-pos-cybersafety-4cnh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dammyreginal/beware-of-fraudulent-pos-cybersafety-4cnh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T21:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[so dear friends, 
Please share any experiences you may have so others can learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dammyreginal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Queries in Times of @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342519</id>
        <link href="https://mxb.dev/blog/media-queries-in-times-of-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T19:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Böck took me up on my challenge to look through a codebase and see how many of the @media queries could ultimately become @container queries.
I took the bait and had a look at some of my projects – 
…
The post Media Queries in Times of @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need an SSH Access Manager - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before diving into this article I recommend you take 5 minutes to have a read of part 1 of our 2 part, "Why you need an SSH Access Manager" blog series.
Part 1 of our article featured more information on the security aspects for why to use one but in this article, I want to talk more about the "managing" of SSH keys as a reason to use one.
To define which SSH keys have access to your server, each server user has its own directory and within, a folder called .ssh. This folder should have a file called authorized_keys and the purpose of this file is to hold the public key for each SSH key that should have access.
It's a very simple system that works great, as it's a simple case of adding a new public key on a new line in the file and saving it, (or deleting a line to remove access).
This how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need an SSH Access Manager - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/serverauth/why-you-need-an-ssh-access-manager-part-2-512o"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before diving into this article I recommend you take 5 minutes to have a read of part 1 of our 2 part, "Why you need an SSH Access Manager" blog series.
Part 1 of our article featured more information on the security aspects for why to use one but in this article, I want to talk more about the "managing" of SSH keys as a reason to use one.
To define which SSH keys have access to your server, each server user has its own directory and within, a folder called .ssh. This folder should have a file called authorized_keys and the purpose of this file is to hold the public key for each SSH key that should have access.
It's a very simple system that works great, as it's a simple case of adding a new public key on a new line in the file and saving it, (or deleting a line to remove access).
This how…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sets of props in React and Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikitarudenko/sets-of-props-in-react-and-typescript-3po7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikitarudenko/sets-of-props-in-react-and-typescript-3po7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when writing an app in React you might have a component that changes its look and logic dramatically depending on provided props. In addition, if a particular prop provided, the other props become either required or restricted. That hidden prop relation can be explained in documentation but if your project uses Typescript there is a great opportunity to utilize what I call "sets of props".
It's usually not the best idea to make buttons look like links and vice versa but let's ignore this for the sake of clarity. The code snippet below is so-called Clickable component which can be either a link or a button that shares the same style but has different behavior depending on props.
import { ReactNode } from 'react'

interface BaseProps {
  children: ReactNode
}

interface AsButtonProps extends BaseProps {
  as: 'button'
  onClick: () => void
  href?: never
}

interface AsLinkProps extends BaseProps {
  as: 'a'
  href: string
  onClick?: never
}

type ClickableProps = AsButtonProps | AsLinkProps

const Clickable = ({ children, as, onClick, href }: ClickableProps) => {
  return (
    <>
      {as === 'a' && (
        <a href={href}>{children}</a>
      )}

      {as === 'button' && (
        <button onClick={onClick}>{children}</button>
      )}
    </>
  )
}

export default Clickable

The component has four props. children is required in any case so it's put under the BaseProps interface. Both AsButtonProps and AsLinkProps extended from BaseProps and represent two sets of props. The active set depends on the value of the as prop while the type never for unused props makes sure that Typescript will yell if someone is using a prop which does nothing.
Here is a scheme:

This pattern is obviously not limited to props in React. It's widely used in the types of various npm packages. Now you can add it to your arsenal and build reusable components/utils with better API for you and your team.
TypeScript Deep Dive: Never Type
SyntaxFM: Episode 348. TypeScript Fundamentals — Getting a Bit Deeper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Rudenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Component Generation in Lazy-Loaded Routes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/dynamic-component-generation-in-lazy-loaded-routes-14eh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/dynamic-component-generation-in-lazy-loaded-routes-14eh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | Jun 2019
— Exploit Data Driven Component Layout, Loaded On-Demand in Angular
One of the fun things about being an applied mathematician in front-end development is the never-ending stream of complex, interactive problems that users wish to solve. These range from gamification of business applications to data-driven user experiences. Two interesting applications of the latter topic include dynamic routing through an application and dynamic component layout. Both are examples of user experiences that vary based on factors such as user role and prior uses of the application. In other words, two different users may be presented with an entirely different experience based on both a priori knowledge of the user and how the user interacts with the application in real tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Component Generation in Lazy-Loaded Routes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/dynamic-component-generation-in-lazy-loaded-routes-14eh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/dynamic-component-generation-in-lazy-loaded-routes-14eh"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | Jun 2019
— Exploit Data Driven Component Layout, Loaded On-Demand in Angular
One of the fun things about being an applied mathematician in front-end development is the never-ending stream of complex, interactive problems that users wish to solve. These range from gamification of business applications to data-driven user experiences. Two interesting applications of the latter topic include dynamic routing through an application and dynamic component layout. Both are examples of user experiences that vary based on factors such as user role and prior uses of the application. In other words, two different users may be presented with an entirely different experience based on both a priori knowledge of the user and how the user interacts with the application in real tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Decorators – How to Create and Use Decorators in Python With Examples]]></title>
        <id>60c3dcb3d3126007592d6c6d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-decorators-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python decorators allow you to change the behavior of a function without modifying the function itself. In this article I will show you how to create and use decorators. You will see how easy it is to use this advanced Python feature. In this article I will discuss the following]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting an Angular application on GitHub Pages using Travis CI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/hosting-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-using-travis-ci-5dip</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/hosting-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-using-travis-ci-5dip"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
GitHub is a source code and file storage service with version control using git tool. GitHub Pages is a static file hosting service using a public repository.
Travis CI is a deployment service integrated with GitHub.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the account. Access the site https://github.com/ and click on the button Sign up.

2. Fill in the fields Username, Email address, Password, click on the button Verify to solve the challenge and click on the butto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Strangler Fig Pattern and How it Helps Manage Legacy Code]]></title>
        <id>602aaaf60a2838549dcc5c7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-strangler-pattern-in-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T17:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any sufficiently old codebase eventually starts to contain legacy code. Architecture, performance, comments, and more begin to degrade the moment after they are written. Some parts of the codebase last longer than other parts, but inevitably new coding standards emerge to reduce technical debt. Then you have to rework a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Python] Coding a TCP Room in 200 lines]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/python-coding-a-tcp-room-in-200-lines-1p0m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yumatsushima07/python-coding-a-tcp-room-in-200-lines-1p0m"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T16:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding made easy, maybe try making a TCP chat room?

This post is also on Medium you may also have a look at it and share both links if one doesn't work!
Medium: [Python] Coding a TCP Room in 200 lines




  
  
  Introduction


Coding a TCP Room in about 200 lines, let’s dive into our adventure! TCP is a transmission control protocol which is one of the main protocols of an Internet protocol suite. This simple program helps us learn about sockets and Client Side Architecture! Python in general is a great language to start with from beginners to advanced! And of course, it allows us to create solid applications very fast and easily. For a further challenge, you can also add custom features like chat rooms, commands, roles, send images etc…
Our application, will need client-server architect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuma-Tsushima</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Open Any Repo in VS Code Without Cloning It]]></title>
        <id>60b7cb6aacb62507dd1d7c1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/you-can-now-edit-anything-on-github-in-vs-code-without-cloning/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T16:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now open anything (that you have access to) on GitHub directly from VS Code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Improve Web Application Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/soorajvn07/how-to-improve-web-application-security-28gm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/soorajvn07/how-to-improve-web-application-security-28gm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web applications play a key role in determining the success of a business. Many companies solely depend on web applications for their business, offering a SaaS product for other customers and also building web apps for internal use.
Yet it’s a fact that many companies don’t know how to keep track of their web application security and improve it.
Content management systems (CMS) like WordPress, Joomla and website builders have made it easy for everyone to create a website. Most of the website owners forget the fact that the attack surface of internet-facing web applications is much wider and that they need adequate security.
Whenever a customer or visitor is on your website you have to make sure that their data is safe.
If you fail to keep your customers’ data safe, you could be at the rece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sooraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just How Niche is Headless WordPress?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342248</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/just-how-niche-is-headless-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder where headless WordPress will land. And by “headless” I mean only using the WordPress admin and building out the user-facing site through the WordPress REST API rather than the traditional WordPress theme structure.
Is it… big? The future …
The post Just How Niche is Headless WordPress? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eu e o Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loboweissmann/eu-e-o-angular-4d1a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loboweissmann/eu-e-o-angular-4d1a"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Semana passada colocamos no ar a nova versão do /dev/All que mudou radicalmente sua arquitetura (detalhes não técnicos neste link): dentre as principais mudanças está o fato de que agora a interface com o usuário é um SPA. Este é o primeiro post no qual compartilho com vocês algumas das coisas que aprendi no processo.
Note que esta é a visão de alguém que tinha como ferramenta principal para o desenvolvimento de aplicações SPA o Vue.js. Sendo assim minhas impressões em sua maior parte fazem uma comparação com ele. Leve em consideração que são "novas novas impressões" a respeito do Angular. Muita coisa pode mudar conforme minha experiência progride.
Por que não gostava
Uma das principais razões pelas quais aprendi Vue.js, confesso, foi para não usar o Angular. Além do trauma da quebra de co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henrique Lobo Weissmann (Kico)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[☑️ SOC 2 Compliance and Certification: What SaaS Businesses Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/soc-2-compliance-and-certification-what-saas-businesses-need-to-know-1cf2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/soc-2-compliance-and-certification-what-saas-businesses-need-to-know-1cf2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📓 SOC 2 is a technical security audit report from the AICPA that evaluates a tech service business’s cloud security controls.


In the last two years alone, cloud-based cyberattacks more than doubled — even though SaaS spending grew just 18%. 
While these numbers are merely a correlation from a statistical standpoint, it does indicate that if your business stores customer data in the cloud, it’s more important than ever for your business to take measures to secure that data. Especially given SaaS spending is expected to increase an additional 36% between 2020 and 2022. 
A SOC 2 certification from the AICPA is a foundational step that will help every service provider reduce security risks. Below is a guide to SOC 2 compliance requirements and certification.
SOC 2 is an independent audit report that evaluates the security controls a tech service business uses to protect the data they process in the cloud. Possession of a SOC 2 report is considered table stakes in the SaaS industry, as the answers to most security questions a customer may have about their business’s security posture can usually be pulled from this report.
“SOC” stands for “System and Organization Controls” and was created by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA). SOC 2 is one of three SOC reports, each with different purposes and/or levels of transparency:
SOC 1. Used to audit internal controls relevant to a customer’s financial systems. Report usage is “restricted,” meaning its use is limited to auditors, the service organization, and authorized users.
SOC 2. Used to audit the overall management of customer data. Report usage is also “restricted” the same way SOC 1 is.
SOC 3. The same as SOC 2, but the report is simplified and publicly available to increase transparency.

Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE CAT COMMAND IN LINUX]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bazeng/the-cat-command-in-linux-1fl0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bazeng/the-cat-command-in-linux-1fl0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T11:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cat(concatenate) command reads data from the file and gives their content as output.
Here are some of the use cases of the command :
$ cat >newfile


Creates a new file called newfile
You may have run into this while checking your os type.
$ cat /etc/os-release

On my Os this outputs:
PRETTY_NAME="Debian GNU/Linux 10 (buster)"
NAME="Debian GNU/Linux"
VERSION_ID="10"
VERSION="10 (buster)"
VERSION_CODENAME=buster
ID=debian
HOME_URL="https://www.debian.org/"
SUPPORT_URL="https://www.debian.org/support"
BUG_REPORT_URL="https://bugs.debian.org/"


$cat [filename-whose-contents-is-to-be-copied] > [destination-filename]


$ cat file1 file2


Outputs contents in file1 and file2 .
$cat file1 >> file2


Will append contents of file1 to file 2
$cat -- "-dashfile"


Will display the content of -dashfile
$cat "filename" | more

$cat "filename1" "filename2" "filename3" > "merged_filename"


Will merge the contents of file in respective order and will insert that content in "merged_filename".
$cat *.html

Will show the content of all html files present in the folder.
$cat >> geeks.txt
The newly added text.

Will append the text "The newly added text." to the end of the file.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bazeng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django: Allauth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-allauth-1lc6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-allauth-1lc6"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up until now we haven't created any registration/login form. We could or should roll our own for a very special business requirement or we could use a ready made and famous authentication packages call django-allauth. Django allauth will handle all your login/registration need, and include plugins for login using 3rd party Oauth such as google, facebook, twitter, github to  name a few. For more 3rd party authentication that Allauth support please refer here.
Lets start will installation of Allauth
Installing django Allauth with the following command in your terminal
pipenv install django-allauth
pipenv lock -r > requirement.txt

after the installation is done, We need to register django-allauth.
Django-Allauth require a significant change to your settings.py file, Lets first check each par…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashrafZolkopli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post to Slack WebHook from Bash using Curl - Adventures in WSL2 Scripting #2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iainrough/post-to-slack-webhook-from-bash-using-curl-adventures-in-wsl2-scripting-2-18c9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iainrough/post-to-slack-webhook-from-bash-using-curl-adventures-in-wsl2-scripting-2-18c9"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T09:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#!/bin/bash
# URL as supplied in your slack bot
url=https://hooks.slack.com/services/{}/{}/{}

#JSON body
data='{"text": ":interrobang: Unable to do something"}'

sendError()
{
    curl -X \
         POST \
         -H 'Content-type: application/json' \
         --data $data \
         $url
}

#Function that checks something
checkSomething

result=$?
#echo "result: $result"
if [ "$result" != "0" ]; then
    sendError
fi


The Result in Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iainrough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10Gbps Network Speed Test Using OpenSpeedTest V2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/openspeedtest/10gbps-network-speed-test-using-openspeedtest-v2-189l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/openspeedtest/10gbps-network-speed-test-using-openspeedtest-v2-189l"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSpeedTest Server V2 Released for Windows Mac and Linux.
http://go.openspeedtest.com/Server 


You can test you network speed from a TV 

http://go.openspeedtest.com/Server]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OpenSpeedtest.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux zip files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/linux-zip-files-3md7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dailydevtips1/linux-zip-files-3md7"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T06:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we'll be looking at how to zip up one or multiple files on Linux systems.
In my case, this situation occurred because I wanted to email attach multiple log files.
Let's first look at the command itself.
zip options zip_name files

Where this works as follows:
zip: The Linux command to zip things
options: We can pass in arguments for the end zip results
zip_name: The output name, without the .zip part
files: One or more files comma separated
To show you the most simple zip command for one file, we could do this.
zip archive test.txt

This will create an archive.zip in that folder containing the test.txt file.
zip on Ubuntu or Centos


To install the zip command on Ubuntu or Debian systems, you can run the following command.
sudo apt install zip

For CentOS and Fedora systems, you can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bongers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a RAID 5 System With LVM Tool and Recover Data After Failures]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-5-system-with-lvm-tool-and-recover-data-after-failures-4fhp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-5-system-with-lvm-tool-and-recover-data-after-failures-4fhp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T05:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore the methods applied to create a software LVM RAID in Linux. Also, we will show you a simple solution to recover any data lost from an LV RAID 5 system as a result of accidental removal or unexpected drive failure.

LVM RAID is a method to create a logical volume (LV) which uses several physical disks to improve performance or fault tolerance. Within LVM, physical disks (abbreviated as PV, physical volumes) belong to one volume group (VG).
Although it is much safer to use MD RAID, if you really need to migrate from conventional disks to a RAID system without having to change their file systems, this method can be very useful.
Allocating information with blocks of logical volume data on physical disks is determined by a specific RAID type. Check the video link be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a RAID 5 System With LVM Tool and Recover Data After Failures]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-5-system-with-lvm-tool-and-recover-data-after-failures-4fhp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-5-system-with-lvm-tool-and-recover-data-after-failures-4fhp"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T05:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll explore the methods applied to create a software LVM RAID in Linux. Also, we will show you a simple solution to recover any data lost from an LV RAID 5 system as a result of accidental removal or unexpected drive failure.

LVM RAID is a method to create a logical volume (LV) which uses several physical disks to improve performance or fault tolerance. Within LVM, physical disks (abbreviated as PV, physical volumes) belong to one volume group (VG).
Although it is much safer to use MD RAID, if you really need to migrate from conventional disks to a RAID system without having to change their file systems, this method can be very useful.
Allocating information with blocks of logical volume data on physical disks is determined by a specific RAID type. Check the video link be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django : ReCaptha Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-recaptha-everywhere-1474</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ashraf_zolkopli/django-recaptha-everywhere-1474"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T04:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post in this series, I talk about how we can use django-recaptcha to make sure our forms are protected from bot spam submission, however it can be tedious to add them to each form and also does not make it hard to add the recaptcha field if the form are generated by a django package that you had installed previously.
Using the django-honeypot middleware method and knowledge on how django-recaptcha work, I had manage to roll my own middleware that inject the Google Recaptcha field into every page that have a form in a Django weebsite.
We Can first start an django app called G_Recaptha, the name of the app can be anything you want but I'm going with this.
python manage.py startapp G_Recaptha

We now should add a middleware.py file in G_Recaptha.
in this file, insert the follo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ashrafZolkopli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Javascript to Rust to WASM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/starsoccer/from-javascript-to-rust-to-wasm-8ci</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/starsoccer/from-javascript-to-rust-to-wasm-8ci"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a while Ive been interested in not only Rust but WASM but having limited familiarity with many of the languages that can be compiled to WASM I never really had a chance to try it out until recently. Over the last few months though I got the opportunity to learn Rust.
Rust in my opinion is very much like typescript on steroids. While Typescript may enforce types in your code if you happen to pass a string to a type expecting a number things will still compile and may even work as expected still. With Rust this is not the case. If you provide an unexpected type either things will not compile in the first place or your software will crash. 
A personal project of mine (Cryptotithe) which is an open source tax software for cryptocurrencies was something I always though would benefit from WA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>starsoccer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-tables-with-sticky-header-and-footers-got-a-bit-easier/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T22:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago when I looked at sticky headers and footers in HTML <table>s in the blog post A table with both a sticky header and a sticky first column. In it, I never used position: sticky on …
The post Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You could have invented lenses!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/safareli/you-could-have-invented-lenses-4ohe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/safareli/you-could-have-invented-lenses-4ohe"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T20:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have a JavaScript code like this:
const someObj = { tags: [], packages: [] };
function hasValue(key, item) {
  return someObj[key].indexOf(item) !== -1;
}

And you are porting this this into TypeScript. You are trying to follow best practices, like using strict mode. And don’t want to use any and unsafe casts. so you start adding types:
type SomeType = {
  tags: (string | number)[];
  packages: string[];
};
const someObj: SomeType = { tags: [], packages: [] };

This was easy, but then you hit one issue that you can’t really write type for hasValue without using some sort of casting. This is your best attempt:
function hasValue<K extends keyof SomeType>(key: K, item: SomeType[K]) {
  return someObj[key].indexOf(item) !== -1;
  //                   ^^^^
  // Argument of type 'Som…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irakλi Safareli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert Express-Generator App To Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chubbystrings/convert-express-generator-app-to-typescript-29md"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys, in this article, I'd show you how to convert an express-generator app to Typescript. It's pretty straightforward we should be done in a flash so stick with me. This is my first ever write-up 😩 😩  , I hope you find a place in your heart to forgive my grammatical errors.😔 😔  

So, I started learning Typescript recently, and honestly, my life has been a lot easier ever since. Enough said, let's jump right in and start coding, shall we? 😎 
Firstly, go to your terminal and navigate to the directory where you'd like to create your express app, type npx express-generator, hit enter you should see a structure like this automatically generated for you.
├── app.js
├── bin
│   └── www
├── package.json
├── public
│   ├── images
│   ├── Javascripts
│   └── stylesheets
│       └── style.cs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emeka Okwor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342229</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-chronicle-xxxx/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T18:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a little link roundup of some off-site stuff I’ve done recently. As I’m wont to do from time to time. 
DevJourney Podcast
#151 Chris Coyier from ceramics to CSS-Tricks and CodePen‘
Chris took us from playing on 
…
The post CSS-Tricks Chronicle XXXX appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS API Gateway Best Practices in-depth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-heroes/aws-api-gateway-best-practices-in-depth-4l0n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices


Forgive me, the Bart Simpson in me couldn't resist using 'Best Practices' once again. Sure, there's a lot to say to stamp out “best practice” and I agree with most arguments in the article. Framing something as a best practice is subjective, and it could give the impression of being arrogant. But, as grown-ups, I'm convinced most of us know how to deal with the term and see why it's used. So pick the practices you agree on, which you see as 'best' practices yourself.
I have the feeling that the importance of API Gateway in a setup is sometimes overlooked. AWS wrote down the practices themselves (also using the term 'Best practices 😉). But IMHO, their documentation is a tad too brief. Also, the documentation lacks a 'WHY' in general.
Assuming the vast majority of API Gatew…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gert Leenders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/securing-your-website-with-subresource-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you load a file from an external server, you’re trusting that the content you request is what you expect it to be. Since you don’t manage the server yourself, you’re relying on the security of yet another third party …
The post Securing Your Website With Subresource Integrity appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khari McMillian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective React Query Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkdodo/effective-react-query-keys-25c5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkdodo/effective-react-query-keys-25c5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Query Keys are a very important core concept in React Query. They are necessary so that the library can internally cache your data correctly and refetch automatically when a dependency to your query changes. Lastly, it will allow you to interact with the Query Cache manually when needed, for example when updating data after a mutation or when you need to manually invalidate some queries.
Let's quickly have a look what these three points mean before I'll show you how I personally organize Query Keys to be able to do these things most effectively.
Internally, the Query Cache is just a JavaScript object, where the keys are serialized Query Keys and the values are your Query Data plus meta information. The keys are hashed it in a deterministic way, so you can use objects as well (on the top le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominik D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up React + TypeScript app from scratch without create-react-app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alekseiberezkin/setting-up-react-typescript-app-without-create-react-app-oph</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alekseiberezkin/setting-up-react-typescript-app-without-create-react-app-oph"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why bother if there is create-react-app?


Good question! In fact, if you are happy with create-react-app — just use it 🙂 But if you want to figure out how everything works together, let's combine all parts ourselves! 
/hello-react
  /dist
    index.html
    main.css
    main.js
    main.js.LICENSE.txt
  /src
    index.css
    index.tsx
  index.html
  package.json
  tsconfig.json
  webpack.config.js

Node.js installation steps depend on your system — just proceed to a download page and follow instructions.
npm doesn't need any installation because it comes with Node. If you wish to check that everything is properly installed on your system, follow these instructions.
Sidenote: npm is not the only package manager, there's also Yarn. If uncertain, I'd recommend staying with npm.
Create the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aleksei Berezkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced TypeScript: A Generic Function to Merge Object Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fullstackchris/advanced-typescript-a-generic-function-to-merge-object-arrays-18ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fullstackchris/advanced-typescript-a-generic-function-to-merge-object-arrays-18ja"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is mirrored on my blog, chrisfrew.in
I just can't stop writing these generic functions! This is another powerful generic function that follows my previous post on building a generic function to update an array at a specific key according to a specific test value. As I try and maintain the cleanest codebase as possible for ReduxPlate, I continue to find new use cases for these easy-to-use yet powerful generic functions.
Often when doing state modifications, you want to merge or add some properties to an object that you get from an API or some other source. You could explicitly write key / value assignments for the keys that you want to update... or you can leverage JavaScript's built in Object.assign function and TypeScript's generic capabilities to only write one such function fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Frewin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate React Native Boilerplate with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joeygoksu/the-ultimate-react-native-boilerplate-with-typescript-3778</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joeygoksu/the-ultimate-react-native-boilerplate-with-typescript-3778"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T18:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The template for React Native that includes all you need to build amazing projects 🔥
📱 React Native — version 0.64.0
🎉 TypeScript - Type checking
📏 ESLint — Pluggable JavaScript linter
💖 Prettier - Opinionated Code Formatter
🌘 Dark Mode - Support dark mode
🌆 UI Kit - Beautiful UI
⚙️ RN Dotenv Environment variable with RN env

👉 Let's try: https://github.com/joeygoksu/LightReactNative
🌸 Built with template
Vocabulary Builder App
Animal Finder Game]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joey Goksu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ng-magical directives series (ng-template)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/valoni01/ng-magical-directives-series-ng-template-41n"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T16:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic is just science that we do not understand yet
...Arthur C. Clarke
This article is part of what I call the magical directives series. In this series, we will unravel the mystery behind some interesting Angular directives. Afterwards, we can add this little magic to our tool box. I call them magical directives because they play a very important role in building reusable components across our Angular applications.
Below are the directives that we will be looking at in this series.
ng-template
ng-container
ng-content
*ngTemplateOutlet
The ng-template directive simply represent an Angular template. Angular uses the ng-template under the hood in our structural directives( *ngIf, *ngFor) and ngSwitch. The ngSwitch controls the structural directives (*ngSwitchCase and *ngSwitchDefault ) and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentine Awe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342429</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/safari-15-new-ui-theme-colors-and-a-css-tricks-cameo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a 33-minute video (and resources) over on apple.com covering the upcoming Safari changes we saw in the WWDC keynote this year in much more detail. Look who’s got a little cameo in there:
Perhaps the most noticeable thing there …
The post Safari 15: New UI, Theme Colors, and… a CSS-Tricks Cameo! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Possibilities of Syndication]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342237</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-possibilities-of-syndication/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the one word that isn’t an adjective in the acronym RSS. 
Really Simple Syndication.
Update: Lol there are literally two mistakes there. RSS is an initialism not an acronym, and “Really” is an adverb not an adjective. 
RSS …
The post The Possibilities of Syndication appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342164</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-shadows-to-svg-icons-with-css-and-svg-filters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T14:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would we need to apply shadows to SVG?
Shadows are a common design feature that can help elements, like icons, stand out. They could be persistent, or applied in different states (e.g. :hover, :focus, or :active) 
…
The post Adding Shadows to SVG Icons With CSS and SVG Filters appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put a Background on Open Details Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/put-a-background-on-open-details-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that can be just a smidge funky about the <details> element is that, when open, it’s not always 100% clear what is inside that element and what isn’t. I’m not saying that always matters or that it’s a …
The post Put a Background on Open Details Elements appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/equal-columns-with-flexbox-its-more-complicated-than-you-might-think/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As awesome as flexbox is, what it’s doing under the hood is actually a little strange because, by default, it is doing two things at once. It first looks at the content size which is what we would get if by declaring width: max-content on an element. But on top of that, flex-shrink is also doing some work allowing the items to be smaller, but only if needed.
Let’s break those two down and see how they work together.
The post Equal Columns With Flexbox: It’s More Complicated Than You Might Think appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Powell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342182</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-headless-cms-with-fauna-and-vercel-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will learn and use headless CMS, Fauna, and Vercel functions to build a blogging platform, Blogify After that, you can easily build any web application using a headless CMS, Fauna and Vercel functions.
The post Building a Headless CMS with Fauna and Vercel Functions appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikeh Akinyemi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Commenting System To A WYSIWYG Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/commenting-system-wysiwyg-editor/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be re-using the foundational WYSIWYG Editor built in the first article to build a commenting system for a WYSIWYG Editor that enables users to select text inside a document and share their comments on it. Let’s dig in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful VS Code Extensions For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet useful Visual Studio Code extensions for web developers: little helpers to minimize slow-downs and frustrations, and boost developer’s workflow along the way. With auto log messages, auto code formatting, file utils, file labels, code snippets, highlight brackets, tags, indents and workspaces, onboarding and remote SSH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build And Launch Powerful Responsive Websites With Editor X]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/build-launch-responsive-websites-editorx/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While web builders have been around for a long time, it wasn’t until recently that they became practical for professional use. Closing the gap between design and code has become the north star for many companies and we are seeing a wave of tools that deliver on this promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miroslav Bekyarov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible SVGs: Perfect Patterns For Screen Reader Users]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/accessible-svg-patterns-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover which SVG patterns we should avoid and which patterns are the most inclusive when comparing different combinations of OSs, browsers, and screen readers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carie Fisher)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>