<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-10-18T01:08:27.398Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-10-18T01:08:27.398Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 8]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-8-3hdi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-8-3hdi"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T23:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Este é o oitavo artigo da série com dicas e truques envolvendo os inúmeros serviços que integram o Microsoft Azure. Caso queira saber mais sobre os conteúdos que já publiquei (ou até mesmo revê-los) seguem os links dos posts anteriores:
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 7
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 6
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 5
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 4
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 3
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 2
Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 1
C# 10: conhecendo as principais novidades - segunda, 18/10 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renato Groffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Py3 101: Getting started with python3.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chris_murimi/py3-101-getting-started-with-python3-27e8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chris_murimi/py3-101-getting-started-with-python3-27e8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T21:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python.


Python is an interpreted high-level general-purpose programming language. Its design philosophy emphasizes code readability with its use of significant indentation. Its language constructs as well as its object-oriented approach aim to help programmers write clear, logical code for small and large-scale projects.
It is very simple to use and implement. 
It is open source and has a very big community of developers.
Object-oriented and functional programming. 
A lot of applications.
The installation procedure involves downloading the official Python .exe installer and running it on your system.
Python website.
.
Run the Python Installer once downloaded. 
.
For all recent versions of Python, the recommended installation options include Pip and IDLE. Older versions might not include such additional features.
Pip is a powerful package management system for Python software packages. Thus, make sure that you have it installed.
To verify whether Pip was installed:
Open the Start menu and type "cmd."
pip -v

.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrisMurimi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on The Phoenix Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/higaguin/some-thoughts-on-the-phoenix-project-3gaj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/higaguin/some-thoughts-on-the-phoenix-project-3gaj"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T20:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Pheonix Project: A Novel About IT, DevOps, And How To Help Your Business Win", a novel written by Gene Kim, Kevin Behr, and Geroge Spafford.
This book follows Bill, an IT manager at Parts Unlimited, he gets an unexpected promotion and the responsibility of successfully implementing a huge and ambitious project. He quickly notices the mess that Parts Unlimited's IT department is, therefore, with the help of a prospective board member, he will begin a learning journey that will help his team achieve all of the company's goals. .
I was intrigued by the idea of ​​there being an IT novel written by a devops expert, so I bought The Phoenix Project with high expectations and let me tell you, I recieved more than I was expecting for.
Before reading the book I thought that maybe this would be …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>higaguin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[{ Zero to Helm }: Part 2 - Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kinagi/-zero-to-helm-part-2-architecture-4am0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kinagi/-zero-to-helm-part-2-architecture-4am0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T19:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the next chapter of { Zero to Helm }. A blog-series in which I create "byte"-sized pieces of content aimed at mastering Kubernetes.
In this section, we are going to look to take a surface dive into Kubernetes by inspecting its architecture. Whether you are a fan of minimal version of k8s like k3s or robust cloud-specific versions like EKS, AKS, or GKE - the information explained here applies to all of them.
So lets start to breakdown this architecture:

Kubernetes at its essence is a collection of servers that work together to achieve a single purpose; run your workloads. These servers are referenced as "Nodes", and their responsibility is to run your workloads by placing containers into Pods.
Since Nodes are servers, they can be anything from physical machines to even virt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install MySQL on Ubuntu 18.04]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sureshramani/how-to-install-mysql-on-ubuntu-1804-33p2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sureshramani/how-to-install-mysql-on-ubuntu-1804-33p2"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T19:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is MySQL?


MySQL is an open-source database management system, commonly installed as part of the popular LAMP ( Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP / Python / Perl ) stack. It uses a relational database and SQL (Structured Query Language) to manage its data.
This article will show you how to install and secure MySQL on an Ubuntu 18.04 machine.
-> The operating system running Ubuntu 18.04 Linux
Updating the local package with apt-get command. Open a terminal window and run the following command:
sudo apt-get update

Please run the following command as sudo to install MySQL from APT-GET repositories.
sudo apt-get install mysql-server

The [Y / n] question to continue with the installation may appear during the installation process, press the Y key from the keyboard and hit Enter. This will insta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Ramani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Microservices comprehensive Guide for beginners!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arohi/nodejs-microservices-comprehensive-guide-for-beginners-587g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arohi/nodejs-microservices-comprehensive-guide-for-beginners-587g"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building real-world applications require dynamic programming, as with each update and upgrade, the application gets bigger and bigger. As a *Node develope*r, you would need to fix the bugs to maintain the code.
To execute the new latest updates, new developer team members need to be added. And this will eventually add more and more complications to the project.
To clear up the mess, you would need to convert this gigantic app into small pieces of information to handle it better way.
Node.js Microservices facilitates these tasks. But for beginners in the development industry, let’s understand what nOde.js Microservices are and how that works.
Microservices are the style of service-oriented Architecture in the web-app development industry. Withy Microservices, the application architecture ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arohi7892</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Microservices comprehensive Guide for beginners!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arohi/nodejs-microservices-comprehensive-guide-for-beginners-587g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arohi/nodejs-microservices-comprehensive-guide-for-beginners-587g"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T19:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building real-world applications require dynamic programming, as with each update and upgrade, the application gets bigger and bigger. As a *Node develope*r, you would need to fix the bugs to maintain the code.
To execute the new latest updates, new developer team members need to be added. And this will eventually add more and more complications to the project.
To clear up the mess, you would need to convert this gigantic app into small pieces of information to handle it better way.
Node.js Microservices facilitates these tasks. But for beginners in the development industry, let’s understand what nOde.js Microservices are and how that works.
Microservices are the style of service-oriented Architecture in the web-app development industry. Withy Microservices, the application architecture ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arohi7892</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pmbanugo/introduction-to-github-actions-4bp5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pmbanugo/introduction-to-github-actions-4bp5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T18:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is fast becoming an all-in-one platform where developers build, maintain and ship their software. You may use it primarily as a collaborative code management tool for your software. But today, you have features like:
Codespaces, a cloud-powered development environment that allows you to build, run and debug your code in the cloud.
Actions, an automation platform that allows you to automate your development workflow.
I'm going to focus on GitHub Actions in this post. This will be a basic introduction to the concept of GitHub Actions for developers of all skill levels. I'll start out with a simple action that prints out text, and then finish off with an Actions workflow that will run the test script of a Node.js application.
GitHub Actions is an event-driven, automation platform that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Mbanugo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Nodejs and Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/moreno8423/introduction-to-nodejs-and-express-4pik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/moreno8423/introduction-to-nodejs-and-express-4pik"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T17:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are going to learn some back end web development using JavaScript. The framework we are going to learn is very useful for back end web development. That framework is Nodejs. We are also going to use the most popular middleware for Nodejs. That middleware is "Express”. In this tutorial we expect you have some JavaScript knowledge. Also some HTML and CSS for templates and styling purposes. At the end of this tutorial you will have a great foundation to start creating your own applications.
To start we first need to download Nodejs from its website. Then we proceed  to install NodeJs. Once the software is installed, "The Node Package Manager" npm will also be installed. 

Once we finish the installation we can check the version of the installed softwares in the terminal. We only need to ty…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moises E Liria Rosario</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add An RSS Feed to a NextJS Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dandydev/how-to-add-an-rss-feed-to-a-nextjs-blog-4phg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dandydev/how-to-add-an-rss-feed-to-a-nextjs-blog-4phg"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T17:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I released a new version of my website with only one new feature: syndication through RSS, Atom and JSON Feed. Even though by some accounts, RSS seems to be dead, I strongly believe RSS is an important feature in the fight to keep ownership over your own content while also increasing exposure. The way I approach publishing and sharing my content, is called POSSE:
Publish (on your) Own Site, Syndicate Elsewhere.
RSS is an important part of that strategy.
Luckily, I'm not the only one who values RSS. There are others
In this article I want to share how I implemented syndication feeds in my NextJS-powered website.
I did some Googling to see how other NextJS users were generating RSS feeds, and there turned out to be many people that had solved this particular problem and wrote about it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daan Debie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14th weekly post, constant assertions and signatures. Also, storytelling in design.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/longyc/14th-weekly-post-constant-assertions-and-signatures-also-storytelling-in-design-49jc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/longyc/14th-weekly-post-constant-assertions-and-signatures-also-storytelling-in-design-49jc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T16:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Items of the week




TypeScript - const assertion can prevent literal types from being treated as more general types, e.g. const config = {light: "ON"} as const; will have light as the literal type "ON" instead of string, making it compatible with type {light: "ON" | "OFF"}. It'll also make light readonly. More explanation can be found on the official documentation page. 


JWT - it can be signed asymmetrically with a key pair or symmetrically with a shared secret. The latter means all parties involved use one secret for both signing and signature verification, which means any party with the shared secret could have signed the JWS - something to be taken into consideration during implementation.


Design & storytelling - good stories are engaging and help build empathy, adapting them to your audience and backing up the points with data could be helpful in getting buy-in during a design process. NN/g has an article on 6  rules for persuasive storytelling.




  
  
  Note of the week


On the week 41 of 2021, I found out about a portable game console powered by a microcontroller - PicoSystem, an interesting product considering it is sporting the RP2040 just like a Raspberry Pi Pico. That's all for this week's post, thank you for reading and if you have got any feedback, do let me know by leaving a comment. Have a nice day!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LongYC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an API using Node, Express, MongoDB, and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koladev/build-an-api-using-node-express-mongodb-and-docker-128p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koladev/build-an-api-using-node-express-mongodb-and-docker-128p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T16:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll be using TypeScript and Docker to build a Menu Restaurant API app from scratch with Node, Express, and MongoDB. The Docker part is optional.
Basically, we should be able to: 
retrieve all menus
retrieve one menu
create a menu
update a menu
delete a menu
Great, let's dive in.
To create a new Nodejs project, we'll first run this command on the terminal.
yarn init

It'll ask a couple of questions before initializing the project. Anyway, you can bypass this by adding a -y flag to the command.
Next step is to create a structure for our project.
├── dist
├── src
   ├── app.ts
   ├── controllers
   |  └── menus
   |     └── index.ts
   ├── models
   |  └── menu.ts
   ├── routes
   |  └── index.ts
   └── types
      └── menu.ts
├── nodemon.json
├── package.json
├── tsconfig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mangabo Kolawole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an API using Node, Express, MongoDB, and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koladev/build-an-api-using-node-express-mongodb-and-docker-128p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koladev/build-an-api-using-node-express-mongodb-and-docker-128p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T16:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we'll be using TypeScript and Docker to build a Menu Restaurant API app from scratch with Node, Express, and MongoDB. The Docker part is optional.
Basically, we should be able to: 
retrieve all menus
retrieve one menu
create a menu
update a menu
delete a menu
Great, let's dive in.
To create a new Nodejs project, we'll first run this command on the terminal.
yarn init

It'll ask a couple of questions before initializing the project. Anyway, you can bypass this by adding a -y flag to the command.
Next step is to create a structure for our project.
├── dist
├── src
   ├── app.ts
   ├── controllers
   |  └── menus
   |     └── index.ts
   ├── models
   |  └── menu.ts
   ├── routes
   |  └── index.ts
   └── types
      └── menu.ts
├── nodemon.json
├── package.json
├── tsconfig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mangabo Kolawole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Lambda on a Schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jannikwempe/how-to-run-lambda-on-a-schedule-280m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jannikwempe/how-to-run-lambda-on-a-schedule-280m"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T16:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running arbitrary code on a schedule is a very common use case. A common way of doing that is by using cron jobs. But how would you do that in the cloud (specifically AWS) without having to run a Linux instance or something similar?
One way of doing that is by leveraging Amazon EventBridge and Lambda. We will be creating a reusable AWS CDK construct that deploys a Lambda which will be executed on a configurable schedule. We will use that construct to deploy an example Lambda which fetches a quote from a 3rd-party API and logs it to the console. This is how it looks like:

You can find the finished example on GitHub.
💡 I'll add some tips that are optional and just reflect the way I like doing stuff. They are formatted like this paragraph.
We'll create the Lambda part of the construct first…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jannik Wempe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brief ETH Wallet Security Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/librehash/brief-eth-wallet-security-guide-2m4d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/librehash/brief-eth-wallet-security-guide-2m4d"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T16:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would recommend taking a look at some of the following links (if you're interested); wouldn't bash Metamask for no reason, but there are just certain facets of their wallet app that make it wholly insecure (in my opinion & in that of most security researchers 'in the wild', I would imagine): 
https://twitter.com/librehash/status/1339040262753038343?s=20


https://twitter.com/librehash/status/1361214665519423488?s=20



There are many more reasons that can be listed, but I won't get into those here. 
Let's just move forward toward ensuring that we can generate a secure Ethereum address. 
Despite all of the drawbacks and negatives listed above, there is a way to ensure that your Metamask wallet is a secure construction. 
The first step to doing so would be downloading Ian Coleman's BIP39 s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>librehash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stage 3: Temporal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zaidrehman/stage-3-temporal-146n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zaidrehman/stage-3-temporal-146n"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T14:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Provides new standard objects and functions for working with dates and times, solving all previous issues with Date.
Date has been a long-standing pain point in ECMAScript. Temporal, is  a global Object that acts as a top-level namespace (like Math), that brings a modern date/time API to the ECMAScript language. 
Date, and the motivations for Temporal, see: Fixing JavaScript Date.
Temporal fixes these problems by:
  Providing easy-to-use APIs for date and time computations
  First-class support for all time zones, including DST-safe arithmetic
  Dealing only with objects representing fixed dates and times
  Parsing a strictly specified string format
  Supporting non-Gregorian calendars
Object Relationship

Code examples
Temporal.Now
Temporal.Now.instant() - get the exact time since Unix epoch
Temporal.Now.timeZone() - get the current system time zone
Temporal.Instant
const instant = Temporal.Instant.from('1969-07-20T20:17Z');
instant.toString();  // => '1969-07-20T20:17:00Z'
instant.epochMilliseconds;  // => -14182980000

Temporal.PlainDate
const date = Temporal.PlainDate.from({ year:  2006, month:  8, day:  24  });  // => 2006-08-24 
date.year;  // => 2006 
date.inLeapYear;  // => false 
date.toString();  // => '2006-08-24'

Cookbook
https://tc39.es/proposal-temporal/docs/cookbook.html
Polyfills
https://www.npmjs.com/package/@js-temporal/polyfill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Rehman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular form group vs form control and form builder in Reactive Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivaramayysola/angular-form-group-vs-form-control-and-form-builder-in-reactive-forms-3400</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivaramayysola/angular-form-group-vs-form-control-and-form-builder-in-reactive-forms-3400"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T14:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oct 17 '21
            Comments: 1
            Answers: 1
        
I'm new to Angular. I came across the code with three variants. I want to know what difference does these three makes implementing in the Reactive forms(Form group, Form builder, and Form control).
Is there any priority based on the application performance of one over the other way of doing…
Open Full Question]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivaram Ayyalasomayajula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Quick Start]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vmtechhub/docker-quick-start-1lb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vmtechhub/docker-quick-start-1lb5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T14:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before talking about Docker, let’s first talk about Virtualization in general.
Virtualization is a way to utilize the underlying hardware more efficiently.
In general, yes. If every single application requires a separate machine, chances are that most of the time that machine will be underutilized and we will be wasting the hardware resources like CPU, memory, etc.
With virtualization, many applications can share the same physical hardware.
A virtualization solution acts as a layer on top of actual hardware.

It does so via a Hypervisor.
Hypervisor is a software through which we achieve desired virtualization.
There are two types of hypervisors:
Type-1 aka bare-metal because it runs directly on the hardware.
Type-2 runs as an application on the host operating system.
Virtual machine as the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vmtechhub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delegating IAM access with permission boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kallu/delegating-iam-access-with-permission-boundary-1ehe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kallu/delegating-iam-access-with-permission-boundary-1ehe"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is first repost in series that covers various details of migrating services from traditional data center to AWS. You can find this and other post from my personal blog https://carriagereturn.nl/
Back in the days, when creating an AWS account was a lot of overhead, common pattern was to have multiple teams sharing a single account. This created a demand to isolate teams from each other by assigning them an IAM policy that would grant access only to their part of the account. While it might have been possible (in theory) to create complex IAM policies to containerize resources by application or team, one fundamental problem did remain. Once you granted a right to create an IAM policy or role, you effectively granted admin level access to everything on the account. IAM has very granular …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Petri Kallberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delegating IAM access with permission boundary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kallu/delegating-iam-access-with-permission-boundary-1ehe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kallu/delegating-iam-access-with-permission-boundary-1ehe"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is first repost in series that covers various details of migrating services from traditional data center to AWS. You can find this and other post from my personal blog https://carriagereturn.nl/
Back in the days, when creating an AWS account was a lot of overhead, common pattern was to have multiple teams sharing a single account. This created a demand to isolate teams from each other by assigning them an IAM policy that would grant access only to their part of the account. While it might have been possible (in theory) to create complex IAM policies to containerize resources by application or team, one fundamental problem did remain. Once you granted a right to create an IAM policy or role, you effectively granted admin level access to everything on the account. IAM has very granular …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Petri Kallberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bypass Google reCaptcha Using Node.Js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/how-to-bypass-google-recaptcha-using-nodejs-364j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/how-to-bypass-google-recaptcha-using-nodejs-364j"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T13:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article is originally published to my blog: Solve Google reCaptcha using Node.Js
Ever wondered about bypassing a Google reCaptcha using some captcha solver techniques? If yes, your next question must be how? Well, I have a quick solution that will help you bypass a Google reCaptcha using Node.Js. You can solve Google reCaptcha v2 and v3 both with the help of this tool.
I am using 2Captcha library to solve the reCaptcha. It is a Captcha Solving Software that bypasses the captcha within seconds.
The process of bypassing a captcha is mentioned below-
Get the Captcha image from page in the form of data-sitekey parameter
Transfer the parameter to 2captcha service
The employee at 2captcha solves it
Once it is solved, we get the response
The response needs to set in the google reCaptcha texta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Bitbucket Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/macmacky/working-with-bitbucket-pipelines-6cd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/macmacky/working-with-bitbucket-pipelines-6cd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T12:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Guys Good Day!


It's been a long time since I posted here there were a lot of changes in my life for over almost 2 years now, mostly because of the pandemic. But anyways, let's learn about Pipelines in Bitbucket.
Before that let's understand few concepts that you may have heard but dont understand.
is a software development practice where developers regularly merge their code changes into a central repository.
Continuous Delivery - is a software development practice where code changes are automatically prepared for a release to production
Continuous Deployment - every change that passes all stages of your production environment.
Basically, the difference between Continuous Delivery and Continuous Deployment is that the former releases our project in a non-production environment like te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark A</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Bitbucket Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/macmacky/working-with-bitbucket-pipelines-6cd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/macmacky/working-with-bitbucket-pipelines-6cd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T12:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Guys Good Day!


It's been a long time since I posted here there were a lot of changes in my life for over almost 2 years now, mostly because of the pandemic. But anyways, let's learn about Pipelines in Bitbucket.
Before that let's understand few concepts that you may have heard but dont understand.
is a software development practice where developers regularly merge their code changes into a central repository.
Continuous Delivery - is a software development practice where code changes are automatically prepared for a release to production
Continuous Deployment - every change that passes all stages of your production environment.
Basically, the difference between Continuous Delivery and Continuous Deployment is that the former releases our project in a non-production environment like te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark A</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key difference between Inheritance and compose]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mcube25/key-difference-between-inheritance-and-compose-5cfk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mcube25/key-difference-between-inheritance-and-compose-5cfk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T12:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Everything in JavaScript is treated as an object. Functions too are  high class objects in a way and are treated as such in javaScript.  
To make large complex objects simple, many small objects are composed together. Composition is a cleaner, reusable and better solution for better code.

const MoneyInbank = {
    highRate(investspeed, devestSpeed) {
      return investspeed + devestSpeed;
    },
    lowrate(investspeed, devestSpeed) {
      return investspeed- investspeed;
    },
  };

const StopDebt = {
    stop(investspeed) {
      this.investspeed = 0;

      return 0;
    },
  };

const Bank = {
    model: "Grco",
  };

To make this large object smaller and reusable and implement functionality we can create a function that implements a functionality.

 const regulator …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Muhktar Musa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Very Simple PHP Redirect]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/katzueno/very-simple-php-redirect-5cf6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/katzueno/very-simple-php-redirect-5cf6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T11:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've moved (are planning to move) to new domain & you don't want to simply redirect to new domain.
This simple PHP script shows very simple message that domain has changed for set amount of seconds, then redirected to the new domain.
It is also render 301 status code. So Google will know your page was moved, too.
It will fetch the current request URL, and redirect to the new domain with exact same URI.
By the way, it has Japanese text, too :)
https://github.com/katzueno/simple-php-redirect
This post was copied from Readme. If there is a newer version and newer description at GitHub readme, refer to GitHub's readme.
For Apache server, mod_rewrite module should be enabled, and allowing to use .htaccess


You could set it in Apache config.
For Nginx server


PHP-FPM
Ability to set nginx config
Change the config values such as new domain to index.php to your desired state.
Place (or upload) index.php script to your old domain's webroot and clear all other files
Edit your apache config, .htaccess or Nginx config so that all request will go through this index.php
Enjoy the rest
$newDomain: Enter the new domain name. Starts with https://
$siteNameEn: Site name in English.
$siteNameJa: Site name in Japanese.
$sec: Seconds to wait and redirect
Create .htaccess file (if your server is allowing it), and enter the following.
RewriteBase.
<IfModule mod_rewrite.c>
RewriteEngine On
RewriteBase / # if it's lives under subdirectory, add the directory accordingly
RewriteCond %{REQUEST_FILENAME} !-f
RewriteCond %{REQUEST_FILENAME}/index.html !-f
RewriteCond %{REQUEST_FILENAME}/index.php !-f
RewriteRule . index.php [L]
</IfModule>


I assume you know about Nginx server and its config.
~ \.php($|/) location to send it to php-fpm.
absolute_redirect must be turned off.
location / {
    index index.php index.html index.htm;
    if (!-e $request_filename) {
        rewrite ^ /index.php last;
    }
}

Enjoy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katz Ueno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency Injection in ExpressWebJs V3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexigbokwe/dependency-injection-in-expresswebjs-v3-444k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexigbokwe/dependency-injection-in-expresswebjs-v3-444k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T11:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software engineering, dependency injection is a technique in which an object receives other objects that it depends on, called dependencies.
Typically, the receiving object is called a client and the passed-in ('injected') object is called a service. 
The code that passes the service to the client is called the injector. Instead of the client specifying which service it will use, the injector tells the client what service to use. The 'injection' refers to the passing of a dependency (a service) into the client that uses it.
We can inject the classes into another class’s constructor and then get the object of that class, and through that object, we can access its methods and properties.
The Service Container in ExpressWebJs is a Dependency Injection Container and a registry for the appli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Igbokwe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency Injection in ExpressWebJs V3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexigbokwe/dependency-injection-in-expresswebjs-v3-444k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexigbokwe/dependency-injection-in-expresswebjs-v3-444k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T11:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In software engineering, dependency injection is a technique in which an object receives other objects that it depends on, called dependencies.
Typically, the receiving object is called a client and the passed-in ('injected') object is called a service. 
The code that passes the service to the client is called the injector. Instead of the client specifying which service it will use, the injector tells the client what service to use. The 'injection' refers to the passing of a dependency (a service) into the client that uses it.
We can inject the classes into another class’s constructor and then get the object of that class, and through that object, we can access its methods and properties.
The Service Container in ExpressWebJs is a Dependency Injection Container and a registry for the appli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Igbokwe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous integration and continuous delivery explanation (ci/cd)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedelagmey/continuous-integration-and-continuous-delivery-explanation-cicd-16j3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedelagmey/continuous-integration-and-continuous-delivery-explanation-cicd-16j3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T11:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will talk about ci/cd continuous integration and continuous delivery.
Continuous-Integration (ci): is a software engineering and coding approach that allows developers and teams to make small releases code changes and merged them into a version control repository. because most modern applications use different tools, technologies, and platforms. teams need automation methodology to integrate and smoothly validate their changes.
Continuous-Delivery (cd): raise where ci ends, the main goal of cd is to automate the application deployment and production, teams practicing cd can changes code, add new features, bug fixes, and configure changes automatically. cd has solved the problem of miscommunication between the Dev team and ops team 
benefits of ci/cd:
 follow this resource to learn more about ci /cd
https://lnkd.in/d3tbJXZ5
https://lnkd.in/dhH6SpYi
https://lnkd.in/d6umzuPk 


  
  
  softwareengineering



  
  
  coding #automation #team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Elagmey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple file based routing for Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matthiaaas/simple-file-based-routing-for-express-1l22</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matthiaaas/simple-file-based-routing-for-express-1l22"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T10:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a bunch of best practices out there that recommend to split your Express.js routes into separate files using Express.Router().
But creating new routes this way isn't straightforward and requires quite a few lines of boilerplate code for each newly introduced endpoint.
// this is messy
import express from "express"

const router = express.Router()

router.route("/")
  .get(async (req, res) => {
    ...
  })

export default router

Fortunately, the framework era taught us better and popularized cleaner alternatives like file based routing.
Consider the following project structure:
├── app.ts // main file
├── routes
    ├── index.ts // index routes
    ├── posts
        ├── index.ts
        └── [id].ts // dynamic params
    └── users.ts
└── package.json

This approach can work for you out-of-the-box too!
npm install express-file-routing

express-file-routing will transform all of your files inside /routes into valid paths.
/routes/index.ts → /
/routes/posts/index.ts → /posts
/routes/posts/[id].ts → /posts/:id
/routes/users.ts → /users




// app.ts
import express from "express"
import { router } from "express-file-routing"

const app = express()

app.use(router())

// /routes/users.ts
export const get = async (req, res) => {
  res.json([])
}

By default, exported functions like get, post, put, patch, del etc. will get matched their corresponding HTTP method automatically.
Adding middlewares is equally intuitive:
// /routes/posts.ts
import { rateLimit, userAuth } from "../middlewares"

export const post = [
  rateLimit(), userAuth(),
  async (req, res) => {
    res.status(201).json({})
  }
]

See matthiaaas/express-file-routing on GitHub for detailed docs & a get started guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Management in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayush11_bhat/management-in-linux-1743</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayush11_bhat/management-in-linux-1743"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T10:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we will be exploring the following fields in Linux:
User Account Management
Group Management
File Permissions And Ownership
Question arises why to have different user accounts? To answer this following are some points that we keep in mind.
Each user will have their own individualized private space.
Will help in distinguishing privileges among users.
Note : root user is a special user who is able to do anything on the system.
UID : It is a unique number that is assigned to the user account. It is also used for determination of user privileges and activity tracking.
GID : Indicates default group of the user.
Comment : Using comment field for contact information.
Home Directory : This is owned by a user and will be found on system under /home directory, except for root.
Login She…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Bhat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWK an old-school tool today]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kh40sz3r0/awk-an-old-school-tool-today-4p3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kh40sz3r0/awk-an-old-school-tool-today-4p3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T03:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is AWK?


AWK is a command-line programming language primarily oriented to text and files processing - some might call it a tool -, simple yet elegant continuous lines of code can replace multiple lines of a more robust language like java or node without losing their intention.
In essence, AWK code is so simple that you can just throw it away after the execution or once your program has finished its work.
% awk 'BEGIN { print "Hello World" }'
Hello World

But there is so much more than that; considering the constant need to process data files, once you have started with AWK, you will stop building complete programs to process CSV or log files for faster and more straightforward with a couple of instructions
% awk '{ print $0 }' example.txt
This is an AWK example

% awk '{ print $4, $1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Marcial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backend, for The Absolute Beginner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/snickdx/backend-for-the-absolute-beginner-4bk5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/snickdx/backend-for-the-absolute-beginner-4bk5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T03:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, it seems that Frontend gets all of the hype in web dev. You build a page with HTML, CSS & JS then let it talk to an API (JAM Stack). However, how do you build an API in the first place? What is server side programming? This is your quick start guide.
To understand backend, I think it's a good understand how web started first. Luckily, I have just the article for you.
A "Brief" History of the Web
Nicholas Mendez ・ Sep 19 ・ 4 min read
#webdev
        #beginners
        #javascript
        #php
      
In any case here is the TLDR;
A guy creates a network protocol (it lets computers talk to each other)
Another person creates a language for formatting documents (HTML)
Web browser software is invented that lets you request and loads documents from one networked computer to another 
Jav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Mendez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Moderno #1 | Variables y Constantes.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jleondev/javascript-moderno-1-variables-y-constantes-23ao</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jleondev/javascript-moderno-1-variables-y-constantes-23ao"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T02:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[En esta serie de posts, voy a compartir y ejemplificar algunas características "modernas" de JavaScript; ya que desde mi punto de vista, el conocer las features modernas de este lenguaje te hacen la vida mucho más fácil. 
En esta primera entrega vamos a ver un tema básico: Variables y Constantes.
JavaScript fue creado en un mundo completamente distinto al que vivimos actualmente (tecnológicamente hablando), tenía otros propósitos y no fue inicialmente diseñado para soportar todo lo que actualmente le delegamos. Es por eso que JavaScript ha ido evolucionando con el tiempo y naturalmente en esa "evolución" han ido quedando vestigios de su antiguo yo, un ejemplo de esto es el uso de la palabra reservada var.
var se utiliza en JavaScript para declarar una variable (un espacio en memoria para a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph León</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working with Files in Linux 💻]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linuxseb/working-with-files-in-linux-51af</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linuxseb/working-with-files-in-linux-51af"/>
        <updated>2021-10-17T00:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Dev community! 😆
After weeks of exams and dealing with imposter syndrome, I am back with another short article on 'file commands' in Linux. These are pretty useful so take a look. 🤠
The 'cd' command moves you into any directory you want. For example, if I have files located in the 'Documents' directory, this is the command I would run:
cd Documents
and this would move me to that directory.

The 'ls' command lists everything that is in that directory. To list everything in the directory, run this command:
ls -l

the 'cat' commands displays what is inside a file. Simply run this command:
cat (name of file)

The cat command also can do other things. 👇
Using this command, you can also create a file.
What I did below was I created the file, typed out what I needed to, then viewed the fil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying applications on Kubernetes using TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brunoa19/deploying-applications-on-kubernetes-using-typescript-3fn9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brunoa19/deploying-applications-on-kubernetes-using-typescript-3fn9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T23:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no doubt that YAML has developed a reputation for being a painful way to define and deploy applications on Kubernetes. The combination of semantics and empty spaces can drive some developers crazy. 
As Kubernetes advances, is it time for us to explore different options that can support both DevOps and Developers in deploying and managing applications on Kubernetes?
Pulumi: Modern infrastructure as code for developers, a.k.a the new kid on the block.
Pulumi targets the widespread infrastructure as code (IaC) space but using a different approach. It allows developers to define infrastructure using their language of choice, such as TypeScript, JavaScript, Python, and others, instead of a proprietary language, such as HCL, from our friends at HashiCorp.
It is an exciting approach that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making React App from Vite Compatible to CRA]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uchihamalolan/making-react-app-from-vite-compatible-to-cra-48pc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uchihamalolan/making-react-app-from-vite-compatible-to-cra-48pc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T23:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I tried to migrate my project's codebase from CRA (create-react-app) to ViteJS. It was not as simple as it seemed actually. Because I wanted to remove react-scripts completely and use just Vite instead.
These are the basic features that I wanted the project setup with Vite to have (that was present in CRA):
Typescript Support
Jest Test Runner with React Testing Library
Import SVG as components (actually decided against it later)
Using Absolute imports
ESLint & Prettier Support
Additionally I went on to add following features also:
TailwindCSS (with JIT mode)
Husky + Lint-Staged (to run eslint & prettier on pre-commit)
CommitLint (to enforce conventional-commits)
Additional ESLint Plugins
Source Map Explorer
React-Error-Boundary
And Tweaked few configurations to support:
Multiple e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malolan B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use PiHole and Block ALL ads in your network]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raissaccorreia/how-to-use-pihole-and-block-all-ads-in-your-network-m1c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raissaccorreia/how-to-use-pihole-and-block-all-ads-in-your-network-m1c"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T23:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to clarify that some ads can't be blocked for example: Youtube, Instagram and TikTok, because the ads' source is the same of the content, because this is a DNS filter. 
I also need to tell that there are some collateral effects, the main one is:
If you're going to buy something all links in google shopping is a google ad, so they can't be loaded you have to disable piHole in the manager address "http://raspberry_pi_ip_address/admin"
Several web pages have problems to load you click the link and Network Error, reaload, DNS Probe Error, reload, loads like normal
I have a smart TV by Samsung, like I do, and if you disconnect from Wi-fi, you have to disable to connect your TV again
All disclaimers aside, let's implement to learn a bit about network!
1) First set up your raspberry pi, wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raissa Correia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditching the "else" Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mkovace/ditching-the-else-statement-5cfh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mkovace/ditching-the-else-statement-5cfh"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T20:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are "else" statements really necessary? When first learning to program we are taught about "if" statements and "else" statements. If this condition is met do something, else do another thing. It's fundamental to nearly every programming language, but can we ditch the "else" statement?
Like with most things in programming there will be scenarios where using an "else" statement is more appropriate than avoiding it, but let's assume that we want to ditch it no matter what scenario arises. How would we do that and why would we want to?
The best way to explore this approach is through examples so let's start with a simple one. All of the examples below are written in Typescript:
// With "else"
const areEqual = (value1: string, value2: string) => {
  if (value1 === value2) {
    return true;
  }…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Kovacevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Processing CPU-intensive Jobs in NodeJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eunovo/processing-cpu-intensive-jobs-in-nodejs-5epd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eunovo/processing-cpu-intensive-jobs-in-nodejs-5epd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T19:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Fidel Fernando on Unsplash
So, I recently had to solve a problem with one of my NodeJS servers. I had to parse and process data from an excel sheet which turned out to be pretty CPU-intensive and it blocked the NodeJS event loop, effectively freezing my server till it's done. I wasn't surprised though; I expected this to happen. While there are several things you could do to resolve this, I'm going to present a solution using the NodeJS worker_threads module. Before we start, let's quickly talk about this thread thing. The code used in this article is available here.
A thread is a path of execution within a process.
Source geeksforgeeks
JavaScript is a single-threaded programming language which means that only a set of instructions can be executed at a time. NodeJS applicati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oghenovo Usiwoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Encrypt and Decrypt in Node JS using Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codewithtravel/how-to-encrypt-and-decrypt-in-node-js-using-crypto-3fm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codewithtravel/how-to-encrypt-and-decrypt-in-node-js-using-crypto-3fm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T17:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn how to use the Node.js crypto module to perform cryptographic operations on data. I'll show you how to encrypt data with a secret key and then decrypt it using the same secret key when required.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9PL7EK4jXLM
Create a new project
Create a new directory in your local file system and switch to it by typing the following
mkdir encr_decr && cd encr_decr
npm init -y

Now install the crypto module
npm install crypto --save

Now make app.js.
Add following code to app.js
var Crypto = require('crypto');
var secret_key = 'fd85b494-aaaa';
var secret_iv = 'smslt';
var encryptionMethod = 'AES-256-CBC';
var key = Crypto.createHash('sha512').update(secret_key, 'utf-8').digest('hex').substr(0, 32);
var iv = Crypto.createHash('sha512').update(secret_iv, 'utf-8').digest('hex').substr(0, 16);
var encryptedMessage = encrypt_string("hello", encryptionMethod, key, iv);
console.log(encryptedMessage); 
// output : L2dOZjlDVmxoSDNWdmpVMkNGd0JEdz09
var decrptMessage = decrypt_string(encryptedMessage, encryptionMethod, key , iv);
console.log(decrptMessage);  
//output : hello

function encrypt_string(plain_text, encryptionMethod, secret, iv) {
  var encryptor = Crypto.createCipheriv(encryptionMethod, secret, iv);
  var aes_encrypted = encryptor.update(plain_text, 'utf8', 'base64') + encryptor.final('base64');
  return Buffer.from(aes_encrypted).toString('base64');
};

function decrypt_string(encryptedMessage, encryptionMethod, secret, iv) {
  const buff = Buffer.from(encryptedMessage, 'base64');
  encryptedMessage = buff.toString('utf-8');
  var decryptor = Crypto.createDecipheriv(encryptionMethod, secret, iv);
  return decryptor.update(encryptedMessage, 'base64', 'utf8') + decryptor.final('utf8');
};

Conclusion
In this article, we looked at how to perform cryptographic operations on a text by using Node.js built-in crypto module.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stemword</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Encrypt and Decrypt in Node JS using Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codewithtravel/how-to-encrypt-and-decrypt-in-node-js-using-crypto-3fm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codewithtravel/how-to-encrypt-and-decrypt-in-node-js-using-crypto-3fm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T17:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn how to use the Node.js crypto module to perform cryptographic operations on data. I'll show you how to encrypt data with a secret key and then decrypt it using the same secret key when required.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9PL7EK4jXLM
Create a new project
Create a new directory in your local file system and switch to it by typing the following
mkdir encr_decr && cd encr_decr
npm init -y

Now install the crypto module
npm install crypto --save

Now make app.js.
Add following code to app.js
var Crypto = require('crypto');
var secret_key = 'fd85b494-aaaa';
var secret_iv = 'smslt';
var encryptionMethod = 'AES-256-CBC';
var key = Crypto.createHash('sha512').update(secret_key, 'utf-8').digest('hex').substr(0, 32);
var iv = Crypto.createHash('sha512').update(secret_iv, 'utf-8').digest('hex').substr(0, 16);
var encryptedMessage = encrypt_string("hello", encryptionMethod, key, iv);
console.log(encryptedMessage); 
// output : L2dOZjlDVmxoSDNWdmpVMkNGd0JEdz09
var decrptMessage = decrypt_string(encryptedMessage, encryptionMethod, key , iv);
console.log(decrptMessage);  
//output : hello

function encrypt_string(plain_text, encryptionMethod, secret, iv) {
  var encryptor = Crypto.createCipheriv(encryptionMethod, secret, iv);
  var aes_encrypted = encryptor.update(plain_text, 'utf8', 'base64') + encryptor.final('base64');
  return Buffer.from(aes_encrypted).toString('base64');
};

function decrypt_string(encryptedMessage, encryptionMethod, secret, iv) {
  const buff = Buffer.from(encryptedMessage, 'base64');
  encryptedMessage = buff.toString('utf-8');
  var decryptor = Crypto.createDecipheriv(encryptionMethod, secret, iv);
  return decryptor.update(encryptedMessage, 'base64', 'utf8') + decryptor.final('utf8');
};

Conclusion
In this article, we looked at how to perform cryptographic operations on a text by using Node.js built-in crypto module.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stemword</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript vs Dart - Coleções iteráveis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wilmarques/typescript-vs-dart-colecoes-iteraveis-1c1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wilmarques/typescript-vs-dart-colecoes-iteraveis-1c1h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T14:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O que são coleções iteráveis
Criando uma lista
Adicionando itens
Obtendo itens específicos
Removendo itens
Iterando sequencialmente nos elementos
Verificando a existência de um item específico
Filtrando itens
Conclusão
Referências
Coleções são, em resumo, uma representação de um grupo de objetos. Uma coleção iterável é um tipo de coleção onde pode-se iterar nos elementos. Em outras palavras, são coleções onde podemos navegar nos seus elementos.
Ambas as linguagens (Dart e TypeScript) tem implementações nativas para criação de coleções iteráveis. Em ambas, esse tipo é chamado de Iterable. Cada uma, obviamente, possui uma implementação diferente, mas ambas têm o mesmo objetivo e funções similares.
Os tipos mais comuns de coleções iteráveis são: Lists (ou Arrays), Maps e Sets. Nesse artigo, v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wiley Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to simplify and organize imports in Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danywalls/simplify-imports-in-typescript-29jo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danywalls/simplify-imports-in-typescript-29jo"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T13:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes we have a long  list of imports, with files that come from the same place, it makes our code noisy and a bit longer, something like:
import { BeersService } from './services/beers.service';
import { WhiskyService } from './services/whiski.service';
import { WineService } from './services/wine.service';

We can simplify it by exposing all files, from a single file, to point to all of them.
Create drinks.ts into the service directory and export all services.
export * from './beers.service';
export * from './whiski.service';
export * from './wine.service';

Now we can update our files, to the new path.
import { BeersService, WhiskyService, WineService } from './services/drinks';

Thanks @lissetteibnz
 , If rename the filename from drinks.ts to index.ts, Javascript understand the file index like the entrypoint for the directory, so  it works only using the directory name.
import { BeersService, WhiskyService, WineService } from './services';

The code looks clean and easy to ready because all of them comes from the same place.
Photo by Marcin Jozwiak on Unsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dany Paredes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 12 and RxJS: Infinite Scroll With API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/angular-12-and-rxjs-infinite-scroll-with-api-48l3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/angular-12-and-rxjs-infinite-scroll-with-api-48l3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T12:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article is originally published to my blog: Angular and RxJS Infinite Scroll
Infinite Scroll is the ability to scroll through a large infinite list without compromising the performance of application. It improves user experience of the application. In this article I will cover how to implement infinite scroll with API in Angular 12 with the help of RxJS Operators.
A question comes in mind that how it works internally. It works like there is a big list say 10k items are there. Displaying all those items in once is not possible as it will break the application. And you can not put numbering pagination as that will look bad on the place or you have dropdown (dropdowns can not number paginations).
In that case you need infinite scroll. It loads only 10 (size is provided in configuration) r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Table with material-ui and material-table]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kojikanao/create-a-table-with-material-ui-and-material-table-f82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kojikanao/create-a-table-with-material-ui-and-material-table-f82"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T11:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we will create a simple table with material-ui and material-table. The sample data is generated by facker.js
 / 
        faker.js
      
    

 




https://rawgit.com/Marak/faker.js/master/examples/browser/index.html
Don't have a local development setup ready?
Try our hosted version of Faker at https://fakercloud.com/api
https://github.com/faker/faker-cloud
    <script src = "faker.js" type = "text/javascript"></script>
    <script>
      var randomName = faker.name.findName(); // Caitlyn Kerluke
      var randomEmail = faker.internet.email(); // Rusty@arne.info
      var randomCard = faker.helpers.createCard(); // random contact card containing many properties
    </script>
    var faker = require('faker');
    var randomName = faker.name.findName(); // Rowan Nikolaus
    v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Koji (he/him)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding the Google reCAPTCHA v3 to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-google-recaptcha-v3-to-an-angular-application-kge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-the-google-recaptcha-v3-to-an-angular-application-kge"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T11:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
ng-recaptcha is a simple and configurable reCAPTCHA v2 and v3 component library.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the account. Access the site https://www.google.com/recaptcha/ and click on the button v3 Admin Console.

2. Fill in the field Email or phone and click on the button Next to login with your Google account and if you don't have an account, just create a new account.

3. Click on the button +.

4. Fill in the field Label, click on the option reCAPT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic CRUD Service in Angular: Part 4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-4-3neo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-4-3neo"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T11:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Xan Griffin on Unsplash.
This article is a part of a series about how to create Generic CRUD Service & Models in Angular:
Part 1 - Understanding Generics
Part 2 - What is CRUD?
Part 3 - Generic CRUD Model
👉 Part 4 - Generic CRUD Service in Angular




  
  
  Generic CRUD Service


Before we start generating and writing code, let’s take a step back and see the bigger picture. The generic service should accept the following arguments:
the HttpClient is used for the HTTP requests
the class of model for creating instances
the path of the API endpoints.
Also, all resources should have 5 main methods related to CRUD…
Create - Returns a new resource.
Get all - Retrieves all resources as a list.
Get by ID - Returns a specific resource by ID.
Update - Updates a specific resource by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikos Anifantis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic CRUD Service in Angular: Part 4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-4-3neo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nikosanif/generic-crud-service-in-angular-part-4-3neo"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T11:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cover Photo by Xan Griffin on Unsplash.
This article is a part of a series about how to create Generic CRUD Service & Models in Angular:
Part 1 - Understanding Generics
Part 2 - What is CRUD?
Part 3 - Generic CRUD Model
👉 Part 4 - Generic CRUD Service in Angular




  
  
  Generic CRUD Service


Before we start generating and writing code, let’s take a step back and see the bigger picture. The generic service should accept the following arguments:
the HttpClient is used for the HTTP requests
the class of model for creating instances
the path of the API endpoints.
Also, all resources should have 5 main methods related to CRUD…
Create - Returns a new resource.
Get all - Retrieves all resources as a list.
Get by ID - Returns a specific resource by ID.
Update - Updates a specific resource by…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikos Anifantis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform IaC Scanning with Trivy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/terraform-iac-scanning-with-trivy-3cai</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/terraform-iac-scanning-with-trivy-3cai"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T11:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trivy Vulnerability Scanner


Trivy is a simple and comprehensive scanner for vulnerabilities in container images, file systems, and Git repositories, as well as for configuration issues in IaC. Trivy detects vulnerabilities of OS packages (Alpine, RHEL, CentOS, etc.) and language-specific packages (Bundler, Composer, npm, yarn, etc.). In addition, Trivy scans Infrastructure as Code (IaC) files such as Terraform, Dockerfile and Kubernetes, to detect potential configuration issues that expose your deployments to the risk of attack.
You can scan your Terraform configuration artifacts easily giving you the confidence that all is well with your configuration before deploying your Terraform (IaC) configurations. It is a free/open source tool by AquaSecurity. For more information go check out th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Angular resolvers to prefetch beers to the party]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/how-to-use-angular-resolver-to-prefetch-beers-into-the-party-49g3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/how-to-use-angular-resolver-to-prefetch-beers-into-the-party-49g3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T07:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we go to a party, I love to have all beers ready to drink and take  one, but sometimes take time to pick from fridge to the table, and stay waiting is not a good experience.
The same happen with our users work with our angular apps, we show the component, but the data is not there or the HTTP request take time, and they are waiting.
A good solution is show a loading until get the data, but if my users want the beers ready from the beginning ? No problem because Angular have a solution, The Resolvers.
The Resolvers help us to prefetch data, before the router finish start the transition between components, and store.
The resolvers are helpful to avoid show an empty component, and  have our data ready, before move to the component.
Let's put the resolver to test, building an app to show …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dany Paredes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The creator of world's most popular JS Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chamberdeveloper/the-creator-of-worlds-most-popular-js-framework-4i30</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chamberdeveloper/the-creator-of-worlds-most-popular-js-framework-4i30"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T02:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vue: Rich Harris
Github]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ChamberSiagian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: broken links in documentation
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @hirdot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible Design System in Angular, the Execution.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srini/accessible-design-system-in-angular-the-execution-1bi3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srini/accessible-design-system-in-angular-the-execution-1bi3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T21:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The how we did it is paramount, in manifesting goals into reality.



Measure twice and cut once.

We wanted the absolute best developer experience for the users. So, we settled after a few trials on a process that worked well for us.
I set up working sessions between the component dev and myself.
Every component started with its own markdown file to document the design.
We put down the ideal developer usage and experience, for the component.
We referenced our existing version, component tickets history and industry leaders.
The states and interactions were then considered.
Once satisfied, we sought feedback from the rest of the dev team.
We also sought the feedback of some key dev community members.
The final design would then be honed, ready for coded implementation.
Maker to maker work,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sri-Ni, Thirumalaa Srinivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 15th October 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-15th-october-2021-17h9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-15th-october-2021-17h9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T20:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


It's yet another day, another Friday, you know what that means? It means it's time for a review of some top security news over the past week that it's worth your time.
This week's review is "multi" in nature in the sense that we have news about privacy, security, cyber-attack_, and vulnerabilities.
Let's go!
Microsoft thwarts record‑breaking DDoS attack


DDoS is short for Distributed Denial of Service attacks and its main objective is to overwhelm a target infrastructure with more than it can handle on a typical day.
In this article, Amer Owaida of welivesecurity details how Microsoft thwarted a DDoS attack against an Azure customer.
Excerpt from the article:
The attack vector was a UDP reflection spanning more than 10 minutes with very short-lived bursts, each ramping up i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a Password Manager with Node.js : Part - 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohanwww/how-to-build-a-password-manager-with-nodejs-part-1-34i5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohanwww/how-to-build-a-password-manager-with-nodejs-part-1-34i5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A password manager is a computer program that allows users to store, generate, and manage their passwords for local applications and online services. A password manager assists in generating and retrieving complex passwords, storing such passwords in an encrypted database, or calculating them on demand. For the past seven years "123456" and "password" have been the two most commonly used passwords on the web. The problem is, most of us don't know what makes a good password and aren't able to remember hundreds of them anyway.
Most web browsers offer at least a rudimentary password manager. (This is where your passwords are stored when Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox ask if you'd like to save a password.) This is better than reusing the same password everywhere, but browser-based password m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NGX-Nework Get Network Speed]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mahmoudshahin1111/ngx-nework-get-network-speed-5cdk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mahmoudshahin1111/ngx-nework-get-network-speed-5cdk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T19:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times you want from client to upload or download something and you need to be sure his network is fast so with simplest package every and updated continuously with new features NgxNetwork you can do that. let's finish the work 👷‍♂️👷‍♀️
https://www.npmjs.com/package/ngx-network
give a user great experiance by add this tool to your angular project with simple steps and make the client see his current network speed 


please support me by comment about any suggestions or anything need to add to this amazing tool]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahmoud shahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧬 The Future of Healthcare Relies on Adaptation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/the-future-of-healthcare-relies-on-adaptation-n65</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/the-future-of-healthcare-relies-on-adaptation-n65"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T19:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delivery of healthcare transformed in the pandemic (SMART on FHIR and the 21st Cures Act). What can patients, providers, payers, and insurance companies gain?



  
  
  
The delivery of healthcare services has gone through an unprecedented transformation during the COVID-19 pandemic. COVID-19 has accelerated the move to a digital-forward model and elevated trends that were previously slow to be adopted. In addition, the final rule of the 21st Century Cures Act, effective June 30, 2020, implements provisions to “advance interoperability and support the access, exchange, and use of electronic health information”.
Technology leaders in the healthcare industry will drive positive business outcomes by continuing to innovate in ways that meet the demands of consumers while also meeting security…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UX Designer Salary – How much do UX/UI Designers Make? Entry Level Range]]></title>
        <id>61063abe3306a507d1bfbfb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ux-designer-salary-how-much-do-ux-ui-designers-make-entry-level-range/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T17:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are new to tech, you might have just discovered UI/ UX design and want to pursue that career path. But what is the starting salary for entry level UX/UI designers? In this article, I will provide definitions for UI/ UX design as well as starting salary information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EKS Security Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/eks-security-best-practices-3f18</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/eks-security-best-practices-3f18"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T17:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog we are going to see the security best practices for EKS cluster related to IRSA roles and service account tokens. 
Sample Trust policy for the IRSA role. 
{


Assume a demo namespace has two IRSA roles create with trust policy system:serviceaccount:demo:*
IAM Role 1 - ServiceAccount01 - access to S3 
Pod1 with ServiceAccount01 can access Role 2 just by exporting the AWS_ROLE_ARN = <ARN OF IAM ROLE 2> so that it will get access to S3 and DynamoDB .
EKS supports IRSA roles for the aws-node daemonset, it is security best practice to use IRSA role instead of system node role. 
Update the pod spec with automountServiceAccountToken=false attribute if there is no need for the application to access EKS Control plane API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sent2020</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to run USSD code in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/neloyahmed/how-to-run-ussd-code-in-linux-50k1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/neloyahmed/how-to-run-ussd-code-in-linux-50k1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T16:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently in one of my home PC I removed windows and installed Ubuntu 20.04.3 LTS. 
One of the very first challenges I faced was making sure I can connect to the internet using my D-Link DWM-157 modem.
After doing some google search I came to know about ‘Modem Manager GUI’ and I was so happy. Opened my terminal and simply typed:
sudo apt-get update


Someone was smiling behind the scene and was whispering not so easy boy! Prepare for the next hurdle.
I was so happy it is a very nice GUI, everything is here for me i just a single click away to check anything. Everything was working perfectly in the GUI except the USSD code !
Modem Manager >= 0.7.0: GDBus.Error:org.freedesktop.ModemManager1.Error.Core.Aborted: USSD terminated by network
I did not find any work around to solve this issue. 
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neloy Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a Page in Word – Remove Blank or Extra Pages]]></title>
        <id>61694be680d82d07c45a51bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-delete-a-page-in-word-remove-blank-or-extra-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T16:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're using Microsoft Word, you don't want blank pages appearing in the middle of your document, or extra pages at the end.  These extra pages could be caused by tables, hitting the ENTER key too many times, unnecessary section breaks, unintentional page breaks, extra paragraph markers, and more.  You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPV4 vs IPV6 – What is the Difference Between IP Addressing Schemes?]]></title>
        <id>61680b4480d82d07c45a4661</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ipv4-vs-ipv6-what-is-the-difference-between-ip-addressing-schemes/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T16:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet is one of our greatest inventions.  Millions of people use the Internet every second of the day, and it has changed many aspects of our lives – from creating new jobs and a new way of working to influencing how news is consumed and how decisions are made.  Although]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expandable Sections Within a CSS Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353473</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/expandable-sections-within-a-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T16:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love CSS Grid. I love how, with just a few lines of code, we can achieve fully responsive grid layouts, often without any media queries at all. I’m quite comfortable wrangling CSS Grid to produce interesting layouts, while keeping …
The post Expandable Sections Within a CSS Grid appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kev Bonett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me how would you speed up Pipelines Using Automated Risk-Based Decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/uleska/tell-me-how-would-you-up-pipelines-using-automated-risk-based-decisions-10f1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/uleska/tell-me-how-would-you-up-pipelines-using-automated-risk-based-decisions-10f1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T15:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The speed of software development today allows us to get products to market at a faster pace than ever before. This is great because you can get releases out there, see the changes and get the updates. But security is typically being left behind, and there are a number of challenges facing agile security.
Increasing regulations like the New York CRR 500, and BaFin in Germany are enforcing timely verification and risk-based approaches. With a need for more frequent and automatable checks, how do we make sure we understand the impact as well as the vulnerability?
With more and more high profile breaches, clients today demand to know the risks from their software supply chain. This challenges security, development and DevOps teams to shift left, to have software security checks in their SDLC …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why detecting generic credentials is a game changer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gitguardian/why-detecting-generic-credentials-is-a-game-changer-5ena</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gitguardian/why-detecting-generic-credentials-is-a-game-changer-5ena"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T15:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At our core, you probably know that we are a company specializing in detecting secrets (if you don't know what a secret is, please take a moment here and come back).
what would be a good way to categorize secrets?
Take a look at this:
AWS_ACCESS_KEY_ID = A3T6AKIAFJKR45SAWS5Z
AWS_SECRET_ACCESS_KEY = hjshnk5ex5u34565d4654HJKGjhz545d89sjkjak

and this:
connect_to_db(host="136.12.43.86", port=8130, username="root", password="m42ploz2wd")

You can spot the difference: the first one is tied to a well identified service, AWS, while for the second, things are a bit blurrier: we immediately understand that it has to do with a database connection, but, without further context it doesn't tell us what doors it opens.
That's the most basic distinction we can make when scanning source code: some secrets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pierre Lalanne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: Error: secretOrPrivateKey must have a value]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nishat96/answer-error-secretorprivatekey-must-have-a-value-2a00</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nishat96/answer-error-secretorprivatekey-must-have-a-value-2a00"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T15:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re:  Error: secretOrPrivateKey must have a value
            
        
Nov  2 '19
        
It looks like your application can't read the environment variable properly.
I don't know which package you are using to load environment variables but the simplest way is using dotenv package.
After installing it with npm i dotenv, import it as early as possible in your application main file like…
Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nishat Tasnim Mithila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Docker on WSL2 the right way]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipecrs/simply-run-docker-on-wsl2-3o8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipecrs/simply-run-docker-on-wsl2-3o8"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, now that Docker Desktop is paid under certain scenarios, you may want to switch to something else.
This is a straight to the point guide on how to make Docker CE run fully on WSL2.
PS: the title says right way, but it is just my personal opinion. I am not claiming that any other guide does it in a wrong way.
A full-fledged Docker installation on WSL2
Docker Daemon automatic start without any crazy hacks
Docker Daemon sharing between Windows and WSL (i.e. you cannot run docker from Windows PowerShell)
Docker Daemon sharing between WSL distributions
I will consider that you already have WSL2 working, and you are using Ubuntu as your distribution.
Install Docker CE on Ubuntu by following the official guide:
# Ensures not older packages are installed
$ sudo apt-get remove docker docker-eng…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Santos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips And Tricks For Evaluating UX/UI Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers may start using your app because you offer a unique product, but user experience is what makes them stay. For that, you need excellent UX designers, and the know-how to spot them when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nataliya Sambir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing access to Scaleway Elements API Keys from Gitlab CI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stack-labs/securing-access-to-scaleway-elements-api-keys-from-gitlab-ci-3p1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stack-labs/securing-access-to-scaleway-elements-api-keys-from-gitlab-ci-3p1h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T11:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many api keys are stored per day as variables in the Gitlab CI configuration? 
When a Scaleway Elements API Key is saved in Gitlab, we face all the security issues of storing credentials outside of the cloud infrastructure: Key rotation, age, destruction, location, etc.
There are 2 common reasons for developers to store GCP credentials in Gitlab CI:
They use shared runners.
They use specific/group runners deployed in a Scaleway Kubernetes Kapsule cluster but do not use (or do not know about) Gitlab additional configurations.
The alternative that Gitlab CI proposes for users is to mount a secret volume to the runner pods that are created for each build.
Install the following tools:
Scaleway cli
kubectl 
Helm
And create 2 projects in your Scaleway organization:
devops
development
The fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chabane R.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level up compliance confidence with AWS Config]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/level-up-compliance-confidence-with-aws-config-15ne</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/level-up-compliance-confidence-with-aws-config-15ne"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T11:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the ever increasing adoption of moving workloads to public cloud providers like AWS, satisfying regulatory compliance has emerged as one of the most demanding requirements for businesses that operate on the cloud.
As an AWS customer, this means that you need to establish a proper governance model for your business operations to continue, particularly for those that operate under specific regulations. This "model", is conceptualised under AWS Control Tower as a collection of guardrails. A guardrail is simply a rule that describes what is allowed or disallowed in your AWS account. Now, a guardrail can be of two forms, a preventive guardrail or a detective guardrail.
A preventive guardrail basically enforces a policy, such as using SCP to deny IAM users to specific APIs, so that those us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Wu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular UI Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/akhromieiev/angular-ui-kits-2h63</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/akhromieiev/angular-ui-kits-2h63"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T10:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I created a table of UI kits for an Angular framework. There is no specific order, I have put them in the order I found.
The full table:
https://akhromieiev.github.io/angular-ui-kits/
Feel free to edit this table:
https://github.com/akhromieiev/angular-ui-kits/edit/main/docs/index.md]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Akhromieiev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a RAID Array. Building a PC and Selecting Hardware for RAID]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-array-building-a-pc-and-selecting-hardware-for-raid-l3o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-create-a-raid-array-building-a-pc-and-selecting-hardware-for-raid-l3o"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T07:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this article to find out how to setup a RAID 5 array at home, what important things to consider when choosing computer parts for a RAID system, how to build a computer and configure a RAID array.
All modern motherboards come equipped with an integrated RAID controller, and top models may have several such controllers on board. That’s a different question, though, if such integrated controllers in consumer-class motherboards are ever used by an average user. Anyway, some motherboards do give a chance to setup a RAID array right inside your home PC.
Below are brief recommendations on building a RAID array on a home computer and a practical tutorial on assembling a PC for RAID.
YouTube: 




  
  
  PC parts


First of all, you need to decide on the purposes for which you want to build a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular vs Blazor? A decision aid for web developers in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/katholder/angular-vs-blazor-a-decision-aid-for-web-developers-in-2022-5e50</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/katholder/angular-vs-blazor-a-decision-aid-for-web-developers-in-2022-5e50"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T06:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent times, if you were a C# developer who wanted to build code for browsers, you had to resort to JavaScript, the most widely used programming language in the world. However, the web development industry is rapidly evolving, and developers no longer need to rely on JavaScript to create high-end online apps. Blazor is making it possible to run.NET in the browser without the need for add-ons or plugins, due to a technique called WebAssembly.
This blog will examine the current status of Blazor, its features, and its preparedness for production use, before comparing it to one of the most popular frameworks, Angular.
Here is why you should choose Angular for your next web development project.
What is Blazor?
Blazor is a new Microsoft web framework that lets programmers build browser code …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kat Holder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React.useEffect Hook – Common Problems and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>61686f8b80d82d07c45a4e4a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/most-common-react-useeffect-problems-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T22:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React hooks have been around for a while now. Most developers have gotten pretty comfortable with how they work and their common use cases. But there is one useEffect gotcha that a lot of us keep falling for. The use caseLet's start with a simple scenario. We are building a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone Downloads Folder – Where are my Downloads? iOS and iPad]]></title>
        <id>615d559e0d91c9077974d3ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/iphone-downloads-folder-where-are-my-downloads-ios-and-ipad/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T21:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone and iPad both have an app called Files where you can locate all of your files from services including iCloud Drive, Dropbox, and more.  If you want to access the Downloads folder, you can find it inside the Files app. In this article, I will show you how to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get into BIOS in Windows 10 – BIOS Setup PC Guide]]></title>
        <id>6167f81c80d82d07c45a4630</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-into-bios-in-windows-10-bios-setup-pc-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T21:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BIOS stands for Basic Input/Output System. It is embedded into computers as a motherboard chip and is primarily responsible for booting the computer system.  Apart from booting up your computer, BIOS is responsible for a lot of other functionality behind the scenes – like managing data flow between an operating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You NEED to know awk]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vineet192/you-need-to-know-awk-33b1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vineet192/you-need-to-know-awk-33b1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T20:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Brief


awk is a powerfull command line tool found included in all modern GNU/linux distributions. It is often excluded from beginner level Linux tutorials, where more fundamental commands like cd , pwd, ls etc are given more priority, and rightfully so. One must have a good grasp on the basic commmand line tools in order  to harness the full power of awk. 
awk in essence is a pattern scanning and processing language, emphasis on the language part because awk possesses functionality akin to most mainstream programming languages. 
awk loves tabulated data. So to begin with, you'll need a piece of text represented as columns delimited by some common character. You see this pattern often in shells, for instance, the ls -l command that prints file information delimited by a space :
ls -l   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vineet Kalghatgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make an NFT in 14 Lines of Code]]></title>
        <id>6163d60c804854468fda82ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-an-nft/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T17:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High-profile celebrities like Jay-Z and Snoop Dog are getting into NFTs. With the cheapest CryptoPunk selling for 103 ETH (~360,000 USD at the time of this article), it is an excellent time for us developers to learn more about the engineering behind them to start building things. At the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start an Open Source Project on GitHub – Tips from Building My Trending Repo]]></title>
        <id>615da5e40d91c9077974dd6a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-an-open-source-project-on-github-tips-from-building-my-trending-repo/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T17:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers around the world use GitHub to share their projects with the global developer community.  In this article, I'll give you some opinionated tips to help you build a great open-source project you can start using. You can also use these tips for building hackathon projects. Quite recently I ended]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rotate Screen in Windows 10 – How to Flip Your Monitor Orientation 90 Degrees]]></title>
        <id>6162db83804854468fda7b4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rotate-screen-in-windows-10-how-to-flip-your-monitor-orientation-90-degrees/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 has a built-in feature that lets you flip or rotate your monitor screen just like you can do on your smartphone.  In this article, I will show you how to flip or rotate the monitor of your Windows 10 machine in several orientations such as reverse-landscape, portrait, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bash solution for docker and iptables conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/garutilorenzo/a-bash-solution-for-docker-and-iptables-conflict-5gac</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/garutilorenzo/a-bash-solution-for-docker-and-iptables-conflict-5gac"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever tried to setup firewall rules on the same machine where docker daemon is running you may have noticed that docker (by default) manipulate your iptables chains.
Docker is utilizing the iptables "nat" to resolve packets from and to its containers and "filter" for isolation purposes, by default docker creates some chains in your iptables setup:
sudo iptables -L

Chain INPUT (policy ACCEPT)
target     prot opt source               destination         

Chain FORWARD (policy DROP)
target     prot opt source               destination         
DOCKER-USER  all  --  anywhere             anywhere            
DOCKER-ISOLATION-STAGE-1  all  --  anywhere             anywhere            
ACCEPT     all  --  anywhere             anywhere             ctstate RELATED,ESTABLISHED
DOCKER     …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorenzo Garuti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Four Node.js and Express.js Projects]]></title>
        <id>61683f7180d82d07c45a4893</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-six-node-js-and-express-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T15:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js and Express.js are popular technologies used for JavaScript backend web development. We just released a 10-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will show you how to create four projects using Node and Express. John Smilga developed this course. John is one of the more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353057</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/different-degrees-of-custom-property-usage/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T14:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One way to work with Custom Properties is to think of them as design tokens. Colors, spacings, fonts, and whatnot. You set them at the root of the page and use them throughout your CSS. Very useful, and the classic …
The post Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Analytics Made Simple With Cumul.io Integrations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353243</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/embedded-analytics-made-simple-with-cumul-io-integrations/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T14:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Browse through SaaS communities on Twitter, LinkedIn, Reddit, Discord, you name it and you’ll see a common theme appear in many of them. That theme can go by many names: BI, analytics, insights and …
The post Embedded Analytics Made Simple With Cumul.io Integrations appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cumul.io</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart CSS Solutions For Common UI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS has probably never been more fun and exciting than it is today. In this post we’ll take a look at common problems and use cases we all have to face in our work and how to solve them with modern CSS. If you’re interested, we’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Awesome Linux Themes For Your Inspiration 🎨😍]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/18-awesome-linux-themes-for-your-inspiration-2ld5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/18-awesome-linux-themes-for-your-inspiration-2ld5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T09:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other day I was browsing Reddit and bookmarked some neat custom-made, one-of-a-kind interfaces from fellow Unix users.
I decided to share my findings, so you can get some inspiration, too.
To find out the configuration details of each setup, click on the author username. That will take you to the original post with detailed info.
u/r1xV3



u/inzar98



u/owl4ce



u/TheSuburbanExorcist



u/WildVibe



u/Marakusa



u/phandungtri



u/woowak01



u/owl4ce



u/SueedBeyg



u/ib_silver20



u/eliverlara



u/L1kbe



u/jom4d4



u/BeerBellyPete



u/H4d35_H1m53Lf



u/jom4d



u/Kuzakor



Hopefully some of these were useful to you and you got some ideas on how you can improve your own design, too.
Also, I would be thankful for RT 🔁.
Source: Reddit (r/unixporn) 🔥🔥
Thread 🧵👇
    
Writing has always been my passion and it gives me pleasure to help and inspire people. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out!
Connect me on Twitter, LinkedIn and GitHub!
Check out my portfolio for all projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep dive Angular : Performance des templates]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/younup/deep-dive-angular-performance-des-templates-2fal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/younup/deep-dive-angular-performance-des-templates-2fal"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T07:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La performance est un sujet récurrent quand on parle de frontend. Les principaux acteurs (librairies/frameworks Javascript) y font tous référence dès la page d'accueil. Angular est connu pour intégrer un bundle plus complet mais plus lourd que ses concurrents directs. Même si ces différentes technologies n'embarquent pas les mêmes fonctionnalités, il reste une problématique à résoudre pour tous : le rendu HTML. Nous allons analyser ensemble le fonctionnement d'Angular dans trois cas précis : la gestion des blocs statiques, la mise à jour du DOM et la mise en cache de valeurs. Cet article se rapproche de ce qui a été fait par Grafikart en comparant Vue à React : https://grafikart.fr/tutoriels/vuejs-perf-react-1941. Certains exemples de code sont volontairement proches pour se donner des élé…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denis SOURON</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Linux to Recover Deleted Files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ravgeetdhillon/how-to-use-linux-to-recover-deleted-files-4p66</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ravgeetdhillon/how-to-use-linux-to-recover-deleted-files-4p66"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T05:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever accidentally deleted important files from your computer and went through these emotions - 🤦😨😱😤🤒?
Well, you’re not the only one. But the good news is there are plenty of ways in Linux to recover deleted files.
I wrote this post to explain exactly the same.
Read the full blog on Adam The Automator.
Thanks for reading 💜
I publish a monthly newsletter in which I share personal stories, things that I am working on, what is happening in the world of tech, and some interesting dev-related posts which I across while surfing on the web.
Connect with me through Twitter • LinkedIn • Github or send me an Email.
— Ravgeet, Full Stack Developer and Technical Content Writer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravgeet Dhillon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonsai Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353719</id>
        <link href="https://bonsaibrowser.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T22:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-browser for research that helps programmers think clearly.
With Bonsai, rather than being like, I’m going to go use my web browser now, you hit Option + Space and it brings up a browser. It’s either full-screen or a …
The post Bonsai Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is Going Gosh-Darned Hog Wild, I Tell Ya What]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352459</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-is-going-gosh-darned-hog-wild-i-tell-ya-what/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T15:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone just sittin’ back watching CSS evolve, it feels like we’re at one of the hottest moments of innovation in CSS history. It was really something when we got flexbox across all browsers, and not terribly long after, grid. …
The post CSS is Going Gosh-Darned Hog Wild, I Tell Ya What appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Less Absolute Positioning With Modern CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353700</id>
        <link href="https://ishadeed.com/article/less-absolute-positioning-modern-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T14:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed blogs the sentiment that we might not need to lean on position: absolute as much as we might have in the past. For one thing: stacking elements. For example, if you have a stack of elements that should …
The post Less Absolute Positioning With Modern CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Live Workshops On Front-End & UX (Oct 2021&ndash;Jan 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like a good interface design challenge? What about accessibility testing and design systems? Or maybe Next.js and advanced CSS? With our new online workshops on front-end & design, we cover all of it. Ah, and [here's what our workshops are like](https://vimeo.com/616485526).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack Developers’ Favorite Frameworks of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353415</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jamstack-developers-favorite-frameworks-of-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T14:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which new framework should I learn this year? Is it time to ditch my CMS? What tools should I pick up if I want to scale my site to an audience of millions? The 2021 Jamstack Community Survey is here …
The post Jamstack Developers’ Favorite Frameworks of 2021 appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Voss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WooCommerce + Google Analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353317</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/woocommerce-google-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T14:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Analytics is powerful analytics software. A common way to use it is to just slap the JavaScript snippet on every page template you have and let it collect basic data about unique visitors and pageviews and such. That’s  useful, …
The post WooCommerce + Google Analytics appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React APIs For Building Flexible Components With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React with JSX is a fantastic tool for making easy-to-use components. Typescript components make it an absolute pleasure for developers to integrate your components into their apps and explore your APIs. Learn about three lesser-known React APIs that can take your components to the next level, and help you build even better React Components in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gaurav Khanna)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging The Gap Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UXPin has recently launched a new feature called “Merge”. This tool aims to break through the chasms of design and development, all while improving the agility and quality our teams expect. This new technology may cause some rethink on how the whole design team and engineering team collaborates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those “Get The App” Banners]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352907</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/those-get-the-app-banners/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T22:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why would a company promote a native app over their perfectly usable website?
We’d have to ask them, I suppose. But it’s hard not to see this push to native as a matter of priorities: that these companies consider native 
…
The post Those “Get The App” Banners appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353431</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cash-tiny-jquery-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T20:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The README for Cash is straightforward:
Cash is an absurdly small jQuery alternative for modern browsers (IE11+) that provides jQuery-style syntax for manipulating the DOM. Utilizing modern browser features to minimize the codebase, developers can use the familiar chainable methods 
…
The post Cash (Tiny jQuery Alternative) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Collaboration With Pull Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352569</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-collaboration-with-pull-requests/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T14:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is part of our “Advanced Git” series. Be sure to follow us on Twitter or sign up for our newsletter to hear about the next articles!
In this third installment of our “Advanced Git” series, we’ll look at …
The post Better Collaboration With Pull Requests appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for ‘Developer Experience’]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353429</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-case-for-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T20:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good essay from Jean Yang. 
What I mean by developer experience is the sum total of how developers interface with their tools, end-to-end, day-in and day-out. Sure, there’s more focus than ever on how developers use and adopt tools, and 
…
The post The Case for ‘Developer Experience’ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353374</id>
        <link href="https://katiekodes.com/jekyll-components-wysiwyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T17:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the pushback from Katie Kodes here. I’ve said in the past that I don’t think server-side languages haven’t quite nailed “building in components” as well as JavaScript has, but hey, this is a good point:
1. Any basic 
…
The post Jekyll doesn’t do components? Liar! appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353066</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-tennis-trivia-app-with-next-js-and-netlify/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we will be learning how to build a tennis trivia app using Next.js and Netlify. This technology stack has become my go-to on many projects. It allows for rapid development and easy deployment.
Without further ado let’s jump in!…
The post Building a Tennis Trivia App With Next.js and Netlify appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brenley Dueck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353062</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-google-analytics-and-plausible-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw this blog post the other day: 58% of Hacker News, Reddit and tech-savvy audiences block Google Analytics. That’s an enticing title to me. I’ve had Google Analytics on this site literally from the day I launched it. …
The post Comparing Google Analytics and Plausible Numbers appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Search Functionality In Your Nuxt App Using Algolia InstantSearch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/search-functionality-nuxt-app-algolia-instantsearch/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many websites have some sort of search feature because it helps users navigate through their content easily. Implementing it the right way can be tricky and might not give a good user experience. In this tutorial, we will be integrating Algolia, a popular and powerful search service for the best experience on our Nuxt site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Miracle Onyenma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time Of Transition (October 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-october-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your desktop ready for fall and the upcoming Halloween season with a fresh batch of desktop wallpapers. Created with love by designers and artists from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for October 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Modern Image Formats: AVIF And WebP]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/modern-image-formats-avif-webp/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-29T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll highlight how modern image formats (AVIF or WebP) can improve compression by up to 50% and deliver better quality per-byte while still looking visually appealing. We’ll compare what’s possible at high-quality, low-quality and file-size targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Accessibility Of Your Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/improving-accessibility-of-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can find Markdown in many places on the Internet. This article covers different aspects of Markdown and how it interacts with other technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>