<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-19T01:03:40.899Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-19T01:03:40.899Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Projects for New Developers – What to Build to Get Coding Experience]]></title>
        <id>614641bf852f4307d373021f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-projects-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a new developer, you're probably familiar with the “Experience Paradox”. It describes the frustrating cycle many of us go through when we're trying to get our first developer jobs: To get a job, you need "work experience". But to get "work experience", you need a job...! Job requires]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubuntu Focus M2 Linux Laptop Review]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mitchellclong/kubuntu-focus-m2-linux-laptop-review-4h3e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mitchellclong/kubuntu-focus-m2-linux-laptop-review-4h3e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T23:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically a Linux machine is a mostly do-it-yourself (DIY) endeavor. You’re usually on your own installing an operating system (OS), regardless of whether you’re using a pre-built machine or custom build. However, there are plenty of off-the-shelf Linux laptops and desktops available. The Kubuntu Focus is an outstanding Linux laptop. It comes with the Ubuntu-based Kubuntu Linux distribution (distro) pre-loaded, boasts an impressive spec sheet, and exceptional build quality. This combination makes is a great choice for programmers, gamers, and anyone switching from Windows or macOS to Linux. But is the Kubuntu Focus M2 right for you? Find out in our hands-on review!

The Kubuntu Focus M2 is a Linux laptop. It ships with the Kubuntu Linux distro pre-installed and, as such, runs Ubuntu with t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moe Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Azure Resources using Spacelift]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/spacelift/managing-azure-resources-using-spacelift-36oh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/spacelift/managing-azure-resources-using-spacelift-36oh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T23:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post I want to show how easy it is to create a Spacelift Stack that manages Azure resources. To keep things simple, I’m going to assume that you already know what Spacelift can do, and the basics of creating and running Stacks, but if not check out our terraform-starter repo that walks you through the process of setting up an account, and getting started.
In order to allow Spacelift to manage Azure resources, we need to do the following:
Create a Service Principal in Azure with the correct ARM permissions to manage our resources.
Create a Stack in Spacelift that uses the Azure provider.
Give our Stack the credentials for our Service Principal.
All of the information you need to configure the Azure provider can be found here. This post just explains how to combine that information w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Connelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily Use SSL on Nginx With Certbot]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/slashtechno/ssl-on-nginx-using-certbot-24hi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/slashtechno/ssl-on-nginx-using-certbot-24hi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T23:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Install Certbot



  
  
  Full instructions are here


To install Certbot, you should have Snap installed as well. For instructions, follow this tutorial.

Then, update snap
sudo snap install core; sudo snap refresh core
sudo snap install --classic certbot
sudo ln -s /snap/bin/certbot /usr/bin/certbot
To use Certbot you should have server_name in your Ngnix config. For example, this is a sample of how my Nginx config file looked like before Certbot.
server{
        root /home/pi/website;
        server_name example.slashtechno.com;
}

Once you have the config set up properly, restart nginx. On most systems it will be the following command.
sudo service nginx restart  
sudo certbot certonly --nginx  
sudo certbot delete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>slashtechno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great node version management]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devinrhode2/great-node-version-management-33aj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devinrhode2/great-node-version-management-33aj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T22:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a package.json:
{
  "...": "...",
  "engines-comment": [
    "When new node/yarn versions are released, you may see these errors:",
    "  engine \"yarn|node\" is incompatible with this module.",
    "Just bump version numbers below:"
  ],
  "engines": {
    "node": "16.13.x",
    "yarn": "1.22.15"
  },
  "node-version-rationale": [
    "Give some flexibility by ignoring patch updates",
    "but otherwise force developers to update node every couple 1-4 months"
  ],
  "yarn-version-rationale": [
    "Exact yarn version helps us produce consistent yarn.lock files"
  ]
}

Our pipeline is set always try and use the latest lts.
Our pipeline will run:
# Always run install+build:ci with latest LTS, to see output
# But verify engines at very end
yarn config set ignore-engines true

yarn in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devin Rhode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Developer's Guide TO Building Notification Systems: Part 3 - Routing & Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/courier/the-developers-guide-to-building-notification-systems-part-3-routing-preferences-3g27</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/courier/the-developers-guide-to-building-notification-systems-part-3-routing-preferences-3g27"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T22:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your CTO handed you a project to revamp or build your product’s notification system recently. You realized the complexity of this project around the same time as you discovered that there’s not a lot of information online on how to do it. Companies like LinkedIn, Uber, and Slack have large teams of over 25 employees working just on notifications, but smaller companies like yours don’t have that luxury. So how can you meet the same level of quality with a team of one? This is the third post in our series on how you, a developer, can build or improve the best notification system for your company. It follows the first post about identifying user requirements and designing with scalability and reliability in mind. In this piece, we will learn about setting up routing and preferences.
Notificat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Zayner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iniciando con Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tris460/iniciando-con-docker-2lfi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tris460/iniciando-con-docker-2lfi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker te permite construir, distribuir y ejecutar cualquier app en cualquier lugar, mediante contenedores.
https://www.docker.com/ y descargar 'Docker desktop' y crear una cuenta en DockerHub.
Contenedores: Dónde va a correr la app, sirve para poder compartir las imagenes con otros servidores, computadoras, etc. Es una agrupación de procesos aislados del sistema.
Imágenes: Encapsulación del contenedor a compartir.
Volúmenes de datos: Archivos del sistema. 
Redes: Permiten la comunicación entre servidores.
docker login Inicia sesión en DockerHub para poder usarlo.
docker run <contenedor> Ejecuta el contenedor.



--name <nombre> Le asigna un nombre al contenedor.
--mount src=<nombre_volumen>,dst=<ruta_contenedor> Asigna un volumen al contenedor, como -v.
-i Abre el modo interactivo.
-t Eje…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beatriz Martínez Pérez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOU.com - the private search engine that summarizes the web for you]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gideononyewuenyi/youcom-the-private-search-engine-that-summarizes-the-web-for-you-35bn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gideononyewuenyi/youcom-the-private-search-engine-that-summarizes-the-web-for-you-35bn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just used a search engine that summarizes information on the web while protecting user privacy and saving time and money with no ad targeting.
welcome to the future of web search - You.com
An AI-driven search engine set to put YOU first!
Richard Socher the CEO of You.com made an announcement on twitter about the launched of You.com, a private search engine that summarizes the web for you.
It didn't take me up to 3 minutes to setup my account and make it my default search, been the best experience of search.
If you are looking for a search engine to summarize the web for you while protecting your privacy and saving you time and money with no ad targeting.
you should check out You.com
Thank me later!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Onyewuenyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps & SRE Words Matter: How Our Language has Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blameless/devops-sre-words-matter-how-our-language-has-evolved-dp5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blameless/devops-sre-words-matter-how-our-language-has-evolved-dp5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the tech world changes, language changes with it. New technologies will always introduce new terms and descriptions to provide clear understanding. For example, the emergence of the cloud introduced language to describe the changing relationship between servers and clients. Then, of course, product providers will also dictate how their products are to be described, i.e. describing services as “cloud-native”.
On other occasions, language changes through deliberate effort to influence behavior. Thought leaders will often invent alternative words to describe existing ideas in order to effect cultural change. Even a slight change in diction can massively affect one’s engagement, attitude, and even their worldview. In this blog, we’ll look at how language colours how we perceive our environm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Arnott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[angularday report]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vanrado/angularday-report-1nfh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vanrado/angularday-report-1nfh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 2021, seems that pandemic situation is still not getting better but on the other hand several frontend or javascript focused conferences provide online attendance. So, why not visit the Italian one and meet several known and impressive people from the dev community :-)
AngularDay


This Italian Angular international conference was organized by GrUSP community on November 12th 2021. The event happened online, on Hopin easy-to-use web platform for conferences.
There were various known speakers from the Angular community and also the official Angular Core Team joined (Emma Twersky, Mark Thompson, Jessica Janiuk) in the last part.
The atmosphere of the conference was easy going and was moderated by Giulia Tosato, Tomas Trajan and also Tracy Lee joined in the last part.
I decided to hi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Radovan Racak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React SketchBoard DevLog #1 - Drawing with mouse, color and width selection and panning.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/react-sketchboard-devlog-1-drawing-with-mouse-color-and-width-selection-and-panning-5h3o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/react-sketchboard-devlog-1-drawing-with-mouse-color-and-width-selection-and-panning-5h3o"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T18:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I started developing a react library for drawing in a browser. It turned out that it's not as trivial as it seemed and there is a lot of cool stuff and interesting problems there. So I decided to do a DevLog and share those thing with you.
I hope you'll enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NordicBeaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Compliance: Fable’s Mission to Improve Digital Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/beyond-compliance-fables-mission-to-improve-digital-accessibility-42c7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/beyond-compliance-fables-mission-to-improve-digital-accessibility-42c7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time we recognize that the way we build digital products is broken. That's because the products we use today represent the people who build them more than the people who use them.
There is a digital divide between the experiences of people with disabilities and people who are able-bodied. Bridging this divide is about more than compliance or checking a box.
Fable is helping companies practice accessibility at scale with the goal of operationalizing accessibility in the same way we already do for things like DesignOps and DevOps.
Listen as Fable's CEO and Co-founder, Alwar Pillai, and Fable's Engineering Manager, Perry Trinier, talk about the importance of inclusive design, the need for digital accessibility and how to integrate accessibility into the development process.
Fable's founding story and mission
The need and importance of inclusive design
How engineering orgs can improve accessibility
Making your tech stack more accessible
Why everyone benefits from inclusive design





  
  
  Join the Dev Interrupted Community


With over 2000 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>

Full transcription available at DevInterrupted.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insecure Direct Object Reference & How to Protect Against it]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/warrant/insecure-direct-object-reference-how-to-protect-against-it-7li</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/warrant/insecure-direct-object-reference-how-to-protect-against-it-7li"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) is one of the most common forms of broken access control which OWASP recently listed as the number one application security issue in 2021. A quick search for "IDOR" on Hacker One's Hacktivity feed shows that many top tech companies (and even the U.S. Department of Defense) have fallen victim to IDOR, in some cases paying out well over $10,000 per bug bounty. In this post, I'll explain what IDOR is, what causes it, and ways to protect your application against it.
IDOR is an access control vulnerability that occurs when an application uses an identifier for direct access to an object in a database but doesn't perform proper access control or authorization checks before querying or modifying the database. This often results in vulnerabilities that allow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Kajla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stress and Mental Health in Tech – What I learned from Dr. Jennifer Akullian&#x27;s freeCodeCamp Tech Talk]]></title>
        <id>619392bd11d3cb08287a6f36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/stress-and-mental-health-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People in the tech industry face mental health issues like depression and anxiety every day, all around the world. But what can we do about it? In this article, I will talk about what I learned from Dr. Jennifer Akullian's freeCodeCamp Tech Talk and share her tips for reducing your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Cognito Pricing and Features – 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/aws-cognito-pricing-and-features-2021-1ef6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/aws-cognito-pricing-and-features-2021-1ef6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Amazon Cognito?


It is a service introduced by AWS (Amazon Web Services) which allows users to add authentication to projects, it allows users to sign in with different social identity providers, and scales to millions of users and requests.
It supports access management standards like OAuth and SAML, users do not have to worry about setting up a UI for authentication as it provides a built-in UI that can be integrated with any application very quickly, this UI can also be customized according to specific requirements of the company.
AWS Cognito Pricing


**DISCLAIMER**
As of today when writing this post, which is Thursday, November 18, 2021, GMT+0530 (India Standard Time), this is the pricing model for Amazon Cognito.
For Cognito User Pools Amazon charges on the basis of how many…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivang Chauhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailing a Postcard with JavaScript Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lob/mailing-a-postcard-with-javascript-part-1-175h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lob/mailing-a-postcard-with-javascript-part-1-175h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Postcard with Lob and Node.js


Lob’s Print & Mail and Address Verification APIs enable developers to interact with Lob’s services programmatically. You can mail a postcard or letter to your customers at critical points in their journey as easily as you might send an email. These physical reminders help you keep in touch with clients, and encourage clients to keep purchasing your products and services.   
In this three-part tutorial, we’ll create a postcard template, verify our recipient’s address, send a postcard, and track it along its journey. We’ll create a Javascript application to do all this, so our users can access everything they need in one place. 
Complete code for tutorial available on GitHub.
To follow along, you’ll need your own Lob account. You can sign up here an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Customize Your Windows 10 Taskbar to Be More Productive]]></title>
        <id>6196275811d3cb08287a850e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-customize-your-windows10-taskbar-for-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On your computer desktop, you can use the taskbar to help you monitor applications, check battery life, and more.  Being able to customize what your task bar can do is crucial for boosting your productivity. And there's more to it than just monitoring applications.  In this guide, I will show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on working with the CDK and serverless architecture in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealdakotal/some-thoughts-on-working-with-the-cdk-and-serverless-architecture-in-aws-3fm8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealdakotal/some-thoughts-on-working-with-the-cdk-and-serverless-architecture-in-aws-3fm8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published to dakotalewallen.me
A lot of grey area exists between SAM and the CDK. SAM makes it nice to verify things locally before pushing out to AWS, CDK doesn't provide anything other than seeing your initial stack. So the dev process for the cdk looks like, read docs -> write js -> deploy to CloudFormation (typically a few minutes for anything more than a s3 bucket) -> manually verify  -> repeat. Not a fast process at all. Honestly if you could just take the support for local debugging from SAM and give it to the CDK it'd be near perfect.
CDK documentation is pretty confusing. Somewhat understandable given how young it is, but still. Also doesn't help that a lot of the guides that exist are also outdated. Some even coming from AWS themselves. There's also a lot modules in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dakota Lewallen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on working with the CDK and serverless architecture in AWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealdakotal/some-thoughts-on-working-with-the-cdk-and-serverless-architecture-in-aws-3fm8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealdakotal/some-thoughts-on-working-with-the-cdk-and-serverless-architecture-in-aws-3fm8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published to dakotalewallen.me
A lot of grey area exists between SAM and the CDK. SAM makes it nice to verify things locally before pushing out to AWS, CDK doesn't provide anything other than seeing your initial stack. So the dev process for the cdk looks like, read docs -> write js -> deploy to CloudFormation (typically a few minutes for anything more than a s3 bucket) -> manually verify  -> repeat. Not a fast process at all. Honestly if you could just take the support for local debugging from SAM and give it to the CDK it'd be near perfect.
CDK documentation is pretty confusing. Somewhat understandable given how young it is, but still. Also doesn't help that a lot of the guides that exist are also outdated. Some even coming from AWS themselves. There's also a lot modules in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dakota Lewallen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Comprehension in Python]]></title>
        <id>6193c41c11d3cb08287a70ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-comprehension-in-python-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are a helpful and frequently used feature in Python.  And list comprehension gives you a way to create lists while writing more elegant code that is easy to read.  In this beginner-friendly article, I'll give an overview of how list comprehension works in Python. I'll also show plenty of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aumentar la productividad con extensiones en Gnome]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luismorenomx/aumentar-la-productividad-con-extensiones-en-gnome-4b9e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luismorenomx/aumentar-la-productividad-con-extensiones-en-gnome-4b9e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hay muchas extensiones en Gnome que son de mi agrado y creo que las de este listado son mis favoritas.
Compartir estos recursos es porque tengo intensión en todo momento de incrementar la productividad a la hora de estar desarrollando software.
No sé si en otros entornos de escritorio se pueda mejorar la productividad, lo que sí sé es que en Gnome ha ido mejorando todo poco a poco y se agradece.
Caffeine- Disable the screensaver and auto suspend
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/3997/app-grid-tweaks/)
Desktop Icons- Add icons to the desktop
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/779/clipboard-indicator/)
Multi Monitors AddOn- Add multiple monitors overview and panel for gnome-shell.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/921/multi-monitors-add-on/)
Tilix Dropdown- Launch Tilix in Quake mode.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/1185/tilix-dropdown/)
Dash to dock- Moves the dash out of the overview transforming it in a dock.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/307/dash-to-dock/)
OpenWeather- Display weather information from https://openweathermap.org/
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/750/openweather/)
App Grid Tweaks- Customize the application grid view.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/3997/app-grid-tweaks/)
Clipboard Indicator- Adds a clipboard indicator to the top panel, and caches clipboard history.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/779/clipboard-indicator/)
Custom Hot Corners- Customizable hot corners.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/1362/custom-hot-corners/)
Desktop Scroller- Switch between desktops scrolling at the upper edge of the screen, including in overview.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/3709/desktop-scroller-gnome-338/)
gTile- Tile windows on a grid.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/28/gtile/)
Screenshot Tool- Conveniently create, copy, store and upload screenshots.
https://extensions.gnome.org/extension/1112/screenshot-tool/)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Moreno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sending Audio Files to Your Express.js Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deepgram/sending-audio-files-to-your-expressjs-server-j03</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deepgram/sending-audio-files-to-your-expressjs-server-j03"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T16:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at Deepgram, we work with audio files all the time. We have SDKs that make it easy for developers to send audio files to our API. But it's also really useful to know how to post an audio file to a backend server in case you ever find yourself needing to do that. So I thought I would introduce a simple way for Node developers to take an audio file that is uploaded through the browser and send it to a backend Express.js server.
Let's start on the backend with our Express.js server. Express.js is a Node.js framework that provides us with so many useful methods and middleware, making working in Node that much easier.
We'll set up the server and implement a middleware package called Multer that helps us handle different file types that we receive to our post endpoint.
We can start our proj…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SandraRodgers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My series on database design <WIP>]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sukrosono/my-series-on-database-design-46h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sukrosono/my-series-on-database-design-46h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLIsQ7ns9vF5BlSWHzSDfrUGrRApl_rKUc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adi Prasetyo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prisma Data Platform's PlanetScale Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/planetscale/prisma-data-platforms-planetscale-integration-j3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/planetscale/prisma-data-platforms-planetscale-integration-j3d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we often want to build faster, but that comes with tradeoffs that we have to deal with in the long run. At PlanetScale, we want to empower developers to be able to build without having to worry about issues of database scalability as their application grows. Similarly, Prisma wants to empower developers to efficiently work with data while making fewer errors. 
PlanetScale and Prisma have partnered up to allow developers to create PlanetScale databases in the new Prisma Data Platform. You can have a starter database schema and a live PlanetScale database ready to accept thousands of new database connections with a few clicks.
The Prisma Data Platform provides you with application templates with Prisma data schemas, so you don't even have to think about a data model to get started. Once set up, you can deploy to Vercel immediately or use the Prisma Data Explorer and Query Builder to explore your PlanetScale database.
Try out creating your first PlanetScale database with one of the application templates and experience the power of Prisma with PlanetScale for yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>etnoctua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configurar virtualhost en Apache y Debian 10]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luismorenomx/configurar-virtualhost-en-apache-y-debian-10-3p9e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luismorenomx/configurar-virtualhost-en-apache-y-debian-10-3p9e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hay veces que desarrollamos más de un proyecto web en la misma computadora y para eso necesitamos configurar nuestro equipo de tal modo que se puedan tener varios proyectos dentro de la misma carpeta, pero con diferente ruta de acceso desde el navegador y para eso yo realice lo siguiente.
Copiar el archivo 000-default.conf a otro (en este caso será blog.local) con el nombre blog.local.conf
sudo cp /etc/apache2/sites-available/000-default.conf /etc/apache2/sites-available/blog.local.conf 

Editar el archivo blog.local.conf y dejarlo como a continuación se muestra (recuerda cambiar 'user' por tu usuario local).
<VirtualHost *:80>  
   ServerName blog.local    
   ServerAlias blog.local   
   ServerAdmin webmaster@localhost  
   DocumentRoot /home/user/Server/blog  
   ErrorLog ${APACHE_LOG_D…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Moreno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ดู document ของ Bash builtin commands ผ่านคำสั่ง help]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iporsut/duu-document-khng-bash-builtin-commands-phaankhamsang-help-559m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iporsut/duu-document-khng-bash-builtin-commands-phaankhamsang-help-559m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[พวกคำสั่งที่เป็น builtin ของ Bash บางครั้งใช้ man เพื่อดู manual ไม่ได้ แต่ Bash เองเตรียมคำสั่งชื่อว่า help มาไว้เพื่อดู document ของพวก builtin commands เหล่านี้ได้
ถ้าเราสั่ง help เฉยๆจะขึ้นลิสต์ command ที่สามารถดู document ได้ เช่น

ถ้าเราอยากดู document ของแต่ละ command ก็สั่ง help ตามด้วยชื่อ command นั้นๆเช่น
help echo

 
คำสั่ง help ช่วยได้เยอะเลยยิ่งถ้าต้องเขียน shell script เพราะบางคำสั่งเราใช้ใน script บ่อยกว่าที่จะสั่งตรงๆเช่น if หรือ for
help for


help if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Weerasak Chongnguluam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Git Tools—Interactive Rebase, Cherry-Picking, Reflog, and more]]></title>
        <id>6196642611d3cb08287a8688</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/advanced-git-interactive-rebase-cherry-picking-reflog-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a software developer, you likely use Git all the time. But many developers don't use advanced git commands that can speed up their worflow. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use advanced git commands. Tobias Günther]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Technology: AI Trends That Matter for Business]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oleksiitsymbal/artificial-intelligence-technology-ai-trends-that-matter-for-business-2a8e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oleksiitsymbal/artificial-intelligence-technology-ai-trends-that-matter-for-business-2a8e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to 2020’s McKinsey Global Survey on artificial intelligence (AI), in 2020 more than 50% of companies have adopted AI in at least one business unit or function, so we witness the emergence of new AI trends. Organizations apply AI tools to generate more value, increase revenue and customer loyalty. AI leading companies invest at least 20% of their earnings before interest and taxes (EBIT) in AI. This figure may increase as COVID-19 is accelerating digitization. Lockdowns resulted in a massive surge of online activity and an intensive AI adoption in business, education, administration, social interaction, etc.
This article aims to overview new and current AI trends that emerged in 2020 and are still increasing in 2021. Based on trends, companies can make projections of the AI future…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OleksiiTsymbal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide on How to Unzip Files in Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudytech147/guide-on-how-to-unzip-files-in-linux-4oee</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudytech147/guide-on-how-to-unzip-files-in-linux-4oee"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it's consistently dangerous when we work with sudo advantages in a Linux machine as you approach all the setup and framework records, and if you mess up with them, your entire framework may crash. So we encourage you to run the underneath referenced orders with absolute attention to detail.
Additionally, to utilize the unfasten order, it's required to have the unfasten bundle introduced on our Linux machine. You can basically utilize the bundle administrator of any famous Linux circulation you are rushing to introduce the unfasten bundle. Notwithstanding, the vast majority of the Linux appropriations come pre-introduced with this bundle.




If you are using Fedora, CentOS, etc. and you have yum package manager, you can use:




  
  
  How to Unzip Files in Linux?


When we run the unzip command without any options, in the most native form, it simply extracts all the files and directories inside the current directory that you are in.




Output Suppression
You can see that the unzip command enlists the details of the files that it is extracting from the archived file. To avoid printing the details and suppress the output, we can simply use the quiet (-q) option along with the unzip command.




If you want to extract them to a different directory, you can use the -d option and specify the path to the destination directory. Please note that if you don’t have write access to the destination directory, you can use the sudo command to get the root privileges.



If you want to unzip a file that is password-protected, you can use the -P option along with the unzip command.




However, typing the password as plain text in the terminal (command line) could be insecure. What you can do is simply extract the zipped file in a normal manner. When it tries to unzip the files and finds a file with a password, it will automatically prompt you to input the password.




To conclude this detailed and comprehensive article, we discussed how to unzip files in Linux using the unzip command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cloudytech147</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animate your Angular App using Motion One]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/animate-your-angular-app-using-motion-one-4bg3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/animate-your-angular-app-using-motion-one-4bg3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motion One is a new animation library built on the Web Animations API. If you have used Popmotion or Greensock before, this library's syntax should look very familiar.
In this blog post, I will show you how to use Motion One in an Angular application. I will walk you through the installation process, create a simple animation, and use Motion One's spring and timeline features.
Check out a live demo I've created that you can interact with as part of my Angular Animation Explorer.
First, we will need to add Motion One's dependency via npm using the following command.
npm install --save motion

If you run into any typings issue from the library, try adding skipLibCheck: true to your tsconfig.json.

To animate an element from your template, you will need to give it an id so you can access them…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Juan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning and Elasticsearch empowering great marketplaces]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/filiphaftek/machine-learning-and-elasticsearch-empowering-great-marketplaces-1f47</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/filiphaftek/machine-learning-and-elasticsearch-empowering-great-marketplaces-1f47"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Speed is the key factor of every online business in a modern world. Buying and selling cars on classified marketplaces also follows this trend. On Publi24, a general classifieds portal in Romania, part of Russmedia Equity Parters group, we are providing our customers a used car marketplace. We focus on the quality of posted listings and enable fast and precise search options to help our users find their dream car. Because the number of posted ads is constantly increasing, our product team conducted a research on how to improve customer satisfaction by making the prices of the car listings more accurate. Our goal is for the sellers and buyers of Publi24 to make great deals on both sides.
Machine Learning technology a try, but also wanted to experiment with one of the most pow…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Filip Haftek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend SvgIcon sizes in React Material UI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karladler/extend-svgicon-sizes-in-react-material-ui-44f8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karladler/extend-svgicon-sizes-in-react-material-ui-44f8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using React Material UI you have the opportunity to use any SVG file like an icon. To do so, you just wrap it into the SvgIcon component.
An example for your HomeIcon component might look like this:
import React from 'react';
import { SvgIcon, SvgIconProps } from '@mui/material';
import { ReactComponent as HomeSvg } from '../../assets/Icons/Home.svg';

function HomeIcon(props: SvgIconProps) {
  return (
    <SvgIcon component={HomeSvg} viewBox="0 0 24 24" {...props} />
  );
}

export default HomeIcon;

Importing svg files as react components required svgr, otherwise you would need to use the SVG code as children of SvgIcon
With SvgIcon you have the possibility to set the fontSize attribute to "small", "inherit", "large" or "medium", but what if we if we would need more of this?
<HomeIcon fontSize="small" />
<HomeIcon />
<HomeIcon fontSize="large" />
<HomeIcon sx={{ fontSize: 40 }} />

Here is where component variants come into play.
In our theme we just add a new variant to the MuiSvgIcon component. E.g. we we want an new size called huge we do it like this:
components: {
   MuiSvgIcon: {
      variants: [
        {
          props: { fontSize: 'huge' },
          style: {
            fontSize: '5rem',
          },
        },
      ],
    },
}

That should already work, but when we are using typescript and setting it, the compiler will complain.
<HomeIcon fontSize="huge" />

So we need to extend the interface for the component too:
declare module '@mui/material/SvgIcon' {
  interface SvgIconPropsSizeOverrides {
    huge: true;
  }
}

Just add the above module declaration e.g. to your theme.ts  and that's it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Adler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your SSD Last Longer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-make-your-ssd-last-longer-45pm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-make-your-ssd-last-longer-45pm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this article to find out what Windows features reduce the lifespan of your SSD and how to disable them. If your computer still uses a conventional HDD, it is high time to consider switching to a solid-state drive – SSD. It is going to add a significant boost to your computer or laptop.
Are SSDs so perfect? Well, not exactly. In comparison with HDDs, solid-state drives have certain advantages, the most prominent being the limited number of read/write cycles. It means that the number of erase/write cycles for SSDs is lower than for conventional hard disks. In today’s article, we will try to explain the cause for such deficiency and how you could avoid wearing out the disk more than needed.
The main component of a hard disk (HDD) is the platters where the information is actually written.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to use Conda and when to use Poetry?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oo_pai_7a4947410fc4a570ec/when-to-use-conda-and-when-to-use-poetry-3k72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oo_pai_7a4947410fc4a570ec/when-to-use-conda-and-when-to-use-poetry-3k72"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T12:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi.
I've been fairly extensively using conda for a while now, ditching the old pip + virtualenv habbit of mine, since I'm collaborating with people on a common source code instead of freelancing by myself like the old days, and therefore this question has come to my mind and gone every few weeks.
Have I chosen the correct dependency manager?
A little background: Miniconda + conda environments (yml files) have been a good fit so far. Our projects are products focusing on datascience solutions, and we develop the data science microservice of the product. But we're still in the heavy exploration phase, and have not really stabilized the "MLOps" loop.
So back to the question.
I see many have advocated for the use of Poetry. Can someone explain to me the pros and cons of each approach? Why poetry seems so loved by many, and when should someone consider switching from conda to poetry?
Thanks!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oo Pai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LFX mentorship @ Vitess]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abhaykatheria/lfx-mentorship-vitess-3nmn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abhaykatheria/lfx-mentorship-vitess-3nmn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T12:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer I was fortunate enough to be selected as linux foundation mentee for Vitess which is a CNCF graduated project. 
vitess.io
Vitess is a database clustering system for horizontal scaling of MySQL through generalized sharding.
Sharding is the concept of breaking up data into smaller chunks distributed across separate database nodes.
My aim for the summer was to develop an exhaustive test suite for Vitess's compatibility with Django's model layer.
During this period, I was mentored by a team of engineers from Planetscale who are currently maintaining Vitess. I was part of daily stand-up meetings and was in constant touch with my mentors, who guided me through the whole project. Also I got a chance to be part of community-day for Vitess in which contributors and maintainers from all around the world interacted. 
Sadly, due to an unfortunate event I was unable to work for weeks. But my mentors and the admins at CNCF were kind enough to understand my situation and granted me an extension for the program. And with the help of my mentors i was able to complete the project within the extended deadline.
I learnt a lot during this mentorship program and will continue to contribute more to the project in future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhay Katheria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Kubernetes Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/squadcast/introduction-to-kubernetes-storage-p3n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/squadcast/introduction-to-kubernetes-storage-p3n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T11:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Kubernetes Pods don't store data persistently, it offers different storage components to prevent this data loss. In this blog, learn how Volume works in Kubernetes, how to create it, and how to attach it to the Pod.

Before exploring Kubernetes volumes, let’s first understand Docker. Docker containers are meant to be transient, which means they will only last for a short period. They are called upon when required to process data and are destroyed once finished.
The same is true for the data within the container. The data is destroyed along with the container. To persist data processed by the container, we attach a volume to the containers created. Now even if the container is deleted, the data generated or processed by it remains.
Now let’s look at how it works in the case of Kubernetes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Squadcast Community</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Remove or Change HTTP Server header in NGINX Plus.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/supachai/simple-remove-or-change-http-server-header-in-nginx-plus-5658</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/supachai/simple-remove-or-change-http-server-header-in-nginx-plus-5658"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T11:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First written, I must have remove or change strings value HTTP Server header in NGINX. Excellet, The NGINX Plus have Core functional (Build-in) without third-party dynamic module for solution this case, detial as like below.
Official Document: https://nginx.org/en/docs/http/ngx_http_core_module.html#server_tokens

Example Configuration for nginx.conf
http { 
....
#server_tokens off; 
#server_tokens "Microsoft-IIS/8.5"; 
#server_tokens none; 
server_tokens ""; 
...
 } 

Noted: Uncomment server_tokens lines for each testing case.
Capture Screen of Testing

Thanks for reading my written, Good luck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>supachai jaturaprom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Remove or Change HTTP Server header in NGINX Plus.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/supachai/simple-remove-or-change-http-server-header-in-nginx-plus-5658</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/supachai/simple-remove-or-change-http-server-header-in-nginx-plus-5658"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T11:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First written, I must have remove or change strings value HTTP Server header in NGINX. Excellet, The NGINX Plus have Core functional (Build-in) without third-party dynamic module for solution this case, detial as like below.
Official Document: https://nginx.org/en/docs/http/ngx_http_core_module.html#server_tokens

Example Configuration for nginx.conf
http { 
....
#server_tokens off; 
#server_tokens "Microsoft-IIS/8.5"; 
#server_tokens none; 
server_tokens ""; 
...
 } 

Noted: Uncomment server_tokens lines for each testing case.
Capture Screen of Testing

Thanks for reading my written, Good luck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>supachai jaturaprom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Onion architecture in NestJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amroabdalla00/implementing-onion-architecture-in-nestjs-1k2f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amroabdalla00/implementing-onion-architecture-in-nestjs-1k2f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Onion architecture?


As shown in the picture, onion architecture is a way to structure the code by dividing it into domain-driven design layers. each layer can only access the layer below it throw its interfaces, and then using the dependency inversion principle each interface will be replaced with its class.

Onion Architecture leads to more maintainable applications since it emphasizes separation of concerns throughout the system.” Jeffery Palermo
NestJs is a service-side framework based on NodeJs. NestJs has many built-in features but most importantly for us now is the Dependency Injection and the possibility to add Dependency inversion which is what we need to apply the Onion Architecture.
In the rest of the article, I’ll try to explain the NestJs implementation using a simple …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Tron (TRX) Node With GetBlock: Here’s How It Works]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/getblock/running-tron-trx-node-with-getblock-heres-how-it-works-2co4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/getblock/running-tron-trx-node-with-getblock-heres-how-it-works-2co4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being cutting-edge nodes API connection provider, GetBlock continues its series of articles designed to demonstrate the opportunities of our toolkit. Today let’s get our hands dirty with Tron Network (TRX) that attempts to become a mainstream ‘Ethereum killer’ since 2017.
Tron (Tron Network, Tron Blockchain) was introduced back in 2018 by Justin Sun, an eccentric Chinese American entrepreneur. Tron is developed and maintained by a Singapore-incorporated non-profit Tron Foundation established in July 2017.
At its core, Tron is a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) blockchain built around native cryptocurrency Tronics (TRX). It works not unlike BitShares (BTS) or Eos (EOS): tokenholders lock their tokens in favour of validators in order to share transactional fees with them.
In July, 2018, Tron acquired th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GetBlock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Tron (TRX) Node With GetBlock: Here’s How It Works]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/getblock/running-tron-trx-node-with-getblock-heres-how-it-works-2co4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/getblock/running-tron-trx-node-with-getblock-heres-how-it-works-2co4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being cutting-edge nodes API connection provider, GetBlock continues its series of articles designed to demonstrate the opportunities of our toolkit. Today let’s get our hands dirty with Tron Network (TRX) that attempts to become a mainstream ‘Ethereum killer’ since 2017.
Tron (Tron Network, Tron Blockchain) was introduced back in 2018 by Justin Sun, an eccentric Chinese American entrepreneur. Tron is developed and maintained by a Singapore-incorporated non-profit Tron Foundation established in July 2017.
At its core, Tron is a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) blockchain built around native cryptocurrency Tronics (TRX). It works not unlike BitShares (BTS) or Eos (EOS): tokenholders lock their tokens in favour of validators in order to share transactional fees with them.
In July, 2018, Tron acquired th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GetBlock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Software Development Companies in the USA.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/steven_d_gital/top-10-software-development-companies-in-the-usa-1o86</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/steven_d_gital/top-10-software-development-companies-in-the-usa-1o86"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know the software development industry is one of the fastest-growing industries in the terms of technologies updates. 
Today, where competition is taking place at the top, all small and big enterprises visit top software development companies to develop their digital presence and to transform their business into digital form.
Here, My article will help you to find the best software development companies around the world.
When a business is thinking about running the business on automated mode, looking to improve productivity by streamlining the workflow management - for that hiring a trusted software development company will be the best thing for business. Software development companies with their software experts help small and big enterprises to design their software business appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing an NgRx project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/timdeschryver/testing-an-ngrx-project-4jdo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/timdeschryver/testing-an-ngrx-project-4jdo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitter at @tim_deschryver | Subscribe to the Newsletter | Originally published on timdeschryver.dev.
No intro needed, let's directly dive into some code snippets for each part of the Angular application!
Actions
Reducers
Selectors
Effects


Effects that use Actions and Services
Effect tests rewritten with observer-spy
Effect tests and fake timers
Effects that don't dispatch actions
Effects that use the NgRx Global Store
Effects that use the Angular Router
Components With Global Store
Component Store


Integration tests
Unit tests
Component store unit tests
Component unit tests that use the component store
Conclusion
Let's start with the easiest one, which are the NgRx actions.
A reducer is a (synchronous) pure function that is invoked with the current state and an action.
Bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Deschryver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Custom Angular Schematics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/introduction-to-custom-angular-schematics-1cn7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/introduction-to-custom-angular-schematics-1cn7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T10:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schematics are very useful. They provide us to achieve more in a shorter amount of time. But most significantly used, we can think less about routine stuff which leaves our limited attention span to focus on solving real changes.
Ensure that you have the following packages installed at a global level on your computer. Note that in a real-life development context, you should have some of these local to your project. But for the having well been stable development environment we will install them globally.
node v12.8.0 npm v.6.10.2 @angular-cli (core y cli) v.10 @schematics/angular @schematics/schematics@0.1000.5
This allows us to use the schematics command and specifically the blank schematics to generate a new schematics project where we can start implementing our custom schematics.
Go to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forem]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/satarii/forem-2fo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/satarii/forem-2fo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forem is open source software for building communities. Communities for your peers, customers, fanbases, families, friends, and any other time and space where people need to come together to be part of a collective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sataniel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fun Linux commands:-]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/digvijay_karadia/fun-linux-commands--3och</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/digvijay_karadia/fun-linux-commands--3och"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux command line can be the home of power users and sysadmins. However, Linux is more than just a lot of hard work. Linux was developed by fun-loving people who created an array of comical commands. Try playing around with these yourself when you want a smile.
Steam locomotive (SL)
locomotive.png
Real uses
Fireplace (aafire)
$ sudo apt install libaa-bin
On Fedora, CentOS, and others:
$ sudo dnf install aalib
fireside.png
Real uses
Yes
$ yes Buffalo Bills
bills.png
Real uses
$ foo
$ yes | foo
Alternatively, you can auto-deny messages using yes as well:
$ yes no | foo
Fortune
Install Fortune with your package manager:
$ sudo apt install fortune
On Fedora:
$ sudo dnf install fortune-mod
The fortune command has many datasets it can draw from. For instance, you can get famous quotes from literature or the science-fiction TV show Firefly, or choose from jokes, tips about Linux, and much more. Search your repository for "fortune" to see what options your distribution provides.
$ fortune
$ fortune | wc --chars
Here's the result of lolcat -h for its help output:
lolcat_rainbow.png
Figlet and banner
$ figlet centos.com
figlet_centos.png
Pipe figlet to lolcat for a colorful banner:
$ figlet centos.com | lolcat
lolcat_figlet_centos.png
$ banner Hello World
hello_world.png
Espeak
Once espeak is installed, turn up the volume on your computer and have some fun listening to your machine talk to you. Espeak is a software speech synthesizer, and there are a few different voice libraries available.
$ espeak "Linux is the best operating system."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Digvijay Karadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a password generator with python.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vaarun_sinha/how-to-make-a-password-generator-with-python-2b1a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vaarun_sinha/how-to-make-a-password-generator-with-python-2b1a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will make a password generator with the secrets module. Why not random module? see the first post in this series to understand.
So Let's Begin!
Generate a random password, according to the user input.
Get user input
Create lists for letters etc...
Loop over lists and make a password.
Print the password.
Get user input
Here we will use try/except blocks so that when user types a string we do not get an error.
We will get inputs for number of special characters, small letters, big letters and numbers required for generating the password.
Code:
try:
        num_of_numbers = int(input("How many numbers should your password have: "))
except ValueError:
        num_of_numbers = int(input("How many numbers should your password have: "))
try:
        num_of_special = int(
     …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaarun Sinha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Step Functions Most Used Nodejs SDK APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/aws-step-functions-most-used-nodejs-sdk-apis-33k3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/aws-step-functions-most-used-nodejs-sdk-apis-33k3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this post, I will be listing some of the most important AWS Nodejs SDK APIs for AWS Step Functions, we will go through the syntax and brief explanation of each of these APIs.
You might want to check out this AWS Step Functions Cheatsheet to know about the most used AWS CLI Commands used with explanations.
Most Important APIs


APIs syntax will be given in a format of Lambda function so it can be directly used.
Create State Machine





exports.createStateMachine = async (event) => {
  try {
    const params = {
      definition: '<String>',
      name: '<String>',
      roleArn: '<String>'
    };
    const data = await stepfunctions.createStateMachine(params).promise();
    console.log(data);
  }
  catch (error) {
    console.log(error)
    // Do something with the error
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivang Chauhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Template String Types as Discriminants in Typescript 4.5]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-string-types-as-discriminants-in-typescript-45-4fdi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-string-types-as-discriminants-in-typescript-45-4fdi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript 4.5 was just released and one of the features that stood out to me is the Template String Types as Discriminants. In this article, we are going to explore this new feature using rudimentary examples.  In my last article, we covered using discriminated unions to write better types that are easy to narrow. 
This is an extension of that but instead of having a concrete literal type, you can use a non-concrete literal type i.e. string, number, etc. instead as part of the template literal type, and Typescript will be able to use it as a discriminant.
In order to understand this feature, we are going to start by creating two types: SuccessType and ErrorType. They are going to represent possible responses for different operations we can perform in a computer system i.e. HTTP Request, F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Template String Types as Discriminants in Typescript 4.5]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-string-types-as-discriminants-in-typescript-45-4fdi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/template-string-types-as-discriminants-in-typescript-45-4fdi"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typescript 4.5 was just released and one of the features that stood out to me is the Template String Types as Discriminants. In this article, we are going to explore this new feature using rudimentary examples.  In my last article, we covered using discriminated unions to write better types that are easy to narrow. 
This is an extension of that but instead of having a concrete literal type, you can use a non-concrete literal type i.e. string, number, etc. instead as part of the template literal type, and Typescript will be able to use it as a discriminant.
In order to understand this feature, we are going to start by creating two types: SuccessType and ErrorType. They are going to represent possible responses for different operations we can perform in a computer system i.e. HTTP Request, F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular vs React vs Vue : Best choice for js Framework?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anquestechnolab/angular-vs-react-vs-vue-best-choice-for-js-framework-2p0n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anquestechnolab/angular-vs-react-vs-vue-best-choice-for-js-framework-2p0n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is a helpful resource for deciding which solution is best for you: Angular vs React vs Vue JavaScript framework.
If you’re a developer just starting out on a project and can’t decide which JavaScript framework to use, this guide should help.
React is a user interface library, Angular is a front-end framework, and Vue.js is a progressive framework.
They can be used almost interchangeably to build front-end applications, but they are not identical, so it is important to compare them and understand their differences.
Each framework is component-based, allowing for the rapid development of UI features.
In this segment, we’ll look at various aspects of Angular, Vue, and React to see how they can meet your needs. This post is not just a comparison of Angular vs. React vs. Vue, but it a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anques Technolabs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Hosting Requirements & Service Provider Selection Tips]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matthieurobin/nodejs-hosting-requirements-service-provider-selection-tips-lpn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matthieurobin/nodejs-hosting-requirements-service-provider-selection-tips-lpn"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T07:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having no idea what Node.js hosting requirements should be covered for your app?
Looking for the best Node.js hosting platform?
In this post, we’ll take in-depth look at all the aspects and subtleties you should analyse to choose the best option.
Also we’ll provide a step-by-step tutorial on how to get Node.js applications hosted in the cloud on the example of Ghost publishing platform.
Why Developers and Enterprises Prefer Node.js
JavaScript code is quite easy-to-understand even for non-professionals, as well as the open-source platform facilitates the application development process.
Moreover, the Node Package Manager includes tons of pre-built modules, which accelerate development speed even more. Scalability, reduced response time and the ability to use the same language on server and client sides are also the proven benefits of Node.js.
As for now most businesses and industries choose Node.js for building their projects. Such a runtime environment is perfect for modern applications because it scales quite well without additional investments into hardware.
REST APIs, real-time apps, single-pages and more can be easily built and executed on almost all known platforms.
Choosing the Best Node.js Hosting Provider
In this guidance, we’ll go through the main aspects you should weigh before choosing the right hosting platform.
Not all the providers support an event-driven JavaScript runtime environment and development framework, so you should do careful research to find the best Node.js hosting for your app.
First of all, you should realise if you have enough time and skills for the system administration routine. If yes, you can get some cloud VM or VPS and install, deploy and manage everything on your own. But, if you prefer to focus on application code than a managed cloud hosting platform would be a perfect choice.
Good luck ;-)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthieu ROBIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White Label Crypto Exchange Software Development - In a Nutshell]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/emmabaker/white-label-crypto-exchange-software-development-in-a-nutshell-43pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/emmabaker/white-label-crypto-exchange-software-development-in-a-nutshell-43pk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T07:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency is becoming a familiar term and grabbed the attention of many people from all parts of the world. It is due to the rising popularity and beneficial factors of top crypto coins like bitcoin, ethereum, Cardano, and more. Already many people started to use these cryptocurrencies for making profits. As the usage of crypto assets is increasing day by day, there is a demand for cryptocurrency exchanges too. Crypto exchange is an online trading platform where one can buy, sell, or exchange all sets of popular crypto assets securely without any hassle. The Crypto industry offers several business opportunities for startups and entrepreneurs. But among them, the cryptocurrency exchange is the best and trending money-generating business model in this modern era.
In today’s modern world…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM Login Not Working]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/clavinjune/npm-login-not-working-2obp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/clavinjune/npm-login-not-working-2obp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T06:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This solution works for Node v16.13.0 and NPM v8.1.3
I don't always hate working using NPM unless it starts downloading tons of node_modules and giving not so verbose logs. Today, my colleague and I found an NPM login bug that's not so interesting and hard to debug. It takes me about an hour to find out what is the root cause.
In this article, I will write the solution just in case you meet the same issue.
In my current company, we use Nexus3 as our private repository for the NPM module. I also use Node v12.22.4 and NPM v8.1.3 for working on my local machine. To login into our Nexus repository, I use .npmrc with this format:
@myorg:registry=https://repo.myorg.com/repository/npm-private
always-auth=true
_auth={{ base64 of username:password redacted here }}

And we're happy with it. No issue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clavin June</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Crud API with Node.js, Express, and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sureshramani/build-crud-api-with-nodejs-express-and-mongodb-14hk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sureshramani/build-crud-api-with-nodejs-express-and-mongodb-14hk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T06:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, most of the websites operate on an API-based backend structure, where we just send a request from the front end of the website by calling an API and obtaining the required results. In this blog, we are going to build a simple CRUD (Create, Read, Update and Delete) app with the application of Node JS, Express JS, and MongoDB from the basics. Before we jump into the application, let's look into the tools we are going to use.
Express is one of the most popular web frameworks for node.js. It is built on top of the node.js HTTP module and adds support for routing, middleware, view system, etc. It is very simple and minimal, unlike other frameworks that try to do way too much, thereby reducing the flexibility for developers to have their own design choices.
Mongoose is an ODM (Object …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Ramani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps Done RIGHT! Why and What to Do.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/devsecops-done-right-why-and-what-to-do-4b2j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/devsecops-done-right-why-and-what-to-do-4b2j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T05:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is something we all keep hearing, and everyone says it is important. 
But why is it important? And how can we adopt DevSecOps the right way without penalizing any aspect of our workflow, especially in a Cloud Native scenario?
Let's take a look at the best practices for DevSecOps, and DOs and DONTs of this practice.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/KaoPQLyWq_g
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
In my role as DevOps Architect I get to work with the biggest, most important, and most strategic Microsoft and GitHub's clients in Asia and Oceania on their DevOps Transformations.
And you know that DevOps is a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and why not to use Linux?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/developerbishwas/why-and-why-not-to-use-linux-5dl0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/developerbishwas/why-and-why-not-to-use-linux-5dl0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T04:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons to use Linux


Linux has a better environment for programming. It can smoothly execute software like PyCharm, Rider and Android Studio. Linux has a huge source of tools to make a specific task easier. Not only aircrack-ng there are many other CLI based tools, that gonna help you. And one thing, docker also executes awesomely in Linux.
Linux has a growing software for video editing which might not fulfill all our requirements. Idiots in the Linux community quarrels over distro i.e. "my distro is better", instead of coding a nice piece of software or staying silent. Image editing and other stuff can be tedious for you. I don't see any point in using Wine, wine just decrease the GUI appearance of the app.
I use Ubuntu, Ubuntu is super awesome. Fool people quarrel over distros but that's not what smart linux users do.
Most of the Linux distro arguments are about the desktop environments. You can literally install any desktop environment in any linux based OS you're using. So, let's not quarrel over Linux Distro (aka: Desktop Environment). 
Let's contribute on making software and games for Linux. Let's do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewLinuxHelper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL Auth without Middleware]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/verneleem/graphql-auth-without-middleware-37c6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/verneleem/graphql-auth-without-middleware-37c6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T04:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if I told you, that you could have one of the most advanced auth built into your GraphQL API without adding any middleware?
Before we begin though, let's break apart Auth into its two sub-categories, Authentication and Authorization. Authentication is "who you are" while Authorization is "what you are allowed" to do. For this short article, we will be covering the latter of these two concepts.
Since GraphQL is a stateless API, it does not create sessions between the client and the API. The common method to authorize clients to query or mutate data is by passing a token known as a JSON Web token (JWT). The common way for a client to obtain a JWT is by authenticating through some auth provider who returns a JWT to the client. This JWT then provided by the client to the GraphQL API in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>verneleem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Got My First Developer Job – Here&#x27;s What I&#x27;ve Learned So Far]]></title>
        <id>617a6ef033422e07df3667f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-ive-learned-at-my-first-developer-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to share with you what I've learned so far at my first programming job as a junior full-stack developer.  Ever since my developer career began in July, 2021 I've been learning constantly. And I'm gonna share some tips from my experiences so that you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Plans, New Pricing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/doppler/new-plans-new-pricing-130g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/doppler/new-plans-new-pricing-130g"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I am excited to share that we have restructured our plans to encourage the use of power features, including making SAML SSO free for everyone! Back in 2020, our team made a faulty assumption that only large teams would want our advanced features. But over time we heard the opposite from you, as developers. We realize that there are a subset of features on our paid plans that would unlock new possibilities and use-cases if they were accessible. You asked to become power users. Going forward Doppler will offer two plans centered around developers and teams.
Doppler is built by developers for developers. We believe that individuals whether that be hobbyists, students, educators, open-source contributors, or something else deserve a developer-friendly way to manage the literal keys to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Vallelunga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lab 8: TESTING !!!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/beamazedvariable/lab-8-testing--25b0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/beamazedvariable/lab-8-testing--25b0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are on our way completing our project piece by piece. This week, we will adding test to our project. You might have wonder why would we need a test if our program is running and not crashing? From my point of view, testing not only figure it out the bugs, make sure very branches is tested but also help you with the designing of your software. When making test for this week, I have to actually refactor my code a bit more so as to be able to test it out such as exposing proccessMarkdown() in html-maker so as to test it out
module.exports.processingFile = processingFile;
module.exports.processMarkdown = processMarkdown;

The test I have written is very simple since my program is still very small.
To be able to use Jest proficiently with Typescript, we will need help from ts-jest
npm i -D j…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amazing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💡 Why Auth0 “Shifted Left” with Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-auth0-shifted-left-with-azure-47ge</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-auth0-shifted-left-with-azure-47ge"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we expanded customer choice while building a security-first architecture.



  
  
  
Choice is good. We like it when our supermarket shelves are stocked with hundreds of varieties of breakfast cereal. We pick the smartphones we use and the cars we drive. The same should be true for businesses and the technologies they use.
Today, we brought the Auth0 Identity Platform to Microsoft Azure, giving our private cloud customers the ability to pick the right infrastructure provider for their needs.
This means a greater selection of regions. Microsoft currently operates in over 60 regions around the world, making it easier to comply with data residency and sovereignty requirements.
And if you’re already running your app on Azure’s cloud servers, you’ll benefit from a converged infrastructure,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular A11y ESLint Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bitovi/angular-a11y-eslint-rules-2fjc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bitovi/angular-a11y-eslint-rules-2fjc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making a web application accessible can feel like a daunting task, particularly if you aren't used to taking accessibility into consideration.
The @angular-eslint repo includes a number of linting rules that can help enforce accessibility best practices within Angular component templates.
It is important to note, however, that these rules do not check attributes and roles set using the host section of the @Component decorator, or ones set using @HostBinding decorators.
While passing these rules isn't a guarantee or metric for ensuring full accessibility, it is a step in the right direction.
For convenience, I've divided the rules I will be covering into three groups. The first group, general, covers ARIA roles and attributes. The second group, content, includes rules related to textual rep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wade H.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Perfect Configuration Format? Try Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tmcneal/the-perfect-configuration-format-try-typescript-5hg2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tmcneal/the-perfect-configuration-format-try-typescript-5hg2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of ink has been spilled about configuration file formats. Popular formats like JSON, TOML, YAML, and XML each have their advantages and drawbacks. There's an alternative that should be receiving more attention: Typescript!
Before getting into why Typescript is a compelling choice for config files, let's review the common file formats used in a typical web application today:
XML: Back in the late 90s to mid 2000s this was king both as a messaging protocol and flat file format. It gets a bad rap, but there is a lot to like about XML as a config file format, including great tooling support and a robust schema definition language in XSD. 
JSON: Extremely common as a data interchange format in REST APIs, and also very popular as a config file format. For a lot of developers this strikes t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd McNeal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Slice and *ngIf for Conditional Ellipsis / Tooltip on Data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/riapacheco/angular-slice-and-ngif-for-conditional-ellipsis-tooltip-on-data-2d4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/riapacheco/angular-slice-and-ngif-for-conditional-ellipsis-tooltip-on-data-2d4h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: Conditional Ellipsis without CSS


I want to add an ellipsis to data that's brought in from a service without having to use CSS' text-overflow: ellipsis feature, since it's unreliable and could break overtime if not monitored during refactoring.
Slice Pipe



  
  
  Determine character max overflow limit



Determine max overflow by number of characters (instead of max-width)
Example: max overflow characters 20 (inclusive, aka 20 or more)
I use slice pipe where you add the start and end of the slice to the interpolated string




<!--Template-->
<a *ngFor="let item of items">
  {{ item.name | slice: 0 : 20 }}
</a>

span



Conditional span is based on data's length




<!--Template-->
<a *ngFor="let item of items">
  {{ item.name | slice:0:20 }}<span *ngIf="item.name.length >= 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ria Pacheco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Slice and *ngIf for Conditional Ellipsis / Tooltip on Data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/riapacheco/angular-slice-and-ngif-for-conditional-ellipsis-tooltip-on-data-2d4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/riapacheco/angular-slice-and-ngif-for-conditional-ellipsis-tooltip-on-data-2d4h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: Conditional Ellipsis without CSS


I want to add an ellipsis to data that's brought in from a service without having to use CSS' text-overflow: ellipsis feature, since it's unreliable and could break overtime if not monitored during refactoring.
Slice Pipe



  
  
  Determine character max overflow limit



Determine max overflow by number of characters (instead of max-width)
Example: max overflow characters 20 (inclusive, aka 20 or more)
I use slice pipe where you add the start and end of the slice to the interpolated string




<!--Template-->
<a *ngFor="let item of items">
  {{ item.name | slice: 0 : 20 }}
</a>

span



Conditional span is based on data's length




<!--Template-->
<a *ngFor="let item of items">
  {{ item.name | slice:0:20 }}<span *ngIf="item.name.length >= 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ria Pacheco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🇧🇷 Guia de Estilos para TypeScript 🎨]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/luisvonmuller/guia-de-estilos-para-typescript-2ahb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/luisvonmuller/guia-de-estilos-para-typescript-2ahb"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔥 Este é um Guia não oficial e você pode opinar através do repositório de GitHub para juntos chegarmos a melhor definição do Ideal! Vamos colaborar? 💪
⭐️ Variáveis & Funções
📦 Classes
🔌 Interfaces
🌟 Tipos
😳 Namespaces
🔢 Enum
📭 null vs  😱 undefined

📑 Formatação
🤔 Aspas simples vs Aspas Duplas
⚙️ Uso de ponto e vírgula ao final de linhas " ; "****
📂 Uma sugestão para uma boa nomeação de Arquivos
🤨 Tipo vs Interface
👯‍♀️ Anotação de Tipos para Array
⚠️ Comparadores, "==" vs "==="
Use camelCase para nomear variáveis e funções
let FulanoVariavel: string = 'Aqui está errado.. ( ఠ ͟ʖ ఠ )';
function CiclanoFuncao(){}

let fulanoVariavel: string = 'Aqui está daora! (✿◠‿◠)';
function ciclanoFuncao(){}

Use PascalCase para nomear suas classes! (Ou use programação funcional 👀)
class fu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luís Von Muller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Serverless Online Payments with Netlify and Stripe]]></title>
        <id>618fda8c11d3cb08287a5a51</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-online-payments/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first steps many young startups take is setting up a static web page, perhaps with an email newsletter, to help them build an audience.  As the weeks go by and the MVP is getting further along, the subject of how to handle payments will eventually emerge. From]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Start Using Docker Right Now]]></title>
        <id>618eaede11d3cb08287a51c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-start-using-docker-now/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a year back, I was just about ready to release Caer, a Computer Vision library in Python that would be publicly available on PyPi. But first, I decided to send it to a friend in Alberta to tinker around with it. A few days later, I found that he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Authentication By The Numbers (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jfgrissom/web-authentication-by-the-numbers-5b0g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jfgrissom/web-authentication-by-the-numbers-5b0g"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How authentication layers are built up to create an authentication system for your website.



  
  
  Audience


This article is intended for intermediate level website developers and software engineers. I've tried to make it approachable for beginners but it's really not for absolute beginners.
Website authentication can be a very confusing topic. There are a lot of considerations when thinking about an authentication system for your web projects. It's overwhelming because authentication can be extremely simple or it can be a layer cake of individual systems that each build on top of each other.
In this series we're going to start with no authentication and then you'll add a very basic authentication system. Then you'll progressively add and remove layers on top of it to make it a full b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay F. Grissom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Authentication By The Numbers (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jfgrissom/web-authentication-by-the-numbers-5b0g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jfgrissom/web-authentication-by-the-numbers-5b0g"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How authentication layers are built up to create an authentication system for your website.



  
  
  Audience


This article is intended for intermediate level website developers and software engineers. I've tried to make it approachable for beginners but it's really not for absolute beginners.
Website authentication can be a very confusing topic. There are a lot of considerations when thinking about an authentication system for your web projects. It's overwhelming because authentication can be extremely simple or it can be a layer cake of individual systems that each build on top of each other.
In this series we're going to start with no authentication and then you'll add a very basic authentication system. Then you'll progressively add and remove layers on top of it to make it a full b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay F. Grissom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging `make: 'build' is up to date.`]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shyamajp/debugging-make-build-is-up-to-date-2o4n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shyamajp/debugging-make-build-is-up-to-date-2o4n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T20:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR - Rename your directory build something else
Makefile
build:
    docker build . -t my-basic-app

Look. I have the most basic app, Dockerfile and Makefile. Why can't it just run make build command properly as I defined in Makefile?
shyamajp@ubuntu:~/Projects/my-basic-app$ make build
make: 'build' is up to date.

Let's get rid of this stupid error. At the root level, you must have a directory named build. That's why you see this unexpected behavior.
In my case, I can change outDir name from build to dist to avoid this specific conflict.
tsconfig.json
{
    "outDir": "dist"
}

Do not name your directory same as Makefile target. Be careful with names like build and test, which are often used for both Makefile targets and directory names.
I know this is a noob question but I've done it a few times already and I thought I might as well document it somewhere for myself. I hope this helps other newbie folks like me.
Feel free to reach out if you have any questions or suggestions to make this article better. Thank you for reading. Happy Coding!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shyamajp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethernet Doesn&#x27;t Have a Valid IP Configuration – How to Fix Invalid Connection in Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>6194a7d111d3cb08287a7a03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ethernet-doesnt-have-a-valid-ip-configuration-how-to-fix-invalid-connection-in-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T18:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every computer or device that you can use to surf the web has an IP address assigned to it. This IP address allows the device to be identified on the internet or within a local area network.  But sometimes, you might get an error that says your Ethernet doesn't have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing vite-react-ts-extended]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/malloc007/announcing-vite-react-ts-extended-2093</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/malloc007/announcing-vite-react-ts-extended-2093"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T17:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Start template! 👉 https://github.com/laststance/vite-react-ts-extended
This year there has been a big movement in build tools in the JavaScript community.

In 2020, Webpack, especially in combination with Babel, seemed to be the de facto standard for build tools.
However, in 2021, the popularity of a completely new development environment/build tool that does not include Webpack has skyrocketed.
Vite.
ESBuild that starts without build.
NPM Trend, you can see that Vite has overtaken the number of downloads of create-react-app since July.
The Next.js team has also responded by abandoning Babel and introducing SWC, an ultra-fast TypeScript compiler, in Next v12.
What does that mean for us React Developers?
The Vite default react-ts template lacked Jest and ESLint (Prettier integrated).
Jest comes pre-installed with React-Testing-Library, Hook-Testing-Library, MSW, and TypeScript support.
You can easily install and run Jest with the following commands, 
yarn
npx degit laststance/vite-react-ts-extended myapp
cd myapp
yarn install
yarn dev

npm
npx degit laststance/vite-react-ts-extended myapp
cd myapp
npm install
npm run dev

github: https://github.com/laststance/vite-react-ts-extended
so I would be happy if you could use it as a way to build a instant React+TypeScript development environment for new libraries or anything else! 💅]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryota Murakami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROLE BASED ACCESS CONTROL IN ADONIS JS WITH NPM ROLE-ACL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/slickdev_raphael/role-based-access-control-in-adonis-js-with-npm-role-acl-4jg3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/slickdev_raphael/role-based-access-control-in-adonis-js-with-npm-role-acl-4jg3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Role based access control or RBAC as it would be called throughout the remainder of this article, refers to an authorization process based on user defined roles in the organization, example: a team-member can create and update collections but they can’t delete a collection, only the team-admin role has authority to delete collections. 
We will be using Adonis JS which is a Node JS framework along with the Role-acl package.
I will assume you have an Adonis server, with the Lucid ORM and a Database already set up.
social authentication in Adonis JS, we talked about using Ally package for social Authentication using google. 
Let’s create the User, teams and collections models and migrations.
node ace make:model User -m

node ace make:model Team -m

node ace make:model collection -m

In the us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raphael Otuya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry-Picking Commits in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356700</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cherry-picking-commits-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 5 of this series, we looked at rebasing and merging. Although there are a couple of differences between git merge and git rebase, both commands have the same goal: they integrate changes from one branch into another.
The post Cherry-Picking Commits in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gap (Design Engineering)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357023</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-gap-design-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egor Kloos describes a situation where a (purely visual) designer asks for some changes to a component. There is a misunderstanding where the (code monkey) developer implements the change exactly as requested—but really what was required was both a bug …
The post The Gap (Design Engineering) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Study Course – Pass the Exam With This Free 13-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>61912f8811d3cb08287a6037</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-certification-study-course-pass-the-exam/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T14:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passing the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam is one of the first steps to a career in cloud development. And freeCodeCamp just published my free 12-hour course that will help you prepare for the exam.  This exam mostly deals with cloud computing concepts. Even if you are new to coding,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementation of Ngx Infinite Scroller using Angular Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/implementation-of-ngx-infinite-scroller-using-angular-application-2p72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/implementation-of-ngx-infinite-scroller-using-angular-application-2p72"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T13:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will introduce infinite scrolling in our Angular application. When we prepare an application, we deal with tons of files at the same time. In this situation, a question will be asked: how to display thousands of registrations on a single page?
It is not a good practice to load thousands of records at once on one page, and there are many benefits to implement infinite scrolling.
Increase the time on our web site so that we can have faster operations
Make it easy to increase the depth of the page
The minimum number of clicks required
Better user interface
Best in mobile layout
One of the major advantages is that it reduces the bounce rate of a website
To implement infinite scrolling in Angular, we can use an npm package named ngx-infinite-scroll.
To begin with infinite scrol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits of build learning management system in Node JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/casyharward/benefits-of-build-learning-management-system-in-node-js-253e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/casyharward/benefits-of-build-learning-management-system-in-node-js-253e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T13:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graduates from top universities in USA, Asia and Europe continue to opt for a career in software development due to increasing demand of software/web applications. Today, many companies offer cutting-edge platforms such as Android and iOS exclusively to their employees so that they can learn technical skills at work. It makes sense to build an LMS using Node js which can be used to train employees and for students for taking online courses.
The LMS which is built using Node js can be deployed on any of these platforms:
Raspberry Pi-  a tiny computer board that uses an SD card as storage, you can run it anywhere with a USB power supply.


Chromebooks - inexpensive laptop that has a web-based Chrome OS


Node js is free and open source, hence you can use open source server software such as N…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CasyHarward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer Road Map 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rameshfadatare/full-stack-java-developer-road-map-2022-ga1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rameshfadatare/full-stack-java-developer-road-map-2022-ga1"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T06:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I am going to talk about how to become a full-stack java developer.
Well if you are a Java developer and if you want to become a full-stack Java developer then you are in a right place and if you are a Java beginner and if you want to become a full-stack Java developer then you are also in the right place.
In this article, I am going to give you a learning path to become a full-stack java developer so basically, we will discuss what are the skills I mean what are the tools and technologies that you are going to learn to become a full-stack java developer. 
Before looking to the learning path for full-stack java developer let's first understand what is a full stack developer. Well full stack developer is an engineer who works on both client-side and server-side software. Fu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramesh Fadatare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using NX to build a monorepo for web and native apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paulmojicatech/using-nx-to-build-a-monorepo-for-web-and-native-apps-om7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paulmojicatech/using-nx-to-build-a-monorepo-for-web-and-native-apps-om7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T06:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an Ionic and Web App With an NX Monorepo



  
  
  Purpose


The purpose of this article is to utilize NX workspace to create both a native application and a web application using the monorepo pattern. The application will track the grocery list items you create. In the application, you will create a grocery list. After creating the grocery list, you will be able to open the application either as a web application or as a native application to see when the items were purchased. You will also be able to mark the item as used. Finally, you will receive a notification when you open the app if you have a perishable item that has not been yet been used and was purchased more than 3 days ago.  You can see the code we use for this article on my Github.
A monorepo is the pattern of havin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paulmojicatech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Way to Create Dynamic Components in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/best-way-to-create-dynamic-components-in-angular-57dk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/best-way-to-create-dynamic-components-in-angular-57dk"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T05:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article is originally published to my blog here.
Angular is a TypeScript based Open Source JavaScript framework. A situation like this happens most of the time where we need to create components dynamically. This article explains what is the best way to create dynamic components in Angular.
A component is a page in Angular. We will try to create it dynamically using the latest Ivy Component API and see how it works. Let’s start!
ComponentFactoryResolver is removed from latest Angular release. This article explains how to use Ivy API to create components dynamically.
We have seen in the latest Angular release, the use of ComponentFactoryResolver is removed. Ivy creates the opportunity to instantiate the component with ViewContainerRef.createComponent without creating an associated facto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching Angular Resolver State]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordyj/caching-angular-resolver-state-487d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordyj/caching-angular-resolver-state-487d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T04:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are certain types of data that we will pull into our applications that do not change, or that change very, very slowly. In these cases, it’s best to load the data into the application once, when it’s needed, and not to ask for it again until the application has been refreshed, or until we decide that we should get the data anew for some other reason.
In my Angular application, I’m using resolvers to pre-fetch any data needed for a route before sending the application to that route. One bit of data that is not likely to change, or will at least change very slowly, would be my repository of state/province data. Though it’s technically POSSIBLE that the U.S. could lose or gain a state, it’s also very unlikely. Therefore, I’d rather cache that data locally in my Angular application the f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Nordmeyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clever Sticky Footer Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357053</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-clever-sticky-footer-technique/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T00:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upon hearing “sticky footer” these days, I would think most people imagine a position: sticky situation where a footer element appears fixed on the screen while in the scrolling context of some parent element.
That’s not quite what I’m talking …
The post A Clever Sticky Footer Technique appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Line length revisited: following the research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356849</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/line-length-revisited-following-the-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Dyson produces nitty gritty research on the long-accepted notion that shorter line lengths are more legible than longer ones. The study finds that shorter lines do not necessarily lead to faster reading. If you’re looking for a definitive answer …
The post Line length revisited: following the research appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting late-December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate a Pull Request of Static Content With a Simple HTML Form]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356491</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/generate-a-pull-request-of-static-content-with-a-simple-html-form/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack has been in the website world for years. Static Site Generators (SSGs) — which often have content that lives right within a GitHub repo itself — are a big part of that story. That opens up the idea of …
The post Generate a Pull Request of Static Content With a Simple HTML Form appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hilman Ramadhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack TV]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jamstack-tv/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T15:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the name of Netlify’s YouTube Channel. Love that. I linked up Rich’s talk the other day, which was a part of this past JamstackConf, but now all the talks are up on there. Rich got to talk …
The post Jamstack TV appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Alpha Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356611</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/color-alpha-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T01:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my “Different Degrees of Custom Property Usage” article, I noted a situation about colors and CSS custom properties where I went “too far” with breaking up HSL color values. Breaking every single color into its H, S, and L parts …
The post Color Alpha Anywhere appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355894</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/defining-and-applying-ui-themes-using-the-mimcss-css-in-js-library/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Theming UI refers to the ability to perform a change in visual styles in a consistent manner that defines the “look and feel” of a site. Swapping color palettes, à la dark mode or some other means, is a good …
The post Defining and Applying UI Themes Using the Mimcss CSS-in-JS Library appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Michlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Other Looks at the Conditional Border Radius Trick]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356304</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/other-looks-at-the-conditional-border-radius-trick/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T23:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when Ahmad Shadeed wrote about that border-radius “toggle” he found in Facebook’s CSS? It was interesting! I covered it. A few weeks after that surge of linkage, a couple of articles came out digging into it a little deeper. …
The post Other Looks at the Conditional Border Radius Trick appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Rebase: Clean up your Commit History]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355658</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/interactive-rebase-clean-up-your-commit-history/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Rebase is the Swiss Army knife of Git commands: lots of use cases and lots of possibilities! It's really a great addition to any developer's tool chain, because it lets you revise your local commit history—before you share your work with the rest of the team. Let's see what you can do with an interactive rebase and then look at some practical examples.
The post Interactive Rebase: Clean up your Commit History appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Semantic menu context]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356652</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/semantic-menu-context/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T20:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott digs into the history of the <menu> element. He traced it as far back as HTML 2 (!) in a 1994 changelog. The vibe then, it seems, was to mark up a list. I would suspect the intention …
The post Semantic menu context appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Quasar Framework: Building Cross-Platform Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar is an open-source Vue.js-based cross-platform framework that allows you, as a developer, to easily build apps for both desktop and mobile using technologies such as Cordova and Electron and writing your code once. The app we’ll build will store and get its data from Firebase, meaning that we will also be seeing how to use Firebase in Quasar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joel Olawanle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>