<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-17T01:00:55.889Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-17T01:00:55.889Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build Crypto Tracker Chart with React 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ayeprahman/how-i-build-crypto-tracker-chart-with-react-4k9h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ayeprahman/how-i-build-crypto-tracker-chart-with-react-4k9h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T00:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Coders 👩🏼‍💻,
Recently, I visit a crypto tracker site to check DogeCoin prices to see whether it going to the moon 🚀

I was curious about how to build a simplified version on that site using React, other libraries, and tools out there.
Here is the link to my cool 😎 project:
https://cryptotracker.ayeprahman.com/
So I did research to find which API to use and came across a free, reliable, and comprehensive API from the team 🦎CoinGecko.
At the same time, my goal also was to focus to find a low-level…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arif Rahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing table filters between components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T23:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; The logic behind this is to pass the table filters as query params when exiting the table route and when trying to re-activate the table route add the {queryParamsHandling="preserve”} directive after the routerLink so that the query params would be preserved.
Introduction

After implementing filters, another issue that arises is how to identify previously applied filters after a component containing a table has been destroyed. Here is a use case: We have a component showing a list of customers in a ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyemade Oyemaja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing table filters between components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/oyemade/managing-table-filters-between-components-3fjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T23:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TLDR; The logic behind this is to pass the table filters as query params when exiting the table route and when trying to re-activate the table route add the {queryParamsHandling="preserve”} directive after the routerLink so that the query params would be preserved.
Introduction

After implementing filters, another issue that arises is how to identify previously applied filters after a component containing a table has been destroyed. Here is a use case: We have a component showing a list of customers in a ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyemade Oyemaja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically forwarding ports within an existing SSH connection]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rtyler/dynamically-forwarding-ports-within-an-existing-ssh-connection-nj4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rtyler/dynamically-forwarding-ports-within-an-existing-ssh-connection-nj4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working over SSH on a big beefy remote machine is a great way to extend the life of any laptop, but presents challenges when developing network-based services. Fortunately OpenSSH has a "port forwarding" feature which has been around for a number of years. Port forwarding allows the user to tunnel a port from the remote machine back to their local machine, in essence allowing you to access a remote service bound to port 8000 on your own localhost:8000. When I first learned about this, I would fiddle around …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>R. Tyler Croy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with AdonisJS and Inertia.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we'll build a simple CRM app utilizing an awesome tech stack consisting of:
React - React really needs no introduction, since it's the most popular front-end framework around.
Inertia.js - Inertia allows you to create fully client-side rendered, single-page apps, without much of the complexity that comes with modern SPAs.
Typescript - A strongly typed superset of ECMAScript.
AdonisJS - A fully featured web framework focused on productivity and developer ergonomics.
If I were inclined to nam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lev Eidelman Nagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with AdonisJS and Inertia.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eidellev/getting-started-with-adonisjs-and-inertia-js-2po0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T20:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we'll build a simple CRM app utilizing an awesome tech stack consisting of:
React - React really needs no introduction, since it's the most popular front-end framework around.
Inertia.js - Inertia allows you to create fully client-side rendered, single-page apps, without much of the complexity that comes with modern SPAs.
Typescript - A strongly typed superset of ECMAScript.
AdonisJS - A fully featured web framework focused on productivity and developer ergonomics.
If I were inclined to nam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lev Eidelman Nagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building custom DSLs in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/matechs/building-custom-dsls-in-typescript-29el</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/matechs/building-custom-dsls-in-typescript-29el"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T19:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do we even need custom domain-specific languages?
First of all, we should define what do we mean by custom domain-specific languages.
In everyday programming, we have to encode real-world problems in code. We are limited by the power of expressivity of the language we are using. The programming languages are fairly low when it comes to model the real world.
Basically, we translate from a human language to a more basic form of language that a computer can understand.
While translating, and for future ref…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Arnaldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Touch Touchpad Gestures on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamst0rm/multi-touch-touchpad-gestures-on-linux-362i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamst0rm/multi-touch-touchpad-gestures-on-linux-362i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T19:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to enable multi-finger gesture support on any Linux distro, be it Ubuntu, Pop!_OS, Fedora or Arch. Supports pinch-to-zoom in Chrome, Firefox & other browsers.
Go to Touchégg's Github Repo.


Scroll down a bit and you’ll see the Installation & Configuration instructions, which will guide you through rest of the process.



Tip: Restart your PC if gestures do not work right away.
Use Touché, the desktop application to configure Touchégg, by the same developer, so less compatibility issues (I found non…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paras Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-2-13da</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-2-13da"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T19:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neste post retomo a série com truques e dicas úteis sobre serviços e tecnologias que integram o Microsoft Azure. Caso ainda não tenha acessado o primeiro post ou, até mesmo, gostaria de revê-lo consulte o link a seguir:
Para informações e efetuar sua inscrição acesse:

Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 1
Nos meses de Maio e Junho/2021 já estão agendadas algumas apresentações cobrindo o uso de serviços do Microsoft Azure, Azure DevOps e GitHub Actions:
.NET 5 + Azure Funct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renato Groffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With TypeScript Compiler (tsc)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mxkvl/getting-started-with-typescript-compiler-tsc-34h2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mxkvl/getting-started-with-typescript-compiler-tsc-34h2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T18:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subscribe to my email newsletter to stay up to date.

From the previous post TypeScript - What Is All About And Why Should You Use It? we know that TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript and programming language. But how can you use it? If you worked with JavaScript in Front End you know that your code is executing by Web browser. In Back End, your code is running by Node. What about TypeScript?
The thing is that TypeScript is provided with a special program, tool - compiler. A compiler is a program that co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kovalevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Tips, Tricks and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpiteng/javascript-tips-tricks-and-best-practices-33dm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpiteng/javascript-tips-tricks-and-best-practices-33dm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T18:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Developers! In this tech article I will cover JavaScript Trips, Tricks and Best Practices. In daily coding many times we wrote a long lines of code, read this article I am going to cover best javascript practices, tips & tricks to reduce lines of code and minimize your works using JavaScript in-built functions. I will cover array of JavaScript function along with example right away, So Let's Start!
Take away -
Replace All
Group By Array Of Objects
Next - next()
Map - map()
Cast Values in array using -…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kpiteng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A fusion of Makefile and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raigaurav/a-fusion-of-makefile-and-docker-45an</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raigaurav/a-fusion-of-makefile-and-docker-45an"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T17:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous article we have created a Dockerfile for our Mojolicious application. In there I mentioned that we have to run several docker command and when we map it across different environment we have to take care of different permutations and combinations.
gmake.exe utility instead of make. It comes with Strawberry Perl.
mojo_react_app/Makefile
DOCKER_TAG ?= mojo_react_app:development
NO_CACHE ?= false
PULL ?= false
BUILD_TYPE ?= development
CONTAINER_NAME ?= mojo_react_app
HTTPS_OUT_PORT ?= 443
HTTPS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Rai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your Code Quality with SonarLint and SonarQube]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leading-edje/improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube-3kk6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leading-edje/improve-your-code-quality-with-sonarqube-3kk6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T17:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Quality Engineer, I am typically involved in building automated tests.  These tests are used to ensure that future code changes don't break existing functionality, and can include integration, API, and end-to-end testing.  All of these tests are run after code has been written and will execute the code to verify it conforms to the functional requirements being validated.
These tests are all considered "dynamic tests", as they are executed against the running application.  
Static code analysis is anoth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis Whalen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure: dicas, truques, conteúdos e eventos gratuitos | vol. 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-1-h89</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/renatogroffe/microsoft-azure-dicas-truques-conteudos-e-eventos-gratuitos-vol-1-h89"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neste post agrupo diversos conteúdos gratuitos que produzi recentemente sobre o Microsoft Azure, sobretudo vídeos com dicas e truques cobrindo diferentes serviços. Meu objetivo é transformar esta iniciativa em uma série, com postagens futuras listando novos conteúdos publicados.
Como podemos melhorar a implementação de aplicações na nuvem, tirando proveito de boas práticas e obtendo assim aplicações escaláveis, com alta disponibilidade, uma maior tolerância a falhas e se ainda valendo dos benefícios de auto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Renato Groffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journey to the real world by cloning DEV.to backend server(part 6)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harshmangalam/journey-to-the-real-world-by-cloning-dev-to-backend-server-part-6-1d40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harshmangalam/journey-to-the-real-world-by-cloning-dev-to-backend-server-part-6-1d40"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our last post we have worked around providing interface to user from where user can register and login into their account. 
But how can our application knew who is sending request . Suppose we want to edit our profile how application will knew who we are hence today we will work on context section in graphql where we will extract jwt token provided by user browser in header and recognise user.
One more problem we generally face in apollo graphql is splitting of schema and resolvers in different file in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harsh Mangalam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular SpringBoot CRUD  DynamoDB Example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb-example-14in</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb-example-14in"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://loizenai.com/angular-springboot-crud-dynamodb/
Angular SpringBoot CRUD  DynamoDB Example
In the tutorial, I introduce how to create an "SpringBoot Angular  DynamoDB CRUD Example" with POST/GET/PUT/DELETE requests to SpringBoot RestAPIs.
Design overview system by Architecture Diagram that includes: Angular Client, SpringBoot RestAPIs, and  DynamoDB database.
Implement Angular CRUD Client with Angular built-in HttpClient to communicate with server side.
Implement SpringBoot RestAPIs that gets data fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWT Authentication in Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/atulkr9/jwt-authentication-in-node-js-1dc6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/atulkr9/jwt-authentication-in-node-js-1dc6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hola Amigos!
I was learning about JWT and its application in Node.js and now I'm pleased to share my learnings with ya'll. I hope you guys enjoy reading it. In this post, I'll talk about:
What exactly is a JSON web token
Why do we need JSON web token
JWT authentication in Node.js with Express.js
01 What exactly is a JWT?


According to the official website of JWT:
JSON Web Token (JWT) is an open standard (RFC 7519) that defines a compact and self-contained way for securely transmitting information between p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atul Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start new Next.js project notes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vladimirvovk/start-new-next-js-project-notes-13m3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vladimirvovk/start-new-next-js-project-notes-13m3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please read the [Getting Started] guide (https://nextjs.org/docs/getting-started) it is really good.
Run yarn create next-app and follow the instructions.
I like to keep all source code in one folder. Next.js supports src folder by default. Create src folder and move pages and styles there.
Next.js provides an integrated TypeScript experience out of the box.
Create TypeScript config file:
touch tsconfig.json

Next.js will automatically configure this file with default values.
Install dependencies:
yarn add …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladimir Vovk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[spotinfo - cli for exploring AWS Spot instances]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexeiled/spotinfo-cli-for-exploring-aws-spot-instances-1o1c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexeiled/spotinfo-cli-for-exploring-aws-spot-instances-1o1c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spotinfo is an open-source command-line tool you can use for exploring AWS Spot instances across multiple AWS regions.
Under the hood, the tool uses the same data feeds as AWS Spot Advisor and AWS Spot Pricing.
Compared with the AWS Spot Advisor, the spotinfo supports advanced filtering and sorting (also with regex), in-place spot prices, cross-region comparison, and multiple output formats (plain text, JSON, table, csv).
A short overview is available on DoiT blogs here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexei Ledenev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Global Thumbnail - Weekend Project #0]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karankeyash/weekend-project-0-21i2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karankeyash/weekend-project-0-21i2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get Video Thumbnails


I recently faced an issue where I had to get YouTube and/or Vimeo video Thumbnails, so naturally, I did what many devs do, search an npm package, but I did not get any good results or the results were not up to my mark.
So, I started from scratch to build that functionality and in a week I was successful. I made the exact thing I wanted.
Who needs thumbnails, right? but sometimes you do need them. One day I was telling this thing I made to my friend @thisisdg (Dhruv), and Dhruv joking…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yash Karanke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Next.js + Strapi: Security first]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rubenmarcus/getting-started-with-next-js-strapi-security-first-3380</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rubenmarcus/getting-started-with-next-js-strapi-security-first-3380"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why worry about Security?


Before starting to see about Strapi's Content-Types, before looking at Next.js' file and route structure, it's good to discuss Security.
A concern that usually is not followed up with due attention in certain teams, and that can cause a very high cost, when a project is put into production.
This article is another introductory article to the Next.js + Strapi stack, we will also cover TypeScript, Data Fetch, Layouts, CI / CD and Deploy, but first of all we will cover security.
Bel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruben Marcus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create games using TypeScript, Snowpack, and ESLint with this template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paulasantamaria/create-games-using-typescript-snowpack-and-eslint-with-this-template-12ef</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paulasantamaria/create-games-using-typescript-snowpack-and-eslint-with-this-template-12ef"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow me on Twitter or Instagram, you may know I've been trying out Phaser lately. 
Phaser is an open-source game framework that allows you to develop games using HTML and Javascript. 
I've always been interested in Game development, but I hadn't found the time in the past to really get into it. I tried some things with Unity over the years, but I was focused on University and work, so those projects always got left behind at some point. Now that I graduated, I have more time to explore these kinds …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paula Santamaría</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to import JSON files in ES modules (Node.js)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stefanjudis/how-to-import-json-files-in-es-modules-node-js-3b24</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stefanjudis/how-to-import-json-files-in-es-modules-node-js-3b24"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ES modules are still reasonably new in Node.js land (they're stable since Node 14). Modules come with a built-in module system and features such as top-level await. 
I just read an informative post on ES modules by Pawel Grzybek and learned that you can't import JSON files in ES modules today. That's a real bummer because I'm pretty used to doing const data = require('./some-file.json') in Node.js. 
While it will be possible to import JSON from within modules eventually, the implementation is still behind a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Judis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configuring GraphQL for backend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ilakshay/configuring-graphql-for-backend-58f6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ilakshay/configuring-graphql-for-backend-58f6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello from the Dev cave! 🍻
This one is about sharing with you all how I configure GraphQL for my backend. It might help someone, or someone might have a better idea and would increase my knowledge.
I also did one about how I configure and consume on frontend and here is a link to that post.
For my setup, I use NodesJS & Apollo Server with MongoDB. You can find its docs and read more about Apollo here.
You need three main things to implement GraphQL - 
Something that can understand the GraphQL spec, impleme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lakshay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching in Node.js using Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/caching-in-node-js-using-redis-2o80</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/franciscomendes10866/caching-in-node-js-using-redis-2o80"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time we are going to implement caching in an existing node.js application using Redis, but first let's understand what it is and how it can help you.
Cache is a high-speed data storage layer, so that future requests for that data are served up faster than is possible by accessing the primary data storage location, such as a database.
The data in a cache is usually stored on fast-access hardware, such as RAM and its primary function is to increase data recovery performance.
Unlike databases, in which da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Mendes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent activity in your github profile readme]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/baalkrshna/recent-activity-in-your-github-profile-readme-2pmo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/baalkrshna/recent-activity-in-your-github-profile-readme-2pmo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to add your recent activity list in your github profile readme?
Don't know what is github profile readme? Then visit github's official docs on profile readme or another unofficial guide on profile readme
 / 
        recent-activity
      
    





This GitHub Action is a Fork of the original GitHub Activity Readme Action by jamesgeorge007.

The core feature of this GitHub Action is to update your Profile README file, or any Markdown file, with the latest activities you made on GitHub.
Issues (O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Puneet Gopinath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Docker commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/steadylearner/how-to-use-docker-commands-42da</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/steadylearner/how-to-use-docker-commands-42da"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we'll learn how to use Docker commands. We will make a web app inside a Docker container and turn it into a Docker image. We'll also learn how to upload it to Docker Hub.
You can find Portuguese version of this post here.
[Prerequisite]
How to install Docker
Docker Website, Docker Curriculum


How to deploy a container with Docker, Docker lifecycle






First, you must install Docker, if you don't have it yet. Type $docker on your machine and you will be shown how to proceed with the installa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steadylearner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como usar comandos Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/steadylearner/como-usar-comandos-docker-1j76</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/steadylearner/como-usar-comandos-docker-1j76"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T14:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neste post, iremos aprender como usar comandos do Docker. Nós faremos um web app dentro de um container Docker, e depois o transformaremos numa imagem. Também aprenderemos como fazer uploads para o Docker Hub.
Pode ler versão inglês dessa postagem aqui.,
[Pré-requisitos]
Como instalar Docker
Docker Website, Docker Curriculum


Como implantar um container usando o Docker, Ciclo de vida do Docker






Primeiro, você deve instalar o Docker, se você não o tem ainda. Digite $docker no seu computador e será most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steadylearner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel File/Data – Nodejs Express RestAPI – Download/Extract Excel(.xlsx) Data/File from MySQL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/excel-file-data-nodejs-express-restapi-download-extract-excel-xlsx-data-file-from-mysql-1agf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/excel-file-data-nodejs-express-restapi-download-extract-excel-xlsx-data-file-from-mysql-1agf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T13:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/node-js/excel-file-data-nodejs-express-restapi-download-extract-excel-xlsx-data-file-from-mysql
Excel File/Data – Nodejs Express RestAPI – Download/Extract Excel(.xlsx) Data/File from MySQL
In the tutorial, Grokonez shows how to download & extract Excel(.xlsx) File/Data from MySQL with Nodejs Express and exceljs lib.
Related posts:
Node.js Extract MySQL Data to Excel(.xlsx) File – using exceljs
Technologies
nodejs
express
exceljs
mysql
Goal
– We create a Node.js project as below structu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import Excel file/data to MongoDB – using Convert-Excel-to-Json + Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-data-to-mongodb-using-convert-excel-to-json-multer-3dal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-data-to-mongodb-using-convert-excel-to-json-multer-3dal"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/node-js/express/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-data-to-mongodb-using-convert-excel-to-json-multer
Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import Excel file/data to MongoDB – using Convert-Excel-to-Json + Multer
In the tutorial, Grokonez shows how to upload & import Excel File/Data to MongoDB using convert-excel-to-json and multer libs.
Related posts:
Node.js Import Excel File to MongoDB – using Convert-Excel-To-Json lib
Technologies
Node.js
Express
Convert-Excel-To-Json
Multer
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import Excel File to MySQL – using Read-Excel-File & Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-to-mysql-using-read-excel-file-multer-35f4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-to-mysql-using-read-excel-file-multer-35f4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T12:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/node-js/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-excel-file-to-mysql-using-read-excel-file-multer
Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import Excel File to MySQL – using Read-Excel-File & Multer
In the tutorial, Grokonez shows how to upload & import Excel File/Data to MySQL using read-excel-file and multer libs.
Related post:
Node.js Import Excel File to MySQL – using Read-Excel-File lib
Technologies
Nodejs
Express
Multer
Read-Excel-File
MySQL
Goal
We create a Node.js project as below structure:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy with Deployer and Github Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andersbjorkland/how-to-deploy-with-deployer-and-github-actions-k07</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andersbjorkland/how-to-deploy-with-deployer-and-github-actions-k07"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T12:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue


If you have many different projects, jumping between them, coding and pushing to production may be tedious. I know it is, because I have projects that I would rather not touch because then I would have to go through the hoops of updating the production. One project would require me to go into the production server, pull the latest commits from Github and then I would install the dependencies with Composer (yes, I would most often be doing backends with PHP so there are many shared hosting service…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anders Björkland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import CSV File to MySQL – using Fast-CSV & Multer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-csv-file-to-mysql-using-fast-csv-multer-2165</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-csv-file-to-mysql-using-fast-csv-multer-2165"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T12:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/node-js/nodejs-express-restapi-upload-import-csv-file-to-mysql-using-fast-csv-multer
Nodejs Express RestAPI – Upload/Import CSV File to MySQL – using Fast-CSV & Multer
In the tutorial, Grokonez shows how to upload & import CSV File/Data to MySQL using fast-csv and multer libs.
Related post:
Node.js Import CSV File to MySQL – using FastCSV
Technologies
Node.js
Express
MySQL
Multer
Fast-CSV
Goal
We create a Node.js project as below structure:

CSV File ->

id,name,address,age
1,Jack Smith…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Extract MySQL Data to Excel(.xlsx) File – using exceljs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/node-js-extract-mysql-data-to-excel-xlsx-file-using-exceljs-12eg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/node-js-extract-mysql-data-to-excel-xlsx-file-using-exceljs-12eg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T12:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/node-js/node-js-extract-mysql-data-to-excel-xlsx-file-using-exceljs
Node.js Extract MySQL Data to Excel(.xlsx) File – using exceljs
In the tutorial, Grokonez shows how to extract data from MySQL to Excel(.xlsx) File with Node.js using exceljs lib.
Technologies
Node.js
MySQL
exceljs
Goal
– We create a Node.js project as below structure:

– MySQL Data:

– Excel File:

Practice
Install MySQL & Exceljs
Init package.json file by cmd: npm init -> Then install mysql & exceljs libs:

$npm insta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step up your developper game SOLID-ifying your codebase]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bernardstanislas/step-up-your-developper-game-solid-ifying-your-codebase-n1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bernardstanislas/step-up-your-developper-game-solid-ifying-your-codebase-n1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T12:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So recently a friend of mine asked me for help on a NestJs project. He was facing a strong coupling between the business services and TypeORM-related code.
// subscription.service.ts

import { Injectable } from '@nestjs/common';
import { InjectRepository } from '@nestjs/typeorm';
import { Repository } from 'typeorm';
import { User } from 'entities/user.entity';
import { Company } from 'entities/company.entity';
import { Job } from 'entities/job.entity';

@Injectable()
export class SubscriptionService {
  co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanislas Bernard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-Time presigned URLs with Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wojciechmatuszewski/one-time-presigned-urls-with-amazon-cloudfront-and-s3-2iog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wojciechmatuszewski/one-time-presigned-urls-with-amazon-cloudfront-and-s3-2iog"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Context


Amazon S3 is an object storage service that, along with many other features, allows you to create presigned URLs that enable external users to access objects within a given S3 bucket.
While there is a possibility to set an expiration date of the URL, there is no native built-in capability of making it a one-time use resource.
The following is an example of how one could add such capability using building blocks exposed by AWS.

I will be using AWS CDK as my IAC tool of choice and TypeScript as a p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wojciech Matuszewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 tips to an effective code review checklist]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eyalk100/8-tips-to-an-effective-code-review-checklist-3mlh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eyalk100/8-tips-to-an-effective-code-review-checklist-3mlh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T11:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uri Shamay is a close friend and wunderkind with a wealth of experience in the devops field both as a founder and lead developer for a number of organizations. He wrote an excellent post detailing some of the most important aspects to remember when creating a code review checklist, and why it is so important in the development cycle.
Code review is the best way to maintain a high level of code quality. The code review acts not only as a gatekeeper for bad code but also as an incentive for coders to improve …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eyal Katz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way (in 🎥 video): part 13 – Resources's Request & Limit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-13-resources-s-request-limit-2h3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-13-resources-s-request-limit-2h3d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T10:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes can be difficult or time-consuming. In order to spread knowledges about Cloud technologies I started to create sketchnotes about Kubernetes, then I've auto-published a book and since now I've started a new serie of video! :-)
I imagined a serie of short videos with a mix of sketchnotes and speech.
I think it could be a good way, more visual, with audio & video to explain Kubernetes (and others technologies).
This episode is focused on Resources's Request and Limit.




The video is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurélie Vache</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[email setup help]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dupuyinsurance/email-setup-help-3f68</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dupuyinsurance/email-setup-help-3f68"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the manager of Dupuy Insurance, the owner gave me access to his agency email. Shame to write, I'm technological savvy, however I'm having trouble setting up an email. I've done it before, it was fairly simple, however for some reason I'm having a mental block.
The business website if it matters to you is https://dupuyinsurance.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dupuy Insurance</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nullish Coalescing support in Angular template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Devs, 
I am going to explain about Nullish Coalescing (??) . Few days back while reading release details about Angular 12 I just got to know about this new word and how to write cleaner code in typescript. So, now Angular 12 view template is supporting Nullish Coalescing(??)
Let's first understand the meaning of Nullish Coalescing (??). Then how it is supported in Angular 12 version view template. 
What is Nullish Coalescing (??) ? 
Nullish - means null or undefined
Coalescing - means combine (element…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avinash Dalvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nullish Coalescing support in Angular template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/nullish-coalescing-support-in-angular-template-48h6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Devs, 
I am going to explain about Nullish Coalescing (??) . Few days back while reading release details about Angular 12 I just got to know about this new word and how to write cleaner code in typescript. So, now Angular 12 view template is supporting Nullish Coalescing(??)
Let's first understand the meaning of Nullish Coalescing (??). Then how it is supported in Angular 12 version view template. 
What is Nullish Coalescing (??) ? 
Nullish - means null or undefined
Coalescing - means combine (element…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Avinash Dalvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checking github status]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pwd9000/checking-github-status-571m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pwd9000/checking-github-status-571m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T09:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can check the status of github in real-time and historical data on system performance, follow incidents or scheduled maintenance by going to: https://www.githubstatus.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel.L</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Send Slack Notification via   InvokeRESTAPI@1 - Azure DevOps Tricks #2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iainrough/send-slack-notification-via-invokerestapi-1-azure-devops-tricks-2-415n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iainrough/send-slack-notification-via-invokerestapi-1-azure-devops-tricks-2-415n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T06:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Need to send a slack notification from an Azure DevOps pipeline? The InvokeRESTAPI@1 task is one of the most versatile and useful in Azure DevOps. It handles sending messages to Slack in a couple of lines of YAML.

    - task: InvokeRESTAPI@1
      displayName: Slack
      inputs:
        connectionType: 'connectedServiceName'
        serviceConnection: 'Slack'
        method: 'POST'
        body: $body
        urlSuffix: $urlSuffix
        waitForCompletion: 'false'


Project Settings > Pipelines > Service…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iainrough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux beginner to pro Commands Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/linux-beginner-to-pro-commands-part-2-3jb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/linux-beginner-to-pro-commands-part-2-3jb5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to another blog of Linux beginner to pro series.
1.1 We use cp command to copy file. Syntax to copy file goes like cp path_of_file path_of_target_file  . In below example we are going to copy the file hello.txt to hello2.txt
$ cp hello.txt hello2.txt

In above command content of hello.txt is copied to hello2.txt regardless to the existence of file. If file does not exist file will get generated.
1.2 If you want to copy all the files from the folder to another location use -r option as shown in follo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Rawas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali linux + Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gabby1024/kali-linux-windows-2di</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gabby1024/kali-linux-windows-2di"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T15:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it possible to install Kali linux and windows on same computer without using any virtual machine!? And how is it done?(if it possible!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabby Mturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do we build our own OS or not?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/askneilpatel/do-we-build-our-own-os-or-not-1po5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/askneilpatel/do-we-build-our-own-os-or-not-1po5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T07:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are considering to fork Android or create our own OS with Linux for our open source metaverse. 
I’m looking for opinions from the community to help me understand the pros and cons of making this decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes de Pipes e Services]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wesleyegberto/angular-testes-de-pipes-e-services-41jm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T04:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular - Testes Unitários


No post anterior falamos sobre o básico de testes, neste iremos iniciar os testes unitários das estruturas do Angular.
Estruturas que iremos testar:
Pipes
Services
Como mostrado no post anterior os testes de Pipes não tem segredo.
Sempre que possível, é interessante testar todas as possíveis variações dos valores de entrada (limites do domínio de entrada) para que não tenhamos nenhum caso não tratato, pois não saberemos quem poderá utilizar nossa Pipe.
Dado a pipe abaixo no arqu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Egberto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Changing Page title Dynamically]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-changing-page-title-dynamically-anb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T03:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step 1. First we need to import Title service -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";

Step 2. Using setTitle -
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }

All together -
import {Title} from "@angular/platform-browser";
@Component({
 selector: 'app',
 templateUrl: './app.component.html',
 providers : [Title]
})
export class AppComponent implements {
 constructor( private title: Title) {
 this.title.setTitle('page title changed');
 }
}






  
  
  Previe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 software for your Homelab in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aaronktberry/top-10-software-for-your-homelab-in-2021-28e1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T02:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have lots of reasons for what you run your lab but there is an always growing list of new things to try in your homelab or server. Check out this quick list of 10 apps that you can try out and see if you can get some new functionality for free through self-hosting.
Portainer



Docker is a powerful tool that can allow you to host and run apps easily on your servers. Now, docker's main interface is a command-line tool but with an application like Portainer you get a nice GUI interface to manage your …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Berry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physical Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeikabu/physical-security-2nm4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love a good caper film. When I was a wee lad my father introduced me to The Great Train Robbery. Over the years I’ve seen several memorable others Rififi, A World Without Thieves, several by David Mamet like The Spanish Prisoner. Just the other day I watched Inside Man.
Numerous vulnerabilities like Spectre, Man-in-the-middle, SQL injection, keyloggers, phishing and a legion of others have loomed over the IT sphere for decades. Seems like every month there’s a new, “largest ever”, high profile security in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeikabu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parent child communication using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/icelandico/parent-child-communication-using-angular-17pk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T21:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's very common in modern web development to handle the communication between the nearest components. The most obvious data flow is a parent to child. In this post, I'd like to show how to share the data between such components in both directions.
Passing the data down to the children's components is very easy.
app.component.html




<p>Item clicked {{ activeElement }}</p>
<div class="box__container">
  <app-box *ngFor="let box of boxCollection"
           [details]="box"
           [isActive]="box.name ==…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michał Muszyński</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SendGrid? SMTP Email Newsletter Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>609d63e962ab9107fe5aa2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-sendgrid-smpt-email-newsletter-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard of the term SMTP before, and wondered what it is. SMTP is a common method for handling email messages. Today I am going to explain what SMTP is, and how to use an SMTP provider such as SendGrid to send emails from your address. What Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🆔 Identity, Unlocked... Explained: Season 2, Ep 8]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-8-284e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🛡 JWT Profile for OAuth 2.0 Access Tokens with Vittorio Bertocci



  
  
  
In this episode of Identity, Unlocked, the CTO and co-founder of Auth0, Matias Woloski, appears as acting host and interviews Vittorio Bertocci, principal architect at Auth0 and the regular host of Identity, Unlocked, on the JWT profiles for OAuth2 access tokens specification. 
This spec describes how to encode OAuth2 access tokens in use JWT format in an interoperable way, by giving a minimal list of claims, how to emit a JWT dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React for Beginners: Complete React Cheatsheet for 2021]]></title>
        <id>609ea83362ab9107fe5aa920</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-for-beginners-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the React for Beginners guide. It's designed to teach you all the core React concepts that you need to know to start building React applications in 2021. I created this resource to give you the most complete and beginner-friendly path to learn React from the ground up. By]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 14th May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-14th-may-2021-4ng6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time waits for no one. It feels like yesterday since the last edition of this round-up only for me to check, and it's 2 weeks already, and I am like: Are you kidding me?
What more could I say? Let's move on.
Hopefully, I can keep track of time and I will be here next week to say: "Yeah I made it this week".
Introduction


This week it's everything security.
Foxit Reader bug lets attackers run malicious code via PDFs


Foxit Reader comes pre-installed on some laptop computers. If you (or anyone else) use Fox…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps -Automate & Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is the practice of integrating a security-first mindset and methodologies into traditional DevOps CI / CD environments. Here are key best practices for organizations seeking to implement DevSecOps.
Being able to get code out the door fast, secure, and efficiently is the name of the game. In a CI/CD environment, it’s important to maintain speed as the main tenet but also to be aware of the security needed to bulk up your pipeline. Without automation, implementing security practices could be a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Bhanushali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps -Automate & Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sidbhanushali/devsecops-automate-secure-5ae4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T19:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevSecOps is the practice of integrating a security-first mindset and methodologies into traditional DevOps CI / CD environments. Here are key best practices for organizations seeking to implement DevSecOps.
Being able to get code out the door fast, secure, and efficiently is the name of the game. In a CI/CD environment, it’s important to maintain speed as the main tenet but also to be aware of the security needed to bulk up your pipeline. Without automation, implementing security practices could be a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth Bhanushali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Lofi Club - Enjoy Hip hop beats to Relax or Code! 🎧]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saviomartin/introducing-lofi-club-enjoy-hip-hop-beats-to-relax-or-code-11ij</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saviomartin/introducing-lofi-club-enjoy-hip-hop-beats-to-relax-or-code-11ij"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Devs 👋


This is Savio here. I'm young dev with an intention to enhance as a successful web developer. I love building web apps with React. I have proved my superiority in frontend technologies. Today, I'd like to share my latest project Lofi Club
I'm a big fan of lofi music, In fact, many of us are. Lo-fi is a music or production quality in which elements usually regarded as imperfections of a recording or performance are audible, sometimes as a deliberate aesthetic choice. Hearing to lofi music mak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Savio Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorization mechanisms in Rust web applications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ddtkey/authorization-mechanisms-in-rust-web-applications-27ag</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ddtkey/authorization-mechanisms-in-rust-web-applications-27ag"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T18:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To ensure application security, we use mechanisms such as authentication and authorization. I think many of you are familiar with these concepts and in this article we will focus on the concept of authorization and related access control models.

Definitions of terms used in the article
  
It's important to understand the difference between authorization and authentication:
Authentication – a process of verifying your identity and proving that you are a user of the system (by means of a password, token or a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artem Medvedev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Development for Beginners – Learn Basic HTML and CSS to Build Your First Web Page]]></title>
        <id>609e8c2162ab9107fe5aa77d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-development-for-beginners-basic-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T17:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how websites are built and designed? Do you want to learn the art of web development but you're not that tech savvy – yet? Well, then this tutorial is for you. It's an introduction to Web Development for beginners so you can learn the basics even if]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH Azure Linux VM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mohan023/how-to-ssh-azure-linux-vm-4k9l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mohan023/how-to-ssh-azure-linux-vm-4k9l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T16:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm glad to write this post about my experience in connecting linux vm. Below are the number of steps to be taken. Keeping this short and simple.
Create Linux VM on Azure


Enable SSH connectivity 

You must enable port 22 for SSH connectivity and create VM with default options.


Download Private Key as prompted. It will be .pem file.


Once downloaded, VM will be created for you. Go to Virtual Machine-->Settings-->Connect




Now here is a twist. People don't know how to use that .pem file downloaded as g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohan Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular forms - NEVER rely on a disabled "submit" button!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're just writing some Angular code.
A form.
That form has some required fields, like email and password.
Your "submit" button is disabled until the form is valid, by using <button type="submit" [disabled]="myForm.invalid">, which you can find in many stackoverflow answers.
You're safe - the feature is working, a user isn't able to submit an invalid form.
Actually, you're not.
Now, try opening the dev console in your browser and manually removing the disabled attribute from the "submit" button.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Manista</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular forms - NEVER rely on a disabled "submit" button!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mmanista/angular-forms-never-rely-on-a-disabled-submit-button-47dd"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're just writing some Angular code.
A form.
That form has some required fields, like email and password.
Your "submit" button is disabled until the form is valid, by using <button type="submit" [disabled]="myForm.invalid">, which you can find in many stackoverflow answers.
You're safe - the feature is working, a user isn't able to submit an invalid form.
Actually, you're not.
Now, try opening the dev console in your browser and manually removing the disabled attribute from the "submit" button.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maciej Manista</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Line filter program that removes digits]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gonzalezlrjesus/line-filter-program-that-removes-digits-3005</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gonzalezlrjesus/line-filter-program-that-removes-digits-3005"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📌 A filter is a program that gets data from standard input, performs some manipulation of the data, and then writes its results to standard output.
📌 Most common functions:
▶️ Convert data to a different format
📌 Unix has many filter programs, most common are: cat, cut, grep,
Go Playground: https://play.golang.org/p/s8FwQRkZXdr]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Gonzalez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple arrow operators in a single function]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/multiple-arrow-operators-in-a-single-function-551d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/earthboundmisfit/multiple-arrow-operators-in-a-single-function-551d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T15:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We may have come across arrow functions in javascript and are almost saturated learning about the difference between normal functions and arrow functions, the difference between ES5 and ES6 and everything that is connected to it. But everytime we come across multiple arrows in a single function, we keep struggling - or it could just be a "me" problem. Here goes, what multiple arrows in a function mean.
A simple ES6 function that demonstrates it:-
const add = x => y => x + y

This can be written in ES5 funct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muzammil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : Getting through that pesky company proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-getting-through-that-pesky-company-proxy-fp5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-getting-through-that-pesky-company-proxy-fp5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are attempting to get an Angular site running on your Windows work computer at XYZ Company the chances are that you are having problems getting through the company proxy.
There are (at least) two package managers that need to get through the proxy:
NPM
Typings
For NPM you need to add the following lines to the .npmrc file:
proxy=http://[DOMAIN]%5C[USER]:[PASS]@[PROXY]:[PROXYPORT]/
https-proxy=http://[DOMAIN]%5C[USER]:[PASS]@[PROXY]:[PROXYPORT]/

For Typings you need to add the following lines to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shifting Left of Bang to Improve Your DevOps Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nextlinklabs/shifting-left-of-bang-to-improve-your-devops-security-bok</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nextlinklabs/shifting-left-of-bang-to-improve-your-devops-security-bok"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early 2000s, the US Marine Corps' Combat Hunter training program introduced, among many other concepts, the ‘left of bang’ idea as a way to improve situational awareness and save lives.
The way ‘left of bang’ works is simple.
Any critical event that causes significant disruption, loss, or other negative outcome -- an attack, injury, or breach of security -- can be mapped out and analyzed on a timeline. The actual occurrence of the event -- the thing that happened -- falls directly in the middle of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nextlink Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340343</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-stylesheet-feature-flags-with-sass-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[!default is a Sass flag that indicates conditional assignment to a variable — it assigns a value only if the variable was previously undefined or null. Consider this code snippet:
$variable: 'test' !default;
To the Sass compiler, this line …
The post Creating Stylesheet Feature Flags With Sass !default appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Babcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Boilerplates]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340403</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-boilerplates/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzović goes line-by-line through a boilerplate HTML document. I like it. It’s a good reference and has a lot of the same type of stuff I tend to put in the main HTML template. It makes me think about …
The post HTML Boilerplates appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Video] Introduction to Git and GitHub Crash Course + Giveaway ⭐]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/video-introduction-to-git-and-github-crash-course-giveaway-3jjh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/video-introduction-to-git-and-github-crash-course-giveaway-3jjh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T14:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello everybody! Welcome to this Introduction to Git and GitHub video series, where you will learn the basics of Git and start using it for your day-to-day tasks.
My name is Bobby and I've been working as a Linux system administrator for the past 7 years and a few months ago I wrote an opensource eBook on how to get started with Git and GitHub.
You can find a link to the GitHub project where you can Download the eBook for free here:
Opensource eBook on how to get started with Git and GitHub
I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Vs Bootstrap- A Comparison Of Frontend Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ltdsolace/angular-vs-bootstrap-a-comparison-of-frontend-frameworks-2gig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ltdsolace/angular-vs-bootstrap-a-comparison-of-frontend-frameworks-2gig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T13:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this competitive market, a creative and responsive UI plays a vital role in the success of web solutions. So for developers, it is important to choose the best frontend framework for app development. Angular and Bootstrap are the two popular frameworks used by developers, but choosing the best one for a project is not an easy task. Angular is a TypeScript based framework with immense codes and vast tools for app development whereas Bootstrap is an HTML/CSS/JS framework with ready-made components. The fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solace Infotech Pvt. Ltd.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are your tools for keeping dependencies and plugins versions up-to-date?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cfecherolle/what-are-your-tools-for-keeping-dependencies-and-plugins-versions-up-to-date-126g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cfecherolle/what-are-your-tools-for-keeping-dependencies-and-plugins-versions-up-to-date-126g"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone!
I rarely post here but today I decided to ask the community about some tooling.
One thing that I find daunting in today's web dev ecosystem is how to keep track of dependencies and plugin versions in all layers of our apps and, say, not miss a lot of versions for one tool or the other.
For example, in the project I'm working on, we have a front-end app made with React, a Java/Spring Boot back-end, a Keycloak authentication system, and so on.
So I was asking myself: is there some kind of tool to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cécile Fécherolle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do you need CIAM?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-do-you-need-ciam-28pa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/why-do-you-need-ciam-28pa"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T12:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how customer identity and access management (CIAM) helps you balance security, privacy, and experience for all users.



  
  
  
Customer experiences happen primarily online. If this wasn’t completely true for your business before 2020, it’s probably true now. Companies have come to understand that a seamless digital experience is no longer a competitive differentiator; it’s a baseline requirement.
Moreover, pressure-cooker economic conditions during the pandemic have shown that companies that unders…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Google Social Login or Sign In Tutorial using angularx-social-login]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/angular-11-google-social-login-or-sign-in-tutorial-using-angularx-social-login-55of</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/angular-11-google-social-login-or-sign-in-tutorial-using-angularx-social-login-55of"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, We at Bacancy Technology, shared a tutorial about how you can implement the Google Social Login with the use of the angular-social-login library which is available in angular. In Angular 9+, you can easily implement this technique. But if you want to implement this in older versions of Angular, it asks for a few modifications in the code(especially in the module.ts file). 
Do you know about the benefits or we can say what is the magic in this tutorial of social login, here you can sign in to the appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bacancy Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : conditional class with *ngClass]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-conditional-class-with-ngclass-3kf2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/angular-conditional-class-with-ngclass-3kf2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is NgClass?


Adds and removes CSS classes on an HTML element.
Angular provides several ways to add classes conditionally:
[class.my_class] = "step === 'step1'"

[ngClass]="{'my_class': step === 'step1'}"

[ngClass]="{'my_class': step === 'step1', 'my_class2' : step === 'step2' }"

[ngClass]="{1 : 'my_class1', 2 : 'my_class2', 3 : 'my_class4'}[step]"

[ngClass]="step == 'step1' ? 'my_class1' : 'my_class2'"

Based on the Official Documentation 
The CSS classes are updated as follows, depending on the ty…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/how-to-use-vim-g1o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/how-to-use-vim-g1o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is a powerful text editor used by programmers and system administrators as a command line interface. Vim is widely used by Linux users. It is also available in Windows, Mac OS X and every other Unix system.
The reason why it is that popular is that vim allows the programmer to code efficiently without leaving the editor. When coding, you don't need to use your mouse. This sounds simple, but this is exactly what any programmer wants from an editor.
Most of its commands are robust and cryptic enough to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking wireless access points]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rootsec1/hacking-wireless-access-points-598j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rootsec1/hacking-wireless-access-points-598j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T07:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know how to hack WiFi access points -- just read this step by step aircrack-ng tutorial, run the verified commands and crack passwords easily.
With the help a these commands you will be able to hack WiFi AP (access points) that use WPA/WPA2-PSK (pre-shared key) encryption.
The basis of this method of hacking WiFi lies in capturing of the WPA/WPA2 authentication handshake and then cracking the PSK using 'aircrack-ng'.
 Download and install the latest aircrack-ng

 Start the wireless interface …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340490</id>
        <link href="https://chenhuijing.com/blog/devtools-for-css-layouts-2021-edition/#%F0%9F%9A%B2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Hui Jing covers some recent movement in DevTools:
Firefox’s grid inspector was pretty full-featured from the get-to and released together with CSS grid in Firefox 52. It was constantly improved upon since. Chrome added a basic grid inspector 
…
The post DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340573</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2021-design-systems-survey-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friends at Sparkbox are doing a survey on design systems, as they do each year. Go ahead and fill it out if you please. Here are the results from last year. In both 2019 and 2020, the vibe was …
The post 2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Email Newsletter [2021 Tutorial] – Design, Layout, Send]]></title>
        <id>609414f32cd0545b5e943526</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-email-newsletter-design-layout-send/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T21:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a large community, chances are you need a way to communicate updates to your members quickly and efficiently. An email newsletter can be a very effective way to do so. In this article, I am going to provide some tips and suggestions for maximizing the impact and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? The 10 Most Common Types of Tests Developers Use in Projects]]></title>
        <id>609952396008950828b3ea8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and testing go hand in hand. And in the era of agile software development, with quick releases of small iterations, you should do testing more and more frequently.  In order to perform effective testing, you need to know about the different types of testing and when you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Tutorial – How to Work with Multiple Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>609bcc6a62ab9107fe5a9f08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-multiple-checkboxes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling multiple checkboxes in React is completely different from how you use regular HTML checkboxes. So in this article, we'll see how to work with multiple checkboxes in React. You will learn: How to use a checkbox as a Controlled Input in ReactHow to use the array map and reduce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Lawyer to Engineer at Google – How to Switch Careers and Learn New Skills]]></title>
        <id>609ccb0d62ab9107fe5aa0ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-lawyer-to-google-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a corporate lawyer for 12 years. I never thought I'd be working at Google as a software engineer, but that's what I have been doing for the past year. I'm working remotely until COVID subsides and we can move to San Francisco.  In this article I'm going to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340036</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/advanced-css-animation-using-cubic-bezier/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with complex CSS animations, there is a tendency to create expansive @keyframes with lots of declarations. There are a couple of tricks though that I want to talk about that might help make things easier, while staying in …
The post Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svgator-3-0-reshapes-the-way-you-create-and-animate-svg-with-extensive-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building animations can get complicated, particularly compelling animations where you aren’t just rolling a ball across the screen, but building a scene where many things are moving and changing in concert. When compelling animation is the goal, a timeline GUI …
The post SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Portfolio with Vue.js Axios, the GitHub REST API, and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>5fde208ae6787e09839407c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-portfolio-with-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this free book, we will build two simple projects and deploy them on Netlify. We will use Vue.js as our front-end framework, and use different technologies to build our projects.  If you follow this tutorial to the end, you will build a simplified version of Twitter and a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the Kivy Python Library to Create Games and Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>609c215862ab9107fe5a9fa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-the-kivy-python-library-to-create-games-and-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kivy is a free and open source Python framework for developing mobile apps and games with a natural user interface. We just released a 5-hour Kivy course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this Kivy course, you will learn to create games and applications with Python for every platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339960</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-disabled-buttons-more-inclusive/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about disabled buttons. Specifically, let’s get into why we use them and how we can do better than the traditional disabled attribute in HTML (e.g. <button disabled> ) to mark a button as disabled.
There are lots of …
The post Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandrina Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Selenium and Python to Scrape Websites More Effectively]]></title>
        <id>6096aafe2cd0545b5e944430</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-web-scraping-with-selenium/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're scraping data from the web with Python, Selenium will often come up as an helpful tool to use. It was originally designed for automated testing, but its scraping capabilities are impressive, too. This is because Selenium can do things that other libraries or frameworks often can't when collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-pie-timer-re-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitty reflected on an ancient blog post here on CSS-Tricks on how to make an animated pie timer. The old technique is still clever. The new technique is equally clever and much easier. I particularly like the steps() animation function…
The post CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I could build this during the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340186</id>
        <link href="https://world.hey.com/joaoqalves/i-could-build-this-during-the-weekend-aa093c5e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you heard that (or even uttered it under your own breath)? I know I’ve heard it in conversations. I also know I’ve wondered the same thing about a product or two — hey, the idea here …
The post I could build this during the weekend appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Gen CSS: @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-gen-css-container/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome is experimenting with @container, a property within the CSS Working Group Containment Level 3 spec being championed by Miriam Suzanne of Oddbird, and a group of engineers across the web platform. @container brings us the ability to …
The post Next Gen CSS: @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Una Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340106</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/distributed-persistent-rendering-dpr/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Jamstack, Netlify is coining this term.
If your reaction is: great, a new thing I need to know about and learn, know that while Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) does involve some new things, this is actually a push …
The post Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topframe]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/topframe/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is extremely fun. Jeff Lindsay has created Topframe, and writes:
Anybody that knows how to mess around with HTML can now mess around with their desktop computing experience. Topframe is an open source tool that lets you 
…
The post Topframe appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340208</id>
        <link href="https://benfrain.com/migrating-from-parcel-to-snowpack-build-tool-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find build tooling endlessly interesting, especially right now as we’re in a juicy next-gen transitional period with players like Vite, wmr, Snowpack, and esbuild. Hugh Haworth has a good run-down of the new players, and we’ve chatted on …
The post Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339203</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/variable-aspect-ratio-card-with-conic-gradients-meeting-along-the-diagonal/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across an interesting problem. I had to implement a grid of cards with a variable (user-set) aspect ratio that was stored in a --ratio custom property. Boxes with a certain aspect ratio are a classic problem in …
The post Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.6]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: The output website didn't have favicon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>