<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-24T01:06:20.381Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-24T01:06:20.381Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.8.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS Event Emitter]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/julianopadilha/nodejs-event-emitter-4l04</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/julianopadilha/nodejs-event-emitter-4l04"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T00:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O que é o Event Emitter?


Event Emitter é um módulo do NodeJS que nos ajuda a criar um padrão de publisher-subscriber.
Com um Event Emitter podemos simplesmente criar um evento de qualquer parte de uma aplicação, escutar este evento e tomar alguma ação baseado nele.

Para criar um event emitter é preciso instanciar o EventEmitter do módulo events no NodeJS.
const { EventEmitter } = require('events');

const eventEmitter = new EventEmitter();

Esse é o básico para criar um event emitter. Mas o que podemos fazer com ele? 🤔
A classe do EventEmitter têm uma série de métodos e podemos usá-los para publicar e ouvir eventos. Por hora, focaremos em dois deles:
emit(eventName...)
on(eventName...)
Para publicar um evento nós utilizamos o método emit(). Já para ouvir, utilizamos o método on(). E a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juliano Padilha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualizing Memory]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thesystemsprogrammer/virtualizing-memory-4b0m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thesystemsprogrammer/virtualizing-memory-4b0m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T00:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article, we asked ourselves how the operating system gives each process the illusion that it has its own address space despite only having one hardware RAM. This is one of the most important and most complicated virtualization techniques that the operating system performs. Because of that we will discuss memory virtualization in three separate articles. The goals of the operating system with respect to memory are as follows:
Give processes a contiguous address space
Give processes memory isolation from each other
Do both of the above efficiently with respect to memory usage and processing speed
Let’s first talk about what memory is. Memory can be thought of as a series of slots. 32-bit memory has 32-bit slots and 64-bit memory has 64-bit slots. The size of a computer’s memory c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thesystemsprogrammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn OpenStack by example: Part 0 - Summary and Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wsidl/learn-openstack-by-examples-part-0-summary-and-goals-p84</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wsidl/learn-openstack-by-examples-part-0-summary-and-goals-p84"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T23:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My whole career up to this point has been built around designing and developing applications for offline or isolated networks and working with severely outdated operating systems with no external dependencies allowed. So when I moved into a new role working on cloud deployments, I took it as an opportunity to learn cloud development and deployments. It didn't take me long to run into a bunch of headaches that comes with working on these platforms.
While searching for solutions and documentation on the various problems I've come across, I would often see references to OpenStack and it got my curiosity going. What is OpenStack? What services does it offer and who owns it? How do I learn to use it? What are it's costs and limitations?

Without going into too much history or detail, OpenStack …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Siddall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditsmod - new NodeJS webframework writen in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T22:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivation to create Ditsmod


Before creating Ditsmod, of course, I was looking for: "Are there ready-made solutions for my purposes?".
I believe that the set of the following features is unique at the moment:
The framework is written in TypeScript (and under the hood there is no ExpressJS or Fastify ;).
Modular architecture with decorators.
Has a hierarchical Dependency Injection that allows you to use classes as a search token, rather than their names.
Clearly delineated providers arrays for DI injectors at the application, module, route, or request level.
Built-in support for nested routes, such as /api/posts/:postId/comments/:commentId.
Check for collisions when importing providers. This feature allows you to detect situations where you import two or more modules that export providers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Костя Третяк</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditsmod - new NodeJS webframework writen in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kostyatretyak/ditsmod-new-nodejs-webframework-writen-in-typescript-19j2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T22:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motivation to create Ditsmod


Before creating Ditsmod, of course, I was looking for: "Are there ready-made solutions for my purposes?".
I believe that the set of the following features is unique at the moment:
The framework is written in TypeScript (and under the hood there is no ExpressJS or Fastify ;).
Modular architecture with decorators.
Has a hierarchical Dependency Injection that allows you to use classes as a search token, rather than their names.
Clearly delineated providers arrays for DI injectors at the application, module, route, or request level.
Built-in support for nested routes, such as /api/posts/:postId/comments/:commentId.
Check for collisions when importing providers. This feature allows you to detect situations where you import two or more modules that export providers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Костя Третяк</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to validate environmental variables in Node.js (with Typescript)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-validate-environmental-variables-in-node-js-with-typescript-1b1a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-validate-environmental-variables-in-node-js-with-typescript-1b1a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T21:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source code: Github





  
  
  The baseline project


This post assumes you are following along with the baseline project tutorial, but the concepts apply to any Typescript project.
Currently, we are storing the configuration for our application externally, in environmental variables. This is beneficial, because it allows us to change our app configuration without changing any of the code in our codebase.
However, we want to ensure that all of the environmental variables needed for our app to run are set when our app starts. Otherwise, our app might start initially, then crash due to an error when a variable is unexpectedly undefined.
It would also be nice to export a single config object that we can use throughout our application, instead of having to reference process.env.VARIABLE_NAME…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to validate environmental variables in Node.js (with Typescript)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-validate-environmental-variables-in-node-js-with-typescript-1b1a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-validate-environmental-variables-in-node-js-with-typescript-1b1a"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T21:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source code: Github





  
  
  The baseline project


This post assumes you are following along with the baseline project tutorial, but the concepts apply to any Typescript project.
Currently, we are storing the configuration for our application externally, in environmental variables. This is beneficial, because it allows us to change our app configuration without changing any of the code in our codebase.
However, we want to ensure that all of the environmental variables needed for our app to run are set when our app starts. Otherwise, our app might start initially, then crash due to an error when a variable is unexpectedly undefined.
It would also be nice to export a single config object that we can use throughout our application, instead of having to reference process.env.VARIABLE_NAME…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Devops 2019.1 Build Agent running on a pod in my Kubernetes cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stevesims2/azure-devops-2019-1-build-agent-running-on-a-pod-in-my-kubernetes-cluster-4m8c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stevesims2/azure-devops-2019-1-build-agent-running-on-a-pod-in-my-kubernetes-cluster-4m8c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T20:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a "toy" I decided to try and revive an old version of Microsoft's Azure Pipelines Agent on an image from before they made that Azure Services Only.   However, I updated the agent on the ubuntu-16.04-tfs-2018-u2 image to a later version of the linux agent.  (2.140.2)
https://hub.docker.com/_/microsoft-azure-pipelines-vsts-agent
I had to also update the Team Explorer Everywhere (TEE/TEE-cli) that was embedded in that to the latest version. And upgrade java to version 11.   But once that was done, it works well.  Its a tad on the large size for an image.  (1gb), but it seems ok on its memory and CPU usage.  See the kubebox graph at the bottom.


Does anyone think this could be more than just a toy ?  I'm a novice at most Kubernetes stuff compared to the folks here, but I wanted to share this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SteveSims2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ծրագրային անվտանգություն՝ SQL Injection (մաս 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-2-46g9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-2-46g9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T19:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Նախորդ գրառման մեջ տեսանք SQL Injection խոցելիության ընդհանուր բնութագիրը։ Այժմ փորձենք OWASP Juice Shop խոցելի վեբ֊ծրագրում փնտրել տվյալ տեսակի խոցելիություններ։
Ծրագիրը արխիվի տեսքով կարելի է ներբեռնել նախագծի GitHub էջից, այնուհետև npm start հրամանի միջոցով գործարկել այն (նախապես npm install հրամանով տեղադրելով ծրագրի պահանջված գրադարանները)։ Գործարկվելիս, Juice Shop֊ը հասանելի է դառնում localhost:3000 հասցեով։ 
Առաջին հերթին կարելի է ուշադրություն դարձնել Account հղմամբ գտնվող մուտք գործման (login) հատվածին և այստեղ փորձել SQL injection֊ի պարզագույն տարբերակ՝
email: ' OR 1=1 --
password: test

Ստանում ենք հաջողված մուտք ադմինիստրատորի օգտահաշվով, այսինքն տվյալ ծրագրի login էջի email դաշտը ենթակա է SQL injection հարձակման։ 
Փորձենք հասկանալ ինչու է առաջանում տվյալ խոցելիությունը։ Juice …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Narek Babajanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Awesome Thing You Can Build With Node.Js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thevikcode/7-awesome-thing-you-can-build-with-node-js-1ke</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thevikcode/7-awesome-thing-you-can-build-with-node-js-1ke"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T19:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js is not just for making simple websites, but awesome, dynamic, real-time experiences. Here are some Node.js project ideas to spark your inspiration:
GIF Chat Room


Build your Own Zoom


Job Search App


Collaborative Drawing Tool


Covid-19 Tracker



At last I want to say that this is just some of the example I gave to you there's anything you can build.
THANKS FOR CHECKING OUT :D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Aditya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't keep me waiting]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vjnvisakh/don-t-keep-me-waiting-3jh9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vjnvisakh/don-t-keep-me-waiting-3jh9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T19:09:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem


We were working on this project where we had to upload n products to an ecommerce application. Sure it isn't such a big deal. The catch was we had to scrape the data from another place and upload to another place. And for some reason the upload APIs were damnnnnnn slow. 
Our UI was the simplest. It had a white screen with a button that said "Scrape & Up". Little did the client know so many things happened behind it. Yes am an obsessed backend dev. Anyways the problem was the user experience. We couldn't just show a loader to the user while the products were uploaded. At any moment we might have from 10 to 10,000 products. If we decided to show a loader for 10k product upload, there was high chance the user might get hypnotized by looking at the loader. 
So here is what we dec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visakh Vijayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feature flags for Infrastructure as Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leading-edje/feature-flags-for-infrastructure-as-code-4hi8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leading-edje/feature-flags-for-infrastructure-as-code-4hi8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T18:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature what?


Feature flags or toggles are often* used in application code to allow for rapid integration of new changes without necessarily enabling them in production.
*I have no real idea how commonly used they really are
Feature flags can prevent the dreaded long running feature branch that keeps accumulating changes that you hold off from merging because you're not ready for it to go into production in the next release.
These same challenges can apply to your Infrastructure as Code (IaC) where having changes to shared resources you want to test in a lower environment but aren't ready to promote to production can be a real problem.
Consider this scenario:
You're making changes to your network in a cloud environment.
You've got your changes in a development environment and everything …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew May</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Guide to Hacking Tetcore Nodes]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marlonhanks/the-guide-to-hacking-tetcore-nodes-8jf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marlonhanks/the-guide-to-hacking-tetcore-nodes-8jf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T18:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tetcoin is the Currency for Change and is now built using the Tetcore Framework.  For more information about Tetcore, visit the Tetcore Developer Hub at https://core.tetcoin.org or https://github.com/tetcore

Please be aware that even though Tetcoin started in 2014, outside factors led to halt of its production in 2016.  Development of the Tetcoin Family of Cryptocurrencies resumed in October of 2020.  This group is made of the XDV, Payshares, Metrocoin, Czarcoin, Vapory, Lite, and Tetcoin blockchains.  Metrocoin is currently being redesigned as a Tetcoin Parachain boostrapped off the Vapory Network.
The Tetcore Army of Two still has a lot of work to do.  As a result, it is a known fact that over 10 Million Links in the Source Repositories need updating along with all Tetcoin Family Websit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marlon Hanks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Testing with Cypress: Part 2 - Creating your tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/murillowelsi/api-testing-with-cypress-part-2-creating-your-tests-270i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/murillowelsi/api-testing-with-cypress-part-2-creating-your-tests-270i"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T18:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello again guys!!


Moving forward with the subject we discussed in the previous post, let's focus on to the part that is most important to us, the tests.
The resources of a microservice based applications can be manipulated in several ways. It is possible to create, update, delete them, and do other operations as well.
When we send a request for a service, we need to inform the URI to identify which resources we intend to handle. We also need to inform the type of manipulation we want to do on the resource. For this, we will use the HTTP protocol methods.
The HTTP protocol has several methods, each one has a different function. The most used are:
GET: retrieve data for a resource.
POST: create a new resource.
PUT: make a change to a specific resource that already exists.
PATCH: partially…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murillo Welsi de Souza Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SELECT PATH OF FOLDER OR DIRECTORY USING JAVASCRPT OR ANGULAR]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/biq12/select-path-of-folder-or-directory-using-javascrpt-or-angular-40p4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/biq12/select-path-of-folder-or-directory-using-javascrpt-or-angular-40p4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T16:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i like to select a path in local drive , the probleme if i choose a directory if it s empty the code nto work if it not empty it work fine 
//  input type="file"   name="currentselectedFile"  (change)="onFileSelected($event)"   webkitDirectory directory multiple 
onFileSelected(event){
 var theFiles = event.target.files;
 var relativePath = theFiles[0].webkitRelativePath;
}
// if the path it s not empty all it s ok]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>biq12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NanoID - Alternative To UUID]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bibekkakati/nanoid-alternative-to-uuid-2kgn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bibekkakati/nanoid-alternative-to-uuid-2kgn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T16:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey coders 👋
If you are a JavaScript developer, I am pretty much sure that you have used the npm package UUID at least once in your development journey.
For those who don't know what is UUID. It is an npm package to generate a unique string ID. Similar packages are available in other languages too.
But in this article I am not going to discuss UUID, rather I will discuss another awesome npm package to generate a unique ID known as NanoID.
A tiny, secure, URL-friendly, unique string ID generator for JavaScript.
It is smaller in size as it has no dependencies.
It is 60% faster than UUID.
It uses cryptographically strong random APIs.
It uses a larger alphabet than UUID (A-Za-z0-9_-).
We can control the behaviour of alphabets to be used.
NanoID is available in almost all the most used program…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bibek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly discoveries #1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/grossetfloriane/weekly-discoveries-1-4im7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/grossetfloriane/weekly-discoveries-1-4im7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T16:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a young and self-taught freelance web developer and designer, learning and expanding my knowledge is part of my job. Every weeks comes with its series of discoveries and lessons, which I am happy to share. Maybe they sounds like facts you have known since forever, or  maybe they are new things for you as well. If you know it already, please don't take it for granted by everybody and teach the ones who need it. 
Since I was a child, I only experienced Windows and Mac Os and it is only recently that I started on Linux with a Debian system. It happened that working on Debian was the only way for me to install node.js and make React working.
So, after a few days working on a React project, something wrong happened on my computer and I got locked out of my session for ever. I tried to repair…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>grosset-floriane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Developer discovers Redux-Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/angular-developer-discovers-redux-toolkit-3bn8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sumodevelopment/angular-developer-discovers-redux-toolkit-3bn8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T15:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an Angular developer, one of my biggest challenges was shifting my thought process from mutable-, to immutable state.
In an Angular service, you can simply assign a new value to a property, and like magic - the change detection would kick in and update any component using the property. 
Switching over to React, suddenly immutable state is the way to go! Then, suddenly Redux - actions, reducers, middleware, dispatchers, and the list goes on. 
The first time I saw Redux toolkit, the very first thing that hit me, in Reducers:
...
reducers: {
    increment: state => {
        state.value += 1;
    }
}
...

Assignment operator in a Reducer? For a brief moment I thought I somehow ended up in the Vuex documentation, this is how you update state in mutations. But No, it was Redux Toolkit. 
I fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dewald Els</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Js Node (Helmet.js)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/feco2019/node-js-helmet-js-4n9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/feco2019/node-js-helmet-js-4n9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T14:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there guys!
As the days going through and summer is nearest a lot of you
Today, i will focus in one depedency called Helmet.js is open repo
helmet-repo which helping us provide some
You can use npm or yarn i will head with npm so simple we can install it npm install helmet --save and save it globally.
So if you already have an express server running,you can just
const express = require("express");
const helmet = require("helmet");

const app = express();

app.use(helmet());

// ...

Helmet is a function used as  middleware and is wrapping 11 smaller middleware's,sets HTTP Headers,origin validations and some other stuff to avoid multiple attacks on your website-webapp.
So the above app.use(helmet());  is equivalent to this
app.use(helmet.contentSecurityPolicy());
app.use(helmet.dnsPre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dimitris Chitas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Referential Data Validations with yupjs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mrsauravsahu/referential-data-validations-with-yupjs-3ieb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mrsauravsahu/referential-data-validations-with-yupjs-3ieb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T14:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Validation?


Data validation is the process of checking whether a given value fits certain criteria based on its business requirements.
For any input - a UI input field or an API input body, data validation is crucial. Any arbitrary input should never be trusted. And data validation plays a vital role in making sure these inputs are rigorously funnelled through the right pipes before they create unintended side-effects in our applications.
In JavaScript projects, both the browser and node.js, that is, there are several npm packages available to do data validation. I've personally used joi and yupjs.
joi was my goto choice for Data Validation for a long time. It worked really well with hapijs and has a great community around it. Trust me, I don't have anything against joi, it'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sahu, S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux Package Management Beginner's Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/flyingcakes/arch-linux-package-management-beginner-s-cheat-sheet-3kb8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/flyingcakes/arch-linux-package-management-beginner-s-cheat-sheet-3kb8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T14:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Arch Linux comes with a powerful package manager called pacman. Often new users take time to figure out its commands because it does not have the usual 'obvious' commands like apt. So here is a short post about pacman commands.
Note : All pacman commands need to be run with superuser privileges. You need to prepend the commands with sudo for them to work. For the sake of brevity, I have omitted sudo.
-S flag asks pacman to synchronize packages.
pacman -S package1 package2 package3

will download install specified packages along with their necessary dependencies.
By default, package is searched in repos in the order they are listed in /etc/pacman.conf.
In case a package is available from more than one source, then you can specify the repo name before package name to select th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Snehit Sah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERN simple authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/feruz00/mern-simple-authentication-5ggh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/feruz00/mern-simple-authentication-5ggh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T13:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone. I am beginner MERN stack. I learn what need and this day try create simple MERN login/register app. I use passportjs for authentication and passport-local-mongoose for plugin database. When I send data using postman all successfully: user loginned registered and logouted. But when I send in frontend I get only currect message in login. But req.user cannot get.
https://github.com/Feruz00/travel-mern-app/tree/master
If someone have simple project this method please write comment or send link video or project. Thanks very much!!!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feruz00</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Clean Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpiteng/react-clean-architecture-114f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpiteng/react-clean-architecture-114f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T13:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Developers! Many of us use various design patterns with React Development to make React Apps more clean, clearly understandable, and more structured. But still we are facing issues with coding standards, we changed at one place and it breaks at another place. Is there any resolution for this? Yes, Try React Clean Architecture!
Quick Highlights  - React Clean Architecture - which makes your code more structured, clean and anyone can easily take over your code and start working with you. So Let’s continue next. Which include everything API, State Management (Redux, Redux Saga), Storybook, Utilities, Component/Container and you can add more relevant features in defined structure hierarchy.
react-clean-architecture
├── android
├── ios
├── src
│   ├── application
│   │   ├── common
│   │ …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kpiteng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morsible - Morse App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ilhamwahabigx/morsible-morse-app-278h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ilhamwahabigx/morsible-morse-app-278h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T13:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morsible - fast and reliable morse translator https://morsible.iwgx.io
✨ Translate text to morse or vice versa
Tech stack:
Reactjs -> Preactjs with Typescript in Next.js
Tailwind CSS with twin.macro and emotion for styling
testing-library and Jest for testing
Analytics with Splitbee
Google Cloud for text-to-speech and speech-to-text
Deployed to Vercel
Link: https://morsible.iwgx.io
https://github.com/iwgx/morsible]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilham Wahabi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical PowerShell Scripting for DevOps - Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mertsenel/practical-powershell-scripting-for-devops-part-2-4cn5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mertsenel/practical-powershell-scripting-for-devops-part-2-4cn5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T12:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this part, I will be extending the monitoring script we wrote on Part-1, with a polling while loop
Hi, I'm back with you with Part 2 of this series. On this part, I will ask you to extend the http ping monitoring script we wrote on Part-1. If you've completed Part-1 challenge then you extend your own script as well. In any case I will be providing my version of Part-1 solution as a starting point. Ok, lets jump on the our problem statement for this challenge. 
Hey fellow DevOps Engineer! We loved the first script you wrote for us, now we can test the health of 10s of our endpoints with ease with just a configuration file. We now have a problem though, we can see that lot's of failures appears to be intermittent, as in if we simply retry couple of more times we will eventually get a succ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MertSenel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way (in 🎥 video): part 14 – Horizontal Pod Autoscaler]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-14-horizontal-pod-autoscaler-1olc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aurelievache/understanding-kubernetes-in-a-visual-way-in-video-part-14-horizontal-pod-autoscaler-1olc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T10:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Kubernetes can be difficult or time-consuming. In order to spread knowledges about Cloud technologies I started to create sketchnotes about Kubernetes, then I've auto-published a book and since now I've started a new serie of video! :-)
I imagined a serie of short videos with a mix of sketchnotes and speech.
I think it could be a good way, more visual, with audio & video to explain Kubernetes (and others technologies).
This episode is focused on HPA (Horizontal Pod Autoscaler).




The video is in French BUT I done the subtitles in english (and french too).
If you liked the video and are interested to watch another ones, please give me some feedbacks (and you can also subscribe to my Youtube channel, if you want to ❤️).
Here the illustrations that you can see in the video:

If you are interested, I published all the sketchnotes on Kubernetes (and new ones!) to make a "book" of 165 pages: "Understanding Kubernetes in a visual way".
If you like theses sketchnotes, you can follow me, I will publish others sketchs shortly :-).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurélie Vache</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get HTTPS working on localhost]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bogkonstantin/how-to-get-https-working-on-localhost-2h6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bogkonstantin/how-to-get-https-working-on-localhost-2h6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T10:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The simplest way is to use mkcert utility.
It is easy to use tool for making local development SSL/TLS certificates. 
At first, you need to install it. You can download a binary file from here to use it immediately without installation. Or follow the installation guide for your OS.
Run command to create local CA (Certificate Authority).
mkcert -install

Run command to create certificate files.
mkcert localhost

That's it. 
You have two SSL certificate files now: *.pem which is a certificate file and *key.pem which is a key file. 
Use these files in the configuration of your local webserver.
If you want to know how to generate it manually, read the How to get HTTPS working on localhost article on my website. The article has a simple Nginx example of configuration to use generated SSL certificate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantin Bogomolov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get HTTPS working on localhost]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bogkonstantin/how-to-get-https-working-on-localhost-2h6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bogkonstantin/how-to-get-https-working-on-localhost-2h6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T10:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The simplest way is to use mkcert utility.
It is easy to use tool for making local development SSL/TLS certificates. 
At first, you need to install it. You can download a binary file from here to use it immediately without installation. Or follow the installation guide for your OS.
Run command to create local CA (Certificate Authority).
mkcert -install

Run command to create certificate files.
mkcert localhost

That's it. 
You have two SSL certificate files now: *.pem which is a certificate file and *key.pem which is a key file. 
Use these files in the configuration of your local webserver.
If you want to know how to generate it manually, read the How to get HTTPS working on localhost article on my website. The article has a simple Nginx example of configuration to use generated SSL certificate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantin Bogomolov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement password reset via email in node.js ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jahangeer/how-to-implement-password-reset-via-email-in-node-js-132m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jahangeer/how-to-implement-password-reset-via-email-in-node-js-132m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T10:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi guys today we gonna implement password reset via email in node.js. If you user forgot there password, we send an link to you user email account. From that link user can add there new password. If you just wanna know how this concept works, you can start from Model section .
So let's start coding...
Demo Video
Project Github Link
App Overview :
Project Structure




Methods
Urls
Actions




POST
/users
create user


POST
/password-reset
Send password reset link


POST
/password-reset/:userId/:token
Reset user password



create Node.js App
$ mkdir node-email-password-reset
$ cd node-email-password-reset
$ npm init --yes
$ npm install express mongoose dotenv nodemailer joi

Express : Express is minimal and flexible Node.js web applicaton framework.
Mongoose : Mongoose is an Object Data Mo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jahangeer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Learn Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/harvey/why-you-should-learn-vim-41ph</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/harvey/why-you-should-learn-vim-41ph"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T10:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vim is the best text editor out there. I have been using it for almost a decade now and I’m not going back to Sublime Text or Atom or even Notepad. The fact that you can do all of your development work in the same tool that is also used to write your code is amazing.
Vim is a powerful text editor with a lot of history and a certain aura of mystique around it. In this article, I'll try to dispel some of the myths around Vim and explain why you should learn to use it on the command line.
Anyone who spends significant time in front of a terminal should consider learning to use vim.
First, why not learn to use Emacs or [insert favorite text editor here]? The two main reasons I like Vim are that it's ubiquitous and easy to use. Most server installations have Vim available. There's even a version included with Mac OS X.
You can use it while coding, writing articles, notes, or even making spreadsheets. It can literally be everywhere you are! You can edit files through ssh! 
Unlike the latest frontend framework or latest shiny language, vim always stays the same through the years. So it's good to learn vim.
Vim has been the main editor used by most Linux users for at least 15 years, so you'll almost certainly find it on any server where you need to log in via SSH.
Learn Vim by interactive exercises, no need to struggle with man pages or blogs.
You can use the keys to navigate your code and vim. Press gg to move to the top of the file, press G to move to the end of the file, press / to search etc.
Once you know the shortcuts, it's a lot easier than grabbing your mouse and going to the menu bar, click edit, click find etc. It saves you a lot of time when coding.
Any reasonably recent version of Vim has strong support for all kinds of programming languages, so it's great for editing source code.
Vim supports all kinds of plugins and can be used even over an ssh connection to a sever. 
On top of that, you can use plugins like YouCompleteMe for code completion and NerdTree for a file browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Command Line Tips and Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/5-command-line-tips-and-tricks-451o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/5-command-line-tips-and-tricks-451o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T09:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're a Linux sysadmin or developer, it's your job to get things done. The command line is the best way to perform some tasks, such as copying or moving files. You can even use it to manipulate strings of text and other data.
Linux has a long history and a lot of great features, such as multiple command line options for each executable, shell aliases, built-in help, and powerful pipes. Unfortunately, all of these features become useless if you don't know how to use them properly. 
Here are 5 tips that could make you more productive at the shell prompt.
When entering commands in Linux, you may skip some of the parameters that are included in them. For example, if you want to view all files inside a directory, you may enter ls by itself instead of ls -a. Both of these commands will list all…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xplr v0.10 ditched yaml and goes the Neovim way with its own "init.lua"]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sayanarijit/xplr-v0-10-ditched-yaml-and-goes-the-neovim-way-with-its-own-init-lua-3f5c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sayanarijit/xplr-v0-10-ditched-yaml-and-goes-the-neovim-way-with-its-own-init-lua-3f5c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking inspiration from Neovim, xplr v0.10 has embraced embedded luajit to enable better hackability.
With only bash and YAML, we are limited to what interpreters, vms or shells are installed in the users system.
For e.g. we can't write a hack that executes a Python script and claim that it will work the same on any machine. Some system doesn't even come with bash installed. Or even if installed, we still need to worry about the version.
Lua on the other hand, can be shipped with xplr natively, because it's really tiny. That means, we can write a lua script and claim that it should work fine on any system. Even if there's no lua installed.
This lets us distribute our customizations for other users to use via a plugin system.
Writing a safe bash script is really difficult. We need to escape…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arijit Basu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a new Angular 4 Component – Multiple Components Angular Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/create-a-new-angular-4-component-multiple-components-angular-application-1k3m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/create-a-new-angular-4-component-multiple-components-angular-application-1k3m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T07:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/frontend/angular/create-new-angular-4-component-multiple-components
Create a new Angular 4 Component – Multiple Components Angular Application
The previous post, We had introduced how to set up an Angular 4 App with SpringBootSuite. In the tutorial, JavaSampleApproach will show you how to create a new Angular 4 Component and build an Angular Application with multiple Components.
Angular 6:
Angular 6 Component – How to create & integrate New Angular 6 Component
Related articles:
How to integrate Angular 4 with SpringBoot Web App and SpringToolSuite
I. Technologies
– Angular 4
II. Angular Component
Example:
import { Component, OnInit } from '@angular/core';
import { Customer } from './customer';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-root',
  templateUrl: './app.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./app.component.css']
})

export class AppComponent implements OnInit {
  customers: Customer[];
  selectedCustomer: Customer;

  constructor() {}

  getCustomers() {
     ...
  }

  ngOnInit(): void {
     this.customers = this.getCustomers();
  }

}
What is Component?
Angular Application. It allows us to mark a logic class, and additional metadata for processing at runtime. Components have a template (in above code is './app.component.html') and only one component can be instantiated per an element in a template. 
NgModule. So you should declare it in a NgModule:
More at:
https://grokonez.com/frontend/angular/create-new-angular-4-component-multiple-components
Create a new Angular 4 Component – Multiple Components Angular Application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to develop with Angular Service (Angular 4 Service)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-develop-with-angular-service-angular-4-service-2567</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/how-to-develop-with-angular-service-angular-4-service-2567"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T06:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/frontend/angular/develop-angular-service-angular4-service
How to develop with Angular Service (Angular 4 Service)
The previous post, we had introduced Angular Components (Angular4 Component). And in the tutorial, JavaSampleApproach will continuously  show you how to use Angular Services (Angular4 Services) to develop an Angular Application.
Related articles:
How to setup Angular IDE with Spring Tool Suite
Create a new Angular4 Component – Multiple Components Angular Application
I. Technologies
– Angular 4
II. Angular Service
What is Angular Service?

Angular Service is an JavaScript function that's responsible for doing a specific task. Using Services to exchange and processing data then keeps Components focused on doing business logic on the view.  So it's very helpful to organize a big project that makes codes more clear and clean for development and reusability.
III. Practice
Step to do:
Create an Angular Service

Implement logic for Angular Application

Run and check results
***Note: to do the tutorial, We reuse the sourcecode and continue with the previous post. So please check out it for more details:
Create a new Angular4 Component – Multiple Components Angular Application
1. Create an Angular Service
/angular4client/src/app, choose: File -> New -> Service:


Press Finish,

-> New project's structure:

Log: "WARNING Service is generated but not provided, it must be provided to be used"

-> Need register the DataService by using providers property. So we will do it later in a below session.
We got 2 new files: data.service.spec.ts and data.service.ts. Check sourcecode of the main file data.service.ts:
More at:
https://grokonez.com/frontend/angular/develop-angular-service-angular4-service
How to develop with Angular Service (Angular 4 Service)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Useful Tips & Tricks for JavaScript Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/super-useful-tips-tricks-for-javascript-developers-702</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/myogeshchavan97/super-useful-tips-tricks-for-javascript-developers-702"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T06:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick way to mask numbers using slice and ES8 padStart method





const creditCard = "4111111111114321"; // 16 digit credit card number
const lastFourDigits = creditCard.slice(-4); // get last 4 digits

// prepend * to lastFourDigits to make length equal to creditCard number length
const maskedNumber = lastFourDigits.padStart(creditCard.length, '*');

console.log(lastFourDigits); // 4321
console.log(maskedNumber); // ************4321

By passing { once: true } as the third argument to the addEventListener method, the event handler function will be executed only once.
document.getElementById("btn").addEventListener("click",
  function () {
    console.log("Button clicked!");
  },
  { once: true }
);

const user = {
  name: 'David',
  age: 30,
  city: 'NY'
};

const newAge = 40;

const upda…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yogesh Chavan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Docker Swarm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afif_ahmed/everything-you-need-to-know-about-docker-swarm-3dck</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afif_ahmed/everything-you-need-to-know-about-docker-swarm-3dck"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Docker is a free and open framework for building, delivering, and running apps. Docker allows you to decouple your code from your hardware, allowing you to easily deliver apps. You will handle the infrastructure the same way you manage your apps with Docker. One of the characteristics you have with docker is that you can run multiple docker environments in the same host environment. 
This is where Docker swarm comes into the picture. A docker swarm is the virtualization of the large number of nodes(running Docker engine) running in a cluster. These nodes can communicate with each other, helping developers to maintain multiple nodes in a single environment.
A swarm mode consists of Multiple Docker hosts which serve as managers (to handle membership and delegation) and workers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mohammed afif ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Docker Swarm]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afif_ahmed/everything-you-need-to-know-about-docker-swarm-3dck</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afif_ahmed/everything-you-need-to-know-about-docker-swarm-3dck"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Docker is a free and open framework for building, delivering, and running apps. Docker allows you to decouple your code from your hardware, allowing you to easily deliver apps. You will handle the infrastructure the same way you manage your apps with Docker. One of the characteristics you have with docker is that you can run multiple docker environments in the same host environment. 
This is where Docker swarm comes into the picture. A docker swarm is the virtualization of the large number of nodes(running Docker engine) running in a cluster. These nodes can communicate with each other, helping developers to maintain multiple nodes in a single environment.
A swarm mode consists of Multiple Docker hosts which serve as managers (to handle membership and delegation) and workers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mohammed afif ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrei do VS Code para o VIM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cezarmzz/migrei-do-vs-code-para-o-vim-4o0p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cezarmzz/migrei-do-vs-code-para-o-vim-4o0p"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T02:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uma mudança gradativa...


Pois é, hoje temos como padrão de editor de código para várias e várias linguagens, é Visual Studio Code, VS Code.
Se você não tem paciência e muito menos vontade de aprender coisas novas, o VIM não é feito para você.Não é uma crítica, mas uma verdade.
A primeira coisa que você vai precisar aprender para usar o VIM é entender que tudo se baseia em uso de teclado e seu fluxo de trabalho é diferente, pois, não é simplesmente abrir e sair escrevendo código.
NORMAL.Para editar, pressionando a tecla i você vai entrar no modo INSERT. 
ESC, para retornar ao modo NORMAL e em seguida pressione a combinação de teclas :w nomedoarquivo.ts. O comando :w vai salvar o arquivo. Para sair do VIM, só pressionar a combinação :q. 
Eu usei muito o VSCode, as vezes 3, 4 projetos abert…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cezar Augusto Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Windows][Node.js][TypeScript] Get installed printer driver names]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masanori_msl/windows-node-js-typescript-get-installed-printer-driver-names-bj2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masanori_msl/windows-node-js-typescript-get-installed-printer-driver-names-bj2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


I wanted to print PDF files.
Windows 10 ver.20H2
Node.js ver.16.2.0
TypeScript ver.4.2.4
pdf-to-printer ver.2.0.4
iconv-lite ver.0.4.24
I can get installed printer driver names by "pdf-to-printer".
GitHub - artiebits/pdf-to-printer: Print PDF files from Node.js and Electron



import ptp from "pdf-to-printer";
async function print()
{
    const printerName = 'Microsoft Print to PDF';
    const printers = await ptp.getPrinters();
    for(const p of printers)
    {
        console.log(`PRINTER Name: ${p.name} compare: ${p.name === printerName}`);
    }
}
print();

PRINTER Name: OneNote for Windows 10 compare: false
PRINTER Name: OneNote (??????) compare: false
PRINTER Name: OneNote (Desktop) compare: false
PRINTER Name: Microsoft XPS Document Writer compare: false
PRINTER Name: Micro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masui Masanori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did I make the npm library?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/user-interactive-modals-on-steroids-31oe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/user-interactive-modals-on-steroids-31oe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T20:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First of all, many thanks for showing the interest in this article. 👀
In the next few passages, I will try to explain why in many Angular projects it is important to have good modal and notification features as well as why I wrote the npm library on that subject.
In the professional world, I have several years as an Angular developer behind me and a few more of developing in other technologies.
Angular is for sure one of the worthy things that improved web development in the last ten years. The way it handles the view of the HTML and how it binds it with typescript is great. 
The small minus is, like in almost any other framework which imposes their own structures, that the developers can be brought into the situation to just follow the basic imposed way of creating things. Often a framew…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Jenicek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did I make the npm library?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/user-interactive-modals-on-steroids-31oe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/costlydeveloper/user-interactive-modals-on-steroids-31oe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T20:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First of all, many thanks for showing the interest in this article. 👀
In the next few passages, I will try to explain why in many Angular projects it is important to have good modal and notification features as well as why I wrote the npm library on that subject.
In the professional world, I have several years as an Angular developer behind me and a few more of developing in other technologies.
Angular is for sure one of the worthy things that improved web development in the last ten years. The way it handles the view of the HTML and how it binds it with typescript is great. 
The small minus is, like in almost any other framework which imposes their own structures, that the developers can be brought into the situation to just follow the basic imposed way of creating things. Often a framew…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Jenicek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as code: part-1 (Terraform to emancipate?)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sayem_omer/infrastructure-as-code-part-1-terraform-to-emancipate-4n9j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sayem_omer/infrastructure-as-code-part-1-terraform-to-emancipate-4n9j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T19:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I have been working on a project, which is based on cloud-native architecture (AWS) and I was in a dilemma about the perfect IaC solution. Despite going into detailed project requirements,simply added the draft diagram below. 

Now, from the above diagram, it is quite conspicuous that this system is based on some AWS components and it's a messaging system. Firstly, it maybe seems overkill to think about the IaC solution deeply. However, In the long run, it can save a ton of deployment time. Thus, I decided to leverage the IasC solutions, which codifies the entire architecture. There are several tools for managing serverless applications, such as AWS SAM, serverless framework, and terraform. However, for the sake of minimality, I will decide between SAM and serverless framework in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Sayem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Orientado a objetos]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/allanrodriguesmachado/php-orientado-a-objetos-1724</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/allanrodriguesmachado/php-orientado-a-objetos-1724"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T18:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> 🧠  Programação Orientada a Objetos



  
  
    Introduçao a POO (OOP) Programação orientada a objetos




  
  
  Classe




As classes são definidas pela delaração CLASS, o seu nome e o bloco de código que contém as suas propriedades e métodos

Por conversão PSR-1, o nome da classe deve ser sempre atribuido na forma de StudlyCaps/PascalCase/MixedCase. 

O corpo deve ser definido da seguindo forma

<?php
    class Humano
    {
        // Propriedades e métodos
    }
?>

O corpo de uma classe contém PROPRIEDADES e MÉTODOS.

Propriedades - São variáveis que guardam as características do objeto.

Métodos - São Funções que definem o que o objeto pode fazer.

As propriedades são também conhecidas como fields(CAMPOS) ou atributos de uma classe, no PHP, as propriedades
têm que ter um nível de acesso especificado.

<?php
    class FiguraGeometrica 
    {
        public $largura, $altura;
        public $x;
        public $y;

        function novaArea($a, $b)
        {
            return $a * $b;
        }
    }
?>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allan Rodrigues Machado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$PATH Environment Variable in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mahendrap1512/path-environment-variable-in-linux-1jb9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mahendrap1512/path-environment-variable-in-linux-1jb9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T18:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have downloaded some custom binary (external program) and want to access it from terminal irrespective of your current working directory, probably you are looking for PATH variable in Linux.
PATH is an environment variable which contains a list of directories separated by :.
echo $PATH it shows me
/home/my_user/.local/bin:/usr/local/sbin:/usr/local/bin:/usr/sbin:/usr/bin:/sbin:/bin:/usr/games:/usr/local/games:/snap/bin

Oh, wait! But what are these folders, and what is their use?
Output for echo $PATH may be different for you based on your Linux distros and program you have installed.
So whenever I typed any command in the terminal, OS will start finding that program one-by-one into these directories, whenever it found first match, it will open it. If it can't find the given command it will display an error command not found. 
$PATH.
flutter I can't access it. To get this working I have to update the $PATH variable, something like this
export PATH="$PATH:/home/my_user/flutter/bin"
flutter in terminal you can access it from anywhere.
Are these changes are permanent, what if I close the terminal or shut down my machine, will they persist?
NO. 
.bashrc file, If you are using zsh or any other terminal please update its respective profile/settings file.
export PATH="$PATH:/home/my_user/flutter/bin"
.bashrc file and save the file.
What is $PATH variable?
Update terminal settings file, for bash it is .bashrc
How to access any program from any working directly in the terminal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahendra Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Lubuntu 21.04]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/afsharm/running-lubuntu-21-04-ekp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/afsharm/running-lubuntu-21-04-ekp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T17:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a long term user of Ubuntu, 2 years recently and another 2 years about 5 years ago. My laptop is not old but it is not so powerful. It has 8 GB of RAM and an AMD A9 CPU. It’s very slow while running Ubuntu specially when using several tabs of Firefox or Chrome and while running applications like Skype. So I decided to give Lubuntu a try. I had ready a lot about how fast it is while being very similar to Ubuntu.
Persian Keyboard was easy to install, but finding/defining a shortcut to switch between keyboard layouts was really though. Finally I find a work-around here.
Sleep by closing lid causes crash. [SOLVED] by arbitrary changes and updates
When using LibreOffice Calc/Writer I encountered several screen mess up in a way that nothing can be read. I forced  to window resize several time again. An update on LibreOffice solved the problem magically.
A border has appeared on my desktop. It is a thick black one. It is not related to graphic card. Because some applications like Firefox and VS Code can easily toggle full screen and used all my screen.
I saw some ACPI Error on startup in first days. It was something related to Graphic card. I did not say the error again.
Wifi interface was not recognized in first place, but some hacks solved the problem.
It seems that my webcam is not recognized yet.
Cannot format/partition USB disk. All guides are about Ubuntu Disks. I need this option specially because my USB is bootable and now it needs to be partitioned again. [SOLVED] I realized that I should use KDE partition manager. Also I can install gnome-disk which is Ubuntu standard.
Anyway, as far as I can program Nodes.js, React.js and ASP.NET Core, I am happy with it. Specially now that is fast enough (yet!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Afshar Mohebi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CRA Cofiguration escape typecheck hell]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dangolbeeker/advanced-cra-cofiguration-escape-typecheck-hell-514d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dangolbeeker/advanced-cra-cofiguration-escape-typecheck-hell-514d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T17:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://scottbeekercodes.medium.com/escaping-type-checking-hell-in-react-typescript-94bb52fd8312]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Our First Controller]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eidellev/creating-our-first-controller-2cjk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eidellev/creating-our-first-controller-2cjk"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T16:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post we set up Inertia and Adonis. Now that we have a solid foundation to build upon, let us continue fleshing out our CRM app.
In my previous post we used a closure route to test everything worked end-to-end. This is fine for simple one-off routes (things like the "about" page for instance), but for more demanding routes, we'll usually reach for a controller.
ace to scaffold a resourceful controller:
node ace make:controller user -r


Take a moment to look at the new controller, Ace created for you. This is a basic template for our future CRUD operations:
import { HttpContextContract } from '@ioc:Adonis/Core/HttpContext'

export default class UsersController {
  public async index ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async create ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async store ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async show ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async edit ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async update ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }

  public async destroy ({}: HttpContextContract) {
  }
}

Now, let's connect some routes to the users controller.
Open start/routes.ts and delete the route we previously created. Instead add this:
Route.resource('users', 'UsersController');

This doesn't look like much, but let's see what routes were automatically created for us:
node ace list:routes


Pretty neat! Adonis automatically created a route for each controller method.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lev Eidelman Nagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Return to the Land of Environment Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maxjacobzander/return-to-the-land-of-environment-variables-2gfp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maxjacobzander/return-to-the-land-of-environment-variables-2gfp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T16:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you read my blog post about deploying my first full-stack app, you may remember our "Quick Deviation into the Land of Environment Variables" (if you haven't read it yet, you can check that out here!). I wanted to write a small follow-up piece for those of you who are trying to protect your data in a React app.
As I mentioned in my last blog post, I have been working on a project for a small business. I built the site with React and, as I mentioned in my last post, utilized EmailJS to help me handle the contact form. When it came to pushing to Github, I knew that I didn't want to push any information that could be traced back to my client's email account and, after using Environment Variables to help do that in Ruby, I figured that I could probably do the same thing in React! Wouldn't yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Zander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Frontend]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bikash9609/understanding-frontend-56d5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bikash9609/understanding-frontend-56d5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T14:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First of all in simple terms, Frontend of a website is a simple structure and arrangements of things in such a way as to make a sense to the user (whoever it might be).
Creating frontend is not as easy as it is learning html/css/js. The real hard work starts when you start using frameworks and libraries to make your frontend look more exciting.
But, once you reach above it all you start to detail with some of the complex process and errors of web development thrown by some of the coolest frameworks and libraries you just used. 
To be frank, debugging these errors is not always hard but sometimes it can be a situation when you don't want to loose the war. The complete outcome depends upon your solution, and uh yes, clock is ticking too. You wanna meet the deadline too.
It's not the end. 
You still have animations and other libraries to use in your project too. So, you don't waste any more time and start using them. Now, you are in the biggest hole you created yourself.
Keep debugging my dear friend.
See you next time.
// If my English is bad, never mind. Some talks just happen for no reason.
// Thanks a lot for giving the time. 😁
// I seem to not find the perfect tags too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bikash9609</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a React project from scratch, with TypeScript and Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexadam/create-a-react-project-from-scratch-with-typescript-and-webpack-2l18</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexadam/create-a-react-project-from-scratch-with-typescript-and-webpack-2l18"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T14:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step by step guide  on how to create a React project from scratch, with TypeScript and Webpack 5.
Prerequisites:
node
yarn
Create the project's folder:
mkdir react-app
cd react-app

Generate a default package.json file with yarn:
yarn init -y

Install React, TypeScript and Webpack:
yarn add react react-dom

yarn add --dev @types/react \
        @types/react-dom \
        awesome-typescript-loader \
        css-loader \
        html-webpack-plugin \
        node-sass \
        sass-loader \
        style-loader \
        typescript \
        webpack \
        webpack-cli \
        webpack-dev-server

Add build, dev & clean scripts in the package.json file:
 ....
  },
  "scripts": {
    "clean": "rm -rf dist/*",
    "build": "webpack",
    "dev": "webpack serve"
  }

Configure TypeScript b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 4 + Spring WebFlux + Spring Data Reactive MongoDB example | Full-Reactive Angular 4 Http Client]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-webflux-spring-data-reactive-mongodb-example-full-reactive-angular-4-http-client-1i2f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-webflux-spring-data-reactive-mongodb-example-full-reactive-angular-4-http-client-1i2f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T13:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/reactive-programming/angular-4-spring-webflux-spring-data-reactive-mongodb-example-full-reactive-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server
Angular 4 + Spring WebFlux + Spring Data Reactive MongoDB example | Full-Reactive Angular 4 Http Client – Spring Boot RestApi Server
In this tutorial, we're gonna build a full Reactive Application in which, Spring WebFlux, Spring Data Reactive MongoDB are used for backend, and Angular, RxJS, EventSource are on client side.
Related Posts:
How to use Angular Http Client to fetch Data from SpringBoot RestAPI – Angular 4
How to use Angular HttpClient to POST, PUT, DELETE data on SpringBoot Rest APIs – Angular 4
How to build SpringBoot MongoDb RestfulApi
How to use SpringData MongoRepository to interact with MongoDB
Angular 4 + Sp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck up story; rotate committed secret(s) on multiple Heroku apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hilleer/fuck-up-story-rotate-committed-secret-s-on-multiple-heroku-apps-26l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hilleer/fuck-up-story-rotate-committed-secret-s-on-multiple-heroku-apps-26l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T11:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


I have read a lot of exciting, helpful and inspiring articles/posts on dev.to and have felt like giving something back for a long time. Additionally a colleague of mine have been pushing me to writing a blog post for a long time (thank you, Jonathan) so I thought this fuck up and how it was solved, might as well be helpful, interesting and inspiring for others.
Please don't hesitate to give any kind of feedback for my first post!
As the title indicates, I committed and pushed a secret to git. I had to run some code locally relying on this secret and as I were eager to resolve the problem I was working on, I eventually forgot all about the secret.... So I staged the file files, wrote a commit message, committed them and pushed it all to GitHub, including the secret and boom! …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Hillmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never trust an upload's filename]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kahdev/never-trust-an-upload-s-filename-3fhj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kahdev/never-trust-an-upload-s-filename-3fhj"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T09:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's generally accepted that we should never simply trust a user's input. Otherwise, we're vulnerable to malicious input (CE-5). For a file upload from a user, it’s common to check their file size or type, especially when restricting them by those two attributes. But one that might get overlooked is the filename.
Checking the filename is especially important when it displayed on a web page to prevent HTML or XSS injection. That’s just on the frontend. On the backend, there are the other usual injections to worry about. Like SQL injection, when storing the name in a database. Or path injection, if storing in a path based on the name.
It might be tempting to dismiss this possibility as something that would never happen. After all, we must make the files first before we can upload them and th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Snowpack, React and Typescript in <1 min]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johnb8005/get-started-with-snowpack-react-and-typescript-in-1-min-5af2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johnb8005/get-started-with-snowpack-react-and-typescript-in-1-min-5af2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T06:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted an easy and (very) fast way to get a frontend project started so I could demo things. I wanted to be able to focus on a business case and not the boilerplate, so I created a github template that allows you to get started in less than 1 minute with a fully setup project.
Go check it out: https://github.com/nexys-system/boilerplate_snowpack_bootstrap]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promises vs Observables. What is ahead of the pack?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sajithahd/promises-vs-observables-what-is-ahead-of-the-pack-3fpe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sajithahd/promises-vs-observables-what-is-ahead-of-the-pack-3fpe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T06:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's revisit basics.
A detail comparison on 
Eager vs Lazy
Single value vs Multiple values
Asynchronous vs Synchronous/Asynchronous
Not cancellable vs Cancellable
Operators
Read more...
https://hdsajitha.medium.com/promises-vs-observables-what-is-ahead-of-the-pack-7567d5f6582a


Image Credit:snopes.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sajithahd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-signed certificates: shell script to generate]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nabbisen/bash-script-to-generate-self-signed-certificates-5hfj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nabbisen/bash-script-to-generate-self-signed-certificates-5hfj"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T06:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* The cover image is originally by OpenClipart-Vectors and edited with great appreciation.
I created Bash script to generate self-signed certificates. It was maybe when I tried some tests on MariaDB or PostgreSQL connection.
#!/bin/sh

# [ global parameters ]
# certificate configuration
readonly CERT_DAYS=36500
readonly RSA_STR_LEN=4096
readonly PREFIX=xxx-
readonly CERT_DIR=./ssl
readonly KEY_DIR=./ssl/private
# certificate content definition
readonly ADDRESS_COUNTRY_CODE=XX
readonly ADDRESS_PREFECTURE=XXXX
readonly ADDRESS_CITY=XXXX
readonly COMPANY_NAME=XXXXXXXX
readonly COMPANY_SECTION=XXXXXXXX
readonly CERT_PASSWORD= # no password
# - ca
readonly CA_DOMAIN=x.domain
readonly CA_EMAIL=ca@email.address
# - server
readonly SERVER_DOMAIN=y.domain
readonly SERVER_EMAIL=server@email.address
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heddi Nabbisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We may not need to install docker daemon on our local system]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aisuko/we-may-not-need-to-install-docker-daemon-on-our-local-system-3j7l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aisuko/we-may-not-need-to-install-docker-daemon-on-our-local-system-3j7l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T06:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to share some interesting things of using the Docker command.
The environment which I have to list at below:
macOS Big Sur Version 11.3.1 with multiple accounts
Homebrew 3.1.8
docker client v20.10.6
Ubuntu 20.04 and which was installed the latest version of docker client and docker daemon
In my local environment, macOS Big Sur Version 11.3.1. We do not need to install Docker desktop for mac on it, only docker client is enough for me.
The Docker desktop for mac installs docker client, docker daemon and a Kubernetes cluster feature on my macOS. I have a situation when I use my old mac(2014) with 8GB memory, these components account too much resource, and several active containers and Goland IDE will make my old mac slow.
So, I'd like to only install docker client on my machine and c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aisuko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add error handling middleware in Express (with Typescript)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-add-error-handling-middleware-in-express-with-typescript-291j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joncodes/how-to-add-error-handling-middleware-in-express-with-typescript-291j"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T06:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Source code: Github





  
  
  The baseline project


This post assumes you are following along with the baseline project tutorial, but the concepts apply to any Typescript project.
In the previous post, we implemented listeners to the uncaughtException and unhandledRejection events in node to ensure any unexpected errors crash the application.
express framework, by default, handles any errors that occur within a route and sends an error response to the HTTP client. Even if these errors are unexpected errors that should cause our program to terminate, they will be caught before they can bubble up to our handle function.
In addition, the default error handler responds with an HTML page, which isn't ideal. For our API, it would be better if we could send some nicely structured, predictable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a super simple Badge component in Angular using directives.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/creating-a-super-simple-badge-component-in-angular-using-directives-ohc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/creating-a-super-simple-badge-component-in-angular-using-directives-ohc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T04:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm back with another small post to show how you can leverage directives to do magical things in your Angular application. Directives are really powerful. Once you get to know about the, you can start leveraging it to move your imperative logic into directives.

We are going to use a pattern that is used by  Angular Material. My intention with this post is to show you how these libraries do it. We just use what the library gives us, and most of the time we use it without actually knowing how it works.
By the end of the post, you would definitely think Was it always this easy to make cool stuff? 
This is a very valid question that you can have. Why can't we just have a simple div and then style it accordingly in our component? Well, you can do that. 
Directives can be easily added to HTM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a super simple Badge component in Angular using directives.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angular/creating-a-super-simple-badge-component-in-angular-using-directives-ohc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angular/creating-a-super-simple-badge-component-in-angular-using-directives-ohc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T04:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I'm back with another small post to show how you can leverage directives to do magical things in your Angular application. Directives are really powerful. Once you get to know about the, you can start leveraging it to move your imperative logic into directives.

We are going to use a pattern that is used by  Angular Material. My intention with this post is to show you how these libraries do it. We just use what the library gives us, and most of the time we use it without actually knowing how it works.
By the end of the post, you would definitely think Was it always this easy to make cool stuff? 
This is a very valid question that you can have. Why can't we just have a simple div and then style it accordingly in our component? Well, you can do that. 
Directives can be easily added to HTM…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adithya Sreyaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure HTTP Security headers with CloudFront Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/configure-http-security-headers-with-cloudfront-functions-1iid</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/configure-http-security-headers-with-cloudfront-functions-1iid"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T01:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of weeks ago, AWS released CloudFront Functions — a “true edge” compute capability for the CloudFront.
It is “true edge” because Functions work on 200+ edge locations (link to doc) while its predecessor, the Lambda@Edge, runs on a small number of regional edge caches.
One of the use cases for Lambda@Edge was adding security HTTP headers (it’s even listed on the product page), and now there is one more way to make it using CloudFront Functions. 
Security Headers are one of the web security pillars.
They specify security-related information of communication between a web application (i.e., website) and a client (i.e., browser) and protect the web app from different types of attacks. Also, HIPAA and PCI, and other security standard certifications generally include these headers in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhii Vasylenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking in .NET or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Perf Regression Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeikabu/benchmarking-in-net-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-perf-regression-testing-55pn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeikabu/benchmarking-in-net-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-perf-regression-testing-55pn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier post we were looking at the performance of function pointers introduced in .NET 5/C# 9.0. To do that we used BenchmarkDotNet (docs), the de-facto .NET benchmarking framework. This is a shotgun dump of notes to get you writing your own benchmarks- mainly for performance regression testing.
# Install benchmark template
dotnet new -i BenchmarkDotNet.Templates
# Create new benchmark project `benchmarks`
dotnet new benchmark -o benchmarks --console-app -v 0.12.1

See BenchmarkDotNet template options



Confusingly, you’ll find references to installing BenchmarkDotNet.Tool global tool which has been deprecated (see issue 1670 and PR 1572). Likewise, the dotnet project template BenchmarkDotNet.Templates defaults to: NET Core App 3.0 (which is out of support), and version 0.12.0 of B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeikabu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Web App access with GCP Identity-Aware Proxy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alvardev/secure-web-app-access-with-gcp-identity-aware-proxy-34b0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alvardev/secure-web-app-access-with-gcp-identity-aware-proxy-34b0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T22:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security is an important part of any architecture, especially for remote workers. 
During the pandemic, many challenges have appeared for security teams, I saw a lot... a lot... a lot of cloud admins  creating VPNs for remote workers in order to access to internal apps.
Imagine this: workers for financial teams, managements teams, people that never heard about VPNs... and now they have to create them to be able to work! Poor people from DevOps, trying to explain and create a peering for each worker on the company =(
So, what if I tell you that you can secure your apps with no VPN client required? Yep, it's possible with GCP Identity-Aware Proxy
The objective for today is create a web app which only authorized accounts can access and it should also be able to consume internal services.

1.-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvaro David</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a Next.js app with AWS Amplify]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploying-a-next-js-app-with-aws-amplify-3bdc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploying-a-next-js-app-with-aws-amplify-3bdc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T20:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week AWS amplify announced support for deploying Next.js SSR apps, which has been a long awaited feature. You can read the announcement here.
For the purposes of this guide we will deploy the basic app scaffold provided by create-next-app
Since we will be using Amplify, we first need to go through the installation and setup process. We can figure out how to do that by following the official docs.
Once we have Amplify configured we can go ahead and create a project. We can achieve that by running amplify init

Amplify provides a zero config deploy similar to vercel, which allows us to connect a git provider to use for our deployments. To get started we can go the the Amplify console and select Host web app.

We can now select our preferred git provider such as Github for this example.

After selecting our desired git provider we can select which branch we would like to deploy from.

After selecting a branch we can now configure our build settings, for the most part we won't need to modify this config as Amplify will take care of that for us.

Now we can review everything looks correct before triggering a deploy.

Finally we can see the deployment starting and in a few minutes our site will be live!

Thanks to Amplify we can now deploy Next.js SSR app on AWS with a relatively low effort. Let me know what you think about this new feature!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ely Alamillo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Custom Scully Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/a-guide-to-custom-scully-plugins-1j0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/a-guide-to-custom-scully-plugins-1j0k"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T17:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preston Lamb | ng-cong | Jan 2021
tldr;


Scully.io is a great tool for Angular developers. Its tagline is, “Scully makes building, testing and deploying JAMstack apps extremely simple.” Essentially, you build your application in Angular and then Scully will take it and generate static HTML and CSS for you. Those assets can be deployed, and the end result is a high quality, blazing fast experience. In this post, we’ll talk about how you can extend the default functionality of Scully to better suit your needs. This article will illustrate how to create a plugin, and adding that extra functionality is simpler than you may think.
Plugin Types


There are several types of plugins you can create for your Scully app, depending on when in the build pipeline you need to jump in. Here are the diffe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como começar em segurança da informação?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leh_mariaa/como-comecar-em-seguranca-da-informacao-2465</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leh_mariaa/como-comecar-em-seguranca-da-informacao-2465"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acho que de toda minha vida, essa foi a pergunta que mais me fizeram. Bem, pra quem chegou aqui de paraquedas, eu sou a Leticia Pereira, atualmente trabalho com segurança da informação em uma consultoria de segurança.
Como começar em cybersecurity?
A primeira coisa que voce precisa perguntar é: Por que cybersecurity?
Falando por mim, voce basicamente vai olhar logs, procurar entender como um ataque acontece através de logs, pensar em todos os possíveis de cenários de segurança e brechas de segurança para voce conseguir defender todos os ativos da empresa, fazer inúmeros relatórios para clientes procurando falhas de segurança, acompanhar atualização de softwares, gastar dias e horas procurando falhas em sistemas, fazer mais relatórios, ler diversos textos postados por pesquisadores e por ai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leh 🚘</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[create an object]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pravenpatel/create-an-object-4j57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pravenpatel/create-an-object-4j57"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[date1: {enabled: false, label: "Date1 Label", eformVisible: false, mandatory: "NOT_MANDATORY", order: 20}
dropdown1: {enabled: true, label: "Country", eformVisible: false, mandatory: "NOT_MANDATORY", order: 30, …}
text1: {enabled: true, label: "Text1 Custom field", eformVisible: false, mandatory: "ADMIN_API", order: 0, …}
const form_template = [
  {
    "type":"textBox",
    "label":"Name",
  },
  {
    "type":"number",
    "label":"Age"
  },
  {
    "type":"select",
    "label":"favorite book",
    "options":["Jane Eyre","Pride and Prejudice","Wuthering Heights"]
  }
]


  
  
  please help me]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>praveen patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up an Angular 12 workspace with Nx and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/setting-up-an-angular-12-workspace-with-nx-and-github-actions-32l5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/setting-up-an-angular-12-workspace-with-nx-and-github-actions-32l5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Nx After Dark, we're creating an Nx workspace for an Angular 12 app called Energy Insights. We're also setting up a GitHub Actions workflow and connecting it to Nx Cloud.




Follow the instructions below to set up a similar workspace or browse the end result at github/LayZeeDK/energy-insights.
Node.js 14.x
PNPM
Note that there's currently an issue with using Cypress with PNPM. Let me know if you figure out how to fix it. Until then, remove Cypress from the workspace or use either Yarn or NPM.
# Install the Nx workspace generator
pnpm install --global create-nx-workspace
# Generate a blank Nx workspace
pnpm init nx-workspace my-workspace --preset=empty --pm=pnpm --npm-scope=my-workspace --nx-cloud

# Install the "json" utility
npm install --global json
# Set the base branch to "main"
json -I -f nx.json -e "this.affected.defaultBase = 'main';"

# Add Angular capability
pnpm add --save-dev @nrwl/angular
# Initialize Angular workspace
nx generate @nrwl/angular:init

# Generate Angular app project
nx generate app my-app

See the video for examples of:
Setting up generator defaults
Creating a GitHub Actions CI workflow
Setting up GitHub workflow triggers
Connecting Nx Cloud for distributed computation caching
Remove Cypress]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Gyrup Brink Nielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🧩 Introducing the Identity Maturity Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/introducing-the-identity-maturity-framework-287d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/introducing-the-identity-maturity-framework-287d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T12:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📌 The Auth0 Identity Maturity Framework helps you understand what’s working about your current identity implementation and what needs to mature.



  
  
  
Today’s users are accustomed to living and working online, and they expect a secure, effortless experience every time they access your platform. Seamless authentication is no longer a nice-to-have; it’s a requirement for success. And since companies are building more custom applications, users need fast, secure access across multiple platforms and devices. Identity touches every aspect of your business, so managing identity is more complex and more critical than ever before.
In response, organizations are exploring the value of third-party identity-as-a-service (IDaaS) platforms like Auth0. These solutions offer a centralized source of truth for authentication, authorization, and customer insight.
Identity maturity is a way of thinking about the efficacy of your existing identity solution and its capacity to handle new business requirements and customer demands as you grow and scale. Achieving identity maturity involves understanding what a fully functional, centralized authentication solution looks like. Evaluating your current state, creating a plan to improve your identity infrastructure, and fostering a culture of continuous improvement are also key to reaching identity maturity.
As an IDaaS provider, Auth0 works with organizations of all sizes in a diverse array of industries to tackle identity challenges. In doing so, we’ve learned a huge amount about the identity models that work for particular business needs and goals.  
In fact, we’ve consolidated our expertise and our customers’ knowledge and experiences into a solution we call the Auth0 Identity Maturity Framework (IMF): a collection of tools, tactics, and expert input that will help you understand what’s working about your identity solution and what needs to change. 
Read more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shift Left on Security: EXPLAINED Easily]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n3wt0n/shift-left-on-security-explained-easily-16e5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security in DevOps is important, but often underrated. So much so that someone has created the DevSecOps word for it. But what does shift left mean? And how to shift left on security?
We will see all of these and more today.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/94AIX5oArIw
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
First, what is the meaning of "shift left".
Shift left is a principle that focuses on executing a practice, implementing a process, or using a tool as early as possible in the development chain.

It is called "shift left" because the soft…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Endpoint Security: Importance & 5 ways to help safeguard IT in the workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sndkcorp/endpoint-security-importance-5-ways-to-help-safeguard-it-in-the-workspace-imf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sndkcorp/endpoint-security-importance-5-ways-to-help-safeguard-it-in-the-workspace-imf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning and earning professionally is something that everyone wants, but what is completely another story, is job security. Ultimately, we all desire job security. We want to know that our job is safe and that we are valued by our management. It’s hard for the employees to perform their best if they have to stress or worry about the future of their job. It’s very important to understand the fact that everyone wants to feel safe and secure. People worry that they could be replaced by a new fresher hired out of university or cheaper labor abroad.
Keeping your goals on track is the most crucial thing to do when it comes to improving your financial stability. Employees who settle into a long-term position are likely to establish their career goals that lead to a positive impact on their finan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SNDK CORP</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ծրագրային անվտանգություն՝ SQL Injection (մաս 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-1-lc0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/n_babajanyan/sql-injection-1-lc0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL injection֊ը հանդիսանում է վեբ֊ծրագրերի ամենատարածված խոցելիություններից (vulnerability) մեկը և գտնվում է OWASP հիմնադրամի 10 ամենատարածված խոցելիությունների ցանկի OWASP Top 10 առաջին հորիզոնականում։
Իրականում OWASP Top 10 ցանկի առաջին հորիզոնականում տեղ է գտել ավելի ընդհանրական Injection տեսակը, իսկ SQL injection֊ը դրա տեսակների մեկն է։
Փորձենք հասկանալ ինչու է առաջանում խոցելիության այս տեսակը, ինչ հնարավորություններ է ընձեռում հարձկավողին և պաշտպանության ինչ միջոցներ կան։
Օրինական ճանապարհով ծրագրային անվտանգություն ուսումնասիրելու համար կարելի է օգտվել հատուկ այդ նպատակով պատրաստված խոցելի ծրագրերից, ինչպիսիք են օրինակ OWASP Juice Shop֊ը և bWAPP֊ը։ Նշվածներից բացի գոյություն ունեն բազմաթիվ այլ խոցելի ծրագրեր, որոնց ցանկին կարելի է ծանոթանալ այստեղ
Դիտարկենք SQL տվյալների բազայի պարզ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Narek Babajanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript - A Free 7-hour Interactive Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60a36742906c5207e3a7da6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-interactive-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last four months, I have recorded what is probably the most interactive JavaScript course that has ever been created. The reason I have done this is because I often see new coders fall into the same pitfalls again and again when trying to learn JavaScript, with the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors to Style Your Web Page]]></title>
        <id>60a341f5906c5207e3a7da61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-css-selectors-to-style-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors are one of the most important parts of CSS. They give you the ability to target HTML elements on your web page that you want to style. Without CSS selectors, you wouldn't be able to style your page to look how you want. Thankfully CSS selectors have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web3? The Decentralized Internet of the Future Explained]]></title>
        <id>60a42386906c5207e3a7dfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is going through a paradigm shift. Learn the differences between Web2 and Web3, and why many developers and companies are shifting their approach in building apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize for Change in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>60a469ec906c5207e3a7e1b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-for-change-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you work at Magic Money Corp, which runs on just three lines of JavaScript: let input = { step1: 'collect underpants' } doStuff(input)  profit(input) // $$$!!! Now imagine that something's wrong with doStuff and you need to take it down for maintenance. What happens if you temporarily comment out the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break into Ethereum, Crypto, and Web3 as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60a53182906c5207e3a7e588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breaking-into-ethereum-crypto-web3-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I've been talking about my move into the Web3, Ethereum, and crypto space since making the switch from a traditional web, mobile, and cloud background. Since making that move, a shocking number of people have reached out to me who are also thinking about doing the same.  It's really]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Development Pricing Guide – Should Freelancers Bill by the Hour?]]></title>
        <id>60a3780f906c5207e3a7db5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you offer your services as a freelance developer, you have a major say in how you price your project.  But how do you go about charging for a website project? "Well, I just bill by the hour and send an invoice every week or month." ...I hear you say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Neon Text With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-neon-text-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon text can add a nice, futuristic touch to any website. I’ve always loved the magic of neon signs, and wanted to recreate them using CSS. I thought I’d share some tips on how to do it! In this article, …
The post How to Create Neon Text With CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia O'Dwyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340716</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Addy Osmani on images in HTML:
The humble <img> element has gained some superpowers over the years. Given how central it is to image optimization on the web, let’s catch up on what it can do and how it can 
…
The post The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Love Letter to HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339522</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-love-letter-to-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see you. In the back there, behind JavaScript and React and PHP and all those “real” programming languages, I see you. And I appreciate you.
The post A Love Letter to HTML & CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Kolodziej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euismod]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340594</id>
        <link href="https://www.euismod.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interactive tool for learning grid syntax from Etesam Ansari. In the Learn section, it teaches you some concepts (involving multiple bits of the grid syntax) then gives you a task to complete by filling out the right syntax. I’m …
The post Euismod appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>