<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-25T01:04:23.029Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-25T01:04:23.029Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Websocket Real Time Communication to Your SaaS App]]></title>
        <id>619ba16011d3cb08287aa2ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-websocket-real-time-communication-to-your-saas-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this conference talk made for Tech Fest 2021, Steven Lemmo talks to you about building SaaS Applications with WebSockets. Here is a full breakdown of what he will cover in this 40 minute talk: The reason for this talkWhy Websockets?Websockets minimal API exampleRest Web ServicesMultiple ListenersFull DuplexWebsockets time-lineTypeScriptVendor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Shades – Hex Code and RGB for Gray Color Palette]]></title>
        <id>619bcc5611d3cb08287aa66f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/color-shades-hex-code-and-rgb-for-gray-color-palette/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colors play an integral role in how usable and accessible your web design projects are.  At times, they can even make or break a project.  Having a color palette comprised of different shades and hues of a specific color can be really helpful. It helps you visualize how you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Universally Unique Identifiers with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember the recommended way to generate unique universal Identifiers in node.js was to the uuid module. These IDs are useful in all sorts of scenarios including for database keys, filenames, URLs, etc. Recently both node.js and the browser began offering nearly identical APIs that will generate 36-character version 4 uuids without any dependencies.
Available in Chrome since July 2021 and coming soon other browsers is crypto.randomUUID(). There's a global crypto object that's available on the global self property. You can use that to generate a UUID like this:
self.crypto.randomUUID();

The UUID it generates is a v4 UUID per the spec and ends up with a string that looks something like this:
"0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"


You want to do the same thing in node? Instead of reaching for the uuid package. As long as you're on version 14.17 or newer, you can do this:
const { randomUUID } = require("crypto");
randomUUID(); // "0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"

It's cool see node and the browser adopting powerful APIs for crypto and improved randomness. I'll definitely be reaching for these in the near future!
You can read more in the WebCrypto section in the MDN or the crypto section in the node.js docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamund Ferguson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Universally Unique Identifiers with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember the recommended way to generate unique universal Identifiers in node.js was to the uuid module. These IDs are useful in all sorts of scenarios including for database keys, filenames, URLs, etc. Recently both node.js and the browser began offering nearly identical APIs that will generate 36-character version 4 uuids without any dependencies.
Available in Chrome since July 2021 and coming soon other browsers is crypto.randomUUID(). There's a global crypto object that's available on the global self property. You can use that to generate a UUID like this:
self.crypto.randomUUID();

The UUID it generates is a v4 UUID per the spec and ends up with a string that looks something like this:
"0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"


You want to do the same thing in node? Instead of reaching for the uuid package. As long as you're on version 14.17 or newer, you can do this:
const { randomUUID } = require("crypto");
randomUUID(); // "0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"

It's cool see node and the browser adopting powerful APIs for crypto and improved randomness. I'll definitely be reaching for these in the near future!
You can read more in the WebCrypto section in the MDN or the crypto section in the node.js docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamund Ferguson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Material Setup Guide - Installation and Quick Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sameer8saini/angular-material-setup-guide-installation-and-quick-demo-3jc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sameer8saini/angular-material-setup-guide-installation-and-quick-demo-3jc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, I will show you how to install and use Angular Material UI in your Angular project.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0h3aDhkVsng
We will use the default themes that Angular Material offers and will see what setup is required in your Angular solution while using Angular Material.
We will make changes to the App.Module.Ts file and then use the Angular Material component in the template and component.


  
  
  AngularMaterial #Angular #UiLibrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sameer8saini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Open Source DevOps Dashboard]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maximwheatley/an-open-source-devops-dashboard-4o81</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maximwheatley/an-open-source-devops-dashboard-4o81"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Dev friends! Forgive the shameless promotion, I'm so proud of my teammates and want to share, and hope you'll help! 
DevLake, is a free and open source tool, it brings together all the data from many of your dev tools (GitHub, Jenkins, GitLab, Jira, etc.) and provides analysis and visualization with a personalized dashboard filled with the metrics that matter to YOU. 
https://github.com/merico-dev/lake
We saw how much time and energy it takes to make practical sense of DevOps data. "NO MORE!" we said, and so we built DevLake to make it easy for developers everywhere to make their data work for them. 
Our motto is: More Dev. Less Ops. 
We hope DevLake helps you achieve exactly that, and we hope you'll join us by contributing, sharing, or simply by making use of this. Thanks gang!
(We built DevLake making the most of Go, Grafana, and Docker, among other things! We'd love to chat about our experience building this if anybody has questions or ideas!) 
GitHub link HERE: https://github.com/merico-dev/lake]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxim Wheatley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things I noticed after using Vim for the first time in one week]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zt4ff_1/things-i-noticed-after-using-vim-for-the-first-time-in-one-week-3b45</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zt4ff_1/things-i-noticed-after-using-vim-for-the-first-time-in-one-week-3b45"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This is my first time using Vim (actually Neovim 😎), so by no means am I an expert.
This article was really helpful while configuring Neovim on my machine.
Vim is basically a text editor for Unix. It's similar to other programs like Notepad, Visual Studio Code, Sublime Text Editor or Atom.
So what led me to Vim


I love new challenges and improving my productivity. VS code was pretty customized and suitable for my current needs. Maybe YouTube videos from this guy (DistroTube) was the motivation to try it out. 
Efficiency: Vim is designed to reduce how often switch from your keyboard to a mouse. They are literally keybinding for any type of operation and you can create custom keybindings too. If you type really fast, this will improve your productivity as you will really need your mouse.
Learning Curve: Vim has quite a learning curve if you're just starting. For the first few days, my focus was shifted majorly from the code I write to the tool I use. This is going to pay off later by building up muscle memory you will be able to exit Vim in your sleep.
A quick meme about exiting vim:

Conclusion


I will continue sharing my learning experience and journey with Vim for the next few months
Whatever editor, language or framework you use, they should be able to solve your problems effectively and efficiently. 
Neovim and it's simpler and maintained. 
Do you think it is worth the time to learn Vim?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mininal Webpack and React.js Starter boilerplate for TypeScript projects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fariasmateuss/mininal-webpack-and-reactjs-starter-boilerplate-for-typescript-projects-3pji</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fariasmateuss/mininal-webpack-and-reactjs-starter-boilerplate-for-typescript-projects-3pji"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say hello to my new open source project!!! 
React.js boilerplate with TypeScript, SASS, Webpack and Babel.
Out now: 
 / 
        webpack-setup-for-react
      
    

Mininal Webpack and React.js Starter boilerplate.
Link to demo
Create a new application using create-react-app with the -e | --example flag pointing to this repository's url, like so:
npx create-react-app project-name -e https://github.com/fariasmateuss/webpack-setup-for-react.git
Clone the project
git clone https://github.com/fariasmateuss/webpack-setup-for-react.git
Go to the project directory
cd webpack-setup-for-react
Install dependencies
yarn
Start the server
yarn dev
Open http://localhost:8080 with your browser to see the result.
To deploy this project run
yarn build
If you have any feedback, please contact me through my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mateus V. Farias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manjaro - Laravel Dev Setup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skino2020/manjaro-laravel-dev-setup-2p3k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skino2020/manjaro-laravel-dev-setup-2p3k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T21:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


I think its fair to say i have a bit of an addiction to Linux distro's.... over the last few months i have tried and tested a number of them and also blogged about a few... here is a brief list of distro's I've tested in the last 3 months.
Ubuntu (Normal)
Kubuntu (KDE)
Lubuntu
Elementary OS (my favourite so far)
Pop!_OS
Fedora 35
Zorin Core
And that's probably missing a few... yes I'm a distro wh*re...
The absolute beauty of Linux Distro's is you can get up and running with what you need really fast. In my case i can get my Laravel development environment setup in less than 30 minutes on Ubuntu based distro and that would include sorting out my ssh access and GitHub keys...
With the exception of Fedora, all of the distributions above all have Ubuntu in common so the commands…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NPM vs. YARN: Basic Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vandnakapoor19/npm-vs-yarn-basic-commands-3bl6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vandnakapoor19/npm-vs-yarn-basic-commands-3bl6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T21:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a quick reference guide for basic commands that we can use when dealing with Node and requiring the use of NPM or YARN.
npm install == yarn
npm install package --save == yarn add package
npm install package --save-dev == yarn add package --dev
npm uninstall package --save == yarn remove package
npm update --save == yarn upgrade
npm install package -g == yarn global add package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vandna kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete Guide To BFF (Backend For Frontend)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T21:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A backend for frontend (BFF) is one of these newer architectural patterns that especially became relevant after the rise of microservices and domain-driven design, as it is a way to simplify the communication between the frontend and backend and make the frontend development simpler.
In this post, I will cover BFFs with Angular and if and how you should do it in your project.
https://christianlydemann.com/the-complete-guide-to-backend-for-frontend-bff/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Lüdemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete Guide To BFF (Backend For Frontend)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T21:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A backend for frontend (BFF) is one of these newer architectural patterns that especially became relevant after the rise of microservices and domain-driven design, as it is a way to simplify the communication between the frontend and backend and make the frontend development simpler.
In this post, I will cover BFFs with Angular and if and how you should do it in your project.
https://christianlydemann.com/the-complete-guide-to-backend-for-frontend-bff/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Lüdemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis with Python for Excel Users Course]]></title>
        <id>619e979225888a07c3e1b545</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analysis-with-python-for-excel-users-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know how to use Microsoft Excel and want to learn how to do data analysis with Python? You are in luck. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to do Data Analysis with Python. This course will be especially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I created my blog with Gatsby, Netlify, and Plausible.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fran_ortiz/how-i-created-my-blog-with-gatsby-netlify-and-plausible-29bf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fran_ortiz/how-i-created-my-blog-with-gatsby-netlify-and-plausible-29bf"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T19:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was originally posted on my blog.
If you want to remember something, write it down.
I’m starting a blog. After some time of doubts (pondering about if it’s worth it, thinking that people have already covered all the topics I will want to write about) I decided to give it a try. It was because of three principal reasons:
Get deeper into some topics I like: I think writing things down leads to better learning.
Help other people.
Improve my communication skills.
That said, I will use the first post to explain how I created the blog.
I was not sure about owning a domain name or publishing content on sites like Medium, Dev.to or Hashnode. After some research, I decided to publish on my own domain. It brings some benefits:
The first one is simple, I own it: I can choose and customize w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco Ortiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding User Authentication from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/propelauth/understanding-user-authentication-from-scratch-3pl2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/propelauth/understanding-user-authentication-from-scratch-3pl2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T19:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is a broad topic that can be both very simple and very complicated. In this series we'll describe what it is and different approaches to implement it, starting from older less-secure methods and ending with modern more-secure methods.
Authentication is the process of determining who someone or something is. In the real world, when you give someone your ID or passport, that's a form of authentication. Online, when you enter an email/password, that's a form of authentication.
While authentication processes can also be for machine-to-machine communication, in this post we'll focus on users identifying themselves to a web server - a.k.a. user authentication.
To simplify the problem, we need two processes:
Some way to create new users
Some way to identify existing users
Let's loo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>propelauthblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Librería con Lit 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/balsalobre/libreria-con-lit-20-4f75</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/balsalobre/libreria-con-lit-20-4f75"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Construyendo el scaffolding con open-wc


Open WC nos provee de una serie de herramientas que nos ayudan a utilizar de una manera más cómoda y sencilla los web components.
  npm init @open-wc

"devDependencies": {
    "@custom-elements-manifest/analyzer": "^0.4.17",
    "@open-wc/eslint-config": "^4.3.0",
    "@open-wc/testing": "next",
    "@typescript-eslint/eslint-plugin": "^4.33.0",
    "@typescript-eslint/parser": "^4.33.0",
    "@web/dev-server": "^0.1.28",
    "@web/dev-server-storybook": "next",
    "@web/test-runner": "next",
    "concurrently": "^5.3.0",
    "eslint": "^7.32.0",
    "eslint-config-prettier": "^8.3.0",
    "husky": "^4.3.8",
    "lint-staged": "^10.5.4",
    "prettier": "^2.4.1",
    "tslib": "^2.3.1",
    "typescript": "^4.5.2"
  },]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balsalobre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Won&#x27;t My Computer Connect to My Hotspot? [Fixed on Windows 10 PC WiFi]]]></title>
        <id>619e3cdd25888a07c3e1b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-wont-my-computer-connect-to-my-hotspot-fixed-on-windows-10-pc-wifi/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T18:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mobile hotspot is a quick and efficient way to share an internet connection with other devices like computers, iPads, or other mobile phones.  A hotspot is also a good alternative to WiFi – especially if the WiFi in your area is unbearably slow or won't connect.  Sometimes, you might experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Basic Coding Terminology: Industry Basics ✏️]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amyoulton/understanding-basic-coding-terminology-industry-basics-43p7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amyoulton/understanding-basic-coding-terminology-industry-basics-43p7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T18:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally written by me for CodeCast.
If you’re just entering the world of development, one of the first things you will likely notice is how much jargon there is. I know when I first started, it felt like there was at least one word in every sentence that I had never heard before. Like any field, there is very specific jargon related to the field of development. With coding, there is specific jargon for different types of programming as well as jargon that is unique to specific languages, libraries, and frameworks. 
I know I've looked up what words mean only to be more confused after reading the definition. It can all feel a little daunting to start, so our goal in this post is to introduce some of the broader and more commonly used terms in coding to help get you starte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Oulton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make a working login and sign up form with Html And CSS(Transparent ,UI)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codeflix/how-to-make-a-working-login-and-sign-up-form-with-html-and-csstransparent-ui-3866</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codeflix/how-to-make-a-working-login-and-sign-up-form-with-html-and-csstransparent-ui-3866"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T17:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, Readers and welcome to my new blog and today I am going to tell you How to make a working login and sign up form with Html, CSS.As you have seen many types of login and sign up form but this one is transparent . As you know that a login form is used to enter authentication credentials to access a restricted page or form. The login form contains a field for the username and another for the password. When the login form is submitted its underlying code checks that the credentials are authentic, giving the user can access the restricted page.
As you know that sign-up forms are an integral part of any website. Depending on the nature of your business, sign-up forms can be used for generating leads, collecting emails for your newsletter, and acquiring new customers. ... A sign-up form is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Codeflix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Docker to Docker compose way!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/from-docker-to-docker-compose-way-56h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/from-docker-to-docker-compose-way-56h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T17:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with docker, typing for every action is not a good deal, and sometimes it can be a nightmare because a typo mistake breaks our process, rerunning all commands. 
Today we will learn about how Docker-compose comes to make our experience with docker easy and fun.
The scope of the article is:
Why docker-compose?
How to create a docker-compose.yml file.
Automate building images and environment variables.
Orchestrate and communicate docker-compose. (Adding ports, volumes, and networks)
Troubleshooting with Container logs and shells.
The idea is to move all our commands, and everyday tasks from the docker command line to docker-compose using a docker-compose.yml file and speed up our productivity. 
If you don't have an idea about docker, please read the preview post about docker from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dany Paredes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[05 AKS - Build, Containerize, Run and Expose Node.js Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wrijugh/05-aks-build-containerize-run-and-expose-nodejs-application-1770</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wrijugh/05-aks-build-containerize-run-and-expose-nodejs-application-1770"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T17:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create a simple Node.js Express.js application, containerize it then push it to ACR and finally deploy in Kubernetes and use as Public Website. Inspired from https://nodejs.org/en/docs/guides/nodejs-docker-webapp/
https://youtu.be/yhyTK0k-WkY]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wriju's Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dependency Confusion - How can you hack Apple, Microsoft and dozens of other companies?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shostarsson/dependency-confusion-how-can-you-hack-apple-microsoft-and-dozens-of-other-companies-2gfj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shostarsson/dependency-confusion-how-can-you-hack-apple-microsoft-and-dozens-of-other-companies-2gfj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security researcher and his team have successfully deployed malware within the source code of companies known to be at the top of computer security, such as Apple, Microsoft, Paypal or Shopify.
Indeed, not really amateurs in terms of know-how to develop software in a secure way.
Well despite this, this researcher has managed to go through all the defenses of his companies simply by going through the development libraries that all developers use so as not to have to constantly reinvent the wheel.
By injecting malware into these libraries, he only had to wait for an update within these companies to be deployed without doing anything.
We talk about it in this video and I explain how to avoid falling into the trap yourself.
And you, have you ever thought about this kind of attack method on your software?
If you like this content, push the like button, that helps spread the message. 👍🏼
If you think it can be useful to anyone in your network, share it. 📨
Video produced by Wild & Secure, your consulting firm to all things security and real estate.
If you want to receive weekly quality content about security, subscribe to our newsletter on our website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rémi Lavedrine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned from The Pragmatic Programmer and The Clean Coder]]></title>
        <id>619c873711d3cb08287aaf76</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lessons-learned-from-the-pragmatic-programmer-and-the-clean-coder/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently finished reading The Pragmatic Programmer 20th Anniversary Edition (2019) and The Clean Coder (2011). You'll find these books on almost every “top 10 Software Development books” list out there.  My goal was to learn, improve, and get the kind of knowledge that a teacher from mine used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your IDE helps if you help the IDE - example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/latobibor/your-ide-helps-if-you-help-the-ide-example-31g2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/latobibor/your-ide-helps-if-you-help-the-ide-example-31g2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written previously about a clean code angle I rarely read about: writing code with the available coding tools in mind.
This is a change in viewpoint.
Instead of scraping together the easiest to write code possible you think about how much the coding tools (particularly your IDE or typescript transpiler) are going to be able to make use of it.
If this sounds alien to you I have found recently a seemingly innocent thing that can actually lead you to problems.
Let's say you want to start up a koa server using routing-controllers library. You have controllers, middlewares, interceptors...
Also you have two options: add these functions as an array or add the directories and createKoaServer function will look it up for you.
Now let's say you have an errorInterceptor.
// 'interceptors/erro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>András Tóth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-generative-patterns-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The browser has long been a medium for art and design. From Lynn Fisher’s joyful A Single Div creations to Diana Smith’s staggeringly detailed CSS paintings, wildly creative, highly skilled developers have — over the years — continuously pushed …
The post Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's different about Amazon Linux 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/whats-different-about-amazon-linux-2022-ilb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/whats-different-about-amazon-linux-2022-ilb"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Linux 2022 was recently opened to Public Preview during pre:Invent 2021. There's a lot of interesting nuances compared to Amazon Linux 2, so I wanted to consolidate the differences and provide some personal opinions.
This was also all written at time of the announcement of Public Preview, so things are liable to change ahead of General Availability.
Amazon Linux has traditionally been built around CentOS. With the transition from its standard release cycle to CentOS Stream, Amazon has decided transition to using Fedora as the base for Amazon Linux 2022, with the kernel from the Linux LTS versions.

Personal opinion: CentOS Stream is a bad choice for production use, and Amazon made a good decision to not try and shoe-horn it into Amazon Linux. Fedora also makes sense since it was alr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Sennett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and How to Add Feature Toggles to Your Software]]></title>
        <id>619e8cba25888a07c3e1b499</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-and-how-to-add-feature-toggles-to-your-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Toggles (aka Feature Flags) are a technique used in software development in order to hide, enable or disable a particular feature during runtime. They allow teams to modify system behavior without changing code. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp YouTube channel that will teach you why and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to stop DDoS attacks?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/botmenot/how-to-stop-ddos-attacks-1kfo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/botmenot/how-to-stop-ddos-attacks-1kfo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The truth is, there is no solution that works in all cases.
Attackers are getting smarter every day and their botnet armies more numerous.
In this article you can read about the most reliable ways someone can protect their network from DDoS attacks!
https://botmenot.com/blog/how-to-stop-ddos-attacks-in-2021/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BotMeNot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing with Mr. Fourier and Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/drawing-with-mr-fourier-and-typescript-5h70</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/drawing-with-mr-fourier-and-typescript-5h70"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if we connect a couple of rotating sticks together and trace the shape they make? We can get something like this.

The most interesting part about this is if we get enough sticks we can draw anything we want!
You can try it yourself here. Just draw a closed (that's pretty important) shape and press 'Start'.
This is based on a thing caller Fourier Transform. Basically, every complex function on a set interval can be represented as an infinite sum of exponents:
f(t)=∑n=−inf⁡inf⁡cnen2πit,0≤t≤1
f(t) = \sum_{n=-\inf}^{\inf}c_n e^{n 2 \pi i t}, 
0 \le t \le 1
f(t)=n=−inf∑inf​cn​en2πit,0≤t≤1



Where
cn=∫01f(t)e−n2πit
c_n = \int_0^1 f(t) e^{-n 2 \pi i t}
cn​=∫01​f(t)e−n2πit



But if we look closer we may notice that every element of that sum is actually a rotating vector Cn. So if we manage to represent a shape as a complex function, we could find these vectors (maybe not all, since there is infinite number of them, but we don't need all) and that would mean drawing the shape just by rotating those vectors!
I made a video where I tried to explain this in more detail and code it in TypeScript.




Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NordicBeaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D3.js Tutorial – Data Visualization for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>618ed39211d3cb08287a5535</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/d3js-tutorial-data-visualization-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to walk you through how to use D3.js in a step by step and beginner-friendly way. We'll talk about what D3.js is, how it works, and we'll create some basic visualizations to add transitions, interactions, and zooming. Table of Contents Getting Started  What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Ember – Ember.js Tips for Beginners Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>619cdd9d11d3cb08287ab09c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-ember-ember-js-tips-for-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, Designer turned Software Developer Lenora Porter talks about her journey learning Ember.js. She also shares her tips for beginners who are about to start their journey. Here are her top 4 take-aways: How to Learn Ember.jsHave the Mindset of a BeginnerThis is the foundational work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-side rendering, server-side rendering or static site generation. Which one should you choose?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nstubbe/client-side-rendering-vs-server-side-rendering-vs-static-site-generation-41mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nstubbe/client-side-rendering-vs-server-side-rendering-vs-static-site-generation-41mh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's more to developing a website than throwing some HTML and back-end code together. An important consideration that is often overlooked, is how a website gets rendered and delivered to users. This can make or break the experience users have, and even severely influence a website's rankings in search engines.
In this article we'll be taking a look at 3 different approaches to rendering websites with dynamic content, alongside their pros and cons
Currently the most popular approach when it comes to web applications. Client-site rendering means the client (our user's browser) is responsible for rendering the dynamic parts of our website by leveraging JavaScript and a separate back-end API.
React, Angular, Vue, JQuery, ... are mostly used for this approach.
Let's say we have a website tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niels Stubbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux / Ubuntu CLI(Command Line Interface) for beginners]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daaahailey/linux-ubuntu-clicommand-line-interface-for-beginners-35jc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daaahailey/linux-ubuntu-clicommand-line-interface-for-beginners-35jc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T14:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ubuntu and Linux?


To start with, I had the same question myself because I had no idea so I am adding this link.
What is difference between Ubuntu and Linux?
Linux


Just like Windows, iOS, and Mac OS, Linux is an operating system. In fact, one of the most popular platforms on the planet, Android, is powered by the Linux operating system. An operating system is software that manages all of the hardware resources associated with your desktop or laptop. To put it simply, the operating system manages the communication between your software and your hardware. Without the operating system (OS), the software wouldn't function.
Kernel – This is the one piece of the whole that is actually called Linux. The kernel is the core of the system and manages the CPU, memory, and peripheral device…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dahye Ji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebase vs Merge]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bernardo/rebase-vs-merge-56a8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bernardo/rebase-vs-merge-56a8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T14:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rebasing e mesclagem são projetados para integrar as alterações de um branch em outro, mas de maneiras diferentes.
Por ex. digamos que temos commits como abaixo, o merge resultará como uma combinação de commits, enquanto o rebase adicionará todas as mudanças no branch de recurso a partir do último commit do branch master:

Quando você rebase um branch de recurso no master, você move a base do branch de recurso para o ponto final do branch master.
O marge pega o conteúdo da ramificação do recurso e o integra à ramificação mestre. Como resultado, apenas o branch master é alterado. O histórico de ramificações de recursos permanece o mesmo.
A marge adiciona um novo compromisso ao seu histórico.
As confirmações serão semelhantes a:

Quando rebase? Quando marge?
Se o branch de recurso do qual você está obtendo mudanças for compartilhado com outros desenvolvedores, o rebase não é recomendado, porque o processo de rebase criará repositórios inconsistentes. Para indivíduos, o rebasing faz muito sentido.
Se você quiser ver o histórico completamente igual ao que aconteceu, você deve usar marge. Merge preserva o histórico enquanto rebase o reescreve.
Rebase é melhor para agilizar um histórico complexo, você pode alterar o histórico de commits por rebase interativo . Você pode remover commits indesejados, esmagar dois ou mais commits em um ou editar a mensagem de commit.
Rebase apresentará conflitos, um commit por vez, enquanto que merge os apresentará todos de uma vez. É melhor e muito mais fácil lidar com os conflitos, mas você não deve esquecer que reverter um rebase é muito mais difícil do que reverter uma fusão se houver muitos conflitos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luiz Bernardo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview Environments with AWS & Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/preview-environments-with-aws-ecs-cloudflare-3hdh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/preview-environments-with-aws-ecs-cloudflare-3hdh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T13:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand preview environment is a strategy to spin up a temporary infrastructure and isolated environments on the fly. This helps us open a discussion with other teams such as Product and QA at an early stage of the release process and improves cross-team visibility. So, In this article, we'll see how we can achieve this with AWS ECS and Cloudflare.
All the code is available in this repository
Let's see how this can bring benefits to our release and team workflow processes. This is an example from my personal experience.
Usual Workflow
Currently, QA and product reviews are tightly coupled to releases and it's often hard to roll back changes once they're in the release itself.

New Workflow
This will provide a huge benefit to QA and the Product team as they will be able to do a soft review…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview Environments with AWS & Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/preview-environments-with-aws-ecs-cloudflare-3hdh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/preview-environments-with-aws-ecs-cloudflare-3hdh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T13:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-demand preview environment is a strategy to spin up a temporary infrastructure and isolated environments on the fly. This helps us open a discussion with other teams such as Product and QA at an early stage of the release process and improves cross-team visibility. So, In this article, we'll see how we can achieve this with AWS ECS and Cloudflare.
All the code is available in this repository
Let's see how this can bring benefits to our release and team workflow processes. This is an example from my personal experience.
Usual Workflow
Currently, QA and product reviews are tightly coupled to releases and it's often hard to roll back changes once they're in the release itself.

New Workflow
This will provide a huge benefit to QA and the Product team as they will be able to do a soft review…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create commits for a year of your choosing in Git and Github]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sugamkarki/create-commits-for-a-year-of-your-choosing-in-git-and-github-2eak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sugamkarki/create-commits-for-a-year-of-your-choosing-in-git-and-github-2eak"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T13:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello folks, 
I have created a simple and silly command-line package that can generate commit logs in your repository for the whole year. 
Go to any local repository.
Run
npx commit_git


Enter the year of your choosing. Eg: 1990


Enter your commit text. Eg: She sells seashells by the seashore.


Voila. It automatically pushes your code after committing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sugam Karki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript weird type system - Type coercion is bad]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/javascript-weird-type-system-type-coercion-is-bad-6n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/javascript-weird-type-system-type-coercion-is-bad-6n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heyaa, welcome back, I hope you're doing well, in the previous article we've discussed basic data types and some discussions around some types, you can check it up if you don't know about that.
But now we're going to talk about the:
One of the most important and underrated concepts related to types, I'd go saying if you don't understand type coercion and how it works, you won't be able to reason about your code base.
How would you make an algorithm if you're ignoring if types coerce to another type?
That's where bugs come from btw, the divergence of your mental model or intention and how JavaScript behaves and thinks, and yeh, JS never mistakes.. umm, maybe a little bit.. aight, JS messes up with types, so help her!
I don't know about you, but I find these anti-coercion people who claim th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Osama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to Load Testing Node.js APIs with Artillery]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/appsignal/a-guide-to-load-testing-nodejs-apis-with-artillery-4he3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/appsignal/a-guide-to-load-testing-nodejs-apis-with-artillery-4he3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artillery is an open-source command-line tool purpose-built for load testing and smoke testing web applications. It is written in JavaScript and it supports testing HTTP, Socket.io, and WebSockets APIs.
This article will get you started with load testing your Node.js APIs using Artillery. You'll be able to detect and fix critical performance issues before you deploy code to production.
Before we dive in and set up Artillery for a Node.js app, though, let's first answer the question: what is load testing and why is it important?
Load testing is essential to quantify system performance and identify breaking points at which an application starts to fail. A load test generally involves simulating user queries to a remote server.
Load tests reproduce real-world workloads to measure how a system…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayooluwa Isaiah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Starting Point; Operating Systems & Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/the-starting-point-operating-systems-systems-11je</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/the-starting-point-operating-systems-systems-11je"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core principles to DevOps and SRE is a skill that a lot of new engineers are losing, which is the understanding of systems (servers, for example) and operating systems. Not too long ago, as an engineer, you had to understand how to install Linux. You needed to know how to dedicate storage to the OS, mount volumes, install the operating system itself, and configure the operating system.
Now, things are slightly different ever since we started living in a cloudy world. Getting a system up and running is as easy as logging into a cloud portal and clicking a few buttons. 
The problem with not knowing about operating systems is; regardless how much abstraction there is, systems are still needed. For example, a Docker container is running a flavor of Linux or a version of Windows. You…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Levan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Starting Point; Operating Systems & Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/the-starting-point-operating-systems-systems-11je</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thenjdevopsguy/the-starting-point-operating-systems-systems-11je"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core principles to DevOps and SRE is a skill that a lot of new engineers are losing, which is the understanding of systems (servers, for example) and operating systems. Not too long ago, as an engineer, you had to understand how to install Linux. You needed to know how to dedicate storage to the OS, mount volumes, install the operating system itself, and configure the operating system.
Now, things are slightly different ever since we started living in a cloudy world. Getting a system up and running is as easy as logging into a cloud portal and clicking a few buttons. 
The problem with not knowing about operating systems is; regardless how much abstraction there is, systems are still needed. For example, a Docker container is running a flavor of Linux or a version of Windows. You…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Levan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IaaS vs PaaS vs SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marketlancing/iaas-vs-paas-vs-saas-1ph7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marketlancing/iaas-vs-paas-vs-saas-1ph7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are chances if you were to ask 5 peoples at a cloud event about “What is Cloud Computing” you would get 5 different answers. This can be really frustrating for those who are beginner in cloud computing field and learning it. The only reason behind this confusion that there are many ways we can utilize the cloud. We can best think of cloud computing in terms like IaaS – Infrastructure as a service, PaaS – Platform as a service and SaaS – Software as a service. 
Now a days, cloud computing growing in a rapid pace that most of the terns falls under category cloud computing  transformation services , and they are IaaS, PaaS, and SaaS. These three acronyms have the same last three and assumed they have the same meaning. Anything that ends with aaS term known as as-a-service in cloud compu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Market Lancing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IaaS vs PaaS vs SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marketlancing/iaas-vs-paas-vs-saas-1ph7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marketlancing/iaas-vs-paas-vs-saas-1ph7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are chances if you were to ask 5 peoples at a cloud event about “What is Cloud Computing” you would get 5 different answers. This can be really frustrating for those who are beginner in cloud computing field and learning it. The only reason behind this confusion that there are many ways we can utilize the cloud. We can best think of cloud computing in terms like IaaS – Infrastructure as a service, PaaS – Platform as a service and SaaS – Software as a service. 
Now a days, cloud computing growing in a rapid pace that most of the terns falls under category cloud computing  transformation services , and they are IaaS, PaaS, and SaaS. These three acronyms have the same last three and assumed they have the same meaning. Anything that ends with aaS term known as as-a-service in cloud compu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Market Lancing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You are wasting resources by using classical surveillance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcosteinke/you-are-wasting-resources-by-installing-surveillance-2nfh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcosteinke/you-are-wasting-resources-by-installing-surveillance-2nfh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings fellow developers on dev.to
Today I am mentioning a topic why is neccessary when owning your own small business, or protecting your by using installing surveillance cameras. 
The cameras which you install to protect your possession do mostly offer no more than a video source, which is persisted on any type of hard drive (in marketing they would say "secure data server") inside of your shop or home and will only be inspected if something happened. 
Some more modern surveillance technologies do also offer motion detection.
Thus the motion detection may somehow be used to update the cameras orientation, as often seen in Action Movies. The camera may follow the motion by a certain degree thus the original field of view is still in sight but the motion can be captured too.
But don't y…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Steinke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Showcase Of Lovely Little Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of spending your coffee break scrolling through your social feeds, how about a lovely little website instead? We came across some fantastic ones that are just too good not to be shared. But be warned, your break might take a bit longer than intended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Angular 11?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/whats-new-in-angular-11-1l16</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/whats-new-in-angular-11-1l16"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T11:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is the most popular framework and platform to build the desktop applications and mobile applications. Angular is written in typescript. Angular 11 has been released in Nov 2020 and it is developed by Google.
Angular is a Typescript based open-source platform that makes it easy to create applications within web/mobile/desktop. It is a framework and platform to create a single page application.
To check the installed version of angular, run the ng version command.
Angular CLI: 10.0.8
Node: 12.18.3
OS: win32 x64
Angular:
...
Ivy Workspace:
Package                      Version
------------------------------------------------------
@angular-devkit/architect    0.1000.8
@angular-devkit/core         10.0.8
@angular-devkit/schematics   10.0.8
@schematics/angular          10.0.8
@schematics…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DhiWise Node.js is now Open Source and there is so much we are stoked about!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhiwise/dhiwise-nodejs-is-now-open-source-and-there-is-so-much-we-are-stoked-about-nmd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhiwise/dhiwise-nodejs-is-now-open-source-and-there-is-so-much-we-are-stoked-about-nmd"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T11:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us double back a few months. The days when the team hardly slept and kept tweaking the Node.js code to make our app builder a reality. Each hour was laden with possibilities, threats, and opportunities to achieve something as monumental as the Node.js Builder that would make server-side app development a walk in the park.
But was it the end of the road for us? Not by a long shot at DhiWise, we made sure to incrementally incorporate new features into the existing set of thrills, only to make the Node.js Builder by going open-source as a ‘ Node.js Code Generator' more interactive, more productive, and more reliable. What lacked was another set of eyes, something that went beyond the team and allowed us to understand the quality of our offering from the perspective of you, the developers.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DhiWise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weird JavaScript type system - typeof and NaNs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/the-weird-javascript-type-system-typeof-and-nans-3c9i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/the-weird-javascript-type-system-typeof-and-nans-3c9i"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T10:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya, nice to see you again in another article, today's topic is kind off functional programming, I thought it my be nice to get back the basics and talk about types which is one of my favourite topics.
So why not have a series that's dedicated to the typesystem that JS has?
In this article I'll to go all beasty about types and why you should really care about types, so hold tight and let's go.
"Stop using double equal, tripe equal for the way", you often see this recommendation in some courses, blogs, and even books that favors the tripe equal === over the double equal == as they claim it's better in terms of handling corner cases. HELL NO
I won't argue that back in time I believed such claim and even spread it in some of my courses, articles. But meh, we all do silly things.
So, let's ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Osama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weird JavaScript type system - typeof and NaNs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/the-weird-javascript-type-system-typeof-and-nans-3c9i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/the-weird-javascript-type-system-typeof-and-nans-3c9i"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T10:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heya, nice to see you again in another article, today's topic is kind off functional programming, I thought it my be nice to get back the basics and talk about types which is one of my favourite topics.
So why not have a series that's dedicated to the typesystem that JS has?
In this article I'll to go all beasty about types and why you should really care about types, so hold tight and let's go.
"Stop using double equal, tripe equal for the way", you often see this recommendation in some courses, blogs, and even books that favors the tripe equal === over the double equal == as they claim it's better in terms of handling corner cases. HELL NO
I won't argue that back in time I believed such claim and even spread it in some of my courses, articles. But meh, we all do silly things.
So, let's ge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Osama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom colour for angular material components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/infinityintellect/custom-colour-for-angular-material-components-4o3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/infinityintellect/custom-colour-for-angular-material-components-4o3d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T10:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem


So, you have an angular material component, say a chip or a button like so:
<button mat-flat-button> Done button>

The designs provided to you show that the background colour of the button should be green and the text should be white.
In your corresponding styling file (.css or .scss), include the following style selector:
.mat-green {
 background-color: green;
 color: white;
}

And then, in your .html file, simply set the color input attribute to green as below:
<button mat-flat-button color="green"> Done button>

And voilà ! There you have it.
Note: You can provide any name to the css selector and prefix it with mat- and set the name to the color attribute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddeshwar Navaneetharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dev]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/caoquyen1913/dev-38he</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/caoquyen1913/dev-38he"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T09:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dev]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trần Cao Quyền</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a simple TODO reactjs app]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yousefshallah/create-a-simple-reactjs-project-567d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yousefshallah/create-a-simple-reactjs-project-567d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T08:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a simple Todo App with React which teaches you the basic principles of CRUD (Create, Read, Update and Delete)
Hello readers! This is the first time I am writing an article on building something with React. Building a Todo App is easy and does not take much time but it teaches you some important concepts in reactjs. It teaches you the principle of CRUD (Create, Read, Update and Delete) which are very important to understand for any developer.
npx create-react-app todo
Now, this would create a folder named ‘todo’ in our current repository. Next, we should move inside the todo folder by
    cd todo

Now, we will install libraries we need using npm which would help us with using the Bootstrap library to apply the styling.
    npm install react-bootstrap bootstrap

Running the above…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yousef shallah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 best practices every Node.js developer must follow]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhiwise/10-best-practices-every-nodejs-developer-must-follow-362m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhiwise/10-best-practices-every-nodejs-developer-must-follow-362m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T08:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the StackOverflow developers survey, Node.js is the most popular development framework among developers from the last few years. It is an open-source, cross-platform, back-end JavaScript runtime environment that runs on a V8 engine.
The syntax is simple and easy to understand, also it is best for asynchronous and event-driven programming. Therefore getting started with Node.js is effortless but once you step into advanced programming, you need to deal with the code complexity and errors that can become troublesome.
However, following the best Node.js practices reduces the possibilities of errors and loopholes in your code and keeps your app safe from the most common Node.js traps.

1. Always create a new project with npm init and save the exact package version
NPM is a package…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DhiWise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join professionals from RedHat, Polypane & Researchers in Quantum Computing at Git Commit Show]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/srbhr/join-professionals-from-redhat-polypane-researchers-in-quantum-computing-at-git-commit-show-b0h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/srbhr/join-professionals-from-redhat-polypane-researchers-in-quantum-computing-at-git-commit-show-b0h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T08:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for the 3rd Season of Git Commit Show LIVE, ONLINE on 27th & 28th November, 2021.



  
  
  Masterclasses and Showcases on DevOps, ReactJS, Web Development, Community Engagement, RPA and much more!


Git Commit Show is the leading online tech conference where senior engineers, researchers, scientists and professors meet while being at home. A 2-day long, online, 100% free meetup  where senior developers and researchers share their knowledge and breakthrough projects.
interactive with opportunities to connect with speakers and fellow attendees face to face. The show started in 2019 to provide a better alternative to physical conferences by being open, free and inclusive of people who come from remote locations and modest backgrounds.
GROW YOUR NETWORK 👫 : Chance of meeting a lot o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saurabh Rai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to prevent Lambda Cold Starts using Serverless Framework?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/how-to-prevent-lambda-cold-starts-using-serverless-framework-m44</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivangchauhan7/how-to-prevent-lambda-cold-starts-using-serverless-framework-m44"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T06:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are AWS Lambda Cold Starts?


Whenever we call a lambda function it doesn't just start instantly if you haven't called it recently, it takes time before it starts executing the code, this happens because AWS shuts down the container responsible for executing the code inside our lambda function if it's not called for some time then, so the time taken to start up a new container before executing the code inside the lambda function is called a cold start or we can say that it is the delay before actual code execution starts inside our lambda function.
If we are using AWS Serverless framework then there is a plugin called serverless-plugin-warmup it is a third party NPM (Node package module) which polls the lambda function of our choice, this way that lambda function stays warm and AWS do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivang Chauhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter Mobile App Development Company | Flutter Staff Augmentation]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dasinfomediamkt/flutter-mobile-app-development-company-flutter-staff-augmentation-4bo5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dasinfomediamkt/flutter-mobile-app-development-company-flutter-staff-augmentation-4bo5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T05:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter programmers construct feature-rich, scalable apps that give users a natural-feeling experience. They provide a wide range of app solutions thanks to their groundbreaking cross-platform development architecture. We provide a variety of Flutter app development services for a variety of mobile platforms, including Flutter experts, QA specialists, cross-platform experts, and material design Design experts to create high-quality solutions, with over 4+ years of expertise.
sales@dasinfomedia.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DasinfomediaMKT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Math You Need to Know in Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>6197c7ce11d3cb08287a9271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-the-math-you-need-in-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an AI researcher, and I’ve received quite a few emails asking me just how much math is required in Artificial Intelligence. I won’t lie: it’s a lot of math. And this is one of the reasons AI puts off many beginners. After much research and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criando e configurando projeto Node.Js com TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pabloferrari013/criando-e-configurando-projeto-nodejs-com-typescript-30lj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T23:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Requisitos necessários


Para iniciarmos a criação de nosso  projeto, precisaremos desses componentes instalados:
Node.js
yarn
Em algum lugar de sua preferência, crie uma pasta e a abra em seu editor de código. No terminal, navegue até a pasta e rode o comando:
$ yarn init -y

Podemos observar que o arquivo packge.json foi criado na raiz de seu projeto, onde estão contidos dados como o nome de seu projeto, a versão, o arquivo principal, a licença e futuramente conterá as dependências. 
No terminal, baixe a dependência de desenvolvimento do TypeScript:
$ yarn add typescript -D

Podemos observar que uma pasta chamada node_modules foi criada, ela é responsável por armazenar os módulos de dependências de seu projeto.
No terminal, inicie o TypeScript:
yarn tsc --init

Podemos observar que o arq…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Ferrari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is GitOps? Principles, Best Practices, and Kubernetes Workflow]]></title>
        <id>619bb55911d3cb08287aa581</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitops-principles-kubernetes-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, CTO Cornelia Davis will teach you what GitOps is and what its four main principles are.  What is GitOps?The first thing you need to know is that GitOps is a set of modern best practises for deploying and managing cloud native infrastructure and applications.  And it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Facebook system design interview questions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/educative/top-10-facebook-system-design-interview-questions-57m7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/educative/top-10-facebook-system-design-interview-questions-57m7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The system design interview is a necessary hurdle as you advance in your career as a software engineer. System design interviews assess your design skills by asking you to build a scalable system. Even seasoned engineers can struggle with this interview round, but you’re already ahead of the game if you’re here for interview preparation.
Today we’ll discuss the top system design interview questions asked at Facebook. These questions are also common fare for system design interviews at all top tech companies, including FAANG (Facebook, Apple, Amazon, Netflix, and Google). 
We’ll cover:
Facebook’s interview process
How to answer system design interview questions
Top 10 Facebook system design interview questions
1. Design Facebook Newsfeed 
2. Design Messenger 
3. Design Instagram
4. Design T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ericaeducative</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎄 Render in Vue, 16+ ways]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/render-in-vue-16-ways-d50</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/render-in-vue-16-ways-d50"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post I will show you 16 ways how to render something in Vue
Talk is cheap. Show me the code.
Here is full example that you can play around 
https://github.com/iamandrewluca/vue-render-everywhere
I'm using Vite with this configuration
import { defineConfig } from 'vite'
import vue from '@vitejs/plugin-vue'
import vueJsx from '@vitejs/plugin-vue-jsx'

export default defineConfig({
  plugins: [vue(), vueJsx()],
  resolve: { alias: { vue: 'vue/dist/vue.esm-bundler.js' } }
})

When refering to a DOM element, this is the HTML for every example
<script type="text/html" id="template-in-script">
  <li>The quick brown fox...</li>
</script>

I'm showing these methods only for learning purposes. Use at your own risk.
template option as string





import { defineComponent } from "vue"

ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Luca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: npm install throwing error in node-sass]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: npm install throwing error in node-sass
            
        
Mar  1 '20
        
Add manually in package.json :  "node-sass": "4.13.0"
and update package.json in terminal npm install
Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error
            
        
Feb 25 '21
        
I solved this issue by typing the following:
 npm install grpc --save
 npm install node-pre-gyp --save

Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS IAM managed policies for Amazon DynamoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws/aws-iam-managed-policies-for-amazon-dynamodb-4g5n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws/aws-iam-managed-policies-for-amazon-dynamodb-4g5n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T20:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For application access, you should not use the managed AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies for Amazon DynamoDB. These IAM policies are designed for use with the AWS Web Console and therefore have more permissions to more services than most applications need access to. Instead, please create your own IAM policies for DynamoDB.
In order to follow least privilege security conventions, it is best practice to create your own custom IAM policy for DynamoDB access by an application. If this is something you have never done before, don't be intimidated. I got ya. To get you started, here are a few templates I created to use to enable full access to only Amazon DynamoDB table resources. 
Once you play with these templates, you should ultimately create a new policy that narrows access down to just the operations the app needs to do on the resources it needs to do it. If all you are doing is SELECT and INSERT with the PartiQL API for DynamoDB on one table, then the only actions you should allow are these two:
"dynamodb:PartiQLInsert"
"dynamodb:PartiQLSelect"
In summary, use security best practices when designing access to Amazon DynamoDB for your apps, create your own customer managed IAM policies and do not use the AWS managed IAM policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirk Kirkconnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/which-svg-technique-performs-best-for-way-too-many-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T19:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Sticka digs in here in the best possible way: by making a test page and literally measuring performance. Maybe 1,000 icons is a little bit of an edge case, but hey, 250 rows of data with four icons in …
The post Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Modern Angular Tooling?


With the Angular CLI no longer including a complete out-of-the-box development solution, it is more important than ever to understand the tools at our disposal to improve the developer experience when building Angular applications.
Modern Angular Tooling is the term used to describe modern tools that will enable you and your team to build a comprehensive development environment. This development environment takes advantage of the latest improvements in the JavaScript ecosystem to improve productivity, consistency, reliability, scalability and developer experience when building Angular applications and libraries. 
We consider Modern Tools to be additional tools that can and should be used when building Angular applications and Angular libraries. These tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colum Ferry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 easy ways to install nodejs in linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aashishpanthi/3-easy-ways-to-install-nodejs-in-linux-lc4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installing node in linux is quite challenging sometimes, especially if you are a beginner and don't have any idea on how to do that.
In this article, I will show you three different ways of installing Nodejs in linux. You can feel comfortable following the same process in any ubuntu-baseds distro you use.
Installation of Nodejs is insanely easy with apt package manager in linux. To install nodejs with apt package manager, just open up your terminal. Copy this command sudo apt update  && sudo apt upgrade and paste here, hit enter, and type your password. Then we use the command sudo apt install nodejs, press enter, wait few seconds and you find your nodejs is successfully installed. To check the version just type the command node —version and you get the version. 
To install linux binaries,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aashish Panthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356977</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/control-layout-in-a-multi-directional-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many business websites need a multilingual setup. As with anything development-related, implementing one in an easy, efficient, and maintainable way is desirable. Designing and developing to be ready for multiple languages, whether it happens right at launch or is expected …
The post Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alaa Abd El-Rahim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handling Client-Side Data Securely]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xf10yd/handling-client-side-data-securely-4onh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transmitting Data Via the Client


Many applications leave themselves exposed because they transmit critical data such as product prices and discount rates via the client in an unsafe manner.
If possible, applications should avoid transmitting this kind of data via the client. In virtually any conceivable scenario, it is possible to hold such data on the server and reference it directly from server-side logic when needed. 
For example, an application that receives users’ orders for various products should allow users to submit a product code and quantity and look up the price of each requested product in a server-side database. There is no need for users to submit the prices of items back to the server. Even where an application offers different prices or discounts to different users, ther…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUT | Read Notebooks in the Terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/waylonwalker/jut-read-notebooks-in-the-terminal-40hp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/waylonwalker/jut-read-notebooks-in-the-terminal-40hp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to read a .ipynb file without starting a jupyter server?  jut has you covered.





watch the video version of this post on YouTube
jut is packaged and available on pypi so installing is as easy as pip installing it.
pip install jut

jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb
jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb --head 3
jut https://cantera.org/examples/jupyter/thermo/flame_temperature.ipynb --tail 2

Take a look at the help of the jut cli to explore all the options that it offers.
jut --help

There is some good information on the projects readme as well.
using pipx
Don't want jut cluttering up your venv, or want to save yourself from making a new one, pipx can manage a separate virual environment for you.  This is one …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Walker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberpunk 2077 on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dyslexicjedi/cyberpunk-2077-on-linux-149e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dyslexicjedi/cyberpunk-2077-on-linux-149e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T13:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I picked up Cyberpunk 2077 on GOG at 50% off for black friday. I had a bit of trouble getting it to work on Linux (POP!_OS), here are my steps in case it helps someone else. 
First, I spun up Lutris and the game downloaded and installed fine. But when I tried to launch it, it first crashed, then on second launch it played but felt like I was watching a stop motion video. 
After googling, I found proton-tkg which is a patched version of Steam's proton. Downloaded:
wget https://github.com/Frogging-Family/wine-tkg-git/releases/download/6.17.r0.g5f19a815/proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release.tar.gz

Unpacked it
tar xf proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release.tar.gz

Then I linked it to the runners and restarted Lutris.
ln -s /home/<user>/Downloads/proton_tkg_6.17.r0.g5f19a815.release/files/ /home/<user>/.local/share/lutris/runners/wine/proton

Selected the proton item under the Runner Options:

I've been playing for an hour now, it's smooth and hasn't crashed. YMMV
Good Luck Have Fun!
If you liked this post:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dyslexicjedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons Why Developers are Shifting Towards ReactJS Instead of Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/reasons-why-developers-are-shifting-towards-reactjs-instead-of-angular-jnc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/reasons-why-developers-are-shifting-towards-reactjs-instead-of-angular-jnc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T11:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Reasons Why Everyone is Opting for ReactJS over Angular
1. Better Performance
React is mostly like a library than just a framework. Therefore, one does not has to work upfront with DOM or Data Object Model. Instead of that, it goes for a Virtual DOM layer. It updates only those parts of the actual DOM which is needed to update. This escalates the development speed in React instead of Angular. 
Moreover, the Virtual DOM is one of the best features to have as it resolves the issues associated with cross-browser.
The developers also get access to a unified API of cross-browser that runs even on old browser versions. Such excellent performance of React has made everyone not hire AngularJS developers and opt for ReactJS developers as it is becoming more and more popular than Angular.
2. JSX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Hacked Shuttl 🚎]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/heykush/how-i-hacked-shuttl-5h1h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/heykush/how-i-hacked-shuttl-5h1h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How it started 🔥


I was in my 2nd-year @delhitechnicalcampus. College timing is 9 to 4 pm, and I have to rush to pick public transport at 7 pm. It took 2 hours to reach college in between route of Noida to Pari chowk. I used this new service Shuttl. 
Shuttl - They provide Transport service from Noida Sector 37 to Pari Chowk. I am inspired by this startup as they provide 30 rupee journey costs in 10 rupees and with AC minibus.

So, for the first ride, they provide a free Coupon Ride, which is one time applicable. BUT why so and why don't we apply again so? For this, I made a Dual app and login with my secondary number, but that code is not valid for the second number. What the Hackman!

I need to figure out how's this thing working and why can't I apply code in my secondary number account…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav kushwaha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Dyslexia-Friendly Mode To A Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little CSS, we can adapt our web designs to be more accommodating for people with dyslexia. In this article, we’ll explore those techniques by adding a dyslexia-friendly mode to an existing design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John C Barstow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Custom Structural Directives in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular comes with many built-in directives. Some of them (eg. NgIf, NgModel or FormControlDirective) are used daily by Angular developers. Those directives can be split into 2 categories:
Attribute directives
They can be used to modify the appearance of behavior of Angular components and DOM elements. For example:
RouterLink
NgModel
FormControlDirective
Structural directives
They can be used to manipulate the HTML structure in the DOM. Using them, we can change the structure of part of the DOM that they control. For example:
NgIf
NgForOf
NgSwitch
In this article, I will focus on the latter.
As I've mentioned above, there are a couple of built-in structural directives in Angular. However, we might come across a case that the ones provided with the framework don't solve. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Custom Structural Directives in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thisdotmedia/getting-started-with-custom-structural-directives-in-angular-4mon"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular comes with many built-in directives. Some of them (eg. NgIf, NgModel or FormControlDirective) are used daily by Angular developers. Those directives can be split into 2 categories:
Attribute directives
They can be used to modify the appearance of behavior of Angular components and DOM elements. For example:
RouterLink
NgModel
FormControlDirective
Structural directives
They can be used to manipulate the HTML structure in the DOM. Using them, we can change the structure of part of the DOM that they control. For example:
NgIf
NgForOf
NgSwitch
In this article, I will focus on the latter.
As I've mentioned above, there are a couple of built-in structural directives in Angular. However, we might come across a case that the ones provided with the framework don't solve. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Trześniewski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Java 17 features for improved security and serialization]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brianverm/new-java-17-features-for-improved-security-and-serialization-5h3f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brianverm/new-java-17-features-for-improved-security-and-serialization-5h3f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T08:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2020, I wrote the article Serialization and deserialization in Java: explaining the Java deserialize
 about the problems Java has with its custom serialization implementation. The serialization framework is so deeply embedded inside Java that knowing how dangerous some implementation can be is important. Insecure
Recently, Java 17 -- the new LTS version -- was released. But how do the new features impact this problem, and can we prevent deserialization vulnerabilities better using these features?
In the blog post, I will look at three main Java 17 features:
Records
Java Flight Recorder (JFR) improvements
JEP 415 (Java Enhancement Proposal) Context-Specific Deserialization Filters.
Records were introduced in Java 14 as a preview feature and became a fully released feature in Jav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Vermeer 🧑🏼‍🎓🧑🏼‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices to protect your smartphone with MobSF]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aviyel/best-practices-to-protect-your-smartphone-with-mobsf-17am</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aviyel/best-practices-to-protect-your-smartphone-with-mobsf-17am"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this era of technology, we are completely relying on smartphones and yet most of us are unaware of its vulnerabilities. A smartphone is a new necessity in our day-to-day life and if intruders get access to our smartphones, it is like intruders have access to our life. This itself states how vital securing our smartphones is. Aviyel is coming with another great event to help you protect your smartphones and making it your top priority.
Why I should join this event?
You’ll learn how to secure your sensitive data.
Know how your digital life is at risk and how to protect it from intruders.
You'll learn how to make use of MobSF to protect your sensitive data from hackers.
Join Edem Gold where he will guide you with some of the most important steps to hack-proof your smartphones using MobSF and secure your digital information by preventing possible malicious activities on your smartphones.
Edem Gold is a teen Nigerian AI Engineer and content creator. He loves converting complex concepts into non-jargon stories. Gold has also experience in Blockchain development on the Ethereum system.
Join us to get hands-on experience with MobSF, open-source, and learn to tackle mobile security!
Date: November 28th, 2021
Time: 8.00 AM PST | 11:00 AM EST
Where 👉: https://bit.ly/3xddbD5
Impressed? Check out the rest of our events!
Let’s build open-source together! 🎉
Edem Gold Socials!
Twitter: Edem Gold
Edem Gold
Edem Gold]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sankalp Swami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going serverless with MongoDB Realm - Vue.js Version]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-vuejs-version-nld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-vuejs-version-nld"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture is a pattern of running and building applications and services without having to manage infrastructure. It involves the applications and services running on the server, but all the server management is done by a cloud provider.
This post will discuss building a fullstack user management application using MongoDB, MongoDB Realm, and Vue.js. At the end of this tutorial, we will learn how to create a database on MongoDB, serverless functions as our endpoints using MongoDB Realm and consume the endpoints in a Vue.js application.
MongoDB Realm is a development platform designed for building mobile, web, desktop, and IoT applications. It offers services like data synchronization, serverless functions, triggers, user authentication, e.t.c. We can build and maintain applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going serverless with MongoDB Realm - React.js Version]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-reactjs-version-jh6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hackmamba/going-serverless-with-mongodb-realm-reactjs-version-jh6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T07:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless architecture is a pattern of running and building applications and services without having to manage infrastructure. It involves the applications and services running on the server, but all the server management is done by a cloud provider.
This post will discuss building a fullstack user management application using MongoDB, MongoDB Realm, and React.js. At the end of this tutorial, we will learn how to create a database on MongoDB, serverless functions as our endpoints using MongoDB Realm and consume the endpoints in a React.js application.
MongoDB Realm is a development platform designed for building mobile, web, desktop, and IoT applications. It offers services like data synchronization, serverless functions, triggers, user authentication, e.t.c. We can build and maintain app…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Demola Malomo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Comprehensive Guide to Angular Performance Tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/the-comprehensive-guide-to-angular-performance-tuning-1l5n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/the-comprehensive-guide-to-angular-performance-tuning-1l5n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T06:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not uncommon to see Angular apps slow down over time. Angular is a performant platform, but if we don't know how to create performant Angular apps, our apps will become slower as they evolve. As a result, any serious Angular developer must be aware of what makes an Angular app slow in order to prevent it from being slow in the first place.
Change detection can be the most performance-intensive part of Angular apps, so it's important to understand how to render the templates efficiently so that we would just re-rendering a component if it has new changes to display.
When an asynchronous event occurs in the app, such as click, XMLHttpRequest, or setTimeout, the default change detection behavior for components is to re-render. This can be a matter of concern because it will result in a l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to store result from async pipe in angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codever/how-to-store-result-from-async-pipe-in-angular-a0k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codever/how-to-store-result-from-async-pipe-in-angular-a0k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T05:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project: codever - File:  snippet-details.component.html
Use the async pipe and store it in variable for later use *ngIf="(snippet$ | async) as snippet". Below the complete snippet example with usage included:
<div *ngIf="(snippet$ | async) as snippet" class="card">
  <div class="card-body show-hide">
    <div class="header-wrapper">
      <div class="titles">
        <h4 *ngIf='inlist; else hyperLinkTitle' class="card-title">
             <span *ngIf="snippet.public; else linkToPrivateSnippet">
                <i class="fas fa-eye fa-xs mr-2" title="Public snippet"></i>
                <a routerLink="/snippets/{{snippet._id}}/details"
                   [innerHtml]="snippet.title | highlight: queryText"></a> </span>
          <ng-template #linkToPrivateSnippet>
                <span>
    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Matei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding form validation to an Angular application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-form-validation-to-an-angular-application-387a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/adding-form-validation-to-an-angular-application-387a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T22:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 13 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
Form validation enables the quality, accuracy, and integrity of the user input data. It’s possible to validate a form in Angular in two ways, one with reactive (using functions in the component class) and the other with template-driven forms (using attributes in the HTML) and we will use the template-driven forms way.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the application with the Angular base structure using the @angular/cli with the route file and the SCSS style…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-user-tracking-and-industry-standards-on-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Eva PenzeyMoog’s new book, Jeremy highlights the widespread user tracking situation in this industry:
There was a line that really stood out to me: 
The idea that it’s alright to do whatever unethical thing is currently the 
…
The post On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; Base64 [LS#1]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-base64-ls1-42d4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-base64-ls1-42d4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encode inline





echo -n 'Hello World!' | base64

base64 ~/.bashrc > encoded-file.txt

cat ~/.bashrc | base64 > encoded-file.txt

echo -n "SGVsbG8gV29ybGQh" | base64 -d

base64 -d encoded-file.txt > decoded-file.txt

cat encoded-file.txt | base64 -d > decoded-file.txt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheus and Grafana, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/muckitymuck/prometheus-and-grafana-part-2-47bg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/muckitymuck/prometheus-and-grafana-part-2-47bg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T20:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prometheus.yml:
# my global config
global:
  scrape_interval:     15s # Set the scrape interval to every 15 seconds. Default is every 1 minute.
  evaluation_interval: 15s # Evaluate rules every 15 seconds. The default is every 1 minute.

scrape_configs:
  # The job name is added as a label `job=<job_name>` to any timeseries scraped from this config.
  - job_name: 'prometheus'

    # metrics_path defaults to '/metrics'
    # scheme defaults to 'http'.

    static_configs:
      - targets: ['localhost:9090']

  - job_name: 'node-exporter'

    # Override the global default and scrape targets from this job every 5 seconds.
    scrape_interval: 5s
    metrics_path: /metrics

    static_configs:
      - targets:
        - <PUBLIC IP>:9100

This is a good starting place for a monitoring system for Linux boxes
Running the services in docker is also advised as it simplifies the rollout.
Docker node exporter:
sudo docker run --restart always -d --net="host" --pid="host"  -v "/:/host:ro,rslave"  prom/node-exporter:latest  --path.rootfs=/host

Docker prometheus:
sudo docker service create --replicas 1 --name dockerprometheus     --mount type=bind,source=/home/ubuntu/prometheus/prometheus.yml,destination=/etc/prometheus/prometheus.yml     --publish published=9090,target=9090,protocol=tcp     prom/prometheus

When you get around to making panels in Grafana, these queries are very useful:
100 - ((node_filesystem_avail_bytes{mountpoint="/",fstype!="rootfs"} * 100) /            node_filesystem_size_bytes{mountpoint="/",fstype!="rootfs"})

node_filesystem_avail_bytes


OR you could just setup a template for Node Exporter:

Enter 405 for the Grafana ID.

Pick up the name and choose a Data Source for the dashboard.

To make an alert, start a NEW dashboard and NEW panel. Template dashboards like above will not work. 
Enter the query for the item you want to track and press the Alert tab.
That should do it for a basic monitoring service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>muckitymuck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS “decorations”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357046</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-decorations/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reader wrote to me the other day asking about this bit of CSS they came across in Wikipedia’s Common.css:
.mw-collapsible-leftside-toggle .mw-collapsible-toggle {
  /* @noflip */
  float: left;
  /* @noflip */
  text-align: left;
}
What’s that @noflip business? That’s …
The post CSS “decorations” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Workshops: Winter 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of CSS, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our [online workshops on UX, front-end and design](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357080</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-layouts-fewer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T15:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We cannot talk about web development without talking about Responsive Design. It’s just a given these days and has been for many years. Media queries are a part of Responsive Design and they aren’t going anywhere. Since the introduction of …
The post Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't panic when using CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/elisboa/dont-panic-when-using-cli-3d99</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/elisboa/dont-panic-when-using-cli-3d99"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T11:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


When using the Command Line Interface, we often find a few long and / or confusing commands. And this post intends to ease the pain of getting along with that.
When things start to get complicated, there are some things that can be done. In this post, we are talking about three of them:
Aliases
Functions
Comments
An alias is exactly what it means: a nickname. It is very useful when running commands that take too much arguments. For example:
alias lah=ls -ltrah

Now, when running the lah command, it will be exactly like running ls -ltrah.
A function is probably the best way to run a group of commands. When adding a if or a for statement, it gets even more interesting. Let's suppose we want to connect to a server which is still being provisioned or rebooted:
function keeptrying() {
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eduardo Lisboa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[change case sensitive setting in less command]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/icy1900/change-case-sensitive-setting-in-less-command-3j57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/icy1900/change-case-sensitive-setting-in-less-command-3j57"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick guide in 2 steps: Do your search:
:/put search lowercase word here after slash
Then after all the case sensitive matches are highlighted:
:-i
This will highlight all matches regardless of case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Wix Websites (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a performance culture is very important. In this article, Dan Shappir shares which actions and processes the Wix team put in place in order to achieve dramatic improvements in the performance of websites built and hosted on their platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Atomic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/reimagine-atomic-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T22:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not the biggest fan of Atomic CSS myself. I don’t like all the classes. I like to express my styles in CSS because I find CSS… good. But I appreciate that a lot of people seem to like it, …
The post Reimagine Atomic CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Font Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/coding-font-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tournament bracket UI where you pick your favorite between two coding fonts and your choices are whittled down all the way to a final winner. A clever way to suss out your own taste and arrive at a choice.…
The post Coding Font Game appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357192</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/parallax-powered-by-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good friend Kent C. Dodds has recently dropped his new website which had a lot of work go into it. I was fortunate enough that Kent reached out a while back and asked if I could come up with some …
The post Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting with a wildcard subdomain enables your users to visit your site on any subdomain of your domain (*.example.com), and as you can imagine, we can use this to create unique user experiences which we’ll be exploring in this article through a Next.js lens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cherry-Picking Commits in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356700</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cherry-picking-commits-in-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In part 5 of this series, we looked at rebasing and merging. Although there are a couple of differences between git merge and git rebase, both commands have the same goal: they integrate changes from one branch into another.
The post Cherry-Picking Commits in Git appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gap (Design Engineering)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357023</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-gap-design-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egor Kloos describes a situation where a (purely visual) designer asks for some changes to a component. There is a misunderstanding where the (code monkey) developer implements the change exactly as requested—but really what was required was both a bug …
The post The Gap (Design Engineering) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting in early January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>