<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-07-09T00:54:31.580Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-09T00:54:31.580Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker for Dummies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stevenmcgown/docker-for-dummies-2bff</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stevenmcgown/docker-for-dummies-2bff"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T00:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions to answer:
What problems does Docker solve?
What are containers?
What is the difference between a container and a VM?
What is the difference between images and containers?
How does Docker help create applications?
Why Docker?
The need for Docker arises from virtual machines on servers being used at large scales. Take a large business for example. For a business that uses hundreds of servers with a cluster of virtual machines for each of their platforms, maintaining these machines is a full-time job. Each server has to have an OS installed, it needs upgrades and patches from time to time, and then dependencies for the applications each machine uses also have to be installed. 
You can see why this quickly becomes very complex. Manually configuring these servers is not feasible, so …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevenMcGown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker for Dummies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stevenmcgown/docker-for-dummies-2bff</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stevenmcgown/docker-for-dummies-2bff"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T00:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questions to answer:
What problems does Docker solve?
What are containers?
What is the difference between a container and a VM?
What is the difference between images and containers?
How does Docker help create applications?
Why Docker?
The need for Docker arises from virtual machines on servers being used at large scales. Take a large business for example. For a business that uses hundreds of servers with a cluster of virtual machines for each of their platforms, maintaining these machines is a full-time job. Each server has to have an OS installed, it needs upgrades and patches from time to time, and then dependencies for the applications each machine uses also have to be installed. 
You can see why this quickly becomes very complex. Manually configuring these servers is not feasible, so …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevenMcGown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GITHUB_TOKEN in GitHub Actions: How it Works, Change Permissions, Customizations]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/github/the-githubtoken-in-github-actions-how-it-works-change-permissions-customizations-3cgp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/github/the-githubtoken-in-github-actions-how-it-works-change-permissions-customizations-3cgp"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T00:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I'm gonna tell you everything about the GITHUB_TOKEN in GitHub Actions. You will learn what it is, how it works, how to customize its behavior, and how to limit or change its permissions.
As usual, if you are a visual learner, or simply prefer to watch and listen instead of reading, here you have the video with the whole explanation and demo, which to be fair is much more complete than this post.




Link to the video: https://youtu.be/jEK07KPEjnY
If you rather prefer reading, well... let's just continue :)
Let's start with what the GITHUB_TOKEN is in GitHub Actions and how it works.
The GITHUB_TOKEN is a special access token that you can use to authenticate on behalf of GitHub Actions. GitHub automatically creates a GITHUB_TOKEN secret for you to use in your workflow, and you can us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide 'CoderDave' Benvegnù</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monkey-patching the Express router]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shalvah/monkey-patching-the-express-router-oo1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shalvah/monkey-patching-the-express-router-oo1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I maintain Scribe, a library for automatically generating your HTTP API documentation from your codebase. When you run the generate command, Scribe fetches your routes from your codebase, uses a bunch of strategies to figure out details about them, and transforms those details into a HTML docs page. There are a lot of moving parts and complexity in this process, but this post is about the first part: how Scribe is able to fetch the routes from your app.
In the Laravel version, this process is hella easy: just call Illuminate\Support\Facades\Route::getRoutes(), and you get an array of Route objects, with each object containing the route details, including the path, HTTP methods, and handler (controller/method). It's a similar thing for the AdonisJS version.
The Express version is another st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shalvah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to cryptography in distributed ledger technology]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xjepsen/an-introduction-to-cryptography-in-distributed-ledger-technology-268l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xjepsen/an-introduction-to-cryptography-in-distributed-ledger-technology-268l"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography is the backbone of distributed ledger technologies like blockchain and other consensus-oriented distributed networks. If you are interested in building decentralized applications, it's essential to understand the wallet generation and transaction signing processes. Both of which rely heavily on underlying cryptographic protocols.
In addition to distributed networks, cryptography is a critical component of cybersecurity. With cybercrime on the rise and cyberattacks costing businesses an average of 2.3 Million dollars per malware attack source, it is increasingly important to have your cybersecurity up to par. With the proper use of cryptography, you could save your business big time by ensuring the confidentiality of sensitive information. 
Modern cryptography is mathematically…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Jepsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner JavaScript Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=344024</id>
        <link href="https://wesbos.com/javascript"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wes has a heck of a set of “notes” for learning JavaScript. It’s organized like a curriculum, meaning if you teach JavaScript, you could do a lot worse. It’s actually more like 85 really fleshed-out blog posts organized into sections …
The post Beginner JavaScript Notes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockerizing a Shopify Node App]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deanandreakis/dockerizing-a-shopify-node-app-1djf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deanandreakis/dockerizing-a-shopify-node-app-1djf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T21:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am in the process of learning to develop apps for the Shopify platform. In doing so, I wanted to establish early on how I would be deploying and managing my apps. I recently earned my GCP Professional Cloud Architect certification so I was pretty sure I would be using GCP in production. I decided that the easiest way to deploy and manage my apps in production would be to containerize them using Docker. If your not familiar with what a container is I highly recommend reading this overview on the docker site. TLDR; a container packages a software application and its dependencies so that it can execute across different environments without the need to pre-configure those environments.
Let's get started!
Node.js v16.4.2
Docker desktop v3.5
Shopify CLI
I started by following along the Shopify…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Andreakis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to fix install typescript found 0 vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/markostrahilov/how-to-fix-install-typescript-found-0-vulnerabilities-659</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/markostrahilov/how-to-fix-install-typescript-found-0-vulnerabilities-659"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T21:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been having problem with the found 0 vulnerabilities error while downloading typescript globally, does someone know how can I fix this error]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MarkJonathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wault: The future of password managers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wault/wault-the-future-of-password-storage-e3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wault/wault-the-future-of-password-storage-e3j"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T21:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password managers are becoming more common these days as we are using an increasing number of sites each day. I have used several password managers for about 4 years, but I've never found the one that fits me. Everyone had some major flaws like it felt outdated or it was too expensive. Then it hit me... why shouldn't I create the next Facebook of password storage?
1. The app must have a generous free tier. I wanted a personal plan, where you can store your passwords safely across multiple devices without hassle.
2. The app must feel new and responsive. When I used Lastpass and Bitwarden I felt like I was using a slightly outdated piece of software. I think the best and easiest way to achieve this is by 
3. Be open-source. I think this one is obvious. If you make an application open source,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gál Péter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wault: The future of password managers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wault/wault-the-future-of-password-storage-e3j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wault/wault-the-future-of-password-storage-e3j"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T21:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password managers are becoming more common these days as we are using an increasing number of sites each day. I have used several password managers for about 4 years, but I've never found the one that fits me. Everyone had some major flaws like it felt outdated or it was too expensive. Then it hit me... why shouldn't I create the next Facebook of password storage?
1. The app must have a generous free tier. I wanted a personal plan, where you can store your passwords safely across multiple devices without hassle.
2. The app must feel new and responsive. When I used Lastpass and Bitwarden I felt like I was using a slightly outdated piece of software. I think the best and easiest way to achieve this is by 
3. Be open-source. I think this one is obvious. If you make an application open source,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gál Péter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Convert LV or MD RAID1 and 0 Into RAID5 Without Losing Data]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-convert-lv-or-md-raid1-and-0-into-raid5-without-losing-data-2agb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/how-to-convert-lv-or-md-raid1-and-0-into-raid5-without-losing-data-2agb"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T20:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to switch from RAID 0 or 1 to RAID 5. How to convert (on Linux, with mdadm or LVM) a software RAID1 (0) system into RAID5 while keeping all the data it stores.

RAID 0 disk arrays are known for relatively high data access time, and that’s why people choose to use them primarily because of the considerable boost in the speed of read and write operations. However, their reliability and fault-tolerance leave much to be desired. Even if one of the drives is out of order, all the data in such a disk array is going to be lost. Recovering the information from this array type is quite a challenge, but even then, all the data you may be able to extract will certainly be damaged. In fact, this type is not much of a disk array because it offers no redundancy at al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Quality fit in CALMS?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/droopy12/does-quality-fit-in-calms-45pj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/droopy12/does-quality-fit-in-calms-45pj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T20:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was originally published on my blog, https://unremarkabletester.com/.
Recently, I was asked to give a 15 minute introduction on Quality Strategy in DevOps for our upcoming "Efficient DevOps with SAP" course and I happily accepted. And then, to my horror of horrors, I realised that I needed to figure out what a Quality Strategy is and what makes it unique in a DevOps world.
Instead of trying to come up with a definition, I started considering what are some quality specific aspects within the CALMS framework that would help a DevOps transformation.
So, here are a few ideas on the Culture, Automation, Lean, Measurement and Sharing aspects to consider that might improve the overall quality of a system, from idea to end user.
When it comes to the online narrative of Quality in DevOps envir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Areti Panou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helpful Tools for Apache Kafka Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/daveklein/helpful-tools-for-apache-kafka-developers-1l89</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/daveklein/helpful-tools-for-apache-kafka-developers-1l89"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post was originally published on the Confluent blog.
Apache Kafka® is at the core of a large ecosystem that includes powerful components, such as Kafka Connect and Kafka Streams. This ecosystem also includes many tools and utilities that make us, as Kafka developers, more productive while making our jobs easier and more enjoyable. Below, we'll take a look at a few of these tools and how they can help us get work done.
kafkacat
We like to save the best for last, but this tool is too good to wait. So, we'll start off by covering kafkacat.
kafkacat is a fast and flexible command line Kafka producer, consumer, and more. Magnus Edenhill, the author of the librdkafka C/C++ library for Kafka, developed it. kafkacat is great for quickly producing and consuming data to and from a topic. I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writeup: HackTheBox Shocker- Without Metasploit (OSCP Prep)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xhuey/writeup-hackthebox-shocker-without-metasploit-oscp-prep-1mnh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xhuey/writeup-hackthebox-shocker-without-metasploit-oscp-prep-1mnh"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello All,
Thing's have gotten a little serious as I have bought my OSCP Certification attempt. So I will hopefully pushing out more HTB write-ups over the next 2 weeks.
Let's begin!!
Nmap -sC -sV -T4 -oN nmap.txt -vvv 10.10.10.56
-sC = Default Scripts
-sV = Probe open ports to determine service/Versions info
-T4 = Set timing for faster output (0-5)
-oN = Output to save it to a file
-vvv = 9 different levels and will cause Nping to print more information during execution more reading link





Port Opens:
80 TCP HTTP
2222 TCP SSH
Let's run a full port scan to see if we missed anything here.
nmap -p- -oN allports.txt 10.10.10.56

So nothing else actually returns which is a bummer.
Let's try and run a quick Vuln scan just for kicks.
nmap --script vuln -oN vuln.txt 10.10.10.56

Nothing here p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris 'Huey' S</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build minimal angular 12 application with webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-build-minimal-angular-12-application-with-webpack-4laa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-build-minimal-angular-12-application-with-webpack-4laa"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow the angular documentation, you find either:
getting started guide that leads you to a stackblitz project with 21 files
tutorial that start with installing the code generator
What if you want to try angular without getting their complete tooling or you want to integrate it into already existing project in a more lightweight way? This article have you covered - we will take a look on a minimal webpack configuration needed to build simple angular app.
Good starting point is this post:
Minimal webpack configuration to build typescript
Marcin Wosinek ・ Jul 8 ・ 2 min read
#webpack
        #typescript
      
with simple webpack configuration to build typescript.
If we want to keep our file footprint as small as we can, we can put all angular logic into just one file src/index.ts:
im…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build minimal angular 12 application with webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-build-minimal-angular-12-application-with-webpack-4laa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/how-to-build-minimal-angular-12-application-with-webpack-4laa"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow the angular documentation, you find either:
getting started guide that leads you to a stackblitz project with 21 files
tutorial that start with installing the code generator
What if you want to try angular without getting their complete tooling or you want to integrate it into already existing project in a more lightweight way? This article have you covered - we will take a look on a minimal webpack configuration needed to build simple angular app.
Good starting point is this post:
Minimal webpack configuration to build typescript
Marcin Wosinek ・ Jul 8 ・ 2 min read
#webpack
        #typescript
      
with simple webpack configuration to build typescript.
If we want to keep our file footprint as small as we can, we can put all angular logic into just one file src/index.ts:
im…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to DevOps on AWS | AWS Whitepaper Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/introduction-to-devops-on-aws-aws-whitepaper-summary-877</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/introduction-to-devops-on-aws-aws-whitepaper-summary-877"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This paper highlights:



AWS capabilities that help you accelerate your DevOps journey, and how AWS services can help remove the undifferentiated heavy lifting associated with DevOps adaptation.
How to build a continuous integration and delivery capability without managing servers or build nodes, and how to leverage Infrastructure as Code to provision and manage your cloud resources in a consistent and repeatable manner.
DevOps is the combination of cultural, engineering practices and patterns, and tools that increase an organization's ability to deliver applications and services at high velocity and better quality. Over time, several essential practices have emerged when adopting DevOps: 
Continuous Integration 
Continuous Delivery
Infrastructure as Code
Monitoring and Logging
Communicat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelrahman Khaled</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Kustomize - How to customize Kubernetes objects]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/katiatalhi/introduction-to-kustomize-how-to-customize-kubernetes-objects-3e08</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/katiatalhi/introduction-to-kustomize-how-to-customize-kubernetes-objects-3e08"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Kustomize?


Kustomize is a tool used to customize Kubernetes objects in a template-free way. It provides several features that allow us to customize the application’s configuration.
We can use Kustomize in two ways: use the standalone version of Kustomize or use kubectl. Kustomize is a part of Kubectl since version 1.14.
Kustomize is easy to learn and use because the customization file is the same as the Kubernetes manifest. It is very handy when you work with Kubernetes. That makes the learning curve low.
One advantage of Kustomize is that it uses a kustomization.yaml file to customize Kubernetes manifests. That avoid us editing directly the manifests. So we can use the original manifests without needing Kustomize.
We will see above, the main features of Kustomize.
With Kustomize…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katia HIMEUR TALHI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I set up my Web Dev environment in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rightonhana/how-i-set-up-my-web-dev-environment-in-linux-4n2h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rightonhana/how-i-set-up-my-web-dev-environment-in-linux-4n2h"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I install a Linux distro on my PC I ended up forgetting some configurations, so I created this article as a cheatsheet for setting up my Web Dev environment in Ubuntu.
First of all install curl




sudo apt install curl

Install Zsh and Oh my Zsh. Also install Spaceship ZSH theme.




# Install Zsh
sudo apt install zsh
# Make it your default shell:
chsh -s $(which zsh)
# Install Oh my Zsh
sh -c "$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ohmyzsh/ohmyzsh/master/tools/install.sh)"
# Install Spaceship theme
git clone https://github.com/spaceship-prompt/spaceship-prompt.git "$ZSH_CUSTOM/themes/spaceship-prompt" --depth=1
# Symlink spaceship.zsh-theme to your oh-my-zsh custom themes directory
ln -s "$ZSH_CUSTOM/themes/spaceship-prompt/spaceship.zsh-theme" "$ZSH_CUSTOM/themes/spac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florencia Gonzalez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should You Be Using Webhooks?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hookdeck/should-you-be-using-webhooks-2gim</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hookdeck/should-you-be-using-webhooks-2gim"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will start by looking at how webhooks work. Then, I will compare the process with other data sharing techniques used by modern architectures in order to pair each technique with the scenarios where you should use them.
After the comparisons comes the answer to the question that might be heaviest on your mind: When should I be using webhooks?
Webhook communication is achieved by sending an HTTP request from a source application to a destination application. When an event takes place in the source application, an HTTP request which might contain data relating to the event is triggered. This HTTP request is sent to the destination application's endpoint. This is the endpoint, submitted by the destination application to the source application, where webhook requests are to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fikayo Adepoju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topological sort]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ricardo_borges/topological-sort-16gg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ricardo_borges/topological-sort-16gg"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topological sort is an ordering of the vertices of a directed acyclic graph, in a way that if there is an edge from a vertex A to B, then A comes before B. For example, let's say there is a set of projects and some of them depend on other projects:

In this example project B and C depends on project A, and project D depends on projects B and C. Therefore, project A must be executed first, then projects B and C, and finally project D. Resulting in this order: [A, B, C, D] or [A, C, B, D].
Note that we start from node A because it doesn't have dependencies and repeat it, that is after A is done, B and C haven't dependencies anymore, so we can choose either one to be the next. That's why this algorithm works only on acyclic graphs.
We can use a modified depth-first search for this algorithm, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Borges</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Milkdown: A plugin driven WYSIWYG markdown editor]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saulmirone/introducing-milkdown-a-plugin-driven-wysiwyg-markdown-editor-17n7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saulmirone/introducing-milkdown-a-plugin-driven-wysiwyg-markdown-editor-17n7"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview


Milkdown is a lightweight but powerful WYSIWYG markdown editor. It's made up by two parts:
  A tiny core which provide markdown parser, serializer and kinds of plugin loader.
  Lots of plugins provide syntax, commands and components.
With this pattern you can enable or disable any custom syntax you like, such as table, latex and slash commands.
online editor
documentation
github
  📝 WYSIWYG Markdown - Write markdown in an elegant way
  🎨 Themable - Theme can be shared and used with npm packages
  🎮 Hackable - Support your awesome idea by plugin
  🦾 Reliable - Built on top of prosemirror and remark

  ⚡️ Slash & Tooltip - Write fast for everyone, driven by plugin
  🧮 Math - LaTeX math equations support, driven by plugin
  📊 Table - Table support with fluent ui, driven by plugin
Milkdown is built on top of these tools:
  Prosemirror and it's community - A toolkit for building rich-text editors on the web
  Remark and it's community - Markdown parser done right
  Postcss - Powerful css tool to build theme
  TypeScript - Developed by typescript
  Prism - Code snippets support
  Katex - LaTex math rendering
We have some pieces for you to create a very minimal editor:
We use material icon and Roboto Font in our theme.
import { Editor } from '@milkdown/core';
import { commonmark } from '@milkdown/preset-commonmark';

// import theme
import '@milkdown/theme-nord/lib/theme.css';

const root = document.body;
new Editor({ root }).use(commonmark).create();

For further information, please visit our website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mirone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webhooks Debugging Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hookdeck/webhooks-debugging-tutorial-5c5p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hookdeck/webhooks-debugging-tutorial-5c5p"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article, we looked at the practice of debugging webhooks. We covered why it is important to debug our webhooks, why webhooks can be difficult to debug, how to know what to debug, and tools that can help make the debugging process easier. In this post, we will put the theory of debugging webhooks into practice by receiving webhooks locally from a Stripe account and debugging them using the Hookdeck CLI.
By the end of this exercise, you will be well equipped to debug webhooks in your development workflows.
In this tutorial, we will go through how to locally receive and debug Stripe webhooks. At the end of this guide, we will have a setup that receives Stripe webhooks locally and gives us visibility into the headers and payload of each webhook request.
The first step in this exe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fikayo Adepoju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elephant in the Blameless War Room: Accountability]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/blameless/elephant-in-the-blameless-war-room-accountability-40ef</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/blameless/elephant-in-the-blameless-war-room-accountability-40ef"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve always advocated that every company can benefit from a blameless culture. Fostering a blameless culture can profoundly boost your organization in powerful ways, from employee retention to developer velocity and innovation. However, there’s an elephant in the room when we talk about blamelessness with executives: accountability. When things go wrong, people still need to get fired, right? 
In a discussion with Ajay Varia, former VPE of MasterClass and COO of Emeritus, he shared an example of a real incident and how he held space for a blameless resolution without sacrificing accountability. An engineer was making changes to the administrative panel of what they thought was a testing environment. Regrettably, it turned out to actually be controlling the production environment. Their ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Arnott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimal webpack configuration to build typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/minimal-webpack-configuration-to-build-typescript-17kg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marcinwosinek/minimal-webpack-configuration-to-build-typescript-17kg"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's take a look on a minimal webpack configuration needed to build typescript.
index.html loads the js from the default webpack output location
<!DOCTYPE html>

<html>
  <head>
    <meta http-equiv="content-type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8" />
    <title>Webpack ts example</title>
    <link rel="shortcut icon" href="#" />
  </head>
  <body>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="dist/main.js"></script>
  </body>
</html>

The demo code is in src/index.ts - a file that is loaded for the default entry point. The code is simple:
const element = document.createElement("div");

element.innerHTML = "hello world!";

document.body.append(element);

For this to work, we need 2 configuration files. 
Webpack configuration goes to webpack.config.js:
module.exports = {
  resolve: {
    extensions: [".ts", ".js"],
  },
  module: {
    rules: [
      {
        test: /\.ts$/i,
        use: ["ts-loader"],
      },
    ],
  },
};

extensions: [".ts", ".js"] make webpack attempt to load ts when extension is missing, and makes it try TS before JS. Object added to module.rules[] sets ts-loader for all files that ends .ts.
The ts configuration is in tsconfig.json:
{
  "include": ["src/**/*"]
}

All dependencies that we need to install:
$ npm install --save-dev webpack ts-loader typescript

This could work would without installing typescript explicitly - but it's better idea to specify the dependency ourselves & keep it simple to pin the version if ever we will want to it.
In this article we have seen to what's the minimal webpack configuration to build ts files. If you want to play with the code, you can find the repo here:
 / 
        webpack-ts
      
    
The working example page:
https://marcin-wosinek.github.io/webpack-ts/
If you are interested in more webpack content:
Webpack links
Marcin Wosinek ・ Jul 3 ・ 1 min read
#webpack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcin Wosinek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to upgrade/install Ubuntu 20.04 LTS (Focal Fossa)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jinxankit/how-to-upgrade-install-ubuntu-20-04-lts-focal-fossa-3ji5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jinxankit/how-to-upgrade-install-ubuntu-20-04-lts-focal-fossa-3ji5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to upgrade/install Ubuntu 20.04 LTS (Focal Fossa)
So let's start:-
https://releases.ubuntu.com/20.04/
https://rufus.ie/ ) easy to use and faster too.
https://support.endlessm.com/hc/en-us/articles/210527103-How-do-I-start-boot-my-computer-from-a-USB-device-or-DVD-with-Endless-OS-
References:
Author:
ankit.2official@gmail.com. Follow me on Dev.to if you're interested in more in-depth and informative write-ups like these in the future!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Feature Toggle with Next.js and React in Under 30 Minutes]]></title>
        <id>60e59724134ad707be00e5d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-feature-toggles-in-next-js-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will show you how to build the Feature Toggle mechanism in your Next.JS application.  We are going to use Next.JS, React, and TypeScript. We will deploy our application to Vercel to demonstrate the real-life example. You can find the code and video in the summary at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top tips and tricks for performance improvement of ASP.NET Core application.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexisdevs/top-tips-and-tricks-for-performance-improvement-of-asp-net-core-application-20ob</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexisdevs/top-tips-and-tricks-for-performance-improvement-of-asp-net-core-application-20ob"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Performance is the key of any web application to get significant long-term success. When it comes to building high-performing applications, High performance .Net Core Applications are always on the top of the charts of the competition.
In this blog, I am going to talk about top .Net Core Tips and Tricks which can lead to optimizing the performance of your application dynamically.
ASP.NET core development technology is an open-source cross-platform technology that allows you to build top-notch web applications that can give your competitors a nudge on the edge.
However, for that, you would need to optimize this robust technology thoroughly by implementing the best practices.
And to take you to this precise goal I have curated this list of Top .Net Core Tips and tricks to facilitate your dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexis Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Secret News]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rmcomplexity/developer-secret-news-hac</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rmcomplexity/developer-secret-news-hac"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are secret news, keep them in the down low, and don’t share them with anyone.
We write unnecessary code.
What we think the code will do is wrong.
Not everything is testable.
Not everyone will understand the code you write.
Code is not always extendible nor manageable.
The Software you build for a company will never be for the greater good.
You are being exploited, and your job exists because others get exploited.
You will never know everything there is about Software.
Technology moves in the direction of money, not progress.
Software will never keep up with real life.
AI will neither save us nor destroy us.
Things change around you; you don’t change things directly.
You don’t need everything in your tech stack.
Your architecture is unnecessarily complicated.
Your documentation is not good.
Every computer system is compromised.

Don't look at these for too long!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josue Balandrano Coronel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D-graph client connection refused]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dwarfwiz/d-graph-client-connection-refused-1of6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dwarfwiz/d-graph-client-connection-refused-1of6"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[D-graph client written in g-r-p-c . When I build container for this d-graph service it throws connection refused?
Please help me if you have any solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WizDwarf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como subir um servidor simples?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpoxel/como-subir-um-servidor-simples-dnf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpoxel/como-subir-um-servidor-simples-dnf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Requisitos básicos:


• NodeJS
Para subir um servidor simples, sem babel e es6, precisamos apenas de uma pasta com um index.js dentro. 
Começamos acessando o nosso terminal(qualquer um que tenha como diretório a pasta que estamos modificando), damos um yarn init -y ou npm init -y para criarmos nosso package.json.
Quando estivermos com ele ja criado, vamos baixar o koa com yarn add koa --dev para dentro das nossas dependencias de desenvolvimento.
Feito isso, podemos pegar agora nosso arquivo index.js e digitar:




 const koa = require('koa');
 const app = koa();
 const port = 3000;

 app.listen(port, () => {
     console.log(`Servidor rodando na porta ${port}`)
});

Digitamos node index.js no nosso terminal. Se aparecer a mensagem que digitamos no console.log e nosso diretório sumir, é que estamos com o servidor local on-line. Caso você queira derrubar o servidor, basta segurar Ctrl + C, que o próprio terminal vai perguntar se você quer mesmo derrubar o server ou não.
Com isso, já podemos rodar o nosso servidor, porém é recomendável fazer uma configuração com um transpiler (babel-cli e o babel-presets-env) para rodarmos novas features do ES6 como import, export e etc...
Obrigado a todos que leram e espero ter ajudado alguém, qualquer coisa é só mandar um feedback!! Também estou aprendendo e gostaria muito de receber alguns :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Bezerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Communication in Node JS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mukilanbalu/communication-in-node-js-24o9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mukilanbalu/communication-in-node-js-24o9"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know that the application makes an API call to get data and display them. so let's see how things work. I will keep it crisp.
Firstly, your application makes an HTTP request call to the Node server.
Now, the Node server gets the request function and makes a call to a remote server for the requested service.
Without waiting for the response message from the remote server, the node immediately returns a response. which indicates the request was sent successfully.
When Node receives an HTTP response message from the remote server, it calls the call back function that has been defined in the HTTP request function call.
This callback function returns an HTTP response message to the calling application,
Ok, now let's see this in a real-time example.
Let's consider you are hungry and order some food, ill leave the choices to you.
First, you will open the APP  to select our choices and place the order. (This is the HTTP request that the application makes to Node JS) 
Now the restaurant receives the order placed and forwards the order to their kitchen.
The restaurant would send an order accepted message to you, without waiting for the food to be actually prepared. (This is the immediate response node, which indicates the status of the request).
Finally, when the food preparation is done, a delivery executive will be assigned for the order. (The delivery executive is the call back function that you defined in the HTTP request).
This executive reaches out and delivers you food. (This is the HTT response message )
I hope, you got an high-level understanding of node calls are processed.
Thank you for being patient with me for my first post, if any beginner errors. I will improve myself in upcoming posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mukilan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🦕 Running your first Deno script]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/velut/running-your-first-deno-script-3f7m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/velut/running-your-first-deno-script-3f7m"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we are going from zero to running a small but nontrivial script that fetches comments from Hacker News in real time using Deno, a new runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript created by Ryan Dahl, the original creator of Node.js.
Oversimplifying, we can say that Deno is an alternative to Node.js.
More precisely, we can read the following description on Deno's website:
Deno is a simple, modern and secure runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript that uses V8 and is built in Rust.
Let's delve deeper into three key characteristics that distinguish Deno from Node.js:
Simple: as we will soon see, Deno is simple to install, being shipped as a single executable file; Deno is also simple to use for small and larger scripts thanks to its powerful CLI, modern features and standard library; fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edoardo Scibona</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Accessible Vue Applications]]></title>
        <id>60e3ae66134ad707be00dbdb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-accessible-vue-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing web pages used to involve writing HTML, CSS, and a little scripting code like JavaScript for functionality.  But over time, we've developed new and more advanced technologies and frameworks to create webpages. We now use things like reusable components, routing, and rendering to the document object model (DOM).  These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn React JS in This Free 7-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>60df723627f80207bcdbcf36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-react-js-in-this-free-7-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Google trends, React is the most popular JavaScript frontend framework. Unless you're in the U.S. state of Nebraska, that is. 😀 Google Trends (React vs Angular)React is a declarative, efficient, and flexible JavaScript library for building user interfaces. We just released a full React course on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrape the latest stock prices with node.js and puppeteer!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/code_jedi/scrape-the-latest-stock-prices-with-node-js-and-puppeteer-4p2g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/code_jedi/scrape-the-latest-stock-prices-with-node-js-and-puppeteer-4p2g"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, fellow devs 👋


If you're looking into web-scraping with javascript, then I've got a great, simple project to start you off, because in this tutorial, I will be showing you guys how to scrape the latest Tesla stock prices using Node.js and puppeteer.
Let's get started!
First of all, you will need to install puppeteer using "npm i puppeteer". Now if you don't have npm and node_modules setup, here's a great tutorial on how to do so: https://www.sitepoint.com/npm-guide/.
After you've installed puppeteer, create a new javascript file and require puppeteer on the first line:
const puppeteer = require('puppeteer');

Then create the async function in which we are going to write our main code:
const puppeteer = require('puppeteer');

async function start() {

}
start();

First of all, you ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Code_Jedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 preguntas y respuestas frecuentes al momento de aprender Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/duxtech/10-preguntas-y-respuestas-frecuentes-al-momento-de-aprender-node-js-1ncl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/duxtech/10-preguntas-y-respuestas-frecuentes-al-momento-de-aprender-node-js-1ncl"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducción
¿Qué es Node.js exactamente?
¿Por qué usar Node.js?
¿Node.js es un lenguaje de programación?
¿Node.js es un framework?
¿Que necesito saber para poder aprender Node.js?
¿Node.js es asíncrono por defecto?
¿Cual es la diferencia entre Módulo/Dependencia/Paquete?
Cuando instalamos Node.js, ¿Cuál es la diferencia entre la versión LTS y la versión Current?
¿Qué es el Global Object u Objeto Global de Node?
¿Por que importamos/exportamos módulos con require/module.exports y no con import de ES6?
Referencias
Conclusiones
Introducción  


Con este breve post intentaré responder algunas de las preguntas más frecuentes que me hicieron y me hice cuando estaba aprendiendo las bases de Node.js.
1. ¿Qué es Node.js exactamente? 


Node.js es un ENTORNO EN TIEMPO DE EJECUCIÓN MULTIPLATAFORMA PA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343623</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-struggle-to-use-and-animate-a-conic-gradient-in-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful company I work for, Payoneer, has a new logo, and my job was to recreate it and animate it for a loader component in our app. I’ll explain exactly how I did it, share the problems I …
The post My Struggle to Use and Animate a Conic Gradient in SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Sheen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-a-command-line-tool-with-nodejs-and-fauna/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Command line tools are one of the most popular applications we have today. We use command line tools every day, and they range from git, npm or yarn. Command line tools are very fast and useful for automating applications and …
The post Building a Command Line Tool with Nodejs and Fauna appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fortune Ikechi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CloudFix now supports Financial Savings]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devgraph/cloudfix-now-supports-financial-savings-1d6o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devgraph/cloudfix-now-supports-financial-savings-1d6o"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Ravi Duddukuru
Since the launch of CloudFix cost optimization platform from DevGraph we have seen huge interest and adoption. Today, we are excited to announce that you can save even more with our new financial savings capabilities in addition to resource related savings that are already available.
Let’s start with understanding the different types of savings opportunities available with AWS. Broadly, there are two types of cloud cost savings opportunities.
First, you can save by optimizing how you use cloud resources.
Second, you can save by managing Financial / Billing aspects such as reserving instances.
CloudFix started with resource optimization and is now expanding to support financial optimization. Our objective is to maximize your cost savings by expanding the number of ways we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevGraph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Into DevSecOps (Part 2) w/ John Willis]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-2-w-john-willis-4ig3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linearb/diving-into-devsecops-part-2-w-john-willis-4ig3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second and final interview with John Willis on the Dev Interrupted podcast.
John Willis is a legendary DevOps speaker, mentor and author of The DevOps Handbook. In this special 2-part DevSecOps series, John takes us on a DevSecOps journey from the origin of the term all the way to how software developers at the team level can implement the practice.
Listen to the full episode







  
  
  Episode Highlights include:



What DevSecOps means at the team-level
First steps for implementing DevSecOps strategies at your organization
Why it’s critical to start thinking about security more holistically
The difference between Security, Compliance, Governance & Risk
What is coming next for software development security
Join the Dev Interrupted Discord Server


With over 1200 members, the Dev Interrupted Discord Community is the best place for Engineering Leaders to engage in daily conversation. No sales people allowed. Join the community >>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Bronsdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase Push Notifications]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/prakashthakur0021/firebase-push-notifications-5efj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/prakashthakur0021/firebase-push-notifications-5efj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T14:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How To Structure Firebase Push Notifications In Your Web App.
I want to use Push notification using firebase in my website using nodejs. If anyone have done that or can help somehow. 
Please feel free to provide resource and your thoughts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prakash Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implantar um aplicativo Angular no Azure pelo Github Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/silverio27/implantar-um-aplicativo-angular-no-azure-pelo-github-actions-3a4f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/silverio27/implantar-um-aplicativo-angular-no-azure-pelo-github-actions-3a4f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T13:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oi Pessoal!
Nesse post vou mostrar como implantar um aplicativo angular no azure pelo github-actions.
Windows Terminal
NodeJs
Angular - CLI
Azure - CLI
GitHub - CLI
e também uma assinatura no Azure
Você pode criar uma conta no azure e consumir os créditos para teste, mas nesse artigo os recursos que irei consumir são gratuítos.
O Coaltime, aplicação fictícia que apresentei no artigo anterior, recebeu permissão para ser continuado e agora precisamos de mais agilidade de implantação devido a contínuas mudanças no código. Outra coisa é que decidimos implantar o aplicativo em um serviço Linux.
Faça download do Coaltime (não clone)
 / 
        Coaltime
      
    
Utilize o windows terminal e navegue até a pasta Coaltime.
Esse projeto utiliza a versão Angular CLI: 12.0.1
Esse artigo prioriza a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Silvério</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🔐 The Working Principles of 2FA (2-Factor Authentication) Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/the-working-principles-of-2fa-2-factor-authentication-software-57c8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/the-working-principles-of-2fa-2-factor-authentication-software-57c8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T13:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[📜 With modern computers capable of testing millions of password combinations per second, securing your online accounts with only a password may not be sufficient anymore.



  
  
  
For the past 30 years or so, we’ve settled on using a password-username pair as a happy compromise between usability and security. You have some knowledge that no one else has, so it must be you who’s trying to log in.
Passwords, however, aren’t foolproof. People pick bad ones and even the good ones are at risk of being exploited (for example, by keyloggers). That’s why a second factor can be useful. On top of something you know, y_ou must also provide something you _have to be authenticated.
A server can use any of these three options to prove that you own the trusted device:
Your phone number (via SMS)
A so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Change Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kuncevic/angular-change-detection-2f34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kuncevic/angular-change-detection-2f34"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💫 The "magic glue" that connects the view and the model, keeping them both in sync.
Angular Change Detection is one of the most complex topics in software engineering and obviously in Angular as it is relying on that a lot. It can definitely be compared to the "magic glue" that connects the view and the model, keeping them both in sync".
On a broader scale, it is a mechanism built into Angular that allows Angular to decide what actions can be performed when the state of the app changes. The good news is that most of the time, developers do not have to deal with change detection manually.
However, if you find yourself caught in a loop, the only way to simplify your journey is to follow specific strategies, for example OnPush and trigger change detection manually if you need to. 
There are four ways you can trigger change detection manually. Let’s look at them in detail:
tick() on ApplicationRef **that activates change detection for the entire application by staying consistent and respectful to the strategy component of the change detection.
detectChanges() on ChangeDetectorRef  runs change detection on a current component.
markForCheck() on ChangeDetectorRef controls change detection through the marked components where the OnPush strategy has been set.
run() on NgZone that allows you to execute a function inside the Angular zone. This function, and all asynchronous operations in that function, trigger change detection automatically at the correct time.
Here is a very handy tip, which can simplify your life. 

If you want to learn more listen to Angular Change Detection Episode at angularrocks.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aliaksei Kuncevič</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools And Practices To Speed Up The Vue.js Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/tools-practices-speed-up-vuejs-development-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though Vue.js claims to have an approachable minimalist framework that can be incrementally adaptable, it can be a little bit overwhelming when starting as a Vue.js newbie. In this article, we’re looking at ways to make writing Vue.js a breeze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Uma Victor)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypting ActiveRecords with Lockbox in Rails 6.1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kudapara/encrypting-activerecords-with-lockbox-in-rails-6-1-45d2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kudapara/encrypting-activerecords-with-lockbox-in-rails-6-1-45d2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T10:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I dive in, I will give you a bit of context.
I am currently working on an application that uses the Stellar blockchain behind the scenes to open up access to capital to farmers in developing countries like Zimbabwe.
The purpose of the blockchain is to provide transparency from the moment the investor parts with their hard-earned money, to the time the farmer starts sharing profits with investors. By nature, blockchain is very complex and the average farmer can not be bothered to worry about setting up wallets, ensuring their keys are safely secured, and all the jargon that is associated with blockchain technologies.
It is essential that we hide the complexity from the end-users, and make their experiences as seamless as possible. Sort of how when we browse websites, we do not even t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kudakwashe Paradzayi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Computing: Security And Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/febnavm/serverless-computing-security-and-challenges-h6c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/febnavm/serverless-computing-security-and-challenges-h6c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T09:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless computing has been on the rise for the past few years. Serverless computing is a new economic model to cloud computing that has proven popular and has emerged to be a boon to many companies.
Types Of Serverless Infrastructures
Serverless architectures are cloud-based and service-based. This means that, instead of provisioning and managing their own servers, organizations buy cloud computing services such as the following:
Software as a Service, or SaaS, delivers centrally hosted and managed software on-demand to end-users over the internet (e.g, Slack, Jira, Salesforce, HubSpot, etc).


Infrastructure as a Service, or IaaS, delivers resources such as networks, data storage, and computers which must be managed by the end-users and offers essential compute, storage and networking …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Febna V M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it the end of var? Here’s a better solution known for years.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/wilkuintheair/is-it-the-end-of-var-here-s-a-better-solution-known-for-years-2lkf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/wilkuintheair/is-it-the-end-of-var-here-s-a-better-solution-known-for-years-2lkf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T09:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Var is a great thing. It served people well all across the world for years. But its time has passed. No one likes it anymore and now we all know it can even cause serious problems. Luckily there’s a better solution and it’s been a while since it was released (June 2015!). Why then do people still use var?
Ok, this is not about football, as some of you probably may think. Of course it’s about JavaScript. I’m a React Native developer, right? It has to be about JS.
Let me take you to the point.
Yep, a replacement for var is obviously let and const. How is it different from this var everyone hates now? 
Scope of var is the whole body of the function it’s declared in. Not a tragedy. But when it’s declared outside of a function, the scope is global. Now this is bad news. It can lead you to some unexpected or even unpredictable stuff in your code.
Scope of let and const on the other hand is only a block. A block, means i.e. a function, but also if/else statement, for/while loops, switch/case statements and whatnot. Basically, it’s between the brackets {}. So this is much more reliable and much safer to use because it stays exactly where you declared it. It won’t go outside.
What’s more, const will make you sure the value of what you declared will not be changed in the future. How great is that?
To be honest, I don’t even remember the last time I have used var instead of let or const. I’m not sure of statistics, but it’s also less and less seen in existing legacy projects I work on. Of course var has its use cases, but there aren’t many of them and still, we can do better than that.
Ok, I won’t say more here. There have been a ton of blog posts written since let and const were first introduced, this one is more like a social experiment. I hope you already forgave me the clickbaitish title!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piotr Wilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Dockerize series]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/introduction-to-dockerize-series-28l1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karanpratapsingh/introduction-to-dockerize-series-28l1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T08:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hey, welcome to the Dockerize series. Here, I will be discussing how to use docker with your applications during both development and production.
We'll also use techniques like Builder pattern, multi stage builds to optimize our production builds.
This will serve as in introduction to upcoming articles where we'll dockerize our React, Node, Go applications!

Docker is a software platform for building applications based on containers, which are small and lightweight execution environments.
It also helps to eliminate environment specific issues since you can replicate your production environment locally, which provides consistency across our teams.

Compose is a tool for defining and running multi-container Docker applications. With Compose, you use a YAML file to configure yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karan Pratap Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS EBS root volume expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/awscommunity-asean/aws-ebs-root-volume-expansion-15jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/awscommunity-asean/aws-ebs-root-volume-expansion-15jm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T08:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[** 

EC2 > Volumes > Actions > Select Volume  > Modify Volume                                                                                                
It can be changed while EC2 Instance is running.






・Restriction                                                                                                  
Once changed, it cannot be changed for 6 hours.                                                                                             

Command
    df -h                                                                                               
    lsblk                                                                                               
    sudo growpart /dev/xvda 1                                                                                               
    lsblk                                                                                               
    sudo xfs_growfs /dev/xvda1                      For Linux 1 AMI: resize2fs /dev/xvda1                                                                       
    df -h                                                                                               

・EC2 Instance (Command)


Ref https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/recognize-expanded-volume-linux.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ha Anh Tai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undash-Javascript utility Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abhilashsreenivasa/undash-javascript-utility-library-11mb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abhilashsreenivasa/undash-javascript-utility-library-11mb"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T07:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have created a JS library that is similar to that of underscoreJS and Lodash with extra functionalities. Feel free to use/test/contribute to my project. I could use some help with a contributor.
https://github.com/abhilashSreenivasa/undash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhilash Sreenivasa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Abstractions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/udayanmaurya/frontend-abstractions-4pca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/udayanmaurya/frontend-abstractions-4pca"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T07:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract thinking facilities us in solving many problems and solving them efficiently. Ability to say A is like B, helps us cheaply export solutions developed in A to solve B. This further refines the abstract pattern and makes it more robust and reusable (evolution!).
To solve problems in astronomy ancient Greeks developed abstract patterns to study geometry of triangles, Trigonometry. Now trigonometry helps us in solving problems ranging from construction of buildings to measuring current in electrical circuits.
Abstraction in Programming:
One of the primary objectives of programming is to come up with a code to mimic a real world process as precisely as possible. More precision results in bug free code which preforms adequately in most of the circumstances encountered in the process.
Ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udayan Maurya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to Deno]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naruhodo/an-introduction-to-deno-5e88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naruhodo/an-introduction-to-deno-5e88"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T07:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deno is a JavaScript and TypeScript runtime build in Rust. It was created by Ryan Dahl, who is also the original creator of Node.js.
Eventually Deno might take over Node.js but at the moment, it's not there yet. Node.js is too popular and is already used in many projects. It has a much bigger community and much more modules/packages available.
Deno does not provide a strong enough incentive for companies to decide to make the switch. At least not yet.
Performance-wise it is comparable to Node.js, another reason not to switch.
So why am I writing an article about it? And what does Deno have that Node.js doesn't?
Well, I believe that if Ryan Dahl decided to build a new JS runtime, he must have had a good reason. He actually gave a talk about this.
In his talk he mentions multiple things he r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NARUHODO</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Files Are Gone After Updating Windows 10… How to Recover Them?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/files-are-gone-after-updating-windows-10-how-to-recover-them-1cn1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hetmansoftware/files-are-gone-after-updating-windows-10-how-to-recover-them-1cn1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T06:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read this article to learn how to recover missing files after updating Windows 10. All possible ways to restore missing documents, photos, music and videos after updating your operating system to the latest version.

The process of adding the latest update and switching from any of the previous versions (for example, Windows 8.1 or Windows 7) to the latest Windows 10 is supposed to be easy, with all your files saved seamlessly just where they belong. However, sometimes the new operating system may behave unpredictably, and your documents, photos, music or videos may disappear after installing the last update.
But even if it happened, there are still grounds for hope, because we have numerous methods to find and restore the missing files.
In this tutorial for Windows 10 we will explore seve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mirosnichenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Tor Browser in Kali Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/suhailkakar/how-to-install-tor-browser-in-kali-linux-53ie</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/suhailkakar/how-to-install-tor-browser-in-kali-linux-53ie"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T06:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux is a security distribution of Linux derived from Debian and specifically designed for computer forensics and advanced penetration testing. 
It was developed through rewriting of BackTrack by Mati Aharoni and Devon Kearns of Offensive Security. 
The Tor Browser is a web browser that anonymizes your web traffic using the Tor network, making it easy to protect your identity online. 
Here is my YouTube video that will guide you on how to install Tor in your Kali Linux]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suhail Kakar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret to configuring the best Postgres-Nest project- Part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bhargavmantha/secret-to-configuring-the-best-postgres-nest-project-part-1-42n4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bhargavmantha/secret-to-configuring-the-best-postgres-nest-project-part-1-42n4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T06:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notations
My Computer setup
Prerequisites
Installation
Project setup
Explanation
My Computer setup
OS: Linux x64 Arch 
Kernal- 1.10.42-1 
Distrubution- Manajro KDE
Code editor: VS CODE-Insiders
Ram - 16 GB
AMD ryzen 7 pro 
Prerequisites 
 This tutorial assumes that you have a basic knowledge of Node js, Postgres, and Docker
Node and npm installed
Docker Installed
Installation
PART-1 ( Docker )
docker run --rm --name pg-docker -e POSTGRES_PASSWORD=poc-estm -d -p 5432:5432 -v $HOME/docker/volumes/postgres:/var/lib/postgresql/data postgres

--rm is used to remove the constaine if it exists
--name is used to specify the name of the container
-e environment variables
-d in detached mode
-p port number to run on
-v volume to store the data internal to the container on
postgres the image to pull
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BhargavMantha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing ScoutX Mobile: An emergency notification app for Diabetics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/superdiana/announcing-scoutx-mobile-an-emergency-notification-app-for-diabetics-3cfe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/superdiana/announcing-scoutx-mobile-an-emergency-notification-app-for-diabetics-3cfe"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T04:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a milestone for me. It's huge. Today I won't write from the technical perspective. Today I am writing as a type 1 diabetic feeling proud of a tool that can save lives as it has saved mine.
Over a year ago i released the ScoutX project. It is comprised of:
A Flask application where users can input their Nightscout entries endpoint. This app is constantly listening for values and when these are above or below range it fires and alert and calls the diabetic patient first, to alert them of irregular values. Should the patient not answer the call, an alert is sent to their trusted contacts to notify of irregular values.


A WisBlock + Helium (IoT + LoRaWan) tracker to send data to nightscout and provide GPS precise location, so emergency contacts can receive notifications with location …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Super Diana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrolling to an Element Only After It Appears using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ferfox1981/scrolling-to-an-element-only-after-it-appears-using-angular-1g6m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ferfox1981/scrolling-to-an-element-only-after-it-appears-using-angular-1g6m"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T00:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an evolution of my previous article. Let's suppose you have the following requirement:
In a long page, wait for a specific HTML Element to appear, and only after its generation scroll to it.
It looks simple right? But imagine that this Element exibition could take some time, for instance, it could be a grid with some information provided from a web service, or some data from a slow SQL query. Nevertheless, there's no reason to scroll before the data is already shown. So how can we do it? My goals are:
Create a button that will generate a grid at the bottom of a long page;
After the button is clicked, some mechanism is needed to simulate random time;
Scroll to the grid only after it was added to the page.
comment: The table to be scrolled is not added to the page by default. This is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Raposo da Camara Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a JavaScript Object? Key Value Pairs and Dot Notation Explained]]></title>
        <id>60e521aa134ad707be00e41d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-javascript-object/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T22:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objects are one of the most valuable things you can learn in JavaScript. You can use them to take your programs to the next level.  An object is a collection of data – or key value pairs – which consist of variables and functions that you can access using dot notation. Now]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi I'm Waylon


I am currently a Masters's candidate studying computer science at Colorado State University. After I completed my bachelor's degree in Mathematics and Philosophy, I was employed as a cybersecurity intern by the academic computing and networking services at CSU. I quickly developed a deep passion for cybersecurity and computer science and decide to go back to school to learn more.
While studying for my master's, I have been employed as a Junior Systems Administrator for the Computer Science department, managing over 600 Unix machines. This summer I am also working for Hedera Hashgraph as a developer advocate intern providing educational content on how to leverage the Hashgraph distributed network.
I love python, Linux, rust, and cryptography. If you share any of these interests, don't hesitate to reach out. I look forward to sharing my technical experiences with all of you hear and learn from the community. Thanks for reading :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Jepsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/0xjepsen/intro-45e5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi I'm Waylon


I am currently a Masters's candidate studying computer science at Colorado State University. After I completed my bachelor's degree in Mathematics and Philosophy, I was employed as a cybersecurity intern by the academic computing and networking services at CSU. I quickly developed a deep passion for cybersecurity and computer science and decide to go back to school to learn more.
While studying for my master's, I have been employed as a Junior Systems Administrator for the Computer Science department, managing over 600 Unix machines. This summer I am also working for Hedera Hashgraph as a developer advocate intern providing educational content on how to leverage the Hashgraph distributed network.
I love python, Linux, rust, and cryptography. If you share any of these interests, don't hesitate to reach out. I look forward to sharing my technical experiences with all of you hear and learn from the community. Thanks for reading :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Waylon Jepsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install multiple node versions on the same machine]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-install-multiple-node-versions-on-the-same-machine-ofc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/corpcubite/how-to-install-multiple-node-versions-on-the-same-machine-ofc"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our headless CMS, Strapi requires node version <= 14.x.x and we had node version 15 installed in our development machine. So that brought a question to my mind, is there a way like python venv for node to install different versions in the same machine. After doing a quick investigation, I found nvm node version manager that lets you have different versions of node on the same machine and switching between them.
curl -o- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nvm-sh/nvm/v0.38.0/install.sh | bash


or
wget -qO- https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nvm-sh/nvm/v0.38.0/install.sh | bash


To verify installation run nvm --version
To list available versions, you can run
nvm ls-remote

To install specific version you can use nvm install VERSION for example
nvm install 12.18.4

You can use nvm use to switch to a specific version. For example
nvm use 12.18.4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cubite Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Project Fonos with Cloud-Init]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/psanders/deploying-project-fonos-with-cloud-init-4a6f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/psanders/deploying-project-fonos-with-cloud-init-4a6f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Fonoster, Inc, we want to help companies and individuals that wish to adopt Project Fonos(PF) as their Programmable Telecommunications solution. To help archive this goal, our team uses Cloud-Init for cloud instance initialization.
You can deploy PF to all major public cloud providers, private cloud infrastructure, and bare-metal installations with Cloud-Init.
In this tutorial, we will also use Multipass. 
Multipass is a Canonical project that offers a lightweight VM manager for Linux, Windows, and macOS. With Multipass, you can deploy Project Fonos on Ubuntu in a local environment in a single command. This deployment method is by far the fastest way to get started with PF.
Before you start this tutorial, you will need the following:
Multipass
NodeJS 14+ (Use nvm if possible)
Fonos comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at Building with Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343495</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-look-at-building-with-astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T21:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astro is a brand new framework for building websites. To me, the big thing is that it allows you to build a site like you’re using a JavaScript framework (and you are), but the output is a zero-JavaScript static site. …
The post A Look at Building with Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need help with your npm audit?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/naugtur/do-you-need-help-with-your-npm-audit-3olf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/naugtur/do-you-need-help-with-your-npm-audit-3olf"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok, I'm gonna try and surf the wave of publicity resulting from Dan Abramov's recent post and its discussions. 
Let me address the elephant in the room too. Or talk about how I'm working to address it.
I've encountered the npm audit fatigue just days after the audit feature was released. It was on a Node.js project. (ok, 20+ of them at once) 
It resulted with the first version of npm-audit-resolver
If you want to know how npm-audit-resolver came to life, I've told the story in this recording:
OpenJS World 2021 pkg vuln talk
apologies for the quality of my webcam
The video introduces Package Vulnerability Management & Reporting Collaboration Space.

Actually, I recommend you stop reading and watch a bit of it now. 
What I want to talk about here is the ideas for the future of npm-audit-reso…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>naugtur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross site scripting(XSS) in 10 mins]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/avishkardalvi/cross-site-scripting-xss-in-10-mins-455d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/avishkardalvi/cross-site-scripting-xss-in-10-mins-455d"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T20:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if we have control over the JavaScript of another website? Let your imagination run wild on this one! What could be the possibilities in this case?
We know that JavaScript has access to the HTML documents via the DOM API's which are provided by the browser itself. This means we can manipulate the DOM and make it look different, like changing the styling or the HTML structure of the page or we can read some cookies using document.cookie and send it over to your website via Ajax request or form submission or some other way.
But I think you get the idea that I am trying to convey here, having access to JavaScript on another website in a different user's context can be very problematic.
Now the question is can we really inject some JavaScript into another web page? Well, the answer is yes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AvishkarDalvi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn Machine Learning – Tips and Resources to Learn ML the Practical Way]]></title>
        <id>60ccd1794dc1a607ed7b4feb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-machine-learning-practical-tips-and-resources/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people want to learn machine learning these days. But the daunting bottom-up curriculum that most ML teachers propose is enough discourage a lot of newcomers.  In this tutorial I flip the curriculum upside down and will outline what I think is the fastest and easiest way to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Comprehension in Python Explained for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>60e25e17134ad707be00d947</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-comprehension-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T17:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List comprehension is an easy to read, compact, and elegant way of creating a list from any existing iterable object. Basically, it's a simpler way to create a new list from the values in a list you already have. It is generally a single line of code enclosed in square]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Interview Prep Cheatsheet – Ace Your Coding Interviews with These Concepts]]></title>
        <id>60c38e76d3126007592d66cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-interview-prep-cheatsheet/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've carefully gone through over 50 resources, I've been through 10 JavaScript interviews, and I've landed a job at a unicorn startup. And throughout this entire process, I started to see a pattern in the most frequently asked JS interview questions.  In this article, I have tried to list the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will we lose if we use regular link instead of React routing in SPA]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/arahman1783/what-will-we-lose-if-we-use-regular-link-instead-of-react-routing-in-spa-2e4h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/arahman1783/what-will-we-lose-if-we-use-regular-link-instead-of-react-routing-in-spa-2e4h"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According some requirements from client to replace routing with real links, as we work Single Page Application there are some features we will lose :
Routing in react is like show and hide some components without reload page so the only part that loaded is the new part only using (virtual Dom), so the transforming between components smooth and easy.
In single page application one of the main concepts is to share data with all components that will use it, so we load it one time and use it many times.
Every time we access any page the application will call again all services that need to call to manage this page although it is called before among of this connecting with Keycloak to get new token even the first not expired 
• https://reacttraining.com/blog/reach-react-router-future/
https://www.pluralsight.com/guides/understanding-links-in-reactjs
https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-the-href-and-routerLink
https://reactjs.org/docs/faq-internals.html
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/23975199/when-to-use-client-side-routing-or-server-side-routing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelrahman Elhussini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typing React Props in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/typescripttv/typing-react-props-in-typescript-5hal</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/typescripttv/typing-react-props-in-typescript-5hal"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One advantage of using React with TypeScript is that you can easily type the props of your (function) components. You don't have to use React's PropTypes because TypeScript already has its own typing system.
In the following, I will show you how to define custom props for a component in connection with already existing props like children.
PostPreview.tsx
import React from 'react';

export interface Props {
  heading: string;
}

const PostPreview = (props: Props) => {
  return (
    <div>
      <h1>{props.heading}</h1>
      {props.children}
    </div>
  );
};

export default PostPreview;

As you can see, our PostPreview component has a heading property. The component is supposed to render the heading and other components (children) below the heading. In technical terms this is called Cont…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benny Neugebauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web’s Worst Default]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343388</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-webs-worst-default/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of great defaults when it comes to browsers and the web. Think about all the accessibility features that are baked into HTML so that you don’t have to do weird stuff, like this example from Manuel…
The post The Web’s Worst Default appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Rendle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State manager of dream]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/betula/state-manager-of-dream-98i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/betula/state-manager-of-dream-98i"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago during one of my interviews, a potential employer asked me to describe a perfect frontend framework in my wildest dreams. I gave quite a thorough answer explaining how it works, and realized that it actually was a description vaguely resembling the synthesis of React and Angular. My dream was born at that moment!
Currently, when it comes to all existing frontend frameworks, those widely popular or not, I prefer React since it has a beautiful integration with the typescript. Using JSX as part of a language is really convenient. It offers a lightweight version with perfect compatibility (4 kB Preact instead of 30), with the possibility to inject it on the Webpack level without changes to your codebase. And React is simply a view system without any special solution builder, appl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Slava Birch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Binary Search?]]></title>
        <id>60d5ec446e1a1407b6b0bcae</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-binary-search/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T13:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binary search is a common algorithm used in programming languages and programs. It can be very useful for programmers to understand how it works. We just released a binary search course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. You will learn how to implement binary search in C and C++, but]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting the most value out of your Angular Component Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/getting-the-most-value-out-of-your-angular-component-tests-1ob5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow me on Twitter at @tim_deschryver | Subscribe to the Newsletter | Originally published on timdeschryver.dev.
I frequently hear that it's hard to know what to test of an Angular component.
In this blog post, I want to share how I think that we can get the most value out of a test.
To accomplish this, I want to closely mimic a user that uses my application.
To help me writing these tests, I'm using the Angular Testing Library. When you're using the Angular Testing Library, you only need the render method and the screen object to test the basics of your component. For interactions with the component, I'm also using userEvent from @testing-library/user-event.
Let's take a look at the first test for a simple component called EntitiesComponent.
import { render, screen } from '@testing-libr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Deschryver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run Frontend of BitClout without running node]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/itsaditya/run-frontend-of-bitclout-without-running-node-1n4f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/itsaditya/run-frontend-of-bitclout-without-running-node-1n4f"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might want to make some changes to the frontend of BitClout but running a node is beyond your league ? Well, you are on the right place of the Internet then!
You can easily run the frontend of BitClout locally on your PC without running node by using some browser hacks :)
docs of BitClout, you will have to run your own node (aka backend) and identity service in order to run the frontend. 
Before you get started make sure you are using the latest version of NodeJS and NPM on your PC. Another prerequisite is to have git installed. The frontend of BitClout is made in AngularJS so you must have atleast some basic knowledge of what single page application is.
Fork and Clone the frontend repository.
Fork the repository of the frontend from here. When done open your terminal and run git clone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Chaudhary👨‍💻</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Figma Interactive Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/introduction-figma-interactive-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Components in Figma allows designers to create a component with states (hover, active, clicked, focus) and make it interactive so that every copy of the component will inherit those same interactions by default. Let’s explore how it can reduce the time and effort needed to create interactions for your mock-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emiliano Cicero)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigitalOcean deploy conference - June 2021 - All product sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rasharm_/digitalocean-deploy-conference-sessions-june-2021-46cj"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T07:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of my favorite sessions from the recently concluded deploy conference by DigitalOcean:








  
  
  Accelerating Modern App Development Using Managed MongoDB and DigitalOcean










  
  
  Is Kubernetes Right for Me? Choosing the Best Deployment Platform for Your Business










  
  
  Be the Boss of Your Base: Tips to Master MongoDB Like a Pro










  
  
  Finding the Right DigitalOcean Virtual Machine Type for Your Business










  
  
  Grow Your Business with Scalable Apps Using DigitalOcean App Platform










  
  
  Building Production-Ready Apps With App Platform, DigitalOcean's Reimagined PaaS










  
  
  Networking Best Practices To Power Your Kubernetes Deployment










  
  
  Kubernetes Starter Kit for Developers: Becoming Productive From Day 1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raman Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Object Deep Clone vs Shallow Clone. Clone JavaScript Object the right way.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/koolkishan/javascript-object-deep-copy-vs-shallow-copy-copy-javascript-object-the-right-way-1d88"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T02:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch This Video To Completely Understand About What is Deep Cloning and Shallow Cloning of Object in JavaScript]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kishan Sheth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automatically Upload an Android App Bundle to the Play Store]]></title>
        <id>60e16e1b134ad707be00d6bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automatically-upload-an-android-app-bundle-to-the-play-store/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T21:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to explain how to automatically upload an Android App Bundle (.aab file) to the Play Store's beta track. We'll use Android Studio and AWS as a cloud infrastructure provider.  Once we've uploaded the app bundle, we'll trigger a Slack notification.  This is a valuable use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Body Toggle]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343438</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/body-toggle/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I appreciate the clarity of this trick that Mikael Ainalem posted over on Reddit:
It’s a one-liner that toggles the class on the <body> so you can mock up different states and toggle between them on click.
<body onclick="this.classList.toggle("active");"
Could …
The post Body Toggle appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343560</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ive-got-one-question-about-jetpack-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And maybe an optional follow-up if you’re up for it.
Automattic, the makers of Jetpack and many other WordPress-y things, have sponsored my site (me = Chris Coyier; site = CSS-Tricks) for quite a while. I use Jetpack myself, …
The post I’ve got one question about Jetpack for you. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minha instalação do Manjaro para programação]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abraaom/minha-instalacao-do-manjaro-para-programacao-1o4k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abraaom/minha-instalacao-do-manjaro-para-programacao-1o4k"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O Manjaro é uma distro Linux baseada no Arch, mas que trás uma instalação muito mais facilitada do que seu irmão maior, a instalação foi feita no Manjaro Gnome, mas os comandos via terminal são todos iguais em qualquer uma das várias interfaces disponíveis para o Manjaro.
A escolha pelo Manjaro ao invés de uma distro mais popular se dá para mim principalmente pela presença do gerenciador de pacotes do Arch, o Pacman, e a possibilidade de acessar o enorme repositório do Arch, considerando o AUR e também a possibilidade de adicionar facilmente o suporte a Flatpack e Snap diretamente no gerenciador de pacotes Pamac, que possui uma GUI, basicamente se existe algo para Linux, então estará disponível para o Manjaro de forma facilitada por meio de algum dos repositórios citados, oficiais ou não. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abraão Moreira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing Tabular Data in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/editing-tabular-data-in-angular-41a4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T18:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | May 2019
A fun dive into everything from custom Directives to advanced ViewChildren




  
  
  Introduction


This article targets beginning to intermediate-level Angular developers and covers a wide variety of topics that arise in production applications. While centered around the concept of editing tabular data, these techniques may be used in a variety of other Angular applications.
For anyone who has read at least one of my articles, you should understand that my background is applied mathematics and scientific computing. So, this article continues the trend of exploring the use of Angular in scientific and business (analytics) applications.
Working with time-series data is a fundamental concept in numerous business and engineering sectors. In this context, f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Authenticate Users and Implement CORS in Node.js Apps]]></title>
        <id>60b22e9611ffb70827ef9547</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-authenticate-users-and-implement-cors-in-nodejs-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to authenticate users and secure endpoints in Node.js. You'll also see how to implement Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) in Node. So let's get started.  Prerequisites You'll need the following to follow along with this tutorial:  A working understanding of JavaScript. A good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can we build Micro VMs with Dockerfile? : Answer is Yes !!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/can-we-build-micro-vms-with-dockerfile-answer-is-yes-14d3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/manishfoodtechs/can-we-build-micro-vms-with-dockerfile-answer-is-yes-14d3"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Answer is : ####Slim
This results in a real VM that can boot instantly, while using very limited resources. If done properly, slim can allow you to design and build immutable unikernels for running services, or build tiny and embedded development environments.
Slim currently supports Virtualbox, KVM, and hyperkit (MacOS only) as providers for running VMs. Slim will discover all available providers, defaulting to virtualbox, if more than one provider is available. The -p flag can be used to force Slim to use a specific provider.
You can find repo here
 / 
        slim
      
    
 

slim will build a micro-vm from a Dockerfile. Slim works by building and extracting a rootfs from a Dockerfile, and then merging that filesystem with a small minimal kernel that runs in RAM.
This results in a real VM that can boot instantly, while using very limited resources. If done properly, slim can allow you to design and build immutable unikernels for running services, or build tiny and embedded development environments.
Create a micro-vm from a Dockerfile. Use build command with a directory containing a Dockerfile.
$ slim build images/alpine3.8-simple



This will add a bootable iso in the slim registry. See example Dockerfile.
slim build will use your default provider unless the -p flag is specified (ie -p hyperkit).
See a list of micro-vm images on your machine.
$ slim images



Provision a new instance…
View on GitHub
Click here for joining my team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>manish srivastava</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-dilemma-of-naming-font-size-variables/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, a project will have a set of pre-determined font sizes, usually as variables named in such a way that seeks some semblance of order and consistency. Any project of considerable size can use something like that. There are always …
The post The Dilemma of Naming Font Size Variables appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Lexelius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an Angular & Amazon IVS player app in less than 15 minutes!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amazonivs/build-an-angular-amazon-ivs-player-app-in-less-than-15-minutes-2668</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amazonivs/build-an-angular-amazon-ivs-player-app-in-less-than-15-minutes-2668"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T13:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro ⭐️


Video & Streaming don't have to be complicated for the web anymore! in this tutorial we will build an Angular app using Amazon IVS & Video.js in less than 15 minutes!!
Amazon IVS (Amazon Interactive Video Service) is a fully managed live streaming solution: simply stream to Amazon IVS, and the service does everything you need to make low-latency live video available to any viewer around the globe. Amazon IVS handles the ingestion, transcoding, packaging, and delivery of your live content, using the same battle-tested technology that powers Twitch.
For more information on Amazon IVS check https://ivs.rocks
Check the twitch stream of this tutorial: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xCsh88xNkKE
I have a personal quest of making infrastructure and development approachable, accessible …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Super Diana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular change detection -OnPush]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-change-detection-onpush-18g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/angular-change-detection-onpush-18g"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T11:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post about change detection, we touched on the basics of it. In this article, we will try to understand more about ChangeDetectionStrategy.OnPush method. So let us get started.
So first thing we will discuss is how to convert the component to the Onpush strategy. Let say we have a Sample component and we are having a default change detection strategy(by default all newly created components are having default change detection), it will be like:
import { ChangeDetectionStrategy, Component, OnInit } from '@angular/core';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-sample',
  templateUrl: './sample.component.html',
  styleUrls: ['./sample.component.scss']
})
export class SampleComponent implements OnInit {

  constructor() { }

  ngOnInit(): void {
  }

}

Now let's add the change detection as O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Dhawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose A Headless CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/how-to-choose-a-headless-cms/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an array of Headless CMSes out there. In this article, we delve into headless CMS features to satisfy your content editors, marketers and yourself as a developer. For the experience headless practitioner, this could be a checklist to see what’s new out there. For those starting out on their headless journey, this could be a guide on what to look for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emmanuel Tissera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop!_OS 21.04 on Zephyrus G14 (Ryzen 5)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vinod/pop-os-21-04-on-zephyrus-g14-amd-ryzen-5-5h5e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vinod/pop-os-21-04-on-zephyrus-g14-amd-ryzen-5-5h5e"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T07:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy to report that - the latest Pop!_OS 21.04 is working without any glitches on G14.

Audio, Video, and Mic are working without glitches
Google Chrome and Firefox browsers work with hardware/GPU video decode support
Screenshare, Video conferencing Apps are working without glitches especially using Chrome
Battery Life is as good as Windows if not a bit more
Graphics mode switching between AMD & NVIDIA is seamless
Gnome 4 is performing without bugs and exceptions - unlike Fedora 34
Trackpad gestures animations aren't smooth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinod Ponmanadiyil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASP.NET CORE 5.0 TLS 1.2 issue on linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/moliveto/asp-net-core-5-0-tls-1-2-issue-on-linux-1ii5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/moliveto/asp-net-core-5-0-tls-1-2-issue-on-linux-1ii5"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T23:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jul  5 '21
            Comments: 1
            Answers: 0
        
I have a problem with TLS 1.2 in asp.net core 5.0 and linux
System.Net.Http.HttpRequestException: The SSL connection could not be established, see inner exception
       ---> System.IO.IOException:  Received an unexpected EOF or 0 bytes from the transport stream.
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.<FillHandshakeBufferAsync>g__InternalFillHandshakeBufferAsync|182_0[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adap, ValueTask`1 task, Int32 minSize)
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.ReceiveBlobAsync[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adapter)
         at System.Net.Security.SslStream.ForceAuthenticationAsync[TIOAdapter](TIOAdapter adapter,
…
    
  
Open Full Question]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcelo Adrian Oliveto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/kubernetes-explained-simply-containers-pods-and-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:17:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you zone out every time someone mentions “Kubernetes,” “containers,” or “pods,” this article is for you. No complex diagrams involved!
As a front-end developer, you don’t have to know how to configure an infrastructure from scratch. However, if you …
The post Kubernetes Explained Simply: Containers, Pods and Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lari Maza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343671</id>
        <link href="https://tympanus.net/codrops/2021/06/04/trigonometry-in-css-and-javascript-beyond-triangles/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web design is such a rectangle-based design medium that literally any deviation from it feels fresh. Michelle Barker gets into using math in various ways to programmatically draw lines, shapes, and animations that end up looking both beautiful and have …
The post Trigonometry in CSS and JavaScript: Beyond Triangles appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using HSL Colors In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/hsl-colors-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ahmad Shadeed explains what HSL is, how to use it, and shares some of the useful use-cases and examples that you can use right away in your current projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fourteenth Fourth]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343496</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-fourteenth-fourth/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T13:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s CSS-Tricks birthday! Somehow that keeps coming around every year. It’s that time where I reflect upon that past year. It’s like the annual vibe check. 
I’m writing this just days after my current home state of Oregon has …
The post The Fourteenth Fourth appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Width Space]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-width-space/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T20:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The name zero-width space is antithetical, but it’s not without uses. In text, maybe you’d use it around slashes because you want to be sure the words are treated individually but not have any physical space around the slash:…
The post Zero-Width Space appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342995</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/good-meetings/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like it or not, meetings are essential to a good working environment and communication. Therefore, it’s crucial that we work on making them as productive as possible. Today we’ll explore myriad ways to keep meetings coordinated, well documented, and talk …
The post Good Meetings appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Drasner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Email Testing Flow As It Should Be]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/email-testing-flow/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many tools and approaches, email still has quite a few pain points, both for developers and email marketers. Email is difficult because it has too many aspects to set and a few instances with no common rules to follow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andriy Zapisotskyi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trick to Enable Printify Shipping Notifications for Orders in WooCommerce? Customer Notes.]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342994</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-trick-to-enable-printify-shipping-notifications-for-orders-in-woocommerce-customer-notes/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T00:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a super niche blog post. But it’s been on my list forever to write down because this caused me grief for far too long.
The setup is that you can use WooCommerce to sell things on a WordPress …
The post The Trick to Enable Printify Shipping Notifications for Orders in WooCommerce? Customer Notes. appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS for Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343637</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/css-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T18:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The marketing for Core Web Vitals (CWV) has been a massive success. I guess that’s what happens when the world’s dominant search engine tells people that something’s going to be an SEO factor. Ya know what language can play a …
The post CSS for Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A (Front-End Testing) Trap! Six Common Testing Pitfalls And How To Solve Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/07/frontend-testing-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing front-end tests, you’ll find a lot of pitfalls along the way. Let’s explore common mistakes developers make, and how to avoid them. Testing doesn’t need to be painful, after all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of Web Workers In 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-workers-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is single-threaded. This makes it increasingly hard to write smooth and responsive apps. Workers have a bad rep, but can be an important and useful tool in any web developer's toolbelt for these kinds of problems. Let’s get up to speed on Workers on the Web!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Surma)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Shades Of July (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome July with some fresh desktop wallpapers. Designed by artists and designers from around the world, they are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down Bulky Builds With Netlify And Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/breaking-down-bulky-builds-netlify-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static Generation is great for performance — until the app gets too big and build-times go through the roof. Today, we’ll have a look at how Netlify’s fresh On-Demand Builders can fix that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 40 With Mike Cavaliere: What Is Chakra UI For React?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-40/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Chakra UI. What is it and how can it help with your React projects? Drew McLellan talks to expert Mike Cavaliere to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Custom Emmet Snippets In VS Code]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/custom-emmet-snippets-vscode/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Manuel explains why Emmet is one of his favorite productivity tools for writing HTML and CSS, and how you can create custom Emmet snippets in Visual Studio Code to help you improve your front-end workflows even more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: support an experimental template for YouTube feed 📺 Demo | Source

Aggregate content from any YouTube channel rss url https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=<replace_with_channel_id>
Videos are embedded via iframe and loading accelerated by youtube-lite-embed
Ads are reduced thanks to YouTube's policy for embedded videos 🙃
Works on mobile devices with butter smooth horizontal scroll.
Caveat: the template works only with YouTube content. You cannot mix textual RSS feed or other video sources such as Vimeo.
Changed: Default HTML template meta tag adjusted to match convention
Changed: sources in template data is now ordered by last update timestamp (as opposed to alphabetical)
Thank you @PiyushLosalka]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>