<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-27T01:01:56.286Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-27T01:01:56.286Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux basics: What are Linux distributions (distros)?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mbbaig/linux-basics-what-are-linux-distributions-distros-3ila</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mbbaig/linux-basics-what-are-linux-distributions-distros-3ila"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T00:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of Linux is large and complex. It's highly competitive world of distributions, desktop environments, window managers, display managers, init systems, and ideologies to name a few. With this series of blog posts, I will be going to through all the basics of the Linux world and trying to explain, as best I can, what each concept or component is.
One of the first questions new users may ask themselves is what is a distribution. So let's explore that and answer that question.
A Linux distribution is a collection of various software, modules, and configuration. Usually a distribution also has it's own purpose and philosophy. There are many distributions that use the Linux system as a core piece of their system. Even the kernel can vary in functionality from distribution to distributio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamed Baig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move WSL File System to another Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/equiman/move-wsl-file-system-to-another-drive-2a3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/equiman/move-wsl-file-system-to-another-drive-2a3d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T00:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the C: drive is running out of space, we can move our WSL2 file system to another drive in a few steps.
If we are using an user different than root, we need to know it, running the whoami command (WSL side):

Also we need to know the distro name and WSL version, running the wsl --list --verbose command on PowerShell (Windows Side):

Knowing the username: equiman, the linux distribution: Ubuntu, and confirm that we are using the WSL 2 version, we are ready to...

All next steep need to be done on PowerShell (Windows Side).
First we need to shutdown WSL to avoid data corruption. Close all WSL terminals that are using it and then run the wsl --shutdown command.
Next we are going to create a backup from our Ubuntu linux distribution.
mkdir D:\backup
wsl --export Ubuntu D:\backup\ubuntu.tar

Don't worry if you not see progress indicators. This can be take a while depending how much data you have. Maybe it's good idea take a rest.

When finish, we need to to unregister the linux distribution from C: drive. It will also release the disk space.
wsl --unregister Ubuntu

And then, import again on our new disk. I'll use D: disk as an example.
mkdir D:\WSL
wsl --import Ubuntu D:\WSL\ D:\backup\ubuntu.tar

By default Ubuntu will use root as default user, to switch to our user (equiman in my case) we need to run this commands.
cd $env:USERPROFILE\AppData\Local\Microsoft\WindowsApps
ubuntu config --default-user equiman

Ensure replacing equiman with yours.
Restart WSL running wsl command and it's done.
That’s All Folks!
Happy Coding 🖖]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilo Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with node-gyp Package on Windows11]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/justinyoo/dealing-with-node-gyp-package-on-windows11-1on3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/justinyoo/dealing-with-node-gyp-package-on-windows11-1on3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T00:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a common practice using node.js for front-end app development. In the Windows dev environment, the same exercise applies. If you use Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL), you can make use of the Linux environment for it. But what if you want to keep your dev environment on Windows 11? One of the most infamous errors you might be able to see is related to the node-gyp package. Throughout this post, I'm going to discuss how to fix the node-gyp error on Windows 11.
node-gyp Package Dependencies


The node-gyp package is a part of npm, which is automatically installed while installing node.js. Therefore, you should be aware of your node.js and npm versions to get the issue sorted out. The latest LTS version of node.js at the time of this writing is 16.13.0 and npm of 8.1.0.

In general, if t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Yoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert a java application into a Linux service]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aernesto24/convert-a-java-application-into-a-linux-service-4ljc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aernesto24/convert-a-java-application-into-a-linux-service-4ljc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T23:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First of all, a Linux Service is an application that runs in the background and performs an essential task. One of the advantages to use a service is that you do not need to start it manually, you can configure it to start with the system using this command:
sudo systemctl enable <service_name>

Some of the most commonly used services are:
httpd
mysql
chronyd
sshd 
You can list all the services inside your Server using
systemctl list-units --type=service

Also you can see the status of an specific service using:
systemctl status <service_name>

Let see an example:
[ernesto.lopez@test-vm ~]$ systemctl status chronyd.service
● chronyd.service - NTP client/server
   Loaded: loaded (/usr/lib/systemd/system/chronyd.service; enabled; vendor preset: enabled)
   Active: active (running) since Tue …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ernesto Lopez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set latin american keyboard - Arch/Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/torswq/how-to-set-latin-american-keyboard-archlinux-34k8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/torswq/how-to-set-latin-american-keyboard-archlinux-34k8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T23:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR
loadkeys la-latin1
setxkbmap -layout latam,es
Introduction




I recently went back to Arch, and had some time figuring out how to set the Latin American keyboard, and it was quite easy, probably some minutes with the man pages and it would've been a cheese, okey so i got some info from stackoverflow and from the Official Arch Linux Wiki
Pre-installation



This is quite easy as you may load the keys with the loadkeyscommand (i.e loadkeys la-latin1) but when you install xorg and a desktop environment (Like XFCE or KDE) you may find that on a tty session your keymap is saved, but in the xfce session no.
Post-installation




(I am going to use XFCE as an example since it is my prefered desktop enviromnent).
xfce4-xkb-plugin but i wanted to do it all in the terminal so i found my way with coffee and patience. First, i could not set the keyboard layout to Spanish, so i googled how to do that, then i realized something was wrong, there where keys that do not correspond (Since i had a Spanish layout, not a Latin American, there are some tiny differences and no minor changes, but still, it annoyed me).
Solution post-installation



I used setxkbmap command with the -layout parameter, like this
setxkbmap -layout latam,es
# If you want it permament just do
setxkbmap -layout latam,es >> $HOME/.profile


And that's it, i hope you Latin American brothers and sisters have found your solution! (Thanks to Terdon for this answer)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>...</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSI Model]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/viveksahu26/osi-model-420f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/viveksahu26/osi-model-420f"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T21:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[History of Internet




January 1, 1983 is considered the official birthday of the Internet.
You can think of a protocol as a language, which allows  communication between two or more people.. Let’s say, people can only be able to share information among themselves if they speak the same language. As we all know every language has its own set of rules and grammar. In a similar way protocols also have a set of rules to communicate.

Let’s get back to the topic ARPANET, the communication between these computers was not completed until 1970, but as they began using the Network Control Protocol (NCP). NCP led to the development and use of the first computer-to-computer protocols like Telnet and File Transfer Protocol (FTP).
NCP’s could not keep up with the demands of the network and the variet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vivek kumar sahu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to TypeScript Monorepos]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mxro/the-ultimate-guide-to-typescript-monorepos-5ap7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mxro/the-ultimate-guide-to-typescript-monorepos-5ap7"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T21:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve written a couple of posts about how to set up JavaScript and TypeScript Monorepos over the past three years (#1, #2, #3, #4, #5, #6, #7), and I kind of thought I had it all figured out — but I didn’t.
It turned out that for various reasons it is fiendishly difficult to develop a JavaScript/TypeScript project that is broken up into multiple independent modules. To make this easier, I even created a little website, Goldstack, that generates modular starter projects.
However, I have always been somewhat unsatisfied with my solutions — with them often involving clumsy workarounds and issues that would prevent them to scale up to larger projects. Now I believe I have finally arrived at a solution that has minimal remaining workarounds and works well for smaller and larger projects.
This so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Rohde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is it “Right” to Reach for  contain and will-change in CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357271</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-is-it-right-to-reach-for-contain-and-will-change-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve got some blind spots in CSS-related performance things. One example is the will-change property. It’s a good name. You’re telling the browser some particular property (or the scroll-position or content) uh, will, change:
.el {
  will-change: opacity;

…
The post When is it “Right” to Reach for  contain and will-change in CSS? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 26th November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-26th-november-2021-541h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-26th-november-2021-541h"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello there. Welcome to this week's review, I am your host Habdul Hazeez.
This week's review is mostly about malware. One news is about a bug and the other, a data breach that affected GoDaddy.
Grab a cup of coffee, and let's get started.
Malware downloaded from PyPI 41,000 times was surprisingly stealthy


Always take a second look at your project dependencies. It won't hurt.
Excerpt from the article:
PyPI—the open source repository that both large and small organizations use to download code libraries—was hosting 11 malicious packages that were downloaded more than 41,000 times in one of the latest reported such incidents threatening the software supply chain.
GoDaddy Data Breach Exposes Over 1 Million WordPress Customers' Data


No system is safe. 
Excerpt from the articl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing A Caesar Shift  De-Cipher Function with JavaScript: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cerchie/writing-a-caesar-shift-de-cipher-function-with-javascript-part-2-5df</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cerchie/writing-a-caesar-shift-de-cipher-function-with-javascript-part-2-5df"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T20:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


In Part 1, I wrote a function that encodes a string of text in a Caesar cipher. 
In the second part of my series, I'm writing some files that decode an English string encoded with a Caesar cipher!
To start, I realized that my program would need to know how to encipher a string in order to decipher it, much the same as human cryptographers start by understanding how something is en-ciphered before de-ciphering.
So I popped the function from part 1 of my blog post into utils.js. Then, in app.js, I imported it:
const { caesarShift } = require('./utils')

Now, since in my enciphering function I only allowed 26 possibilities (technically 52 counting the negative shifts, but those are also technically the same as the positive ones since I 'wrapped around'), I could generate them by calli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucia Cerchie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of my Telegram bots]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lucifer25x/all-of-my-telegram-bots-2l8o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lucifer25x/all-of-my-telegram-bots-2l8o"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bot list:
Quiz Bot 
Quote Bot (with own API)
Secure Message Bot
Logo creator Bot
Word game Bot
User info Bot
Youtube Bot
Source code: 
https://github.com/Lucifer25x/telegram-bots]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucifer25x</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client / Server Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sagordondev/client-server-chat-36bc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sagordondev/client-server-chat-36bc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Github Repo

# client_server_chat
#   This is a program to demonstate a chat between client and server using UDP.
#   Run this program and add either client or server as an argument.
#   Once you have run both client and server you can chat between them.
# by Scott Gordon with help from Educative.com

import argparse, socket

MAX_SIZE_BYTES = 65535  # Mazimum size of a UDP datagram


def server(port):
    s = socket.socket(socket.AF_INET, socket.SOCK_DGRAM)
    hostname = "127.0.0.1"
    s.bind((hostname, port))
    print("Listening at {}".format(s.getsockname()))
    while True:
        data, clientAddress = s.recvfrom(MAX_SIZE_BYTES)
        message = data.decode("ascii")
        print("The client at {} says {!r}".format(clientAddress, message))
        msg_to_send = input("Input message to send to client:")
        data = msg_to_send.encode("ascii")
        s.sendto(data, clientAddress)


def client(port):
    s = socket.socket(socket.AF_INET, socket.SOCK_DGRAM)
    host = "127.0.0.1"
    while True:
        s.connect((host, port))
        message = input("Input message to send to server:")
        data = message.encode("ascii")
        s.send(data)
        data = s.recv(MAX_SIZE_BYTES)
        text = data.decode("ascii")
        print("The server replied with {!r}".format(text))


if __name__ == "__main__":
    funcs = {"client": client, "server": server}
    parser = argparse.ArgumentParser(description="UDP client and server")
    parser.add_argument("functions", choices=funcs, help="client or server")
    parser.add_argument(
        "-p", metavar="PORT", type=int, default=3000, help="UDP port (default 3000)"
    )
    args = parser.parse_args()
    function = funcs[args.functions]
    function(args.p)


Verify my Python
Photo by Kelvin Ang on Unsplash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IsEven API - SaaS platform for checking if number is even 🚀]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/skona27/iseven-api-saas-platform-for-checking-if-number-is-even-498k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/skona27/iseven-api-saas-platform-for-checking-if-number-is-even-498k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever heard about the SaaS platform for if a number is even? Well, I've decided to recreate a service like this of my own! 😄 
Not for the profit, of course - who would need the paid service for checking the parity of a number? 😄 I wanted to create a full-stack project from start to end and then deploy it. It seemed like a great challenge that would require gathering all my knowledge, structuring it, and maybe even learning some new stuff along. So this idea of creating a non-real SaaS platform fascinated me!
So this is it! I present to you my latest project - is-even.eu. It is open-source, so go ahead and check the codebase.
The main idea behind this SaaS platform is that a customer can purchase a plan (different plans allow different API usage). He can then perform an analysis o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Skoneczny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeremyjosephabraham/need-advice-3oh3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeremyjosephabraham/need-advice-3oh3"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, I need some advice, what would you recommend to a beginner who wants to get into cybersecurity, network security , cloud security etc. I don't know where to start really. I hope someone can give some pointers :). 
Thank you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Joseph Abraham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; jq (JSON) [LS#4]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-jq-json-ls4-1b6b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-jq-json-ls4-1b6b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jq 🧹


JSON formatter/prettifier.
🏠 https://stedolan.github.io/jq/
https://github.com/stedolan/jq
sudo apt-get install jq

echo -n '{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}' | jq

{
  "who": [
    "me",
    "you"
  ],
  "when": "now"
}

--tab





echo -n '{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}' | jq --tab

-c





cat << EOF | jq -c
{
  "who": [
    "me",
    "you"
  ],
  "when": "now"
}
EOF

{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}

-S





echo -n '{"z":"z","a":"a"}' | jq -S

{
  "a": "a",
  "z": "z"
}

-M





echo -n '{"who":"me","when":"now"}' | jq -M]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; jq (JSON) [LS#4]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-jq-json-ls4-1b6b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-jq-json-ls4-1b6b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[jq 🧹


JSON formatter/prettifier.
🏠 https://stedolan.github.io/jq/
https://github.com/stedolan/jq
sudo apt-get install jq

echo -n '{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}' | jq

{
  "who": [
    "me",
    "you"
  ],
  "when": "now"
}

--tab





echo -n '{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}' | jq --tab

-c





cat << EOF | jq -c
{
  "who": [
    "me",
    "you"
  ],
  "when": "now"
}
EOF

{"who":["me","you"],"when":"now"}

-S





echo -n '{"z":"z","a":"a"}' | jq -S

{
  "a": "a",
  "z": "z"
}

-M





echo -n '{"who":"me","when":"now"}' | jq -M]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic Terms to know before getting started with Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mayankcse/basic-terms-to-know-before-getting-started-with-cloud-27m6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mayankcse/basic-terms-to-know-before-getting-started-with-cloud-27m6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T17:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who have not read my previous blog, my name is Mayank and I have started a learning streak, #WeekendwithAzure In this I'll be posting my learning in azure every weekend
This is my contribution to help students in my community. Hope you'll find my efforts useful.
If you like it please add a comment of appreciation 
Getting Started!
Before taking our first step in the world of cloud and Azure, we should get familiar with the 7 basic terms that every cloud engineers uses and knows about.
Network Operating System
Client Operating System
Traditional IT
Virtualization
On-Premise Computing
Cloud Computing
On-Demand-Service and Pay-As-You-Go
Question to Client will be referred to as 'QTC'.
A Network Operating System (NOS) is a computer operating system (OS) that is designed primarily to supp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mayank-cse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ES2020: New Features & What's Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/workshub/es2020-new-features-whats-beyond-5doc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/workshub/es2020-new-features-whats-beyond-5doc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T17:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of JavaScript( officially ECMAScript ) changes fast and with awesome features getting added each year, it's certainly hard to keep up. The last big overhaul happened in ES2015 when a bunch of new features, sugarcoated syntax were added to the language.
ECMAScript community releases new features every year. In this post, we will have a look at 7 key features that were introduced in ES2020
*Big Int *

Nullish Coalescing Operator
Optional Chaining
Global this
Promise.allSettled
Dynamic Import
String.prototype.matchAll
Let's get into each one by one
BigInt is a special data type introduced in ES2020 to define numbers that exceed the Number data type range. The Number data type limits between -(2^53-1) to -(2^53-1), which we can check using
Number.MAX_SAFE_INTEGER & Number.MIN_SAFE_IN…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihaela</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish my first project!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jjung99/release-my-first-project-346b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jjung99/release-my-first-project-346b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T17:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[npm ERR! code E403
https://registry.npmjs.org/a1-ssg - Forbidden

npm ERR! 403 a package version that is forbidden by your security policy, ornpm ERR! 403 on a server you do not have access to.
npm ERR! A complete log of this run can be found in:
npm ERR!     C:\Users\Jiyun\AppData\Local\npm-cache_logs\2021-11-26T16_28_53_739Z-debug.log]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jjung99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incident Post-Mortems at Jobber]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jobber/incident-post-mortems-at-jobber-43ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jobber/incident-post-mortems-at-jobber-43ja"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how stable your software product is, occasionally things go wrong in production, and Jobber is committed to doing a post-mortem investigation to follow up and learn from each incident.
At a high-level, an incident post-mortem answers these questions:
What went wrong?
What did we do to fix it?
What will we do differently, so it doesn't happen again?
What went well during the incident, that we should keep doing?
As we’ve grown and moved to a remote working environment, we’ve changed our process to work better for remote teams and super busy schedules. This is a summary of what we’re doing to make sure that incidents remain rare and our customers can keep getting their work done!
Our process is broken down into 4 steps: Resolve the incident, investigate it, debrief about it, then sh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse van Herk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a real-time web application with Materialize and AdonisJS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/building-a-real-time-web-application-with-materialize-and-adonisjs-2ief</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bobbyiliev/building-a-real-time-web-application-with-materialize-and-adonisjs-2ief"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


In this tutorial, we are going to build a web application using AdonisJS and integrate it with Materialize to create a real-time dashboard based on streaming data using standard SQL.
Materialize lets you define views you want to maintain on your data, just as you would with any SQL table, and then get the results in real-time, unlike traditional databases which frequently act as if they've never been asked that question before.
You need to have the following things installed before getting started:
Install Docker
Install Docker Compose
Install Node.js
Materialize is a streaming database that takes data coming from sources like Kafka, PostgreSQL, S3 buckets, and more and allows you to effectively transform it in real-time using SQL.
Unlike a traditional database, Materialize …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bobby Iliev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Handy Little System for Animated Entrances in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357239</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-handy-little-system-for-animated-entrances-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love little touches that make a website feel like more than just a static document. What if web content wouldn’t just “appear” when a page loaded, but instead popped, slid, faded, or spun into place? It might be a …
The post A Handy Little System for Animated Entrances in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neale Van Fleet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a bare-metal Kubernetes cluster on Raspberry Pi]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anthonynsimon/building-a-bare-metal-kubernetes-cluster-on-raspberry-pi-4pko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anthonynsimon/building-a-bare-metal-kubernetes-cluster-on-raspberry-pi-4pko"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I originally posted this article on my personal blog. Now sharing my posts here too. Feel free to drop me a question in the comments section below.
In this post I’ll be walking you step by step on how I built a bare-metal, 3-node Kubernetes cluster running on Raspberry Pis. I'll also share some tips and tricks I learned along the way, and towards the end I'll honor the classic "I run my blog on Kubernetes" meme by deploying a basic Ghost server.

The already assembled cluster.
While this is not meant to be a tutorial, feel free to use my article as reference if you’re building a cluster too. You can add more nodes if you'd like. I chose three nodes simply because I’d run out of budget otherwise. After all, it's just my hobby project.
There's lots of guides on the internet on how to build s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anthonynsimon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn off Defender antivirus protection in Windows 10 Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mohammadtaseenkhan/turn-off-defender-antivirus-protection-in-windows-10-security-4nhh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mohammadtaseenkhan/turn-off-defender-antivirus-protection-in-windows-10-security-4nhh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T15:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turn off Defender antivirus protection in Windows 10 Security

-Select Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Virus & threat protection > Manage settings (or Virus & threat -protection settings in previous versions of Windows 10).
-Switch Real-time protection to Off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MD Taseen Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript weird type system - Boxing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/javascript-weird-type-system-boxing-k8e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedosama_st/javascript-weird-type-system-boxing-k8e"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aloha, it's nice to have you again in another article, in this one we'll be talking about one concept that exists withing JS but probably mis-understood and this misunderstanding leads to inaccurate mental models.

So what is boxing? well let me define boxing according to how I understand it.
Boxing is more like wrapping some value of type of x in a container that is type of y which has more functionalities that x can use - Some panda
Hopefully I did great job getting you confused, I think that's what academic definitions are all about after all 🥲
But let's break down this definition, let's assume that we have some value of the type x, for simplicity, let's say that x is the well known type string, so our value may be name = 'ahmed osama'
So that's the first part of my definition, that we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Osama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SSO Tutorial with Google Workspace (Gsuite) as an IdP Step-by-Step]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ukmadlz/aws-sso-tutorial-with-google-workspace-gsuite-as-an-idp-step-by-step-1866</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ukmadlz/aws-sso-tutorial-with-google-workspace-gsuite-as-an-idp-step-by-step-1866"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SSO and AWS Organization were released around 2017 and are probably the best way to manage AWS access at scale.
"AWS Single Sign-On (SSO) is a cloud SSO service that makes it easy to centrally manage SSO access to multiple AWS accounts and business applications. It enables users to sign in to an AWS IAM user with their existing corporate credentials and access all of their assigned accounts and applications from one place."
Quote From AWS SSO page
This is a huge security and operational win, some highlights:
No need to rotate another new password in AWS IAM
2FA is already managed at your IdP (Google Workspace (Gsuite)/Okta/AzureAD) level
When a user is leaving an organization he is automatically removed access from the organization
Easily automate the provisioning of AWS access when a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Elsmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SSO Tutorial with Google Workspace (Gsuite) as an IdP Step-by-Step]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ukmadlz/aws-sso-tutorial-with-google-workspace-gsuite-as-an-idp-step-by-step-1866</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ukmadlz/aws-sso-tutorial-with-google-workspace-gsuite-as-an-idp-step-by-step-1866"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS SSO and AWS Organization were released around 2017 and are probably the best way to manage AWS access at scale.
"AWS Single Sign-On (SSO) is a cloud SSO service that makes it easy to centrally manage SSO access to multiple AWS accounts and business applications. It enables users to sign in to an AWS IAM user with their existing corporate credentials and access all of their assigned accounts and applications from one place."
Quote From AWS SSO page
This is a huge security and operational win, some highlights:
No need to rotate another new password in AWS IAM
2FA is already managed at your IdP (Google Workspace (Gsuite)/Okta/AzureAD) level
When a user is leaving an organization he is automatically removed access from the organization
Easily automate the provisioning of AWS access when a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Elsmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRUD API using NestJS, MongoDB and Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/francescoxx/crud-api-using-nestjs-mongodb-and-docker-39jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/francescoxx/crud-api-using-nestjs-mongodb-and-docker-39jm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:38:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will set some CRUD API using:
NestJS (NodeJS Framework)
Mongoose (ODM that helps you to create a Schema based on the Model)
MongoDB (NoSQL Database)
Docker (Platform to deploy applications using containers)
Video Version: https://youtu.be/2eY_iQ9iCtE

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/FrancescoXX/nest-docker
Prerequisite: NodeJs installed, Docker (Docker desktop on windows/Mac Machines, Docker installed natively on Linux)
But you can follow way better if you:
Know how to run a "hello world" application using NestJS
Know what MongoDB Atlas is and how it works
Have an idea of what Mongoose is
Know what a Dockerfile and a Dockerfile is

NestJs is a Node.js framework for building efficient and scalable applications, with full support to Typescript. It has a CLI you can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Ciulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a typescript component library with Vite]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/josip2312/build-a-typescript-component-library-with-vite-58dh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/josip2312/build-a-typescript-component-library-with-vite-58dh"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Example repo at: https://github.com/josip2312/typescript-lib-vite
Vite ships with a pre-configured build command that has many performance optimizations out of the box. It uses Rollup under the hood and provides an abstraction over the default rollup configuration. This makes it way easier to set up the build step without knowing all the internals of rollup.
For the sake of the example, I'm going to create a simple button component, but the build step remains the same for any number of components. In this example, I'm using the <script setup> syntax.
Component code:
<script setup lang="ts">
import { reactive } from "vue";

interface Props {
  primary?: boolean;
}

const props = withDefaults(defineProps<Props>(), {
  primary: false,
});

const { primary } = reactive(props);
</script>

<temp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josip Ivancic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dev.to clone]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/quod_42/devto-clone-1e6m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/quod_42/devto-clone-1e6m"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T12:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i create dev.to clone on mern stack :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Алексей Яковлев</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Maintain A Large Next.js Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/maintain-large-nextjs-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/maintain-large-nextjs-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nirmalya discusses some of the complex problems that he faced while building and maintaining large Next.js applications. He always explains how these problems can be solved by using various tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nirmalya Ghosh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Security: OWASP List]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/surhidamatya/mobile-security-owasp-list-1fee</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/surhidamatya/mobile-security-owasp-list-1fee"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T11:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technological revolution has been the most dynamic thing in the world to change it's dynamics. Less than a decade ago, smartphones were a little device which would be accessible to wealthy persons only. Today, smartphone has been an integral part of everyone's life. With the rise in use of smartphone there has been rise in use of mobile application as well. These apps running on our mobile saves/shares our personal information, pictures, recordings, notes, account data, business information, location and much more.
With every enhancement in technology gives birth to new security risks and mobile technology is no different. Even though mobile operating systems like iOS and Android are arguably more secure by design compared to traditional Desktop operating systems, there's still a lot of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surhid Amatya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React, Typescript with Laravel]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/olivertembo/react-typescript-with-laravel-3f20</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/olivertembo/react-typescript-with-laravel-3f20"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it is much more convenient to build a monolith up.
For this we will make a simple Laravel, React, Typescript App. We will call it. Laravel-Guava
PHP/Laravel
Inertia/Breeze
React/Typescript
I am using a windows with WSL, ubuntu for this. using a mac should be the same experience. 😉 
Feel free to fork it make improvements as you like.
Technology: Make sure you have composer, typescript, node, docker installed. If not I'll add a few lines to make it work.
Step One: Install the latest version of Laravel and run it.
curl -s https://laravel.build/<name-of-your-app> | bash
./vendor/bin/sail up later composer-docker up is enough
npm install
npm run install
Initialize typescript in your project. this will create a ts config file. If that doesn't work, install typescript here[https://www.typescriptlang.org/download]
npx tsc --init
these are my configuration for my typescript
{
  "compilerOptions": {
anytype




Install the dependencies


Configure Laravel Mix






configure  webpack.config.js to resolve typescript extensions
module.exports = {
.ts and .tsx as a resolvable extension.
Then, let Mix know that it should handle the JavaScript code as TypeScript. Laravel Mix comes with built-in TypeScript support.
webpack.mix.js
-mix.js('resources/js/app.js', 'public/js')
That is it; you are all set! You can keep writing code the way you used to and utilize some TypeScript features and improve your front-end experience.
Run npm install for any additioal mix dependancies
npm run watch
link to repo: https://github.com/olivertembo/laravel-react-typescript-inertia-boilerplate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>olivertembo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; grep (Part 2) [LS#3]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-2-ls3-47om</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-2-ls3-47om"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep🎖️


Prints/filters lines that match a Regular Expression (RE) pattern.
-n





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -n "G."

  2:Im Going!
  3:Goodbye!

-A -B





cat ~/.bashrc | grep "if" -A 5 -B 1

Prints next 5 lines and previous 1 line when caught any "if".
-q





cat ~/.bashrc | grep -q "alias"

Returns with 0 exit code on any match, otherwise 1.
-c





cat ~/.bashrc | grep -c "alias"

-o





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -o "G..d"

  Good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; grep (Part 2) [LS#3]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-2-ls3-47om</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-2-ls3-47om"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep🎖️


Prints/filters lines that match a Regular Expression (RE) pattern.
-n





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -n "G."

  2:Im Going!
  3:Goodbye!

-A -B





cat ~/.bashrc | grep "if" -A 5 -B 1

Prints next 5 lines and previous 1 line when caught any "if".
-q





cat ~/.bashrc | grep -q "alias"

Returns with 0 exit code on any match, otherwise 1.
-c





cat ~/.bashrc | grep -c "alias"

-o





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -o "G..d"

  Good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[navigation.navigate("somescreen") show errors with typescript and react-native]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hafdiahmed/navigationnavigatesomescreen-show-errors-with-typescript-and-react-native-2mp4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hafdiahmed/navigationnavigatesomescreen-show-errors-with-typescript-and-react-native-2mp4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argument of type 'string' is not assignable to parameter of type '{ key: string; params?: never; merge?: boolean; } | { name: never; key?: string; params: never; merge?: boolean; }'.ts(2345)
that happens always when we cant to navigate to anther screen with typescript in react-native an help ?
example of code :
navigation.navigate("page_2")} />


  
  
  solution :]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AHMED HAFDI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and deploy Lambda function on AWS with CDK and API endpoint to Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdulwaqar844/how-to-create-lambda-function-on-aws-with-cdk-and-api-endpoint-to-lambda-3eca</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdulwaqar844/how-to-create-lambda-function-on-aws-with-cdk-and-api-endpoint-to-lambda-3eca"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T08:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1.What is AWS and CDK ?


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the world’s most comprehensive and broadly adopted scaleable cloud platform. AWS offering over 200 fully featured services from data centers globally. Millions of customers—including the fastest-growing startups, largest enterprises, and leading government agencies—are using AWS to lower costs, become more agile, and innovate faster.
AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) is an open source software development framework to define your cloud application resources using familiar programming languages.CDK is used to define structure of our application as Code. We can call it Infrastructure as Code which is best for scaleable
AWS Lambda  is a serverless, event-driven compute service that lets you run code for virtually any type of application…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdul Waqar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Features of clean code architecture | Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhiwise/features-of-clean-code-architecture-nodejs-1big</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhiwise/features-of-clean-code-architecture-nodejs-1big"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T08:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goal: Make our code resilient against changes over time

Software architecture is primarily the structure of the software components to be arranged in a purposeful and efficient system. The goal of software architecture is to minimize the human effort required to build and maintain software systems. One of the most effort-consuming processes in the software development cycle is to accommodate change. In software development, the primary method of handling change in the system is to create a separation of concerns between the layers of your software. This is where the Clean code architecture, created by Robert Cecil Martin (a.k.a Uncle Bob), shines.
Following are the benefits of implementing a clean code architecture with snippets from a node application.
Using the framework for a lot of op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DhiWise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NuxtJS v.2.15.8. How to hide private keys?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vadiminsk/nuxtjs-v2158-how-to-hide-private-keys-3h62</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vadiminsk/nuxtjs-v2158-how-to-hide-private-keys-3h62"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T07:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! Currently I am working on PWA project. We build pwa with nuxt and drupal as backend. So I have a lot of secrets from backend and don`t know where store it.
Can you share your best practices?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vadim Gadjimuradov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Detailed Guide on Angular Onpush Change Detection and Component Design]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/a-detailed-guide-on-angular-onpush-change-detection-and-component-design-254n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/a-detailed-guide-on-angular-onpush-change-detection-and-component-design-254n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T07:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


For all of our favorite projects, we've switched to Angular. We understand what Angular has to offer and how we can use it to create fantastic online applications. However, there are a few things to know about Angular that will help us use it more effectively in our projects.
Because data flow is at the heart while performing everything through Angular, change detection is something to be aware of. It will make it much easier to track out errors and improve our apps when working with large data sets.
Did we ever try to implement the Angular OnPush Change Detection technique in our project but run into some difficult-to-debug bugs and have to revert to the default change detection?
In this article, we’ll look at Angular change detection, data structures, and the process of ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Best Android Apps and Games Download Sites in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/teckieman/top-5-best-android-apps-and-games-download-sites-in-2021-5g6k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/teckieman/top-5-best-android-apps-and-games-download-sites-in-2021-5g6k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T07:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently joined Dev and I must say I am impressed by all the community they are really helpful and charming!
I posting because I want to let you guys know about the best trustworthy sites from which you can download Android apps.
This is just a tip of Iceburg you can read 20+ sites to download Android apps so don't forget to check them out.



① CNET Download:
CNET Download provides software and apps to download for Windows, Mac, iOS and Android devices, music, and videos are also available to download.
Previously, the site’s domain name was Download.com, now cnet.Download.com is the official domain that has been an excellent website since 1996, providing downloadable software and apps for a variety of operating systems.
CNET also publishes articles to help users to use software and apps.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teckie Man</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Typescript | Generics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mariusbongarts/advanced-typescript-generics-32lm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mariusbongarts/advanced-typescript-generics-32lm"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T07:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn advanced Typescript features and apply them to practical code exercises
Typescript Generics provide a way to write flexible code that can work with various data types rather than a single data type. That allows users of the code to provide their own types.
Advanced Typescript | Generics. Learn advanced Typescript features and… | by Marius Bongarts | Nov, 2021 | Medium
Marius Bongarts ・ Nov 26, 2021 ・ 
      
        
        Medium]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marius Bongarts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple way to generate random string in PHP]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/techmesh/simple-way-to-generate-random-string-in-php-25gj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/techmesh/simple-way-to-generate-random-string-in-php-25gj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T06:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While developing an application, sometimes it requires generating a random but unique string, e.g. Password Generator, CSRF token, and many more.
There are so many methods to generate random and unique strings in PHP. For Example:
rand();
uniqid();
bin2hex(random_bytes(20));


function random_seed(){
  list($usec, $sec) = explode(' ', microtime());
  return $sec + $usec * 1000000;
}

function getRadomSeed(){
    mt_srand(random_seed());
    $prefix = substr(str_shuffle(str_repeat($x='abcNOPQRSTUVWXYZdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzABCDEFGHIJKLM', ceil(5/strlen($x)) )),1,5);
    $suffix = substr(str_shuffle(str_repeat($x='wxyzABCDEFGHIJKLMNOabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvPQRSTUVWXYZ', ceil(5/strlen($x)) )),1,5);
    $randval = mt_rand();
    if(strlen($randval) % 2 == 0){
        $random = $prefix.$randval.$suffix;
    }else if(strlen($randval) % 3 == 0){
        $random = $prefix.$suffix.$randval;
    }
    else{
        $random = $randval.$prefix.$suffix;
    }
    return $random;
}

Execute:
$rd = getRadomSeed();
echo $rd;

Just to be sure that this is not the only way to generate random strings in PHP. I am just sharing one of my ways to generate random strings.
Happy Thanksgiving! 🦃]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Server-sent Events in Node.js?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dhiwise/how-to-implement-server-sent-events-in-nodejs-11d9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dhiwise/how-to-implement-server-sent-events-in-nodejs-11d9"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T06:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server-sent events **are a new **HTTP API for pushing events from the server to the client. Unlike W*ebSockets, server-sent events (SSE* for short) are built on top of the HTTP protocol, so no need for ws:// URLs or additional npm modules. Server-side events also handle reconnecting automatically, so you don’t have to write code to reconnect if the connection is lost.

After discussing with plenty of developers during the last few days, I have realize that a more of them don’t know what “Server-Sent Events” (or “SSE” or “EventSource”) is. My aim here is to give you all the information you may need about Server-Sent Events.
With Server-sent events you are able to send one-directional events to a web page.
Using Server-Send-Events eliminates the need to poll a server periodically for informa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DhiWise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a WordPress Site With Terraform & Ansible]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gsidhu13/deploy-wordpress-site-terraform-ansible-2m07</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gsidhu13/deploy-wordpress-site-terraform-ansible-2m07"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T03:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Summary



Provision resources with Terraform
Configure EC2 instance with Ansible
Install CodeDeploy to deploy a website to an instance
Bash scripts to make changes afterward
Create SSH key
Code is more than 150 lines long, so here's module link
Resources created with this module: 
Service role for CodeDeploy


CodeDeploy needs permissions to make changes to other resources to deploy the site. AWS managed policy and inline policy to get objects from S3 have been attached to the role. 
Security group for EC2 Instance


Allow HTTP traffic to the instance, so the website can be accessed from a browser. 
Instance profile for EC2


Permissions for the EC2 instance to make changes on other resources. The instance profile will use the same role that we created for CodeDeploy above.
EC2 Inst…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gurlal Sidhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[☢️ HTML Comment in React]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/html-comment-in-react-5243</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iamandrewluca/html-comment-in-react-5243"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T00:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever started learning React and saw it's syntax JSX, you maybe thought. "This looks like HTML"
And one day you want to comment something in JSX, and your first try would be to do:
function Component() {
  return (
    <div>
      <!-- This is my comment -->
      The quick brown fox ...
    </div>
  )
}

And for sure your bundler started complaining, that your syntax is invalid, and then you search the internet, and realise that a HTML Comment is not valid in JSX, and you learn that you have to use a JavaScript comment.
Well in this blog post I will show you for learning purposes how to trick React to render a real HTML Comment in your browser in a few steps.
Generate a React app using Create React App
npx create-react-app my-experiment --template typescript
cd my-experiment
npm run…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Luca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get or access the properties and methods of div HTML element tag without errors in TypeScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/melvin2016/how-to-get-or-access-the-properties-and-methods-of-div-html-element-tag-without-errors-in-typescript-19gp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/melvin2016/how-to-get-or-access-the-properties-and-methods-of-div-html-element-tag-without-errors-in-typescript-19gp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally posted here!
To get or access the properties and methods of the div HTML element tag without having errors or red squiggly lines in TypeScript, you have to assert the type for the div HTML element tag using the HTMLElement interface in TypeScript.
The errors or warnings are shown by the TypeScript compiler since the compiler doesn't know more information on the div HTML element tag ahead of time. But we know that we are referencing the div HTML tag and thus we can tell the compiler to use the HTMLElement interface which contains the declarations for properties and methods.
// get reference to the first 'div'
// HTML element tag in the document
// with type assertion using the HTMLElement interface
const divTag = document.querySelector("div") as HTMLElement;

// no errors or red …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MELVIN GEORGE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating MacOS with multiple Github or Bitbucket accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jeffshomali/integrating-macos-with-multiple-github-or-bitbucket-accounts-1an4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jeffshomali/integrating-macos-with-multiple-github-or-bitbucket-accounts-1an4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T22:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assume you want to use your personal Github account on your work laptop, and wanted to commit to your personal account without breaking your work repository configuration. In this tutorial I will show you how to easily manage multiple Github/Bitbucket accounts on MacOS without conflict each other. 
To achieve our goal we need to tell Github/Bitbucket Git's engine that we have multiple account in one computer. 
So bare with me to achieve our goal. 
Go to SSH directory $ cd ~/.ssh

Create a new SSH key ssh-keygen -t rsa -b 4096 -C <your_email@example.com? More on Github




  
  
  Register created SSH key to Github



This is very strait forward, just follow the Adding a new SSH key to your GitHub account




  
  
  Create SSH Config


To connection to multiple remote server through the SS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Shomali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIL about specific Array combination types]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vanquard/til-about-specific-array-combination-types-28bo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vanquard/til-about-specific-array-combination-types-28bo"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, so its not actually called "specific Array combination types", but that was the best description I had for it, before I looked it up.
https://www.tutorialsteacher.com/typescript/typescript-tuple
I'll come back to why this blew my mind today, but first, lets scroll back a bit, to some of my first steps into JS/TS programming. I started my programming career in Java, and one of the things that annoyed the hell out of me, was the fact that I could only have 1 object returned from a function (This was before the Pair class was introduced).
But in JS we can easily just return an array with 2 values:
const someFunction = () => {
    return ['Mathias', 28];
}

And combined with some destructuring on the recieving, it was all nice and easy:
const [myName, myAge] = someFunction();

Until today I never had to add types onto a scenario like this, usually when I work with arrays, I either just do a basic string[], or when its required in complex object scenarios: Array<{name: string, age: number}>.
[string, number]:
const someFunction = (): [string, number] => {
    return ['Mathias', 28];
}

I came across this when I working with Vue2 combined with TS, and was trying to create a v-for loop over a Map, but Vue2 did not support this, so I had to come up with a different approach that supported the same end goal.
So this is where the new tuples came in handy! Given an example with some data in a Map:
const map = new Map<string, object>();
map.set('key1', {data: 'lots of data'});
map.set('key2', {data: 'more data'});

I could then destructure it into an array like so:
const asArray = ...map.entries();
// Yielding:
[
    ['key1', {data: 'lots of data'}],
    ['key2', {data: 'more data'}],
]

And in order to Type this we now have:
const asArray: Array<[string, object]> = ...map.entries();

Thank you for reading this far, hope you gained something from this post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VanQuard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Voting Smart Contract with Near Protocol and Typescript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lkskrn/building-a-voting-smart-contract-with-near-protocol-and-typescript-3p08</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lkskrn/building-a-voting-smart-contract-with-near-protocol-and-typescript-3p08"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voting App Smart Contract Tutorial


Welcome to the Voting App Near Smart Contract Tutorial!
near-sdk-as Starter Kit which contains AssemblyScript written in Typescript
yarn tasks to build the smart contract.
Make sure you have installed nodejs 12+, yarn and the latest near-cli.
The Voting App Contract we are going to build is designed to support multiple ongoing elections. Here are the supported features:
Any election can have unlimited amount of candidates.
Every near user can vote, but only once for one of the candidates.
Every election has startDate and endDate properties which are used to control the election process.
Any candidate can add his candidacy before the election startDate.
A user can only add his vote for the specific election, if the election has already started, meaning c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleksandr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish a CLI project to NPM]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dukemanh/publish-a-cli-project-to-npm-10mc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dukemanh/publish-a-cli-project-to-npm-10mc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I will be releasing my little static site generator tool, OSD_SSG, to NPM package manager.
Before publishing a package, we need to assign a unique version to it following the Semantic versioning requirements. In a system with many dependencies, if the dependency specifications are too tight or too loose, we are in danger of dependency hell, which prevents us from easily and safely moving the project forward. Semantic versioning was introduced as a solution to the problem by standardizing how versions are assigned and incremented. Consider a version format of X.Y.Z (Major.Minor.Patch). Bug fixes not affecting the API increment the patch version, backwards compatible API additions/changes increment the minor version, and backwards incompatible API changes increment the major ve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DukeManh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nodejs And Express CRUD]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/moreno8423/nodejs-and-express-crud-2g8j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/moreno8423/nodejs-and-express-crud-2g8j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T19:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now we are going to learn how to create a Nodejs and express CRUD application. A CRUD application is the simplest web  application that we can create. The term CRUD comes from  "Create," "Read," "Update", and "Delete."  We create CRUDs Applications using the HTTP Verbs. In this tutorial we are also going to learn how to connect and use  a MongoDB Database in a Nodejs application. In this tutorial we assume that you have some JavaScript knowledge. We also assume that you have read something about MongoDB. You can take this tutorial as a second part for our Nodejs and Express Tutorial. Now let us start learning.
In this tutorial we are going to build the simplest Nodejs and express application. Applications like this serve as part of  more complex applications. The application will be a list…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moises E Liria Rosario</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Azure Subs One Github Action]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karl_itnerd/multiple-azure-subs-one-github-action-3230</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karl_itnerd/multiple-azure-subs-one-github-action-3230"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T19:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the benefits of working for an Azure MSP is that no two days are the same. You are constantly presented with different challenges to solve. It’s a lot of fun! I decided to write about how we solved one particular challenge below.
You’re working on a project that requires you to automatically deploy resources to Azure when a new branch is created in your GitHub repository. In this use case, you’re working with a company that is creating Azure Functions to bridge the gap between Azure and their software platform. Every time they want to test some tweaks or changes, a new branch is created. To support this testing, they need to create an Azure Function and a few other supporting resources. This can be time consuming when done manually. This is where GitHub Actions Workflows or Azure De…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Cooke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running Cardano (ADA) Node With GetBlock: What’s Under Hood of Our APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/getblock/running-cardano-ada-node-with-getblock-whats-under-hood-of-our-apis-19g0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/getblock/running-cardano-ada-node-with-getblock-whats-under-hood-of-our-apis-19g0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T16:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September, blockchain Cardano by Input Output Global, made headlines by the activation of smart contract functionality. As such, starting from Q3, 2021, GetBlock can connect your dApps to Cardano! Here’s how we do it.
Cardano is a blockchain network based on the top of Proof-of-Stake consensus. It was proposed in 2015 by Charles Hoskinson. Cardano’s mainnet went live in 2017.
In 2020, Cardano launched staking of its native asset ADA. ADA holders became able to delegate their coins and support favourite staking pools. For doing so, token holders receive periodical guaranteed rewards in ADA.
Since Q1, 2021, Cardano network is fully decentralized: no nodes are controlled by Cardano founders and early contributors. In Sept., 2021 with the mainnet activation of Alonzo hardfork, Cardano becam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GetBlock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to lazy load modules in Angular with loadChildren]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/codever/how-to-lazy-load-modules-in-angular-with-loadchildren-3g0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/codever/how-to-lazy-load-modules-in-angular-with-loadchildren-3g0j"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T16:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project: codever - File:  app.routing.ts
To lazy load Angular modules, use loadChildren (instead of component) in your AppRoutingModule routes configuration as follows.
import { RouterModule, Routes } from '@angular/router';
import { NgModule } from '@angular/core';
import { PageNotFoundComponent } from './not-found.component';
import { SnippetNotFoundComponent } from './not-found/snippet-not-found.component';

const routes: Routes = [
  {
    path: 'personal',
    loadChildren: () => import('app/personal/personal-bookmarks.module').then(m => m.PersonalBookmarksModule)
  },
  {
    path: 'dashboard',
    loadChildren: () => import('app/user/dashboard/user-dashboard.module').then(m => m.UserDashboardModule)
  },
  {
    path: 'settings',
    loadChildren: () => import('app/user-settings/use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Matei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to monitor your Laravel application by services not by hostnames]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ilvalerione/how-to-monitor-your-laravel-application-by-services-not-by-hostnames-2o9n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ilvalerione/how-to-monitor-your-laravel-application-by-services-not-by-hostnames-2o9n"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T16:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm Valerio, software engineer, founder & CTO at Inspector.
This post was born after responding to a support request by a developer who asked me how he can monitor his application by services, not by hostnames.
We have investigated this request and here is the solution we have found.
The company is developing the backend API of a fitness App, powered by two autoscaling groups.
An Autoscaling Group contains a collection of VM instances that are treated as a logical grouping for the purposes of automatic scaling and management of specific component of your system.
You could run your API in a different autoscaling group of the Background Workers. So they can scale in and out indipendently based on their specific workload.
Autoscaling can be managed by a cloud provider (like GCP, SWA, etc.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to download PDF files in Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aakashgoplani/how-to-download-pdf-files-in-angular-1bgl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aakashgoplani/how-to-download-pdf-files-in-angular-1bgl"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T15:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use case: Parse the blob response or base64 encoded string received from backend and Download PDF file on the fly.
The backend service sends blob data as response
%PDF-1.5
or base64 encoded string
data:application/pdf;base64,JVBERi0xLjUKJeLjz9MKMSAwI.....
First step here would be to process & parse response. If the response is base64 string, we first need to convert that to blob object as the file download is possible with blob data only!
private processFileResponse(fileResponseData: any, fileName: string, render: string): void {
  if (render === 'base64') {
    this.base64Response = fileResponseData;
    const binaryString = window.atob(fileResponseData);
    const bytes = new Uint8Array(binaryString.length);
    const binaryToBlob = bytes.map((byte, i) => binaryString.charCodeAt(i));
   …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aakash Goplani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need To Know About Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ioeshu/everything-you-need-to-know-about-microsoft-azure-kcc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ioeshu/everything-you-need-to-know-about-microsoft-azure-kcc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T15:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Azure is a cloud computing service operated by Microsoft, often referred to as Azure. it offers more than 200 cloud products and services designed to solve today’s challenges.
Azure is not only the one cloud player out in the market there are Amazon, Google, IBM also offer similar services and cloud solutions to the industries. what’s so special in Azure? Azure entered into cloud space in 2010 a 4 years later to amazon’s but azure has made significant advances over the years, it now offers a set of features and capabilities far surpassing its competitors and secured 2nd place in the cloud market by leaving 1st place to Amazon.
Enterprises across the globe are realizing great success with business solutions powered by Cloud. Startups and small businesses are also moving to the clo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eswar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does anti-virus work?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vspranav21/antivirus-14dj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vspranav21/antivirus-14dj"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T13:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antivirus software scans program using selected chunk of data from its database. If it gets a code that resembles to that of a malware stored in its database then that code is flagged as malware. Now this is either isolated or deleted


Complete System Scans. these scans are not much needed if there is on hand access feature on the system.it is well used if the anti-virus is installed for the first time or the security of the system is not updated for long time .this is implemented to ensure that there are no malware hiding in the most difficult locations and deep behind the codes of the system. Full framework scans are vital to scan your contaminated system

Virus Definitions - Antivirus software codes are based on the definitions to differentiate a virus from a genuine file and a malware. This the vital step to check on new virus definitions. The virus definitions clears of the of the marks of any codes which are considered as hazard in the system code.in the scenario of virus definition finds a file with marks of malware that matches accordingly, then that file is immediately terminated from execution and is isolated. The antivirus software runs through the malware, analyses it, and sends to lab to find out the origin and purpose of the malware in the system]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vspranav21</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing JavaScript Breadcrumb Control in Essential JS 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/syncfusion/introducing-javascript-breadcrumb-control-in-essential-js-2-25ja</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/syncfusion/introducing-javascript-breadcrumb-control-in-essential-js-2-25ja"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T11:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to introduce the new JavaScript Breadcrumb control in the Essential JS 2 suite.
The Breadcrumb component is a graphical user interface that serves as a navigation header for your web application or site. It helps to identify or highlight the current location within the hierarchical structure of a website.
The Essential JS 2 suite has a huge set of controls, and all these controls possess common web standards and functionalities such as web accessibility, right-to-left rendering, keyboard interaction, modular architecture, and responsiveness, with touch-friendly and lightweight UIs. Now, the Breadcrumb is included in this suite with all these JS 2 features as well as control-specific features.
This blog will provide a walk-through on the new Breadcrumb control, its UI designs, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Shell; grep (Part 1) [LS#2]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-1-ls2-15ld</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/babakks/living-in-the-shell-grep-part-1-ls2-15ld"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T10:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grep🎖️


Prints/filters lines that match a Regular Expression (RE) pattern.
echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep "Good"

  Goodbye!

cat ~/.bashrc | grep "alias"

grep "alias" ~/.bashrc

-P





cat ~/.bashrc | grep -P "^#"

Prints lines beginning with #.
-i





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -i "go"

  I'm Going!
  Goodbye!

-v





echo -n 'Hello World!\nI''m Going!\nGoodbye!' | grep -i -v "go"

  Hello World!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Babak K. Shandiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing Intellectual Property Theft with Jscrambler]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jscrambler/preventing-intellectual-property-theft-with-jscrambler-39l8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jscrambler/preventing-intellectual-property-theft-with-jscrambler-39l8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T10:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is intellectual property theft?


Intellectual property theft (also called IP theft) refers to someone illegitimately taking possession of someone else’s proprietary inventions or developments. In the context of business, and specifically in IT, IP theft typically refers to a competitor or malicious actor getting access to trade secrets or proprietary algorithms to be used to the thief's own advantage.
The acceleration of digital transformation, which was exacerbated by the Covid pandemic, has stimulated the development of new technologies, consequently increasing the value of companies’ intellectual property.
This, of course, creates a huge opportunity for attackers and scammers. We have witnessed copycat apps going rampant in app stores and stealing business away from original devel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jscrambler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate PowerShell Terminal Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bekbrace/the-ultimate-powershell-terminal-guide-2li6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bekbrace/the-ultimate-powershell-terminal-guide-2li6"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T10:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to Scott Hanselman, my terminal looks fabulous, and it's not only the looks but also the productivity.
You can find the whole guide on his blog (quick guide):
https://www.hanselman.com/blog/my-ultimate-powershell-prompt-with-oh-my-posh-and-the-windows-terminal
Also, there's around one hour video with details - including mistakes which I though was great for learning from such a great teacher and expert - on YouTube:




This is how my terminal looks like now :


YouTube : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7EVSn5inapL20oPSwAwEUg
https://www.facebook.com/bekbrace​​​​
https://twitter.com/BekBrace
https://www.instagram.com/bek_brace/
https://github.com/BekBrace
https://bekbrace.com
Enjoy !]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bek Brace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Password-Synchronization with Syncthing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/marceljurtz/password-synchronization-with-syncthing-i7a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/marceljurtz/password-synchronization-with-syncthing-i7a"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T07:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are reding this, chances are you already use a password manager. I have been doing that for several years now. But I have to admit that my password manager has only run on my phone so far and I have always transferred passwords that I use on my PC by hand. Probably out of sheer laziness. Today, I use this blog post to finally synchronise my password database between any number of devices - and to show you how to do it. The whole thing not only makes dealing with passwords more convenient, but naturally also reduces the inhibition threshold to actually use the applications. This in turn improves the overall security of your accounts.
Let’s briefly talk about the software: I use Keepass 2 on my PC and Keepass2Android on my mobile phone. This article should work with all applications t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel Jurtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide On Ngrx Store Architecture Using Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/a-complete-guide-on-ngrx-store-architecture-using-angular-1ha2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/a-complete-guide-on-ngrx-store-architecture-using-angular-1ha2"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T06:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is NgRx?


NgRx is a type of Angular framework for building reactive applications. NgRx provides picture perfect library support for:
Managing global and local state.
To promote a cleaner component architecture, it is an isolate of side effects.
Entity collection management.
Integration with the Angular Router.
When building many different types of applications, it uses Developer tooling that enhances developer experience.
NgRx packages are mainly divided into these categories
State
Store - RxJS used for global state management for Angular apps.
Effects - Side effect model for @ngrx/store.
Router Store - connect the Angular Router to @ngrx/store for Bindings.
Entity – To manage record collections, it will use Entity State adapter.
ComponentStore - Standalone library for managing local…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount usb/hdd and copy files in linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abbazs/mount-usbhdd-and-copy-files-in-linux-3c4l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abbazs/mount-usbhdd-and-copy-files-in-linux-3c4l"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T05:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List all the usb drives




sudo fdisk -l

Mount the drive required




sudo mount /dev/sda1 /media/usba

https://help.ubuntu.com/community/Mount/USB]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>abbazs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pi Network Performance Test]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/openspeedtest/raspberry-pi-network-performance-test-3m1k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/openspeedtest/raspberry-pi-network-performance-test-3m1k"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T04:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get OpenSpeedTest Server https://go.openspeedtest.com/Server
For full 1Gbps Test. Close all other programs running on your pi.

Docker install instructions:
Install Docker and run the following command!
docker run --restart=unless-stopped --name openspeedtest -d -p 3000:3000 -p 3001:3001 openspeedtest/latest
Now open your browser and direct it to:
A: For HTTP use: http://YOUR-SERVER-IP:3000
B: For HTTPS use: https://YOUR-SERVER-IP:3001
How to use your own SSL Certificate?
You can mount a folder with your own SSL certificate to this docker container by adding the following line to the above command.
-v /PATH-TO-YOUR-OWN-SSL-CERTIFICATE*:/etc/ssl/*
I am adding a folder with nginx.crt and nginx.key from my desktop by using the following command.
docker run -v /Users/vishnu/Desktop/docker/:/etc/ssl/ --restart=unless-stopped --name openspeedtest -d -p 3000:3000 -p 3001:3001 openspeedtest/latest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OpenSpeedtest.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Websocket Real Time Communication to Your SaaS App]]></title>
        <id>619ba16011d3cb08287aa2ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-websocket-real-time-communication-to-your-saas-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this conference talk made for Tech Fest 2021, Steven Lemmo talks to you about building SaaS Applications with WebSockets. Here is a full breakdown of what he will cover in this 40 minute talk: The reason for this talkWhy Websockets?Websockets minimal API exampleRest Web ServicesMultiple ListenersFull DuplexWebsockets time-lineTypeScriptVendor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Color Shades – Hex Code and RGB for Gray Color Palette]]></title>
        <id>619bcc5611d3cb08287aa66f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/color-shades-hex-code-and-rgb-for-gray-color-palette/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colors play an integral role in how usable and accessible your web design projects are.  At times, they can even make or break a project.  Having a color palette comprised of different shades and hues of a specific color can be really helpful. It helps you visualize how you can]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Universally Unique Identifiers with JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/xjamundx/generating-universally-unique-identifiers-with-javascript-2919"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For as long as I can remember the recommended way to generate unique universal Identifiers in node.js was to the uuid module. These IDs are useful in all sorts of scenarios including for database keys, filenames, URLs, etc. Recently both node.js and the browser began offering nearly identical APIs that will generate 36-character version 4 uuids without any dependencies.
Available in Chrome since July 2021 and coming soon other browsers is crypto.randomUUID(). There's a global crypto object that's available on the global self property. You can use that to generate a UUID like this:
self.crypto.randomUUID();

The UUID it generates is a v4 UUID per the spec and ends up with a string that looks something like this:
"0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"


You want to do the same thing in node? Instead of reaching for the uuid package. As long as you're on version 14.17 or newer, you can do this:
const { randomUUID } = require("crypto");
randomUUID(); // "0aa9d4f3-efdb-4a06-806c-5f8fa5f1767d"

It's cool see node and the browser adopting powerful APIs for crypto and improved randomness. I'll definitely be reaching for these in the near future!
You can read more in the WebCrypto section in the MDN or the crypto section in the node.js docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamund Ferguson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Material Setup Guide - Installation and Quick Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sameer8saini/angular-material-setup-guide-installation-and-quick-demo-3jc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sameer8saini/angular-material-setup-guide-installation-and-quick-demo-3jc"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T23:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, I will show you how to install and use Angular Material UI in your Angular project.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0h3aDhkVsng
We will use the default themes that Angular Material offers and will see what setup is required in your Angular solution while using Angular Material.
We will make changes to the App.Module.Ts file and then use the Angular Material component in the template and component.


  
  
  AngularMaterial #Angular #UiLibrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sameer8saini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Complete Guide To BFF (Backend For Frontend)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/chrislydemann/the-complete-guide-to-bff-backend-for-frontend-5a61"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T21:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A backend for frontend (BFF) is one of these newer architectural patterns that especially became relevant after the rise of microservices and domain-driven design, as it is a way to simplify the communication between the frontend and backend and make the frontend development simpler.
In this post, I will cover BFFs with Angular and if and how you should do it in your project.
https://christianlydemann.com/the-complete-guide-to-backend-for-frontend-bff/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Lüdemann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis with Python for Excel Users Course]]></title>
        <id>619e979225888a07c3e1b545</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-analysis-with-python-for-excel-users-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T20:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know how to use Microsoft Excel and want to learn how to do data analysis with Python? You are in luck. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to do Data Analysis with Python. This course will be especially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Won&#x27;t My Computer Connect to My Hotspot? [Fixed on Windows 10 PC WiFi]]]></title>
        <id>619e3cdd25888a07c3e1b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-wont-my-computer-connect-to-my-hotspot-fixed-on-windows-10-pc-wifi/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T18:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mobile hotspot is a quick and efficient way to share an internet connection with other devices like computers, iPads, or other mobile phones.  A hotspot is also a good alternative to WiFi – especially if the WiFi in your area is unbearably slow or won't connect.  Sometimes, you might experience]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned from The Pragmatic Programmer and The Clean Coder]]></title>
        <id>619c873711d3cb08287aaf76</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lessons-learned-from-the-pragmatic-programmer-and-the-clean-coder/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently finished reading The Pragmatic Programmer 20th Anniversary Edition (2019) and The Clean Coder (2011). You'll find these books on almost every “top 10 Software Development books” list out there.  My goal was to learn, improve, and get the kind of knowledge that a teacher from mine used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357294</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-generative-patterns-with-the-css-paint-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The browser has long been a medium for art and design. From Lynn Fisher’s joyful A Single Div creations to Diana Smith’s staggeringly detailed CSS paintings, wildly creative, highly skilled developers have — over the years — continuously pushed …
The post Creating Generative Patterns with The CSS Paint API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Francis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and How to Add Feature Toggles to Your Software]]></title>
        <id>619e8cba25888a07c3e1b499</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-and-how-to-add-feature-toggles-to-your-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature Toggles (aka Feature Flags) are a technique used in software development in order to hide, enable or disable a particular feature during runtime. They allow teams to modify system behavior without changing code. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp YouTube channel that will teach you why and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D3.js Tutorial – Data Visualization for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>618ed39211d3cb08287a5535</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/d3js-tutorial-data-visualization-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to walk you through how to use D3.js in a step by step and beginner-friendly way. We'll talk about what D3.js is, how it works, and we'll create some basic visualizations to add transitions, interactions, and zooming. Table of Contents Getting Started  What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Ember – Ember.js Tips for Beginners Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>619cdd9d11d3cb08287ab09c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-ember-ember-js-tips-for-beginners-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T15:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, Designer turned Software Developer Lenora Porter talks about her journey learning Ember.js. She also shares her tips for beginners who are about to start their journey. Here are her top 4 take-aways: How to Learn Ember.jsHave the Mindset of a BeginnerThis is the foundational work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Showcase Of Lovely Little Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/showcase-lovely-little-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of spending your coffee break scrolling through your social feeds, how about a lovely little website instead? We came across some fantastic ones that are just too good not to be shared. But be warned, your break might take a bit longer than intended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Angular 11?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tarungurang/whats-new-in-angular-11-1l16</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tarungurang/whats-new-in-angular-11-1l16"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T11:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is the most popular framework and platform to build the desktop applications and mobile applications. Angular is written in typescript. Angular 11 has been released in Nov 2020 and it is developed by Google.
Angular is a Typescript based open-source platform that makes it easy to create applications within web/mobile/desktop. It is a framework and platform to create a single page application.
To check the installed version of angular, run the ng version command.
Angular CLI: 10.0.8
Node: 12.18.3
OS: win32 x64
Angular:
...
Ivy Workspace:
Package                      Version
------------------------------------------------------
@angular-devkit/architect    0.1000.8
@angular-devkit/core         10.0.8
@angular-devkit/schematics   10.0.8
@schematics/angular          10.0.8
@schematics…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Gurang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom colour for angular material components]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/infinityintellect/custom-colour-for-angular-material-components-4o3d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/infinityintellect/custom-colour-for-angular-material-components-4o3d"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T10:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem


So, you have an angular material component, say a chip or a button like so:
<button mat-flat-button> Done button>

The designs provided to you show that the background colour of the button should be green and the text should be white.
In your corresponding styling file (.css or .scss), include the following style selector:
.mat-green {
 background-color: green;
 color: white;
}

And then, in your .html file, simply set the color input attribute to green as below:
<button mat-flat-button color="green"> Done button>

And voilà ! There you have it.
Note: You can provide any name to the css selector and prefix it with mat- and set the name to the color attribute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddeshwar Navaneetharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the Math You Need to Know in Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>6197c7ce11d3cb08287a9271</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/all-the-math-you-need-in-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an AI researcher, and I’ve received quite a few emails asking me just how much math is required in Artificial Intelligence. I won’t lie: it’s a lot of math. And this is one of the reasons AI puts off many beginners. After much research and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is GitOps? Principles, Best Practices, and Kubernetes Workflow]]></title>
        <id>619bb55911d3cb08287aa581</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/gitops-principles-kubernetes-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk, CTO Cornelia Davis will teach you what GitOps is and what its four main principles are.  What is GitOps?The first thing you need to know is that GitOps is a set of modern best practises for deploying and managing cloud native infrastructure and applications.  And it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: npm install throwing error in node-sass]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-npm-install-throwing-error-in-node-sass-28f8"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: npm install throwing error in node-sass
            
        
Mar  1 '20
        
Add manually in package.json :  "node-sass": "4.13.0"
and update package.json in terminal npm install
Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answer: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coolqa3/answer-error-with-npm-install-a-pre-gyp-error-id5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[answer re: Error with npm install - a pre-gyp error
            
        
Feb 25 '21
        
I solved this issue by typing the following:
 npm install grpc --save
 npm install node-pre-gyp --save

Open Full Answer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolqa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357412</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/which-svg-technique-performs-best-for-way-too-many-icons/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T19:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Sticka digs in here in the best possible way: by making a test page and literally measuring performance. Maybe 1,000 icons is a little bit of an edge case, but hey, 250 rows of data with four icons in …
The post Which SVG technique performs best for way too many icons? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nrwl/modern-angular-2mp0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Modern Angular Tooling?


With the Angular CLI no longer including a complete out-of-the-box development solution, it is more important than ever to understand the tools at our disposal to improve the developer experience when building Angular applications.
Modern Angular Tooling is the term used to describe modern tools that will enable you and your team to build a comprehensive development environment. This development environment takes advantage of the latest improvements in the JavaScript ecosystem to improve productivity, consistency, reliability, scalability and developer experience when building Angular applications and libraries. 
We consider Modern Tools to be additional tools that can and should be used when building Angular applications and Angular libraries. These tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colum Ferry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356977</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/control-layout-in-a-multi-directional-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many business websites need a multilingual setup. As with anything development-related, implementing one in an easy, efficient, and maintainable way is desirable. Designing and developing to be ready for multiple languages, whether it happens right at launch or is expected …
The post Control Layout in a Multi-Directional Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alaa Abd El-Rahim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding A Dyslexia-Friendly Mode To A Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dyslexia-friendly-mode-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a little CSS, we can adapt our web designs to be more accommodating for people with dyslexia. In this article, we’ll explore those techniques by adding a dyslexia-friendly mode to an existing design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John C Barstow)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357149</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-user-tracking-and-industry-standards-on-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Eva PenzeyMoog’s new book, Jeremy highlights the widespread user tracking situation in this industry:
There was a line that really stood out to me: 
The idea that it’s alright to do whatever unethical thing is currently the 
…
The post On User Tracking and Industry Standards on Privacy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS “decorations”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357046</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-decorations/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reader wrote to me the other day asking about this bit of CSS they came across in Wikipedia’s Common.css:
.mw-collapsible-leftside-toggle .mw-collapsible-toggle {
  /* @noflip */
  float: left;
  /* @noflip */
  text-align: left;
}
What’s that @noflip business? That’s …
The post CSS “decorations” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Workshops: Winter 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashingconf-workshops-winter-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of CSS, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our [online workshops on UX, front-end and design](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357080</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-layouts-fewer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T15:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We cannot talk about web development without talking about Responsive Design. It’s just a given these days and has been for many years. Media queries are a part of Responsive Design and they aren’t going anywhere. Since the introduction of …
The post Responsive Layouts, Fewer Media Queries appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Wix Websites (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/improving-performance-wix-websites-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a performance culture is very important. In this article, Dan Shappir shares which actions and processes the Wix team put in place in order to achieve dramatic improvements in the performance of websites built and hosted on their platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagine Atomic CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/reimagine-atomic-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T22:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not the biggest fan of Atomic CSS myself. I don’t like all the classes. I like to express my styles in CSS because I find CSS… good. But I appreciate that a lot of people seem to like it, …
The post Reimagine Atomic CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coding Font Game]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357227</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/coding-font-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tournament bracket UI where you pick your favorite between two coding fonts and your choices are whittled down all the way to a final winner. A clever way to suss out your own taste and arrive at a choice.…
The post Coding Font Game appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=357192</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/parallax-powered-by-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good friend Kent C. Dodds has recently dropped his new website which had a lot of work go into it. I was fortunate enough that Kent reached out a while back and asked if I could come up with some …
The post Parallax Powered by CSS Custom Properties appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting with a wildcard subdomain enables your users to visit your site on any subdomain of your domain (*.example.com), and as you can imagine, we can use this to create unique user experiences which we’ll be exploring in this article through a Next.js lens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-many-faces-of-vs-code-in-the-browser/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code is built from web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript), but dare I say today it’s mostly used a local app that’s installed on your machine. That’s starting to shift, though, as there has been an absolute explosion of …
The post The Many Faces of VS Code in the Browser appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Date and Time Recipes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356570</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/php-date-and-time-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with dates and times is one of those things that can frustrate programmers a lot. At the same time, they are fundamental to software development, used from everything from meta and how things are ordered to time-based triggers and …
The post PHP Date and Time Recipes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arjuna Sky Kok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356895</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/zero-trickery-custom-radios-and-checkboxes/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like half of all “custom-designed radio buttons and checkboxes” do two things:
Make them bigger
Colorize them
I always think of SurveyMonkey for having big chunky radios and checkboxes. And indeed, just poking at their interface quickly, even …
The post Zero Trickery Custom Radios and Checkboxes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get for using a search input type?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=356885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-do-you-get-for-using-a-search-input-type/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T23:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like this: <input type="search">
You get an extra-round-y appearance in Safari, which at one time matched the macOS look for search inputs, but not really anymore. I don’t hate the look, except…
Safari totally ignores the font-size you set on 
…
The post What do you get for using a search input type? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Modern CSS Colors With RGB, HSL, HWB, LAB And LCH]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/guide-modern-css-colors/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll take a look at the best ways to handle colors in CSS today, some tips for using them in a design system, and what we can expect from our colors in the not-too-distant future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces, A New Smashing Book By Steven Hoober]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/touch-design-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide on designing for mobile with proven, universal, human-centric standards. 400 pages. Shipping starting in early January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powerful Terminal And Command-Line (CLI) Tools For Modern Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/powerful-terminal-commandline-tools-modern-web-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite command-line tool? In this post, Louis Lazaris shares a collection of relevant command-line apps and utilities that he has personally come across in the past few years. If there’s a useful one that hasn’t been mentioned and one you use regularly, please do share it in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React Hooks That You Can Use In Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/useful-react-hooks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The React team introduced several hooks in React 16.8 which you can use from third-party providers in your application, or even create your own custom hook. In this tutorial, we’ll take a look at some of the most useful hooks in React and how to use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ifeanyi Dike)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Good To Great In Dashboard Design: Research, Decluttering And Data Viz]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/dashboard-design-research-decluttering-data-viz/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dribbbleshots just might be the hotbed of questionable dashboards. Striking visuals, little context, and no research: all recipes for mediocrity. Mediocrity won’t do. We’ll pursue greatness. And in that pursuit, we’ll cover research, decluttering, and data visualization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adam Fard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Localizing Your Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/localizing-your-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internationalized routing is not exactly a new feature on Next.js. In this article, we are not only checking what we get from this feature, but also how to leverage such functionalities to achieve the best user experience and a smooth developer experience as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically Transforming And Optimizing Images And Videos On Your WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/transforming-optimizing-images-videos-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz explains how Cloudinary’s integration can be used with WordPress to produce and deliver optimal digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Hydrogen: A React Framework For Dynamic, Contextual And Personalized E-Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/hydrogen-react-framework-dynamic-contextual-personalized-ecommerce/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great commerce experience is not a Lighthouse score or a set of Core Web Vitals figures (although both are important inputs), but it’s also a trilemma that carefully balances competing needs of delivering a great customer experience, dynamic storefront capabilities and long-term business objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Grigorik)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value Of Concept Testing As Part Of Product Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/concept-testing-part-of-product-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concept testing ideas before moving into a detailed design is good UX practice. In this article, Victor Yocco presents details on how and when to engage in concept testing, as well as case studies providing details on the insights gained in two very different settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 43 With Matthew Phillips: What Is Astro?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/smashing-podcast-episode-43/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Astro. Will this modern static site builder launch you into the stratosphere? Drew McLellan talks to developer Matthew Phillips to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GraphQL On The Front-End (React And Apollo)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/graphql-frontend-react-apollo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the last decade, technologies like GraphQL have changed how we build web apps and how they communicate with each other. GraphQL provides certain benefits over REST APIs — let’s find out what they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (David Atanda)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into Serverless UI With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/deep-dive-into-serverless-ui-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless UI is simply a free, open-source command-line utility for quickly building and deploying serverless applications on the AWS platform. In this article, we will learn and cover everything needed on using Serverless UI to deploy our projects or serverless applications to cloud services providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ikeh Akinyemi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Magento PWA: Customizing Themes vs. Coding From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/magento-pwa-customizing-themes-coding/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article sheds the spotlight on Magento PWAs and explains why business owners are getting them (often instead of native applications). Alex Husar introduces ways of how progressive web applications can be developed on Magento, as well as go over the major pros and cons of each development path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alex Husar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>