<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-11T16:42:00.506Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-11T16:42:00.506Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.6.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NativeScript, Databases, and You]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ozymandiasthegreat/nativescript-databases-and-you-3kn4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ozymandiasthegreat/nativescript-databases-and-you-3kn4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T16:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or how to get recent versions of typeorm and NativeScript to play nicely together.
By recent, I mean the latest version of typeorm as of this writing and NativeScript 7.
Whether you're upgrading or starting a new project, you're likely to run into some issues.
Another thing to consider is typeorm's viability going forward. The work on current architecture has stalled, and
For the reasons above you should not use typeorm on new projects. If you're OK with writing raw SQL queries,
nativescript-sqlite. Otherwi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas Ravinskas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No need to handle Express.js with this MERN Stack project template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/scaledynamics/no-need-to-handle-express-js-with-this-mern-stack-project-template-1bm6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/scaledynamics/no-need-to-handle-express-js-with-this-mern-stack-project-template-1bm6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At ScaleDynamics we have one recurrent passion: to make web developers’ life easier 🙈.
 
BAM! And we strike again! We built a fully open source MERN template ready to use for our platform. 
One command to develop with frontend and backend live reload... 
Let’s get started! 
It is located here (https://github.com/ScaleDynamics/react-mongodb-template) - use it as you wish and start coding your projects with it! We hope you’ll find it helpful! 🤗
Quick reminder — MERN stands for MongoDB, Express, React and No…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Hash Table – Associative Array Hashing in JS]]></title>
        <id>60856789dd38b9088c2bf4ff</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-hash-table-associative-array-hashing-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hash Tables are a data structure that allow you to create a list of paired values. You can then retrieve a certain value by using the key for that value, which you put into the table beforehand. A Hash Table transforms a key into an integer index using a hash]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Start Using Chakra UI]]></title>
        <id>60977de12cd0545b5e944661</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-should-you-start-using-chakraui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T15:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll talk about what ChakraUI is and why you should use it.  Chakra UI is a component-based library. It's made up of basic building blocks that can help you build the front-end of your web application.  It is customizable and reusable, and most importantly it supports ReactJs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Gen CSS: @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-gen-css-container/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome is experimenting with @container, a property within the CSS Working Group Containment Level 3 spec being championed by Miriam Suzanne of Oddbird, and a group of engineers across the web platform. @container brings us the ability to &#8230;
The post Next Gen CSS: @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Una Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340106</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/distributed-persistent-rendering-dpr/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Jamstack, Netlify is coining this term.
If your reaction is: great, a new thing I need to know about and learn, know that while Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) does involve some new things, this is actually a push &#8230;
The post Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promises aren't just a way to deal with async operations...]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/promises-aren-t-just-a-way-to-deal-with-async-operations-18oi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sebastienfilion/promises-aren-t-just-a-way-to-deal-with-async-operations-18oi"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, hey there!
So you think you understand Promises, huh?
In JavaScript, Promises are both a way to handle asynchronous operations and a data structure.
This article is a transcript of a Youtube video I made.
Whether you are making a HTTP request, querying a database or writing to the console, I/O operations can
A good example of this is setTimeout. It's a function that takes another function as argument which will be
console.log("Before...");

setTimeout(() =&gt; console.log("...One second later"), 1000);
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastien Filion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes rocks - but non-boring solutions also have costs.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/gitlab/kubernetes-rocks-but-non-boring-solutions-also-have-costs-56j2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/gitlab/kubernetes-rocks-but-non-boring-solutions-also-have-costs-56j2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perspectives shared in "Honestly we shouldn't have used microservices" can also be applied to a) the pure operations side of b) off the shelf software c) that you self-manage. https://url2go.to/ei9]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darwin Sanoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's oak9?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bluegrounds/what-s-oak9-6a1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bluegrounds/what-s-oak9-6a1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us have experienced how liberating it is to use a Cloud Service Provider (AWS, Azure, etc.) to carry the weight of managing infrastructure for us, and how they let us instead focus on just building our application.
oak9 wants to give you the same efficiency and ease of mind but for your cloud infrastructure's security, where you delegate the process of keeping up with the changes of your app's infrastructure to oak9 and it makes sure that you application is always meeting the security requirements i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eyad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's oak9?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bluegrounds/what-s-oak9-6a1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bluegrounds/what-s-oak9-6a1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us have experienced how liberating it is to use a Cloud Service Provider (AWS, Azure, etc.) to carry the weight of managing infrastructure for us, and how they let us instead focus on just building our application.
oak9 wants to give you the same efficiency and ease of mind but for your cloud infrastructure's security, where you delegate the process of keeping up with the changes of your app's infrastructure to oak9 and it makes sure that you application is always meeting the security requirements i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eyad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project: Basic Authentication System]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ulzahk/project-basic-authentication-system-2mjp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ulzahk/project-basic-authentication-system-2mjp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Table Of Contents



Project Structure
Authentication Level Zero
Authentication Level One
Authentication Level One Advantages and Disadvantages
References
When you hear or see the word authentication you relate it to identification and that is a correct approach to this term. We just need to add permissions to perform a specific action in an app and we will have a more complete definition for the technology area.
In this project we are going to have a series of authentication systems in order to better unde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ulzahk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Good Typography - Free Treehouse Course]]></title>
        <id>60998ee76008950828b3ed10</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-design-good-typography/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typography is one of the most important aspects of good design. It is especially important for web designers. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all you need to know about creating good typography as a UX Designer. Hope Armstrong developed this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git-flow, non-technical intro.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/theowlsden/git-flow-non-technical-intro-3ahh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/theowlsden/git-flow-non-technical-intro-3ahh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Yancy Min on Unsplash
Howdy DEV clan? 
We've all heard of the recommendation and best practice: "Use a version control for your project." While this is true, it might save you from F*CK-ups, not many blogs proclaiming the use of version control mention how to use it or the best way to use it.
Here comes Git-flow. Git-flow is a git workflow you can use to streamline your use of version control for your whole application. In today's post, I'll go over the basics of Git-flow and how it can improve you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaquil Maria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[API Request Schema with Joi Validation in NodeJS and Express]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/api-request-schema-with-joi-validation-in-nodejs-and-express-kkf</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/api-request-schema-with-joi-validation-in-nodejs-and-express-kkf"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello readers, Today we are going to discuss one of the interesting topics - Joi Validation. You know when you are working on any platform and the platform asks for any user data like age, phone number, name, address, Pincode, state, etc. but due to hurry, many a time use enter the numerical data at the place of name, when the system expects alphabetic information. Even many times we make the mistake of entering the birthdate or Pincode, in the form of formatting or wrong information. Now, you don't want to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bacancy Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decode TOTP(Time-based One-time Password) QR Code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/iainrough/decode-totp-time-based-one-time-password-qr-code-3ed6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/iainrough/decode-totp-time-based-one-time-password-qr-code-3ed6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How not to do this.



DO NOT USE AN ONLINE SERVICE
  
While an online service such as https://webqr.com/ or https://www.qrstuff.com/scan are fine for normal QR codes they should never be used for TOTP QR Codes.
A TOTP QR code contains the following details (all values are placeholders).
Information from: oathtool
For more information visit oathtool
brew install zbar
sudo apt-get install zbarimg
/mnt/c/Users/rough$ zbarimg /mnt/c/tmp/a.png
otpauth://totp/hub.docker.com:{username}?algorithm=SHA1&amp;digits=6…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iainrough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript Interview Question: Select only the numbers in the array (with strange cases).]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lautarojayat/javascript-interview-question-select-only-the-numbers-in-the-array-with-strange-cases-1p50</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lautarojayat/javascript-interview-question-select-only-the-numbers-in-the-array-with-strange-cases-1p50"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article we will try to solve something that looks like a simple problem but can scale and become very strange deal. The problem is the following one:
let array = [1, 2, 3, '4', undefined, 'a', [], null];

If you have an array make a function that returns other array wich contains only numbers. The array is the following one:
But now they change the question and says: “Oh! but could you please also include numbers that were written as strings, like '2' or '404'?
First we could tryisNaN() , because is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lautaro Jayat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt's Tidbits #95 - Defining constants in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mpeng3/matt-s-tidbits-95-defining-constants-in-typescript-1163</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mpeng3/matt-s-tidbits-95-defining-constants-in-typescript-1163"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last time I wrote about how to write safe enums in TypeScript. This week's tidbit is also TypeScript related - how to define constants!
Defining a constant in TypeScript can be pretty simple - you can just write something like const SOME_CONSTANT="FOO";. However, that const keyword only works if you're defining variables at file-scope or inside a function. What if you want to group your constants under some kind of named object (as is common in other languages such as Java, C++, etc.)
The obvious way (and w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Groves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginners Introduction to Dockerfile]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohithv07/beginners-introduction-to-dockerfile-2kek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohithv07/beginners-introduction-to-dockerfile-2kek"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T12:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Dockerfile


A Dockerfile is a text document that contains all the commands a user could call on the command line to assemble an image.
A very basic Dockerfile will look like
# Use an existing docker image as a base
FROM alpine


# Download and install the dependency
RUN apk add --update redis


# Tell the image what to do when it starts as a container
CMD ["redis-server"]

It generally have 3 steps : 
FROM command which is to specify a base image


RUN command to download and install the dependan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohith V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 4 + Spring JPA + MySQL example | Angular 4 Http Client – Spring Boot RestApi Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-jpa-mysql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server-3eo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-jpa-mysql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server-3eo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/angular-4-spring-jpa-mysql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server
Angular 4 + Spring JPA + MySQL example | Angular 4 Http Client – Spring Boot RestApi Server
In this tutorial, ozenero shows you Angular 4 Http Client &amp; Spring Boot Server example that uses Spring JPA to interact with MySQL and Angular 4 as a front-end technology to make request and receive response.
Related Posts:
How to use Spring JPA MySQL | Spring Boot
How to use Angular Http Client to fetch Data f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to allow dynamic Terraform Provider Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/camptocamp-ops/how-to-allow-dynamic-terraform-provider-configuration-20ik</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/camptocamp-ops/how-to-allow-dynamic-terraform-provider-configuration-20ik"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform relies heavily on the concept of providers, a base brick which consists of Go plugins enabling the communication with an API.
Each provider gives access to one or more resource types, and these resources then manage objects on the target API.
Most of the time, a provider's configuration is static, e.g.
provider "aws" {
  region = "us-east-1"
}

However, in some cases, it is useful to configure a provider dynamically, using the attribute values from other resources as input for the provider's confi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raphaël Pinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to choose React JS or Angular UI Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nazneenprojects/when-to-choose-react-js-or-angular-ui-framework-16c5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nazneenprojects/when-to-choose-react-js-or-angular-ui-framework-16c5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I was going through React and Angular Comparison online (latest versions) &amp; found both are good fit for Web Application UI. While I was also wondering, there must be some differences which must be focused while deciding between two of them.
Lets suppose, I have one Java based web application with Spring MVC framework , Hibernate &amp; JSF/JSP. Assuming this application is doing massive backend operations &amp; displaying data on UI.
If in todays date, if I want to rebuild this type of applicati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am I the only one frustrated with oh-my-zsh?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/psiho/am-i-the-only-one-frustrated-with-oh-my-zsh-ne0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/psiho/am-i-the-only-one-frustrated-with-oh-my-zsh-ne0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel lonely :) Help me stop this feeling I'm the only one. Just switched from bash to zsh, and while I completely get why somebody would want to use oh-my-zsh, and I don't have anything against the project, it just seems like everybody is using it!? It's difficult to Google for any zsh configuration help/tutorials without ending up with oh-my-zsh. Again, it's not that oh-my-zsh itself bothers me, it bothers me that all my search results are infested with it :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mirko Vukušić</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipelines as Code (and some tips!) with Azure Pipelines YAML Multi-Stage Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudwithchris/pipelines-as-code-and-some-tips-with-azure-pipelines-yaml-multi-stage-pipelines-pol</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudwithchris/pipelines-as-code-and-some-tips-with-azure-pipelines-yaml-multi-stage-pipelines-pol"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard about Software Code or Infrastructure as Code. Well, in this video, we'll be talking about pipelines as code. If you're familiar with tools like Azure DevOps, Circle CI, GitHub, GitLab and Jenkins, you may notice a trend where these platforms are allowing you to define your pipelines as code. Throughout this video, we'll be defining a multi-stage pipeline in Azure DevOps, and picking up some tips along the way.
There is also a blog post available on the topic at cloudwithchris.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cloud With Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT MarketPlace Software]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/maticz/nft-marketplace-software-4617</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/maticz/nft-marketplace-software-4617"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT MarketPlace Software
NFT Marketplace Software is a readymade NFT Marketplace built with Blockchain technology to trade digital collectibles like music, art, game attributes, photography, metaverse, sports, etc. #Maticz offers White Label NFT MarketPlace Software that allows customization based on user requirements that allow users to buy, sell or list digital collectibles.
Benefits of NFT MarketPlace Software
NFT MarketPlace Clone
NFT MarketPlace Clone is a readymade Blockchain-powered NFT MarketPlace S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maticz Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to prevent folder to deploy on Azure app serive]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/keshav12345/how-to-prevent-folder-to-deploy-on-azure-app-serive-2ch</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/keshav12345/how-to-prevent-folder-to-deploy-on-azure-app-serive-2ch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I build a node js project for learning purpose and i deploy it on azure app serivce. It works fine, I don't face any kind of issue during deployment or after deployment. But i want to prevent or restrict a folder to not to deploy on azure app service during deployment. Suppose my folder name is logs. So how i prevent logs folder to not to deploy.
Can any one please help me on this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Kumar Naharwar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An automated quick-launch service for staging servers]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/evrone/an-automated-quick-launch-service-for-staging-servers-30a6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/evrone/an-automated-quick-launch-service-for-staging-servers-30a6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evrone focuses on project quality, and using DevOps tools has long been a part of our culture. Some clients even ask us to implement Evrone-style development management in their own companies.
When Docker was released, we immediately began testing new ways that we could use it to increase the quality and efficiency of our work. With Docker’s help, we developed the Teatro.io project, which automated the creation of test (stage) servers for the demonstration and testing of new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evrone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: template inside template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jrubzjeknf/angular-template-inside-template-287c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jrubzjeknf/angular-template-inside-template-287c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use a template inside a template to allow a parent component to replace a wrapper around important content.
See this stackblitz.
In my case, I have a highly reusable component with two important parts, which are tightly coupled. The issue arose when a wrapper around the second part needed to be replaced.

Here I want to be able to optionally replace the wrapper for part B, while being able to keep part B, like this.

For optionally replacing parts of a component, providing a template using a directi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jrubzjeknf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Node.js/Express REST API with MongoDB and Swagger]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mikefmeyer/build-a-node-js-express-rest-api-with-mongodb-and-swagger-3de9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mikefmeyer/build-a-node-js-express-rest-api-with-mongodb-and-swagger-3de9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will create a Movie Catchphrase API that allows you to Create, Read, Update and Delete Catchphrases, or in short perform CRUD operations. 
We are going to use Node.js and Express with Mongoose in order to interact with the MongoDB instance. We will use Swagger to document the API we created.
For this project I assume you already have set-up a MongoDB cluster (or a local MongoDB installation) and have the connection URI. If not you can refer to these links for a installation guide: MongoD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours &mdash; but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magento Developer Experience Level]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karlgorman6/magento-developer-experience-level-1b60</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karlgorman6/magento-developer-experience-level-1b60"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T09:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experience is always a crucial factor for employers to hire a candidate for a particular job role. Just like any of the roles in software development companies, employers also put forth varying experience requirements depending on the type of position and role they will play. Here’s a brief description of each category:
Junior
However, they ought to have basic knowledge of technologies associated with Magento eCommerce and aspects of testing. They should also be familiar with PHP, a programming language use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Gorman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 6 ElasticSearch example – simple Full Text Search]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-6-elasticsearch-example-simple-full-text-search-42jm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-6-elasticsearch-example-simple-full-text-search-42jm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T08:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/elasticsearch/angular-6-elasticsearch-example-simple-full-text-search
Angular 6 ElasticSearch example – simple Full Text Search
In the previous posts, we had know how to get All Documents in Index and show them with pagination. This tutorial show you way to implement a simple Full Text Search in an Angular 6 Application.
Related Posts:
Angular 6 ElasticSearch – Quick Start – How to add Elasticsearch.js
Angular 6 ElasticSearch example – Add Document to Index
Angular 6 ElasticSearch examp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Need To Know About Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/louiseelambertf/what-you-need-to-know-about-proxies-3e70</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/louiseelambertf/what-you-need-to-know-about-proxies-3e70"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T08:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People working in the corporate network environment will know and understand the meaning of ‘proxy server’ and that without it, it is impossible to access websites and other networks.
Most people have not about the term or may have come across it on the browsers of their devices but have never paid attention to its meaning.
This article is written specifically for them. This article will explain the benefits and the more reason why they should understand and use proxies.
A proxy server is an intermediary or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LouiseeLambertf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes: Apprentice Cookbook]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aveuiller/kubernetes-apprentice-cookbook-4j6h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aveuiller/kubernetes-apprentice-cookbook-4j6h"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T08:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably already heard of Kubernetes, a powerful orchestrator that will ease deployment and automatically manage your applications on a set of machines, called a Cluster.
With great power comes great complexity, even in the eyes of Google. Thus, learning Kubernetes is oftentimes considered as cumbersome and complex, namely because of the number of new concepts you have to learn. On the other hand, those very same concepts can be found in other orchestrators. As a result, mastering them will ease your on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Veuiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Techniques to scale your Relational Databases - Part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/techniques-to-scale-your-relational-databases-part-3-5flb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vishnuchilamakuru/techniques-to-scale-your-relational-databases-part-3-5flb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T07:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Techniques to scale your Relational Databases - Part 1
Vishnu Chilamakuru ・ May 7 ・ 3 min read
#database
        #architecture
        #performance
        #devops
      
Techniques to scale your Relational Databases - Part 2
Vishnu Chilamakuru ・ May 9 ・ 3 min read
#database
        #architecture
        #performance
        #devops
      
This blog post is a continuation of my previous blog posts mentioned above. In my previous posts, I mentioned Scaling Relational Databases using 
Replication
Federation
S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Chilamakuru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloud Resume Challenge (series): Part 13 - Monolithic vs Single Purposed Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/the-cloud-resume-challenge-series-part-13-monolithic-vs-single-purposed-functions-31kp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/the-cloud-resume-challenge-series-part-13-monolithic-vs-single-purposed-functions-31kp"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T06:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey cloud engineering friends! I've just hit publish on another episode in the series about the cloud resume challenge.
If you've not already heard of the cloud resume challenge, it's a free, online challenge started by the hero (AWS hero, and general cloud hero) Forest Brazeal to help people get into the cloud by giving you a real, hands-on project and challenge to complete. You can find the original announcement post here.
In the last few episodes we wrapped up building out the front-end and front-end inf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lou (🚀 Open Up The Cloud ☁️)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular DynamicDialog]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/angular-dynamicdialog-439</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/angular-dynamicdialog-439"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T06:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular DynamicDialog can be created dynamically with any component as the content using a DialogService.
Refer to PrimeNG setup documentation for download and installation steps for your environment.
import {DynamicDialogModule} from 'primeng/dynamicdialog';

Dynamic dialogs require an instance of a DialogService that is responsible for displaying a dialog with a component as its content. Since the dynamically loaded content is not defined at build time, a configuration is necessary using the entryComponen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular VirtualScroller]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/angular-virtualscroller-5cc1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/angular-virtualscroller-5cc1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T06:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular VirtualScroller is an efficient way of rendering lists by displaying a small subset of data in the viewport at any time.
VirtualScrolling depends on @angular/cdk's ScrollingModule so begin with installing CDK if not already installed.
npm install @angular/cdk --save

Refer to PrimeNG setup documentation for download and installation steps for your environment.
import {VirtualScrollerModule} from 'primeng/virtualscroller';

VirtualScroller requires a collection of items as its value, height of an ite…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[window manager (i3wm) screen share solution]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zzehli/window-manager-i3wm-screen-share-solution-2jm9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zzehli/window-manager-i3wm-screen-share-solution-2jm9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T04:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a desktop manager like windows and macOS, you can choose specific windows to share. But that is not an option in windows manager like i3. There is an advanced sharing option on zoom to only share part of the screen. Currently it is not working in my linux distro. So is there a way to work around this without second screen or complicated config?
Window managers usually have a notion of workspace that refers to windows groupings. You can only show the programs you need in a standalone workspace if you do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kabocha-Porter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with React.....]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joshboat365/getting-started-with-react-2i1l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joshboat365/getting-started-with-react-2i1l"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T04:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. You need to install node 
Now what is node: Node allows developers to write JavaScript code that runs directly in a computer process itself instead of in a browser. Node can, therefore, be used to write server-side applications with access to the operating system, file system, and everything else required to build fully-functional applications.
Click to install node: node
**Note: Download the LTS version of node that is compactible with every operating system**
node, check whether it has been installed b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Nyarko Boateng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iterating Through All an Array's Items Using For Loops]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rthefounding/iterating-through-all-an-array-s-items-using-for-loops-4g04</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rthefounding/iterating-through-all-an-array-s-items-using-for-loops-4g04"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T04:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when working with arrays, it is very handy to be able to iterate through each item to find one or more elements that we might need, or to manipulate an array based on which data items meet a certain set of criteria. The technique which is most flexible and offers us the greatest amount of control is a simple for loop.
Ex: I have defined a function, filteredArray, which takes arr, a nested array, and elem as arguments, and returns a new array. elem represents an element that may or may not be prese…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Randy Rivera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js : Scopes and repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-scopes-and-repositories-742</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-scopes-and-repositories-742"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T04:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Set the repository for the scope "myscope"
npm config set @myscope:registry http://registry.corporation.com

Login at a repository and associate it with the scope "myscope"
npm adduser --registry=http://registry.corporation.com --scope=@myscope

Install a package "mylib" from the scope "myscope"
npm install @myscope/mylib

All together will be -
# Set the repository for the scope "myscope"
npm config set @myscope:registry http://registry.corporation.com
# Login at a repository and associate it with the scop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js : Updating NPM and packages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-updating-npm-and-packages-298n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/node-js-updating-npm-and-packages-298n"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T03:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since npm itself is a Node.js module, it can be updated using itself.
npm install -g npm@latest

If you want to check for updated versions you can do:
npm outdated

In order to update a specific package:
npm update &lt;package name&gt;

This will update the package to the latest version according to the restrictions in package.json
In case you also want to lock the updated version in package.json:
npm update &lt;package name&gt; --save


With all that being said, I highly recommend you keep learning!
Thank …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js: Listing currently installed NPM packages]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/npm-listing-currently-installed-packages-3gd4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rajeshkumaryadavdotcom/npm-listing-currently-installed-packages-3gd4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T03:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To generate a list (tree view) of currently installed packages, use
npm list

ls, la and ll are aliases of list command. la and ll commands shows extended information like description and repository.
The response format can be changed by passing options.
npm list --json

json - Shows information in json format
long - Shows extended information
parseable - Shows parseable list instead of tree
global - Shows globally installed packages
depth - Maximum display depth of dependency tree
dev/development - Shows d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajesh Kumar Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/10 TIL]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davidhwangij/5-10-til-1nd7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davidhwangij/5-10-til-1nd7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T03:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tsconfig.json configuration: 


"noEmit": true will not have Typescript emit Javascript out after compilation
https://www.sitepoint.com/react-with-typescript-best-practices/
react-app-env.d.ts references the types of react-scripts, and helps with things like allowing for SVG imports
React.ReactNode vs. React.FC


function Heading(): React.ReactNode { return hello }
const HeadingTwo: React.FC = () ⇒ hello
using string literal type for useReducer (described in the link above)
npm vs npx vs yarn


npx only exe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hwang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melhores maneiras de usar middlewares no express.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shougnaii/melhores-maneiras-de-usar-middlewares-no-express-js-mc9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shougnaii/melhores-maneiras-de-usar-middlewares-no-express-js-mc9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T01:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atualmente,express.js é um dos frameworks mais utilizados em aplicações node.js.
Você vai precisar instalar node em sua máquina e em seguida criar um projeto utilizando npm ou yarn
Escolha uma pasta e dentro dela, via terminal:
npm init -y ou yarn init -y
Vamos instalar o express e o morgan como dependências do projeto.
npm install express morgan --save
Crie um arquivo index.js e cole o seguinte código:
Segundo a própria documentação sobre middlewares: "um aplicativo express é uma série de chamadas de funçõ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caio frias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Your First Developer Job through Intelligent, Genuine Networking]]></title>
        <id>605cf4879618b008528a77e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/networking-for-aspiring-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T01:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's not about what you know, it's about whom you know." "70-80% of jobs are found via someone's network." Most of us have heard cliches and stats like the above. And I think most of us intuitively know that having a network of people that can help us find opportunities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable forms - React-TS - in 2 custom hooks and 1 object]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/georgexx009/scalable-forms-react-ts-in-2-custom-hooks-and-1-object-2p4c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/georgexx009/scalable-forms-react-ts-in-2-custom-hooks-and-1-object-2p4c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T22:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR


We are going to have an array of objects that defines our form. The properties from the objects are going to be the properties from the inputs from our form. These objects should have the same interface. The array could be store in the back-end or in a directory in the front-end, its up to you.
Then we are going to have a hook which return an object that will map the properties from the object properties one by one and returns the input component with the properties that we passed. For handle the fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emmanuel Galindo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🆔 Identity, Unlocked... Explained: Season 2, Ep 7]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-7-21jb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/robertinoc_dev/identity-unlocked-explained-season-2-ep-7-21jb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🛡 Identity protocols for internet browsers with Sam Goto (Google Chrome) and George Fletcher (Verizon)



  
  
  
In this episode of Identity, Unlocked, principal architect at Auth0 and podcast host Vittorio Bertocci speaks with Sam Goto, software engineer working on Google Chrome, and George Fletcher, Identity Standards architect at Verizon, on the ever-changing world of identity protocols for internet browsers.
Sam focuses on working with browsers to create better functionality in their foundation proto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robertino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topframe]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/topframe/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is extremely fun. Jeff Lindsay has created Topframe, and writes:
Anybody that knows how to mess around with HTML can now mess around with their desktop computing experience.&#160;Topframe&#160;is an open source tool that lets you 
&#8230;
The post Topframe appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340208</id>
        <link href="https://benfrain.com/migrating-from-parcel-to-snowpack-build-tool-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find build tooling endlessly interesting, especially right now as we&#8217;re in a juicy next-gen transitional period with players like Vite, wmr, Snowpack, and esbuild. Hugh Haworth has a good run-down of the new players, and we&#8217;ve chatted on &#8230;
The post Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XSS Attacks Types on Web]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/obetomuniz/xss-attacks-types-on-web-36mh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/obetomuniz/xss-attacks-types-on-web-36mh"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know how each Cross-Site Scripting Attack behaves is crucial to start to think about how vulnerabilities in our web apps allow malicious codes to be executed using the browser to take sensible data from users.
That's what this article is about. 
🔓 Reflected XSS
📌 This attack XSS use URL parameters or data submitted via POST in forms to inject malicious code on that server request that persists some data for later execution in the browser. Third-party Browser extensions could even be an access point to inj…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beto Muniz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symmetric v/s Asymmetric Encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ssukhpinder/symmetric-v-s-asymmetric-encryption-nkn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ssukhpinder/symmetric-v-s-asymmetric-encryption-nkn"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T20:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# CONCEPTS



  
  
  Symmetric encryption is performed on streams whereas asymmetric encryption works on a small number of bytes.



  
  
  What is Encryption?


Encryption means the conversion of data to symbols so that its contents cannot be understood if intercepted.
There are mainly two types of encryption techniques:
Symmetric Encryption


Asymmetric Encryption




  
  
  What is Symmetric Encryption?


Symmetric encryption is executed on streams and therefore, it’s useful to encrypt vast volumes o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sukhpinder Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular simple form with async testing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/angular-simple-form-with-async-testing-227m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/angular-simple-form-with-async-testing-227m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topic


The developer should test the code. In this example, I will create a simple form with an HTTP request after submission and test.
I used Angular CLI to create the project (default CLI answers):
ng new notification-example

I used Material Angular to provide propper styling by typing (default answers):
ng add @angular/material 

To be able to use required Material modules I added them in imports in AppModule:
  imports: [
    BrowserModule,
    BrowserAnimationsModule,
    ReactiveFormsModule,
    Htt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomasz Flis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular simple form with async testing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/angular-simple-form-with-async-testing-227m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomwebwalker/angular-simple-form-with-async-testing-227m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topic


The developer should test the code. In this example, I will create a simple form with an HTTP request after submission and test.
I used Angular CLI to create the project (default CLI answers):
ng new notification-example

I used Material Angular to provide propper styling by typing (default answers):
ng add @angular/material 

To be able to use required Material modules I added them in imports in AppModule:
  imports: [
    BrowserModule,
    BrowserAnimationsModule,
    ReactiveFormsModule,
    Htt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomasz Flis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting Errors Before Running Code With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mxkvl/detecting-errors-before-running-code-with-typescript-44e4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mxkvl/detecting-errors-before-running-code-with-typescript-44e4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem


In the previous post we talked about what is TypeScript and why should we use that. Now it's time to go to practice.
We need to know how to start using TypeScript in our JavaScript project. In examples of this post series, I will use mostly code that written in Node environment. It won't be any specific code that is understandable for only developers who worked with Node before. Because this material is about TypeScript I want to specify more on TypeScript itself. 
Okay, let's start with an in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kovalevsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how does antivirus work?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vspranav21/how-does-antivirus-work-953</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vspranav21/how-does-antivirus-work-953"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antivirus software scans program using selected chunk of data from its database. If it gets a code that resembles to that of a malware stored in its database then that code is flagged as malware. Now this is either isolated or deleted

Features of Antivirus Software

Complete System Scans. these scans are not much needed if there is on hand access feature on the system.it is well used if the anti-virus is installed for the first time or the security of the system is not updated for long time .this is implem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vspranav21</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Component-Based Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/component-based-forms-11he</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/component-based-forms-11he"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | Mar 2020
Reactive sub-forms implemented with independent, highly re-usable Angular Components
This article was inspired by a recent discussion with a manager regarding how to integrate someone with a math/Aerospace Engineering background (that would be me) into a group that worked on heavily form-based applications. I inquired about the nature of their forms and they were mostly very long and complex, a few of which required a bit of math in the process of validation. The manager w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Component-Based Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ngconf/component-based-forms-11he</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ngconf/component-based-forms-11he"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T18:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Armstrong | ng-conf | Mar 2020
Reactive sub-forms implemented with independent, highly re-usable Angular Components
This article was inspired by a recent discussion with a manager regarding how to integrate someone with a math/Aerospace Engineering background (that would be me) into a group that worked on heavily form-based applications. I inquired about the nature of their forms and they were mostly very long and complex, a few of which required a bit of math in the process of validation. The manager w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ng-conf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did my Java Web App stop working with MySQL!?!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stevesmashcode/why-did-my-java-web-app-stop-working-with-mysql-1oig</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stevesmashcode/why-did-my-java-web-app-stop-working-with-mysql-1oig"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are different kinds of bugs and they show up in different places.  This bug was hard because it showed up where we didn't expect it.  
We noticed last week that our Java web app deployments to kubernetes (k8s) stopped working last week.  It started with a smaller team that did a deployment (to non-prod).  The error started with a failed deployment.  We use liveliness and readiness probes to help k8s let us know if the application is running correctly.  Our liveliness probe was failing.  That's strange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>STeve Shary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ace Your Coding Interview – Advice from a Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>60953e202cd0545b5e943a8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-acing-your-coding-interview-advice-from-senior-software-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T17:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical interviews are one of the most stressful parts of landing a job in tech.  You don't know what questions the interviewer is going to ask. What if you have no idea how to solve the problem in front of you? What if you freeze up and look like you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 THINGS I HATE ABOUT WINDOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saimanojk/4-things-i-hate-about-windows-2nk7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saimanojk/4-things-i-hate-about-windows-2nk7"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T15:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 has improved a lot since its 2015 release, but it has a long way to go
 DESIGN: 

Starting off number one is Design
PRIVACY AND DATA CONTROL:

It seems to me that the biggest Flaw that many people point to on Windows 10 is Privacy and Data control and also the forced updates, especially combined with poor quality control on those updates. You probably have heard that windows 10 "spy" on you and collects all sorts of information. Even if its a rumor but it will affect us.
CORTANA:

RESTARTING ISSU…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KARTALA SAI MANOJ 221910302024</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My approach to the command line]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kalabro/my-approach-to-the-command-line-1kfm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kalabro/my-approach-to-the-command-line-1kfm"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an idea that every developer should master tons of sophisticated tools and keyboard shortcuts to be truly professional and efficient. 
My experience doesn't confirm it. As an example, let me show you my command line setup. I'm not a sysadmin, but as a full stack developer with 10+ years of experience I use the terminal on a daily basis yet I've got a very basic setup:
No tmux
No aliases
No special .dotfile configs
No shell preference. I'm fine with zsh, bash, ksh, etc
No jokes on how to quit vim 🔫…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339203</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/variable-aspect-ratio-card-with-conic-gradients-meeting-along-the-diagonal/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across an interesting problem. I had to implement a grid of cards with a variable (user-set) aspect ratio that was stored in a --ratio custom property. Boxes with a certain aspect ratio are a classic problem in &#8230;
The post Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I made a Spotify web clone with React, Typescript and SCSS]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bastiendmt/i-made-a-spotify-web-clone-with-react-typescript-and-scss-557b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bastiendmt/i-made-a-spotify-web-clone-with-react-typescript-and-scss-557b"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello friend !
Here is the app i made : Spoty-like
spotify-like-web
I made this project as close as I could to the real Spotify. My goal was to make my app indistinguishable from the real version. I've had to copy some css but it allowed me to understand how to do certain tricks and how complex the real app was.
The project features two pages : 
Browsing featured playlists
Browsing songs within a specific playlist
On the tech side, I started it with JSX but mid-way through the project, I figured that it was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bastien Dumont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Commands Cheat Sheet]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/soniarpit/linux-commands-cheat-sheet-150c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/soniarpit/linux-commands-cheat-sheet-150c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This commands helps you anytime
Basic Linux commands


Command
Description



ls
Lists all files and directories in the present working directory


ls-R
Lists files in sub-directories as well


ls-a
Lists hidden files as well


ls-al
Lists files and directories with detailed information like permissions,size, owner, etc.


cd or cd ~
Navigate to HOME directory


cd ..
Move one level up


cd
To change to a particular directory


cd /
Move to the root directory


cat &gt; filename
Creates a new file


cat fil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CodeSnail 🐌</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regular Expression Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thomasstep/regular-expression-vulnerability-406o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thomasstep/regular-expression-vulnerability-406o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T13:23:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I stumbled across something interesting the other day that I dove into and wanted to share. There exists a vulnerability called ReDos (Regular expression Denial of Service) which results from a poorly written regular expression taking a long time to complete matching. If an attacker can determine that a regex has been written with this type of vulnerability, they can exploit the long running times to block processes. Since regexes are used for loads of different web services nowadays, I think it is importan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Step</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MultipartFile – How to create Spring AngularJs MultipartFile application to download/upload files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/multipartfile-how-to-create-spring-angularjs-multipartfile-application-to-download-upload-files-4c1o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/multipartfile-how-to-create-spring-angularjs-multipartfile-application-to-download-upload-files-4c1o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T12:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://grokonez.com/spring-framework/spring-boot/multipartfile-create-spring-angularjs-multipartfile-application-downloadupload-files-springboot-angularjs-bootstrap
MultipartFile – How to create Spring AngularJs MultipartFile application to download/upload files | SpringBoot + AngularJs + Bootstrap.
In the past post, we had learned how to upload MultipartFile with SpringBoot and JQuery Ajax. Today, JavaSampleApproach shows how to create a Spring AngularJs MultipartFile application to download/upload file w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding port "8080/tcp" using UFW]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/adding-port-8080-tcp-using-ufw-4bbe</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/adding-port-8080-tcp-using-ufw-4bbe"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there!!1 
how to add the port 8080/tcp in my system and list all the active ports in a text file called "zones.txt". I use a Linux Mint 20.1 XFCE system and I came across the apt-package named Uncomplicated Firewall. This package allows you to open ports on your system and makes them ready for use using ssh. 
Here is a screenshot on how to progress with the procedures.

I am also attaching my GitHub gist which provides an detailed explanation on how to implement this in your system.



  

 


  
  
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritabrata Das</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do I exit the Vim editor?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/how-do-i-exit-the-vim-editor-529f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/how-do-i-exit-the-vim-editor-529f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T10:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you stuck in vim and cannot exit? 
Vim is a powerful text editor, but if you are new to vim it may seem very confusing.
Personally I use the command ZZ to exit. This saves the file and exists. I use this all the time because what is simpler than pressing Z twice?
Vim works using commands. Before you enter a command, hit the Esc key. 
You can exit without saving your changes with :q!. This is useful if you accidentally modified a file you didn't want to.
If you don't want to quit without saving, instead …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Captcha]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/primetek/angular-captcha-abg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/primetek/angular-captcha-abg"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Captcha is a form validation component based on Recaptcha.
Refer to PrimeNG setup documentation for download and installation steps for your environment.
import {CaptchaModule} from 'primeng/captcha';

Captcha is used with a siteKey and a callback to verify the response.
&lt;p-captcha siteKey="YOUR_SITE_KEY" (onResponse)="showResponse($event)"&gt;&lt;/p-captcha&gt;

In addition include the captcha widget resource to your page.
&lt;script src="https://www.google.com/recaptcha/api.js?render=explicit&a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PrimeTek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (&lt;time&gt;) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 4 + Spring JPA + PostgreSQL example | Angular 4 Http Client – Spring Boot RestApi Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-jpa-postgresql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server-273f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/angular-4-spring-jpa-postgresql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server-273f"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/angular-4-spring-jpa-postgresql-example-angular-4-http-client-spring-boot-restapi-server
Angular 4 + Spring JPA + PostgreSQL example | Angular 4 Http Client – Spring Boot RestApi Server
In this tutorial, ozenero shows you Angular 4 Http Client &amp; Spring Boot Server example that uses Spring JPA to interact with PostgreSQL and Angular 4 as a front-end technology to make request and receive response.
Related Posts:
How to use Spring JPA with PostgreSQL | Spring Boot
Spring JPA + PostgreS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django + Angular 6 example | Django Rest Framework + MySQL CRUD example – Part 2: Django Server]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loizenai/django-angular-6-example-django-rest-framework-mysql-crud-example-part-2-django-server-bbb</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loizenai/django-angular-6-example-django-rest-framework-mysql-crud-example-part-2-django-server-bbb"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T07:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://ozenero.com/django-angular-6-example-django-rest-framework-mysql-crud-example-part-2-django-server
Django + Angular 6 example | Django Rest Framework + MySQL CRUD example – Part 2: Django Server
This tutorial is part 2 of Django-Angular-MySQL series. Today, we will create Django server to do CRUD with MySQL (including finder method).
&gt;&gt; Part 1: Overview
Part 3: Angular Client
Related Post:
Django RestApis example – GET/POST/PUT/DELETE requests MySQL database with Django REST Framework
Video
Dj…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loizenai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Video] Manage configuration and multiple environments in Node.JS with Foal]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/loicpoullain/video-manage-configuration-and-multiple-environments-in-node-js-with-foal-j0m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/loicpoullain/video-manage-configuration-and-multiple-environments-in-node-js-with-foal-j0m"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T07:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial describes how to manage configuration with Foal across one or more environments using:
JSON, YAML and JS files,
.env files
and environment variables.
It also explains how to check and convert the types of configuration values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Loïc Poullain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Code Analyses - Terrascan, Terraform and Azure DevOps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/officialcookj/static-code-analyses-terrascan-terraform-and-azure-devops-3690</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/officialcookj/static-code-analyses-terrascan-terraform-and-azure-devops-3690"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T06:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous post I looked at Static Code Analyses with two of the three tools I am going to use in this post. We are now going to look at Terrascan as our analyses tool and have it running from CI/CD platform Azure DevOps which will also host the Terraform code we want to review.
To follow with the post in configuring this setup, you will need the above mentioned tools with permissions on Azure DevOps to be able to create a Pipeline, add extensions from a marketplace and commit to a repository.
As per my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Install latex with Tinytex]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zzehli/install-latex-with-tinytex-1a5c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zzehli/install-latex-with-tinytex-1a5c"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T06:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tinytex is a relative new Latex distribution by Yihui Xie from the R community. The distribution is tiny, less than 100mb, which is a great alternative to TexLive and MikTex for basic users. I this post, I will show how to install Tinytex as a standalone package independent of R for more general latex workflow.
To install Tinytex on a Linux distribution, run the following command to download and install Tinytex, as indicated in the website:
wget -qO- "https://yihui.org/tinytex/install-bin-unix.sh" | sh

Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kabocha-Porter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Como personalizar tu terminal utilizando oh-my-zsh con powerlevel10k 👨‍💻]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/christopherjael/como-personalizar-tu-terminal-utilizando-oh-my-zsh-con-powerlevel10k-4bdi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/christopherjael/como-personalizar-tu-terminal-utilizando-oh-my-zsh-con-powerlevel10k-4bdi"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T06:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Siempre llega el momento donde queremos personalizar nuestra terminal ya sea porque nos parece poco atractiva o queremos mayor funcionalidad para aumentar la productividad a la hora de utilizarla. Aunque el punto fuerte de las Terminales no sea su apartado estético ni las extensas utilidades. Pero eso no quiere decir, que no podamos hacer algo al respecto 🙋.
Para darle un powerup 💯 a la terminal solo necesitaremos los siguientes requisitos:
Equipo con Sistema linux 🐧


Fedora
Debian
Ubuntu
Arch Linux
ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Montero D'oleo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to lit-html.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/anuragvohraec/introduction-to-lit-html-js-55ko</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/anuragvohraec/introduction-to-lit-html-js-55ko"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T03:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[lit-html is a templating library.
Templating Library helps you create DOM nodes/element at runtime.
If you have to create a DOM node tree like this at run time:
&lt;body&gt;
    &lt;!--START: create this at run time and append to body--&gt;
    &lt;div id="myid1"&gt;
        &lt;div style="width:50px;height:50px:background-color:red;"&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;!--END--&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;

Ordinarily without any templating library, you would have written a JS code something like this(n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anurag Vohra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[𝖜𝖍𝖆𝖙 𝖈𝖆𝖓 𝖇𝖊 𝖉𝖔𝖓𝖊]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mikejason91/-4nl0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mikejason91/-4nl0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T03:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is too short to do everything you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Jason (MJ)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nginx HTTP Basic Authentication(Kimlik Doğrulama) Kurulumu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aslanfatih/nginx-http-basic-authentication-kimlik-dogrulama-kurulumu-445o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aslanfatih/nginx-http-basic-authentication-kimlik-dogrulama-kurulumu-445o"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T14:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aşağıdaki paketlerin kurulumunu gerçekleştirin.
Ubuntu;
sudo apt install nginx apache2-utils

Redhat/CentOS;
yum install epel-release nginx httpd-tools

Nginx “/etc/nginx/sites-available/sites.conf” altındaki kaynak konfig dosyası “/etc/nginx/sites-enabled/sites.conf” altında link’li olduğunu düşünerek, Yapılandırma şekli aşağıdaki gibi yapılabilir.
İlk önce aşağıdaki komutları yürütün,
- mkdir /www/sites/indexpage
- mkdir /www/sites/files
- mkdir /www/sites/files/exclude
- echo “Welcome to nginx” &gt; /www…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatih ASLAN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i3 Ricing]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/i3-ricing-19ih</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ritabratadas343/i3-ricing-19ih"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T14:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello guys!!!
Linux Mint 20.1 XFCE using the i3-window manager. Developers mostly use upgraded ricing tools like the Awesome window manager for their ricing models. Ricing in Arch-based systems is comparatively easier than in Ubuntu-based systems. Although, I preferred i3-window manager as it is good for beginners and we get to build the ricing model from scratch. 
My Ricing model is uploaded on YouTube on my friend's channel:
i3-riced model 




The configuration file for the ricing model is uploaded on Gi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritabrata Das</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How useful is learning VI/VIM for a new programmer?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jones268/how-useful-is-learning-vi-vim-for-a-new-programmer-1h57</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jones268/how-useful-is-learning-vi-vim-for-a-new-programmer-1h57"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T13:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been using a text editor called "vim" for more than a year now, and it has changed my programming life. Let's take a look.
If you are going to be writing code in Python, then it would be useful to learn to use a text editor called "Vim". I don't say that because I wrote the book on this topic (I didn't), but because it will help you be more efficient as a programmer. 
Vim is an extremely powerful text editor used by programmers and system administrators around the world. Often described as a "programme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jones268</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access Key Vault secret from Web Application]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivappa/access-key-vault-secret-from-web-application-4nem</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivappa/access-key-vault-secret-from-web-application-4nem"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T08:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous parts we have learnt how to create Azure Key Vault and how to add the principal in Azure Key Vault by whom it must be accessed.
Let's write a simple flask app to fetch the secrets from Key Vault.
KeyVaultDemo on your computer and open it in VS Code.
requirements.txt which contains the packages required.
flask
azure-keyvault-secrets
azure-identity


azure-keyvault-secrets: It is a client library in python to access the secrets stored in Azure Key Vault. More information on this package can be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivappa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand and use Azure Key Vault Easily (Most Secured Secrets Storage)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shivappa/understand-and-use-azure-key-vault-easily-most-secured-secrets-storage-19n0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shivappa/understand-and-use-azure-key-vault-easily-most-secured-secrets-storage-19n0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-09T06:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now a days the term security becoming the must follow topic for all the organizations to have a good brand name.
To solve this issue we can use Azure Key Vault resource.
Securely store the keys, secrets and certificates.
Only authorized user can access the key vault.
Frequently rotate the secrets, keys.
Automatically renew the certificates.
Centralized storage for all keys, secrets and certificates.
Azure Key Vault can be used in many services, here I will be showing how to use it in Azure app service.
Prer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shivappa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Systems Book Recommendations – Learn How to Build and Understand ML Systems]]></title>
        <id>609558382cd0545b5e943c6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/machine-learning-systems-book-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T21:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life.” ― Mark TwainI hope you’re reading this blog in your pjs looking forward to a rejuvenating and healthy weekend.  I have been working on multiple projects lately, from creating Machine Learing Engineering and Machine Learning Operations courses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recursion Might Seem Scary – But it Doesn&#x27;t Have to Be]]></title>
        <id>609551f02cd0545b5e943bc0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/recursion-doesnt-have-to-be-scary/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T16:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any concept that we don't fully understand can be scary at first. Recursion is a topic that programming students don't learn right away. But that doesn't mean it needs to be scary or cause anxiety. In fact, recursion is a concept that we can define rather simply. According to Wikipedia:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CSS a Programming Language?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339781</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-css-a-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a real distaste for this question. It might seem like a fun question to dig into on the surface, but the way it enters public discourse rarely seems to be in good faith. There are ulterior motives at &#8230;
The post Is CSS a Programming Language? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are a few great links about typography that have been burning a hole in my saved bookmarks folder that I'm just now getting around to sharing. There's good stuff in there, from how to choose typefaces for app design to ideas for how to fix the concept of font sizing in CSS.
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Email…]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339822</id>
        <link href="https://www.caniemail.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T02:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I&#8217;m 85% certain you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Use&#8230;, I bet there is only a 13% chance that you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Email&#8230;. It&#8217;s the same vibe—detailed support information for web platform features—except instead &#8230;
The post Can I Email&#8230; appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is &quot;Lifting State Up&quot; in React?]]></title>
        <id>609409c201fc34080ef81f97</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-lifting-state-up-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T21:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a simple and practical example what it means to "lift state up" in React, and how it can help you build your applications. Lifting state up is a common pattern that is essential for React developers to know. It helps you avoid more complex (and often unnecessary) patterns]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently, You Can Use Route53 as a Blazingly Fast Database]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340015</id>
        <link href="https://betterprogramming.pub/apparently-you-can-use-route53-as-a-blazingly-fast-database-dd416b56b005"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T20:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Route53 is DNS management service by AWS. DNS is absolutely not a database, and yet here&#8217;s Nicholas Martin writing up some very clever trickery originally done by Corey Quinn:
When you think about it, DNS configuration is actually a 
&#8230;
The post Apparently, You Can Use Route53 as a Blazingly Fast Database appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Google’s New Page Experience Update Means for Images on Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339936</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-googles-new-page-experience-update-means-for-images-on-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T19:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to forget that, as a search engine, Google doesn’t just compare keywords to generate search results. Google knows that if people don’t enjoy their experience on a web page, they won’t stay on the page long enough to &#8230;
The post What Google’s New Page Experience Update Means for Images on Your Website appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use the Chrome DevTools to Troubleshoot Websites]]></title>
        <id>609415eb2cd0545b5e943534</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-use-the-chrome-devtools-to-troubleshoot-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome DevTools is a set of web developer tools built directly into the Google Chrome browser. They can be super helpful for web developers. We just published a crash course that will teach you how to use Chrome DevTools to improve your productivity as a web developer. You will learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optional Types in Swift – How to Use and Unwrap Optionals]]></title>
        <id>60939bde01fc34080ef81a19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optional-types-in-swift/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're coming from Java, C++, or other object-oriented languages, chances are that you've never come across optional types or "optionals". And you might be quite surprised to know that such a concept exists in Swift. Optionals are a fundamental topic that you need to thoroughly understand to code in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom State Pseudo-Classes in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339586</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/custom-state-pseudo-classes-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T14:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an increasing number of “custom” features on the web platform. We have custom properties (--my-property), custom elements (&#60;my-element&#62;), and custom events (new CustomEvent('myEvent')). At one point, we might even get custom media &#8230;
The post Custom State Pseudo-Classes in Chrome appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astro]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339563</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/astro/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T21:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can&#8217;t even look at code or documentation for Astro (publicly) yet — it&#8217;s an in-progress idea — but you can watch a video of Fred showing it off to Feross. 
I gotta admit: it looks awesome. I&#8217;m bullish &#8230;
The post Astro appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Delayed Is Progress Denied]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339954</id>
        <link href="https://infrequently.org/2021/04/progress-delayed/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T16:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bombshell article of the week is from Alex Russell of Google/Chrome. Alex has long been super critical of Apple, particularly about how there is literally no option to run any other browser than Safari on iOS. This article isn&#8217;t &#8230;
The post Progress Delayed Is Progress Denied appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Vendor Prefixing Dead?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339518</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-vendor-prefixing-dead/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T14:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let‘s take a quick stroll down memory-lane to revisit how vendor prefixing CSS properties came to be. I hope I don’t trigger PTSD for anyone!
It‘s not clear who started prefixing, or when it began exactly. What is clear, is &#8230;
The post Is Vendor Prefixing Dead? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob O'Leary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Avoid crwalers.
Fixed: Error logging from XML parser.
Fixed: Typo in docs.
Thank you: @dym-sh, @tabokie, @cheese1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.3.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Customize cache lifespan with cacheMaxDays property in osmosfeed.yaml.
Added: Documentation for osmosfeed.yaml.
Fixed: More intuitive logging during build.
Chore: Refactored parameter passing for enrich step.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.3"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: favicon update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.2.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.2.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Display CLI version in footer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.6]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.6"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: The output website didn't have favicon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Item description didn't use the description property from feed item.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.1.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T05:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: MIT license
Added: cache.json is stamped with the version of the builder. This allows future builder with breaking change to ignore incompatible cache.
Added: Feed source retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Item enrichment retry on fetch error (3 times total, 15 seconds timeout).
Added: Console log for cache restore and update behavior.
Added: npx command: npx osmosfeed
Changed: Improved console log that breaks down rendered item count into "new" and "cached".
Fixed: Item…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16px or Larger Text Prevents iOS Form Zoom]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339455</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/16px-or-larger-text-prevents-ios-form-zoom/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T21:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was a great &#8220;Today I Learned&#8221; for me from Josh W. Comeau. If the font-size of an &#60;input&#62; is 16px or larger, Safari on iOS will focus into the input normally. But as soon as the font-size is &#8230;
The post 16px or Larger Text Prevents iOS Form Zoom appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early &mdash; when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Mistakes To Avoid In Your Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that the technical interview process leaves something to be desired; it’s often riddled with anxiety and stress. In this article, we’ll take a look at seven of the most common mistakes candidates make in their technical interviews and explore ways you can avoid them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emma Bostian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Web Design Clients Fast (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling is key to growing your web design business, but it doesn’t have to be complicated! With clear goals, customer research, and proven closing techniques, anyone can find new clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephen Roe)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cats With Love: New Navigation, Guides And Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Smashing, we’ve been busy over the last few months. We’ve set up new workshops, redesigned our navigation, refined performance and improved accessibility. There are subtle UX changes coming in, and we’d love to share what we’ve been cooking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overflow Issues In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/css-overflow-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/css-overflow-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore the causes of overflow issues and how to solve them. We will also explore how modern features in the developer tools (DevTools) can make the process of fixing and debugging easier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Video Streaming App With Nuxt.js, Node And Express]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/building-video-streaming-app-nuxtjs-node-express/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/building-video-streaming-app-nuxtjs-node-express/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-13T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building a video streaming app using Nuxt.js and Node.js. Specifically, we’ll build a server-side Node.js app that will handle fetching and streaming videos, generating thumbnails for your videos, and serving captions and subtitles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Deven Rathore)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To HTML Email]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-html-email-templates-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-html-email-templates-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently we’ve covered CSS generators, SVG generators and accessible front-end components. This time we look into HTML email, with tools, templates and guides for designers and developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>