<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-09-28T01:03:15.241Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-28T01:03:15.241Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Status Modal HOC]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/brunofrigeri/global-status-modal-hoc-24of</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/brunofrigeri/global-status-modal-hoc-24of"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T00:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I was having a problem in my current job, that basically we were refactoring stuffs in our code, and one of them was the Status Screen.
How to have a global Status for our API responses, without to have it as a Screen?
The response takes a bit to come for me, but, at evening the light came, why not use a High Order Component to get around this problem?!
So, let's start doing it, first and formals, we are going to use React Native (Expo Bare-Workflow), to be able to get our results more quickly, but the same can be achieved using React Native CLI.
First, we're going to init our project, as I'm using Expo, I'll do:
expo init

After that, I'm going to select my workflow, based on expo. So I'll select:
minimal (TypeScript)  same as minimal but with TypeScript configuration 

Okay, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Frigeri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Repo Guide – How to Increase Engagement on your Public GitHub Repositories]]></title>
        <id>6149e65e9456b407b870fdc5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/increase-engagement-on-your-public-github-repositories/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-28T00:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub is a collection of web-based tools that helps you work with version control and Git methodologies.  With the help of GitHub, you can create, manage, and collaborate on projects with multiple other team members. You keep the project folders and files in a store (file system) on GitHub. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building ToDo in Real-Time]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ivanz123/building-todo-in-real-time-3pbl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ivanz123/building-todo-in-real-time-3pbl"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T22:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to start with a question Have you ever wondered how applications such as Messenger, WhatsApp can update new messages without the need to refresh the page? Well, in this article we are developing a ToDo with real-time communication so that you can better understand how it works.
The end of this tutorial you will have the following result.

Have Node.js installed.
Have a code editor installed (in my case VSCode)
Create a project on my desktop with the name we want to assign it.
mkdir todo-realtime
cd todo-realtime
code .
Execute the following commands.
npm init -y
tsc --init
npm init -y: This command generate a file named package.json in the root of the project, this file contains all the necessary settings for your application to work properly. For more information https://docs.npmjs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Zadivar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building ToDo in Real-Time]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ivanz123/building-todo-in-real-time-3pbl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ivanz123/building-todo-in-real-time-3pbl"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T22:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to start with a question Have you ever wondered how applications such as Messenger, WhatsApp can update new messages without the need to refresh the page? Well, in this article we are developing a ToDo with real-time communication so that you can better understand how it works.
The end of this tutorial you will have the following result.

Have Node.js installed.
Have a code editor installed (in my case VSCode)
Create a project on my desktop with the name we want to assign it.
mkdir todo-realtime
cd todo-realtime
code .
Execute the following commands.
npm init -y
tsc --init
npm init -y: This command generate a file named package.json in the root of the project, this file contains all the necessary settings for your application to work properly. For more information https://docs.npmjs…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ivan Zadivar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favicon for Next.js and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jcubic/favicon-for-next-js-and-typescript-9gk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jcubic/favicon-for-next-js-and-typescript-9gk"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T20:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm still learning Next.js and after having hard time to find out of the box solution to create favicon that will work everywhere, after done this myself, I've decided to create quick article about this.
Favicon is small icon that is usually shown in browser tab text to title of the site. Some Operating System display it differently, like Android or MacOS.
The best way to get favicon that will work on every device is to use generator that will do that for you.
I personally use Real Favicon Generator I trust that It create favicon for every possible use case.
To generate favicon you just upload an image. If you want best possible favicon you can generate one for MacOS and Windows that often need different background (those are 
I personally always create favicon (that is just based on logo)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub T. Jankiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A real-life example of making a custom Promise in JavaScript/TypeSctipt]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/a-real-life-example-of-making-a-custom-promise-in-javascript-typesctipt-5d1n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nordicbeaver/a-real-life-example-of-making-a-custom-promise-in-javascript-typesctipt-5d1n"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T20:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like we've completely moved from callbacks to Promises and async/await in the JavaScript world. So much, that almost every library and framework provides async versions of their functions. And the logic usually goes like this: 'I see async -> I type await and mark my function async as well -> done!'. I got so used to it, so I started to forget how to create and use my own Promises. 
But life always finds a way to remind you that old habits die hard, especially if you're talking about browsers APIs.
So, if you're like me and need a little reminder on how to make custom Promises, I hope you'll find this post helpful.
So here is the problem. We need to create an Image element using a browser's API and set its source to a dataUrl of some picture. At first, I wrote something like this.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NordicBeaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-Closed Principle – The Software Development Concept Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6148802f9456b407b870f041</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/open-closed-principle/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T19:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many articles about the Open-Closed Principle, but I can never find one that explains it in a way that really works for me.  So here, hopefully, is a good one – with a non trivial and real life example, what changes to support, and a description of the trade]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tonic (Component Framework)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/tonic-component-framework/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T18:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy little frameworks like Tonic. It’s essentially syntactic sugar over <web-components /> to make them feel easier to use. Define a Class, template literal an HTML template, probably some other fancy helpers, and you’ve got a component …
The post Tonic (Component Framework) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complete Automation Integrating Docker, Github with Jenkins Multibranch CI/CD Pipeline on AWS EC2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/amsal/complete-automation-integrating-docker-github-with-jenkins-multibranch-ci-cd-pipeline-on-aws-ec2-3l0o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/amsal/complete-automation-integrating-docker-github-with-jenkins-multibranch-ci-cd-pipeline-on-aws-ec2-3l0o"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T18:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is CI/CD?



CI stands for Continous Integration
CD stands for Continous Delivery or Continous Deployment
Let me explain through a example: 
When you make a commit and push sources to Git SCM(Source Code Management like Github, GitLab etc), then automatic builds and tests are run with the latest changes, this is knows as Continous Integration
With Continous Delivery, code changes are automatically built, tested, and prepared for a release to production. Continuous delivery expands upon continuous integration by deploying all code changes to a testing environment and put on a manual approval for adding them in production envirment.
Continous Deployment expands upon continuous delivery and pushed to production environment automatically without any approval.

A DevOps pipeline is a set o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amsal Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner's guide to Docker and Docker CLI commands]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paru429/beginner-s-guide-to-docker-and-docker-cli-commands-1p75</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paru429/beginner-s-guide-to-docker-and-docker-cli-commands-1p75"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T18:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Docker? - "build once and run anywhere."


Docker is a software development tool and a virtualisation technology that makes it easy to develop, deploy, and manage applications by using containers. Container refers to a lightweight, stand-alone, executable package of a piece of software that contains all the libraries, configuration files, dependencies, and other necessary parts to operate the application.
In other words, applications run in the same way, irrespective of where they are and what machine they are running on because the container provides the environment throughout the software development lifecycle of the application. Since containers are isolated, they provide security, thus allowing multiple containers to run simultaneously on the given host. Also, containers are li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paru429</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Share Your Knowledge as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>61508279ccc97307eb2bca3f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-you-should-share-your-knowledge-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing your knowledge can help you improve your skills and level up your career as a developer. Many developers are already doing it, and if you aren't, this article is for you. In it, I will show you why you should share your coding expertise by looking at five extraordinary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reactive Forms in Angular The basics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mcube25/reactive-forms-in-angular-the-basics-3jol</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mcube25/reactive-forms-in-angular-the-basics-3jol"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular uses reactive methods to process and manage form. It is easy to use reactive forms to capture user inputs events, validate the inputs and create form models in large angular applications. This enables the tracking of data and changes in the form model in all parts of the application.
Reactive forms provide a model-driven approach to handling form inputs whose values change over time. It uses an explicit and immutable approach to manage the form at a given point in time and it is built around observable streams.
Register the reactive form module in the app module declaration of an angular app. This module declares a reactive form directives needed to use the reactive form
 Generate a new form control instance and save in the component class
Register the form control i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Muhktar Musa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Checklist to Quickly Evaluate SaaS Security]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zmre/a-checklist-to-quickly-evaluate-saas-security-3hj3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zmre/a-checklist-to-quickly-evaluate-saas-security-3hj3"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large companies have security teams that scrutinize every partner and vendor they use. They put the vendor through the wringer with security reviews that usually involve long and tedious spreadsheets. 
The result of those painful security reviews is generally an analysis on the relative level of risk that comes with the solution. Then the business stakeholder can choose to take the advice of security or overrule it (spending political capital in the process) to say that the benefits outweigh the risks.
The review process is painful for everyone and, frankly, despite the intentions of various startups and others, it seems to be getting worse, not better.
And we have another problem: only the biggest companies even get to evaluate the security of their vendors. The rest of us aren't privvy t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Walsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application-Layer Encryption Defined]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zmre/application-layer-encryption-defined-4pnk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zmre/application-layer-encryption-defined-4pnk"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T17:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Not Overcomplicate It


Definition: Application-layer Encryption (ALE) is when you encrypt data before sending it to a data store. There are many variations, but at its core, that's it.
There are three main ways in which implementations may differ:
Code vs. Service: In some implementations, the encryption/decryption truly happens inside the application, which calls encrypt() or decrypt() routines. In others, an intermediate service or proxy essentially does that for you.
Client vs. Server: Some systems are strict about only encrypting and decrypting data in the client, which brings zero-trust data systems using end-to-end encryption (E2EE). E2EE is a subset of application-layer encryption. But encryption/decryption may alternately happen on the server. For server-side application-lay…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Walsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the DOM? Document Object Model Meaning in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>613f3cd3852f4307d372c7e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-dom-document-object-model-meaning-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have just started learning JavaScript, you might have heard of the DOM. But what is it exactly? In this article, I will explain what the DOM is and provide some JavaScript code examples.  We will take a look at how to select elements from an HTML document, how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OpenSSH 8.8 cannot find a host key type if ssh-rsa is provided]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/cloudx/why-openssh-8-8-cannot-find-a-host-key-type-if-ssh-rsa-is-provided-49i</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/cloudx/why-openssh-8-8-cannot-find-a-host-key-type-if-ssh-rsa-is-provided-49i"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T16:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenSSH 8.8 is now in the stable channel of Arch Linux and could reach other distributions any time soon.
In the release 8.7, the OpenSSH team announced that the ssh-rsa signature scheme will be disabled by default in the next version: 8.8.
The ssh-rsa signature scheme uses SHA-1 and it's sensible to chosen-prefix attacks.
This should not be a problem unless you are connecting to a server using the weak ssh-rsa public key algorithm for host authentication.
💡 If you're using the version 8.7 or a previous one, you can test your remote hosts like a GitLab or a cloud server using:
ssh -oHostKeyAlgorithms=-ssh-rsa user@host

If the connection fails, that means that the signature algorithm is not compatible with the default configuration of OpenSSH 8.8.
If you can't upgrade the signature algorithm on your remote servers but you still need to use them, you can use the following command:
ssh -oHostKeyAlgorithms=+ssh-rsa user@host

Right now, Bitbucket uses this weak signature algorithm, I guess you need to use your Git repositories hosted there. 🥺 You can check your connection with the following command:
ssh -oHostKeyAlgorithms=+ssh-rsa git@bitbucket.org

How can we enable this flag for all the Git commands? An easy solution is coming... You can create an SSH configuration file with the following content:
Host bitbucket.org
     HostKeyAlgorithms +ssh-rsa
     IdentitiesOnly yes

The default location of this file is under ~/.ssh/config, maybe you already have one. Once you add this configuration value you can use any git command without restrictions.
I hope this will help you to still SSHing the world 🗺️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Axel Navarro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 command line tools you should try]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nspired/top-5-command-line-tools-you-should-try-1c95</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nspired/top-5-command-line-tools-you-should-try-1c95"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T16:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ripgrep


You've probably used grep before. ripgrep is like grep, just better. Faster, with nicer defaults, and more powerful! https://github.com/BurntSushi/ripgrep
fzf


I probably use fzf more than any other tool in this list. If you have a hard time remembering where you put this very important module in your codebase, just type fzf and it'll bring up a list of files that you can easily sift through https://github.com/junegunn/fzf
jq


If you're working with JSON, you need to try jq. It allows you to parse, filter and transform any JSON file with an a simple query language. https://github.com/stedolan/jq
less +F


You might have used less before. But did you know you could use it like tail --follow? less +F logfile will stream any new lines added to your log file! You can also filter the stream with & or pause it with Ctrl+C
entr


If you're tired of having to run your test suite manually any time you update a file, try this: git ls-files | entr -c <command to run your tests>. It will run your command every time you update a file in your project.
https://github.com/eradman/entr
Thanks for reading this far! Do you have any other cool command line tools that you think should have made this list?
For more tech content like this, follow us @nspiredTech
Visit https://nspired.tech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Byte Sized</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Typescript and why should you be using it?🤔]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kardev07/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-be-using-it-2lde</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kardev07/what-is-typescript-and-why-should-you-be-using-it-2lde"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T15:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am sure that in your web development career you must have used JavaScript at least once. And I am sure you must have found it very useful and very powerful. But what if I say there is another language that is just as powerful as JavaScript and has way lesser bugs when compared to when you use JavaScript in your app.
Now, what's the language that I'm talking about?
That language is TypeScript.
TypeScript?


TypeScript is a programming language developed and maintained by Microsoft licensed using the Apache License 2.0. TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript, meaning that all the concepts of JavaScript are present in TypeScript which is combined with TypeScript's own concepts that make the language increasingly powerful.
If you know JavaScript, it mustn't be a problem switching to TypeScri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karthik Pariti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting Email Signups With the Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352211</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/collecting-email-signups-with-the-notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T15:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people these days are setting up their own newsletters. You’ve got the current big names like Substack and MailChimp, companies like Twitter are getting into it with Revue, and even Facebook is getting into the …
The post Collecting Email Signups With the Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravgeet Dhillon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda Function in Python – Example Syntax]]></title>
        <id>614ad5b79456b407b871028d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/lambda-function-in-python-example-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T15:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambda functions are anonymous functions that can contain only one expression. You may think that lambda functions are an intermediate or advanced feature, but here you will learn how you can easily start using them in your code. In Python, functions are usually created like this: def my_func(a)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Angular content projection for prepare a burger]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danywalls/use-angular-content-projection-for-prepare-a-burger-46pj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danywalls/use-angular-content-projection-for-prepare-a-burger-46pj"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T15:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the easiest things is eating a burger, the burger has the same base but changes its content, so let's build our burger component.
Today’s we explain how to use ng content to provide an area flexible and multiple slot.
Use ng content for content projection.
Use multiple slot for content projection.
If you want to play with the https://burger-angular-content-projection-demo.stackblitz.io
We have a list of ingredients components to be use for prepare our burger component.
<top-bun></top-bun>
<cheese></cheese>
<bottom-bun></bottom-bun>
<tomato></tomato>
<onion></onion>
<meat></meat>

The main idea is create a burger component and put our ingredients inside of him, like a normal burger using two great angular feature content projection.
Angular allows us to make our component reusable us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dany Paredes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker DNS: The Odyssey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/joojscript/docker-dns-the-odyssey-39dc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/joojscript/docker-dns-the-odyssey-39dc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, well, well...How could I imagine that configuring a VPN would not be so easy? Hahahaha, ok, I'll explain.
Recently I changed my workstation, I used to code on a Macbook Air before, but now I moved to a desktop, and because of it, I needed to configure my VPN all again, no big deal.
I'm currently using Deepin as my distro, and I did not have much problems until today.
If you have skipped the last part, just to let you know, I need to configure a VPN.
"Ok, but what does this have with docker?" - you may ask.
Well, the VPN setup came up alright, I use OpenVPN and it works just fine.
But the problem came when I tried to access a private address, visible only to the ones with VPN access, and I could not, even though I was connected, but why?
Digging in, I realized that the IP of this spec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Augusto Perin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce AWS EC2 Development Instances Cost by 60%]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nilanth/reduce-aws-ec2-development-instances-cost-by-60-2li8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nilanth/reduce-aws-ec2-development-instances-cost-by-60-2li8"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steps to reduce EC2 development instances cost using scheduled scaling.
We are all aware that Amazon Web Services is one of the most popular and used Cloud platforms. Most of us use AWS for hosting. When building apps, we might have different environments for development, staging, UAT, and production.
So if our app uses a web machine and a worker, then we have these same machines in all environments. For example, if we use a development and production environment, we will have 4 instances. But when compared to production instances, Our development environment will have low-end instances. But the low-end instance also adds cost to our billing.
We can reduce the development instance cost up to 60%. We can save this cost and use it in any other way. We will see how to cut down the cost.
The d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilanth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Features Every Angular Developer Needs to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bitovi/typescript-features-every-angular-developer-needs-to-know-4b82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bitovi/typescript-features-every-angular-developer-needs-to-know-4b82"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re an Angular developer, you’re missing out if you’re not using advanced TypeScript features to help you build better code.
And it’s well worth the effort: TypeScript has some great features that can make you a stronger Angular developer. 💪
BigInt lets you represent numbers bigger than 253. This is useful when you need to perform mathematical operations on very large integers. And you can work directly with large integer IDs and high resolution timestamps.
You can create a bigint primitive in two ways:
const n0 = 1n;
const n1 = new BigInt(1);

There is no interoperability between bigint and number primitives, but they can be compared.
NOTE: BigInt support is only available for the esnext target.
Numeric separators are great for readability. They don't change how the actual numeric …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fábio Englert Moutinho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TypeScript Features Every Angular Developer Needs to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bitovi/typescript-features-every-angular-developer-needs-to-know-4b82</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bitovi/typescript-features-every-angular-developer-needs-to-know-4b82"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re an Angular developer, you’re missing out if you’re not using advanced TypeScript features to help you build better code.
And it’s well worth the effort: TypeScript has some great features that can make you a stronger Angular developer. 💪
BigInt lets you represent numbers bigger than 253. This is useful when you need to perform mathematical operations on very large integers. And you can work directly with large integer IDs and high resolution timestamps.
You can create a bigint primitive in two ways:
const n0 = 1n;
const n1 = new BigInt(1);

There is no interoperability between bigint and number primitives, but they can be compared.
NOTE: BigInt support is only available for the esnext target.
Numeric separators are great for readability. They don't change how the actual numeric …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fábio Englert Moutinho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH 是什麼？]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ben66yueh/ssh-3o6o</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ben66yueh/ssh-3o6o"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[學習緣由
在開始做 Side Project 的時候，因為我使用 create-next-app 時，
沒有用成 typescript 版，我的 mentor 幫我處理的時候，
發現現在好像需要用 ssh 才能 push 到 github 上，
然後中間過程半聽半懂的 XD，想說趁機來了解一下～

 


  
  
  SSH 是什麼？


一個協定(protocol)，為 Secure Shell 的縮寫，
 


  
  
  SSH 資料傳輸方式


在此協定下，資料傳輸的方式可以用把包裹寄給朋友來說明

今天我想寄一個很機密包裹給朋友，要確保不能被別人拿走


我先加一個鎖在自己的包裹上，再傳給朋友


傳給朋友後，他看到我的鎖後，也加了自己的鎖


我看到朋友的鎖後，將自己的鎖解除，再回傳給朋友


朋友將鎖解除後，成功拿到包裹



 
這樣一來，我們可以增加傳送過程中的安全性，
但在這之前，我們需要將兩台電腦達成 SSH 連結，
 


  
  
  如何建立 SSH 連結呢？


SSH 連結採用 Client-Server 模型
 


 



在本機利用 RSA 的加密方式，產生一組公鑰(Public Key)和私鑰(Private Key)，為一對 SSH keys


將私鑰放在 Server 上


Client 利用終端機等產生一組 ID，範例格式如下：
ssh username@my_ip_address


Server 會用公鑰加密(encrypt)，產生一組隨機的挑戰訊息 (random challenge message)回傳給 Client


Client 會用私鑰將挑戰訊息解密(decrypt)後，回傳給 Server


如果解密後的挑戰訊息回傳 Server 後相符，則 SSH 連結就成立了



 
以上就是 SSH 的介紹，如果有其他想法也請大家不吝指教～
 
 
GitKraken
jumpcloud
School Of Basics
Level Up
Larry Lu Medium]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>YuehBen66</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Accessibility Tools – How to Build More Accessible React Apps]]></title>
        <id>614c40119456b407b8710b0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/react-accessibility-tools-build-accessible-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making a website or web app accessible improves the user experience for people with disabilities and for all users as well. Since developers deal with tight deadlines and competing priorities, it is easy to accidentally ship unresolved accessibility issues to production. And things becomes even more complex when working with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Development mocking External Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-development-mocking-external-calls-504j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-development-mocking-external-calls-504j"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a previous client project, I saw a use of local JSON for quick development that was horrible in that particular definition. I've refined the definition into something I can use more efficiently.
First, in the tsconfig.json file at the root of the project, I clean up the imports and allow JSON files to be resolved on import, as shown ...
{
  "compilerOptions": {
    ...
    "allowSyntheticDefaultImports": true,
    "resolveJsonModule": true
   ...
  }
} 

In the assets folder, I define the mock-data in the following path ...
assets/mock-data/api/

For this article, assume there is a users.json file in the api folder.
Within the project, I create a config.json file that can be imported.
{
  "features": {
    ...
    "useLocalJSON": false,
    ...
  }
} 

This file is imported as such.
imp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.js</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Development mocking External Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-development-mocking-external-calls-504j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rfornal/angular-development-mocking-external-calls-504j"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a previous client project, I saw a use of local JSON for quick development that was horrible in that particular definition. I've refined the definition into something I can use more efficiently.
First, in the tsconfig.json file at the root of the project, I clean up the imports and allow JSON files to be resolved on import, as shown ...
{
  "compilerOptions": {
    ...
    "allowSyntheticDefaultImports": true,
    "resolveJsonModule": true
   ...
  }
} 

In the assets folder, I define the mock-data in the following path ...
assets/mock-data/api/

For this article, assume there is a users.json file in the api folder.
Within the project, I create a config.json file that can be imported.
{
  "features": {
    ...
    "useLocalJSON": false,
    ...
  }
} 

This file is imported as such.
imp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bob.js</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Language Processing with spaCy &amp; Python - Full Course]]></title>
        <id>6151be27ccc97307eb2bcfa2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/natural-language-processing-with-spacy-python-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natural language processing, or NLP, is a branch of linguistics that seeks to parse human language in a computer system. spaCy is a popular Python library used for NLP. We just published a NLP and spaCy course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In the course you will learn all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Object Storage for Data Parallelization and Experimentation]]></title>
        <id>614bc3bd9456b407b87108b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-object-storage-for-parallelization-and-experimentation/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T14:09:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By using big data, companies can learn a lot about how their businesses are performing. Analytics on sales, churn rates, and other basic metrics are available in almost real time as data comes in.  Then there are more complex analyses that you'll need to do. At times relationships between two]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FULL CALENDER]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/pratikdungarani/full-calender-237k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/pratikdungarani/full-calender-237k"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T13:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[=> HOW To Design Parent title and sub-title Design in Full calendar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pratikdungarani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SigNoz - Open-source alternative to New Relic]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/signoz/signoz-open-source-alternative-to-new-relic-138n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/signoz/signoz-open-source-alternative-to-new-relic-138n"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T13:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're looking for an open-source alternative to New Relic, then you're at the right place. SigNoz is a perfect open-source alternative to New Relic. SigNoz provides a unified UI for both metrics and traces with advanced tagging and filtering capabilities.

In today's digital economy, more and more companies are shifting to cloud-native and microservice architecture to support global scale and distributed teams. But distributed systems also make it impossible for engineering teams to track how user requests perform across services. Application performance monitoring tools provide the visibility needed to resolve performance issues quickly in distributed systems.
New Relic is a great SaaS tool when it comes to application performance monitoring. But there are a few challenges when it com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Anand ✨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Dev, Peer, and Regular Dependencies]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thawkin3/understanding-dev-peer-and-regular-dependencies-gmi</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thawkin3/understanding-dev-peer-and-regular-dependencies-gmi"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building a modern JavaScript app, you will likely rely on many other packages and third-party dependencies. For example, you might use react and react-dom for your UI, lodash for utility helper methods, webpack or rollup as your bundler, and jest with @testing-library/react for unit tests.
All of these packages are stored as dependencies in your package.json file. Understanding whether to include them as dependencies, devDependencies, or peerDependencies can sometimes be a struggle for newer developers.
In this article we'll look at the three types of dependencies found in the package.json file and what each does.
dependencies are packages used in your app's production bundle. If you're building a React app, then react and react-dom would be dependencies. If you're using react-router …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless benefits for Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dashbird/serverless-benefits-for-startups-3nb6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dashbird/serverless-benefits-for-startups-3nb6"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve had a great conversation with a buddy of mine who is launching a new service, and while he is not a technical person, he came up to me asking about serverless and if it could have an actual impact on his startup. 
Naturally, I got very excited about the topic and proceeded to list all the benefits of serverless technology and how decentralized technology has revolutionized the industry, so on so forth. After a 15-minute monologue, the guy stops me and politely asks me the question again.
How does serverless affect early-stage startups, and how it differs from the traditional monolith architecture?
I was forced to look at the problem from a different angle. Big companies get tons of benefits from huge cost cuts, better security, and a way to scale their applications on-demand without a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taavi Rehemägi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic CDK Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/thebenforce/dynamic-cdk-dashboards-54f1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/thebenforce/dynamic-cdk-dashboards-54f1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the CDK's greatest strengths is the ability to create a library of components to be shared across your company, or shared with the world on constructs.dev. But how do you create a construct based on other constructs in the same stack without forcing the developer to call a method for each one? That's exactly what aspects allow you to do.
You can find the final source for this tutorial at https://github.com/theBenForce/dynamo-dashboard
The CDK uses a four step process to convert your code into a CloudFormation template: construct, prepare, validate, and synthesize. Since aspects are used during the second step, you need to understand how the first two steps are related.

When you run a CDK command, it starts by executing your code. Usually this is some file in the project's bin/ dire…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Force</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VSCode-nGQL, nGQL extension for VSCode]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lisahui/vscode-ngql-ngql-extension-for-vscode-56g5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lisahui/vscode-ngql-ngql-extension-for-vscode-56g5"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[nGQL extension VSCode is built to integrate the Nebula Graph with VSCode for an awesome developer experience.
VS Code nGQL Syntax Highlight

Download
here.
Features
0.0.2
Reference
https://docs.nebula-graph.io/
https://github.com/vesoft-inc/nebula-graph/blob/master/src/parser/scanner.lex]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lisahui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Créer un backend en Javascript : Introduction à Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/creer-un-backend-en-javascript-introduction-a-node-js-3014</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/creer-un-backend-en-javascript-introduction-a-node-js-3014"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voici une série d'articles qui vous permettra créer des applications backend en Javascript.
Node.js est aujourd'hui un incontournable, il est donc essentiel pour un développeur de le maitriser.
Je vais donc publier un nouvel article environ au deux jours et petit à petit vous apprendrez tout ce qu'il y a à savoir sur Node.js
Pour ne rien manquer suivez moi sur twitter : https://twitter.com/EricLeCodeur
NodeJS permet d’exécuter du code Javascript en dehors d’un navigateur.
Node.js est un environnement serveur, open source, gratuit, et qui utilise le language Javascript pour créer des applications Web côté serveur. (backend)
Node.js fonctionne sur différentes plateformes (Windows, Linux, Unix, Mac OS X, etc.) Avec Node.js, nous pouvons créer une application Web rapide et hautement évolutive.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Le Codeur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geraldine Przybylko Strategy Consultant - Tkxel Client]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkxel/geraldine-przybylko-strategy-consultant-tkxel-client-5042</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkxel/geraldine-przybylko-strategy-consultant-tkxel-client-5042"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T12:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to thank TkXel for building a Comprehensive Health Digital platform for us! really appreciate the efforts you and your team have put together to get this job done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Software Services</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Dive Into Cypress For End-to-End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/cypress-end-to-end-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is end-to-end testing a painful topic for you? In this article, Ramona Schwering explains how to handle end-to-end testing with Cypress and make it make it not so tedious and expensive for yourself, but fun instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypress Basic Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/twitvital/about-cypress-26on</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/twitvital/about-cypress-26on"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Cypress
Cypress Features
Pros & Cons
Tech Stack
Installation of Cypress
https://nodejs.org/en/download/ as per your operating 
https://docs.cypress.io/guides/getting-started/installing-cypress#npm-install
Understanding folder structure
Thanks,
Linkedin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vital</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Resource Access Manager — Simple and powerful service for multi-account resource governance]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/svasylenko/aws-resource-access-manager-simple-and-powerful-service-for-multi-account-resource-governance-11na</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/svasylenko/aws-resource-access-manager-simple-and-powerful-service-for-multi-account-resource-governance-11na"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T11:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a multi-account approach of building the infrastructure, there is always a challenge of provision and governance of the resources to subordinate accounts within the Organization. Provision resources, keep them up to date, and decommission them properly — that's only a part of them.
AWS has numerous solutions that help make this process reliable and secure, and the Resource Access Manager (RAM) is one of them.
In a nutshell, the RAM service allows you to share the AWS resources you create in one AWS account with other AWS accounts. These can be your organizations' accounts, organizational units (OU), or even third-party accounts.
So let's see what the RAM is and review some of its usage examples. 
There are several benefits of using the RAM service:
Reduced operational overhead. Elimin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhii Vasylenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BangaJS - Nodejs Framework for Bootstraping Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ebereplenty/bangajs-nodejs-framework-for-bootstraping-your-project-4ee3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ebereplenty/bangajs-nodejs-framework-for-bootstraping-your-project-4ee3"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T10:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Nodejs is now one of the most popular tool for backend purpose. This is so especially because of how easy it is to understand the language. It is built on JavaScript.
However, it doesn't have so much frameworks out there that gives you all the basics (boring) stuff off the box. Basics includes things like setting up server, folder structure, authentication, mailers and so on.
Just incase you are new to Nodejs, I have a few courses you might want to checkout:
Setting Up a Simple, Secure and Robust Node JS Server
CRUD APP with Nodejs, Cloudinary, PostgreSQL and Heroku
Docker - An introduction with Nodejs
Full-Stack Authentication and Hosting (Nodejs, Reactjs, Heroku, Netlify)
These basics can be so tiring and consumes a lot of time. Where is the fun in doing same thing over an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NJOKU SAMSON EBERE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Code Execution Monitoring can help you to identify bugs and bottlenecks in your application before your customers do]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/inspector/application-monitoring-principles-why-when-what-1cj5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/inspector/application-monitoring-principles-why-when-what-1cj5"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T09:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I’m Valerio, software engineer, CTO & founder at Inspector, a monitoring platform used by developers in more than ten countries. In this article I would share my experience working in the monitoring industry trying to help you better understand:
What is the right tool for each specific monitoring problem;
 When, or in which situations, monitoring can be effective and worth the investment;
Why you should monitor certain parts of your system and not others, based on your stage of growth.
The time many developers discover the need to monitor their applications often coincides with when they first start working on a medium / large project.
The reason is simple: when your software becomes complex, or serves highly valuable customers, software bugs become expensive; doubly so when your custo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build maintainable software in a human friendly way]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/redchaser1994/build-your-software-in-a-human-friendly-way-5a78</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/redchaser1994/build-your-software-in-a-human-friendly-way-5a78"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T08:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a software engineer in Amazon for 5 years (To those that know, I am a yellow badger). I have been in Amazon retail, Kindle, and AWS. These three departments have drastically different business objectives, they build entirely different software using different technology stack, yet throughout this three teams, there is always one single topic that I would always hear from people: “XXX (some engineer) write such shi**y code and I could not make sense of it!!!”
I have said this sentence at least 101 times in my career. I am very sure that other people have said more than that. I personally have been drowning myself in code with 12 different layers of nested for and in loops, spams of try-catch blocks that penetrates at least 5 stacks of method invocation, variable names that doesn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuangyou Yao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Keyboard Avoiding View for React Native in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/fullstackchris/a-keyboard-avoiding-view-for-react-native-in-2021-die</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/fullstackchris/a-keyboard-avoiding-view-for-react-native-in-2021-die"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T08:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is mirrored on my blog, chrisfrew.in
I've been deep in the React Native world recently as I develop big features for InClub, an app that enables you to join and host private events!
Our latest sprint (for "v.1.3.0🥳") was designed to culminate in a chat functionality. That's right - I built an entire chat function in a mobile app in 3 weeks. 😉 This wasn't your grandma's chat either - the full feature set included profile picture uploading, routing push notifications to the correct chat window based on sender, and creation of new channels based on various events around the app. I know, I know, most dev consultants would need teams of people to get this done...

You know how many people they needed to get the chat working?! TEAMS!
Yeah, I'm pretty awesome. 😎
All bravado aside, I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Frewin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Types using Discriminated Unions in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/better-types-using-discriminated-unions-in-typescript-4i3g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/better-types-using-discriminated-unions-in-typescript-4i3g"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T08:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we define our types in Typescript impacts how effective typescript is at warning us when we make mistakes. If we take a broad approach i.e. to cover many types in a single type, we end up handicapping typescript and it becomes less effective. 
The more specific we are, the more effective typescript can be at catching possible errors. In this article, we are going to look at how we can use discriminative unions to write better and more specific types and help typescript to be more helpful to us.
Let's take the simplest example I can think of - Shapes. In shapes, we can have Circles, Rectangles, Squares, etc; you get the idea. There is no way you can have a single type alias that can cover all shapes without compromising on something.
If we were to define a Shape type alias for just the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Types using Discriminated Unions in TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/better-types-using-discriminated-unions-in-typescript-4i3g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/better-types-using-discriminated-unions-in-typescript-4i3g"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T08:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we define our types in Typescript impacts how effective typescript is at warning us when we make mistakes. If we take a broad approach i.e. to cover many types in a single type, we end up handicapping typescript and it becomes less effective. 
The more specific we are, the more effective typescript can be at catching possible errors. In this article, we are going to look at how we can use discriminative unions to write better and more specific types and help typescript to be more helpful to us.
Let's take the simplest example I can think of - Shapes. In shapes, we can have Circles, Rectangles, Squares, etc; you get the idea. There is no way you can have a single type alias that can cover all shapes without compromising on something.
If we were to define a Shape type alias for just the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maina Wycliffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would you use NodeJS in your next project?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davidcam/would-you-use-nodejs-in-your-next-project-2kf0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davidcam/would-you-use-nodejs-in-your-next-project-2kf0"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T07:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A post by David Camarena]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Camarena</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in Ethical Hacking]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/paosa20/starting-in-ethical-hacking-egk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/paosa20/starting-in-ethical-hacking-egk"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T06:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When starting in the world of cybersecurity/hacking, we always want to run and hack anything but it's important to know the basics. 
The reason why you lock your house when you go out so no bad guy comes inside and steal your belongings is similar to why companies are so serious about information security, Spoiler alert: no one wants their personal belongings get stolen.
Information security means securing or protecting sensitive and important information as well as the systems that store this information from any unauthorized handling.
Information security consists of various important elements, we will first start with the CIA triad and later with the rest of elements. 
The CIA triad consists of three important elements:



1. Confidentiality(C)
2. Integrity(I)
3. Availability(A)


Now, what do they mean?
Confidentiality: Only those with authorized access will be able to access the information. Example: Encryption

Integrity: The assurance that the information/data haven't suffered any unauthorized modification. Example: Hashing

Availability: Data always been accessible for authorized users when required. Example: Backups, clustered machines

Non-repudiation: Senders of a message can't deny having sent a message and the receivers can't deny having received it. Example: Digital Signatures

Authenticity: Guarantee of something being genuine. Example: Digital certificates,bio-metrics



  
  
  Why Information Security attacks happen?



Attacks occur for a variety of reasons like attackers wanting to steal sensitive information, data disclosure, ransomware and many others. 
It's important to understand the threats that a system may face to implement required preventive measures. 
You can start learning and understanding the different hacking phases:
1. Reconnaissance(Footprinting)
2. Scanning
3. Gaining access
4. Maintaining access
5. Clearing logs

Thanks for reading my first post! it may not be much but you start with something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paola Sánchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[useState vs useReducer]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkdodo/usestate-vs-usereducer-c09</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkdodo/usestate-vs-usereducer-c09"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T06:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The question about which state management solution to use might be just as old as React itself (or maybe even older), and answers to it are manifold. To me, there is only one good answer, and it's the same answer I will give to every seemingly complex question:
It depends.
— TkDodo
It depends on the type of state. It depends on update frequency. It depends on scoping.
If you know me, you know I have strong preferences on what to do with server state. So lets keep that out of the picture and look at everything that's left:
Before hooks, there was only one way of managing client state locally: in class-based components with this.setState. The state had to be an object, and the update function accepted a partial version of it.
Hooks changed that in a fundamental way. Not only could you now al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominik D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS - Conditional & Mathematical Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-learning/rxjs-conditional-mathematical-operators-1hh7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-learning/rxjs-conditional-mathematical-operators-1hh7"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T06:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Guys and welcome back,
These operators are useful to check if there are values in the observables or to find some specific value in them. Some of these operators are similar to some array methods, with the difference that they work with observables and not with arrays.
defaultIfEmpty
Emits a given value if the source Observable completes without emitting any next value, otherwise mirrors the source Observable.
import { EMPTY, Observer } from "rxjs";
import { defaultIfEmpty } from "rxjs/operators";

const observer: Observer<number> = {
    next: x => console.log('value', x),
    error: err => console.error('error', err),
    complete: () => console.log('complete'),
};

EMPTY.pipe(
    defaultIfEmpty(10)
).subscribe(observer);

value 10
complete


every
Returns an Observable that emits wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Del Puppo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own Blog Portfolio with Web Components: Lit Library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mariusbongarts/build-your-own-blog-portfolio-with-web-components-lit-library-57pa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mariusbongarts/build-your-own-blog-portfolio-with-web-components-lit-library-57pa"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T06:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last article of our series, we will simplify the process of creating Web Components by using the Lit library.
“Every Lit component is a native web component, with the superpower of interoperability.” - lit.dev
Build Your Own Blog Portfolio with Web Components: Lit Library | by Marius Bongarts | Sep, 2021 | Medium
Marius Bongarts ・ Sep 27, 2021 ・ 
      
        
        Medium]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marius Bongarts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sunitha_nair/state-management-19b2</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sunitha_nair/state-management-19b2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T05:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am sure you have heard about state management when it comes to developing enterprise applications. Let’s get started with the concept by understanding what it means for us and how it helps us build a Reactive application. This blog will focus on how to maintain state in Angular applications but the concepts are the same for all the component based frameworks including React and Vue Js.
State in application is the single source of truth containing the user contexts or other global information. Let us consider the scenario where you wanna build an application which will use login functionality. Let’s say you have multiple components using the login information to display the information about the login like Login name, email and your avatar, when you update any of these information you wan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sunitha-premakumaran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[📊 Calculating DORA Metrics - Deployment Frequency]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lornasw93/calculating-dora-metrics-deployment-frequency-38ib</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lornasw93/calculating-dora-metrics-deployment-frequency-38ib"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T00:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The easiest metric to calculate - get a list of project deployments by environment and then group by date format(s) i.e. by day, by month and by year; and finally to calculate the throughput % score which is essentially:
throughput % = (count of deployments by environment * count of all deployments) * 100
I've parsed the data into a specific format for my charts in the frontend. Check out my repo here.
Result:
{
    "score": 4.16,
    "result": [
        {
            "title": "By Day", 
            "content": [
                {
                    "name": "29 Aug 21",
                    "value": 2
                },
                {
                    "name": "10 Sep 21",
                    "value": 2
                }
            ],
            "average": 2
        },
        {
            "title": "By Month", 
            "content": [
                {
                    "name": "Aug 21",
                    "value": 2
                },
                {
                    "name": "Sep 21",
                    "value": 2
                }
            ],
            "average": 2
        },
        {
            "title": "By Year", 
            "content": [
                {
                    "name": "21",
                    "value": 4
                }
            ],
            "average": null
        }
    ]
}

Thanks for reading!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorna Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[📊 Intro: DORA Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lornasw93/calculating-dora-metrics-3k1l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lornasw93/calculating-dora-metrics-3k1l"/>
        <updated>2021-09-27T00:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've created a small Node.js project to calculate DORA Metrics, it's ongoing so is not finished but you can find the repo here. 
References/useful links: Accelerate: State of DevOps 2021, DORA metrics explained
DORA (DevOps Research and Assessment) represents 7 years of research by a team at Google to identify the most effective and efficient ways to develop and deliver software. They surveyed more than 32,000 industry professionals to find out and understand what makes a high performing team different than a low performing team. As a now industry standard, DORA's research has identified four key metrics (depending on where you look will have slightly different names):
Measure throughput by how often an organisation successfully releases to production.
For elite performers: on demand, multiple deploys per day
Measure throughput by the amount of time it takes a commit to get into production.
For elite performers: < one hour
Measure stability by how long it takes an organisation to recover from a failure in production.
For elite performers: < 1 hour
Measure stability by percentage of deployments causing a failure in production. 
For elite performers: 0% - 15%
This is a first post in a series #AllAboutDora, hope this post was useful and interesting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lorna Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create DatePicker By TailWindCss + Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/timsar2/create-datepicker-by-tailwindcss-angular-3p8k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/timsar2/create-datepicker-by-tailwindcss-angular-3p8k"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T20:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello friends,
https://tailwind-elements.com/docs/standard/forms/datepicker/
It has a DatePicker made by Tailwindcss and alpine js.

First add TailWindCss to your project:
https://www.npmjs.com/package/@ngneat/tailwind
date-picker.component.ts:
import { Component, OnInit } from '@angular/core';

@Component({
  selector: 'app-DatePicker',
  templateUrl: './date-picker.html'
})
export class DatePickerComponent implements OnInit {
  MONTH_NAMES = [
    'January',
    'February',
    'March',
    'April',
    'May',
    'June',
    'July',
    'August',
    'September',
    'October',
    'November',
    'December'
  ];
  DAYS = ['Sun', 'Mon', 'Tue', 'Wed', 'Thu', 'Fri', 'Sat'];
  days = ['Sun', 'Mon', 'Tue', 'Wed', 'Thu', 'Fri', 'Sat'];
  showDatepicker = false;
  datepickerValue!: string;
  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>timsar2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.2"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T18:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: unicode characters in URL caused download error
Fixed: project root npm install error
Added: unit test library
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @CaptNo1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Cron keep your eyes in check]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/has12zen/using-cron-keep-your-eyes-in-check-k83</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/has12zen/using-cron-keep-your-eyes-in-check-k83"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T16:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[basic syntax for cron


a typical cron job looks like this
# m h  dom mon dow   command
  * *   *   *   *   /usr/bin/sh ls

stand for wildcard
this is not a cron tutorial this is just how i use it. 
the bash script looks like
#!/bin/sh
export DISPLAY=:0
notify-send "EYES CHECK" "Look away for 15 seconds"

without line no 2 it wont work as it sets the display for notify-send. I am using notify-send as my notification daemon. 
make sure that your display is :0 
echo $DISPLAY

first you will need to make sure cron is running you can do this  by:
systemctl status cronie

p.s. this is specific to arch based system.
once cron is running you can create/edit cron job with crontab -e
then paste the code present below into the window.
*/15 * * * * /usr/bin/sh  /home/elnovo/.noti/eyes.sh

it runs every 15 min and eyes.sh is the bash script we discussed above. save it. 
crontab -l
notify-send doesn't work from crontab]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>has12zen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating RESTful APIs with Node and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/angha_ramdohokar_0b6505c2/creating-restful-apis-with-mongodb-and-node-js-25ap</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/angha_ramdohokar_0b6505c2/creating-restful-apis-with-mongodb-and-node-js-25ap"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T16:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During my career as a software developer, I have written RESTful APIs in different languages and used different frameworks for it like VB.net, C#, Java, ASP.NET etc. But recently I got an opportunity to create RESTful APIs using Node js.
Node.js is a server-side platform built on Google Chrome's JavaScript Engine (V8 Engine). Node.js provides a backend web application framework called as Express. It is designed for building web applications and APIs. MongoDB is an open-source document-oriented database.
We’ll be building a RESTful CRUD (Create, Retrieve, Update, Delete) API with Node.js, Express and MongoDB. We’ll use Mongoose for interacting with the MongoDB instance.
Prerequisites
Install Node.js and MongoDB on your machine if you have not done already and use any development environment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angha Ramdohokar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setup new angular app from scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raghvendrac/setup-new-angular-app-from-scratch-225p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raghvendrac/setup-new-angular-app-from-scratch-225p"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T16:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Guys , here we are going to see how to initiate when we are going to create angular app from scratch,initially i am adding steps for module generation and lazily loaded components inside those components.later you will get the updated on things in same blog.please visit below link and leave comments here. if you have any query.
https://dotheblog.herokuapp.com/user/viewBlog/Setup_a_new_Angular_project_from_scratch./615078c4c74b9e0016ab0031]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raghvendrac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask - Internal JSON-RPC error]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/coderbang1/metamask-internal-json-rpc-error-38gd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/coderbang1/metamask-internal-json-rpc-error-38gd"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T15:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i was following nader full stack nft marketplace, where i can mint nfts but when i try to buy it gives me this error :MetaMask - Internal JSON-RPC error 
code: 3, message: "execution reverted: Please submit the asking price in order to complete the purchase", data:
along with this:Uncaught (in promise) 
any solution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coderbang1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to implement Google Authentication in your React Applications!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/shaan_alam/how-to-implement-google-authentication-in-your-react-applications-jb6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/shaan_alam/how-to-implement-google-authentication-in-your-react-applications-jb6"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T14:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


Hey ya folks!
OAuth is a Open Standard Authorization protocol that provides appliactions the scopes of the user's data without sharing their password to other applications. It also makes authentication process a lot easier both for the developer and the user. For example, you might have seen "Login with Google" button on some websites. When you click that button, a request is made to Google's servers and the user's data (without password) is returned to the client side. This response can also be used against our own API to authenticate the user.

We are gonna be creating a React App which will use Google OAuth to authenticate the user. For the simplicity of the application I'm gonna store the user's data inside the component state.
Implementing Google Authentication in your React A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaan Alam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MERN stack - an example]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/linhtch90/mern-stack-an-example-4j43</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/linhtch90/mern-stack-an-example-4j43"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T13:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
I want to share with the community the source code of a fullstack web application that I have just developed using MERN stack demonstrating basic features of a bookstore.
I hope this would be a good resource for anyone who enjoys learning Javascript in general and MERN stack in particular.
The live demo is accessible at:
https://bn-bookstore.herokuapp.com/#/
Source code is available at:
https://github.com/linhtch90/bn_bookstore_public_source
Happy coding and if this is useful for you, please give me a Github star for encouragement!
Thank you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linh Truong Cong Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to ensure the highest quality of Software code]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/someshthakur/how-to-ensures-highest-quality-of-software-4917</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/someshthakur/how-to-ensures-highest-quality-of-software-4917"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T09:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: By following best industry practices like linting, unit testing, static code analysis and continuous monitoring of the software.
The software development process has changed a lot in last few years. Many of the modern tools & frameworks has built-in support to ensure that the code is clean, maintainable and readable. But any developer can make mistakes while coding a feature on mind and that's totally fine. We all have gone through that stage & we learnt through making mistakes.
In this article I am going to share some of the basic to advanced levels of checks which I learnt through working on Enterprise software applications. These are some of the best practices that you can follow or explore.
One of the basic setup that gives many advantages in long run is code linting. It leaves …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Somesh Thakur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux, Should you use it? Can you use it?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dilutewater/linux-should-you-use-it-can-you-use-it-4aeo</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dilutewater/linux-should-you-use-it-can-you-use-it-4aeo"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T08:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some context:


I'm just a student and I have been using windows from my childhood, but I switched  to linux about a month ago. I install ubuntu on my main PC as windows was lagging a lot. My PC is a very low end PC so I taught to give linux a try. I then installed kde plasma environment on my ubuntu. And I am so happy with it that I would never switch to windows again.
Linux has a lot of awesome features. Lemme list few of the notable ones. 
Completely Free :


Customisation :


Flexibility :


Runs better on low end hardware :



and many other features...
If you are a developer, there is a high chance you are already using linux, but if you are not, then you can give it a try. 
I haven't tried many distros but according to me , you can try Ubuntu for basic users. Or you can try Kubuntu, it has KDE environment & has a lot of customisation features while is still very user friendly. 
After all linux is used everywhere from the high end servers to your android smartphones, so why not give it a try on your desktop computer as well. 
TL;DR - Give Linux a try, especially KDE plasma environment (Kubuntu)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachit Khurana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up Doppler's CLI on Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dpkreativ/how-to-set-up-doppler-s-cli-on-windows-10-52bc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dpkreativ/how-to-set-up-doppler-s-cli-on-windows-10-52bc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T08:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary


This article is about setting up Doppler’s Command Line Interface (CLI) on a Windows 10 Personal Computer (PC). You will install Scoop package manager, use Scoop to get the repo for Doppler’s CLI, then install the CLI binaries on your PC. You will then log into Doppler through its CLI, and configure Doppler for a project.
By following this article you will learn about Scoop package manager and how to install software packages like Doppler CLI on Windows 10 with it. You will also learn how to set up and configure Doppler for a project through its CLI.
This article assumes you have some familiarity with Doppler and what it does. You can quickly find out here. You will also need the following:
A PC with Windows 10 operating system
Windows PowerShell 5 or later
.NET Framework 4.5 or …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divine Orji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the most beginner-friendly Linux distro?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/madza/what-s-the-most-beginner-friendly-linux-distro-2bb5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/madza/what-s-the-most-beginner-friendly-linux-distro-2bb5"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T06:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are hundreds of Linux distributions out there each varying in their purpose of use and the level of expertise the user needs. 
There are tools like DitroWatch to help users narrow down their options, but, still, choosing the right one could be quite a challenge. 
What are some of the Linux distros you would recommend to users switching from other OS with no prior knowledge?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up a DSLR Camera Webcam on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/austingil/setting-up-a-dslr-camera-webcam-on-linux-2dbc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/austingil/setting-up-a-dslr-camera-webcam-on-linux-2dbc"/>
        <updated>2021-09-26T03:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finally set up my DSLR camera as a webcam, and it’s pretty cool. I wanted to share this post because I couldn’t find good, complete resources about it and I thought it might be useful for folks out there (and because future me will probably want it). Here’s everything I learned.
Here’s what I’m working with. Your setup may be different:
Camera: Canon EOS 60D
Operating System: Ubuntu 20.10
Before we get started, this may be a non-issue for a lot of folks as it’s common for camera manufacturers to create software for this. Canon, for example, make their EOS Webcam Utility that makes it easy for Windows or OSX users. But I use Linux (cue sad trombone).
If you’re like me and a handy webcam utility is not an option, let’s continue.
Firstly, make sure your camera is supported by checking this …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TryHackMe - OhSINT Writeup]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/l0wk3y/tryhackme-ohsint-writeup-4e4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/l0wk3y/tryhackme-ohsint-writeup-4e4b"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T17:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this TryHackMe room you will be tasked with gathering intel on a target based on an image, you must use Open Source Intelligence to solve the questions. 
What information can you possibly get with just one photo?

To get started you will need to extra metadata from the photo, this can be done using a tool called Exiftool. This tool needs to be downloaded but I will be using an online version of this tool called ExifMeta. After uploading the image to exifmeta, you will be presented with a list of RAW data pulled from the image's metadata. Right off the bat, I see a few things that catch my eye. XMP-exif:GPSLatitude, XMP-exif:GPSLongitude, and XMP-tiff:Copyright. After Googling OWoodflint the first result should be a twitter user with the profile picture of a cat.



System:FileName
Windo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L0WK3Y | I.A.A.N</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security by incident and surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schreddies/security-by-incident-and-surprise-2ijn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schreddies/security-by-incident-and-surprise-2ijn"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T17:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Story about weird and totally unplanned countermeasures for CSRF vulnerability that should not work



  
  
  Intro 1


To properly reheat your pizza: turn on stove on the middle heating option. After putting pizza on a hot skillet, heat it for a few minutes. Then, add some water drops around pizza and put the lid on top and heat for a few more minutes. Done.
Story of how I was stumbled, by a fairly simple non-vulnerable vulnerability. 
Let's begin with CSRF definition from OWASP: 
Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) is an attack that forces an end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they’re currently authenticated.
Successful attacks consist of a user entering a malicious site (phishing), while being authenticated to a vulnerable application, which is without CSR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Balsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication bypass in cryptography library]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schreddies/authentication-bypass-in-cryptography-library-3bcp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schreddies/authentication-bypass-in-cryptography-library-3bcp"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T17:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post originally created on github.io on January 2021
Vulnerability was found by the Synopsys CyRC researchers in the Bouncy Castle java library, in OpenBSDBcrypt class - see following article for more info from their side.
As it was already written in that post, the issue was with implementation method doCheckPassword- method that checks password against a 60 character Bcrypt string. Let's dive into that and see what was the core issue and how it was fixed.
In file core/src/main/java/org/bouncycastle/crypto/generators/OpenBSDBCrypt.java we can directly go to method doCheckPassword, where we have couple major checks: whether the Bcrypt string is really Bcrypt string, and if cost factor is from proper range. Nothing special, nothing wrong, just ifs. Relevant to our issue, line 268, states th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Balsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure by default, unsafe by you]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schreddies/secure-by-default-unsafe-by-you-1gnn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schreddies/secure-by-default-unsafe-by-you-1gnn"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T16:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post originally created on github.io on October 2020



This post is the presentation of how to make code UNSAFE. Please, do not use these code snippets in your application, unless you fancy to have a XSS. Read that, for extra protection: https://owasp.org/www-community/xss-filter-evasion-cheatsheet






In this small repo/blog will show you how to make modern, secure JS Frameworks, unsafe in nice way. Using purely these frameworks, we are going to end up with XSS. Following examples might be useful during code review or making a new version of DVWA, it’s up to you. Yes, you can find all these informations in the docs, but let's be honest - RTFM is not for everyone. 
Using this marvellous blog post Top JS Frameworks 2019 and followed by this awesome research State of JS 2019 it’s naturall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Balsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corona Virus Threat Modelling]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/schreddies/corona-virus-threat-modelling-3jkn</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/schreddies/corona-virus-threat-modelling-3jkn"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T16:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post originally created on github.io on March 2020
Well, we are doomed. And to add that, we are having the CORONA-19 virus around. Some of you might be familiar with the Threat Modelling in IT security but today I would like to make a Threat Modelling for your daily activity but with corona virus as main threat.  



DISCLIMER




This post should NOT be treated as real measurement for preventing virus, neither it's a good representation of threat modelling of IT systems. This post reflects NONE medical value beside link to WHO. Treat it as mind puzzle.




For those, not familiar with Threat Modelling: it is the structured and continuous process of identifying security threats in the software. The definition is not really precise about, what kind of processes and techniques we should use,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Balsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How browsers handle authentication?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ahmedossama22dev/how-browsers-handle-authentication-1fhk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ahmedossama22dev/how-browsers-handle-authentication-1fhk"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T14:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I’ll talk about authentication and how your browser handles such a process, First of all, authentication is the act of validating that users are who they claim to be. This is the first step in any security process. There are different ways to authenticate a user, the most popular methods are using SESSION IDs and JWT each of them has its pros and cons, In this article, I’ll discuss a brief about them. so let’s dive into the article.
Imagine the login process that you are doing every day when you enter your username/mail and your password to enter a website...
The browser sends a POST request to the server containing the username and password


The server checks whether this user exists or not then compare the saved hashed password to that in the request if everything is fine:






…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Ossama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hosting an Angular application on GitHub Pages using GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/hosting-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-using-github-actions-5ag8</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rodrigokamada/hosting-an-angular-application-on-github-pages-using-github-actions-5ag8"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T12:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Angular is a development platform for building WEB, mobile and desktop applications using HTML, CSS and TypeScript (JavaScript). Currently, Angular is at version 12 and Google is the main maintainer of the project.
GitHub is a source code and file storage service with version control using git tool. GitHub Pages is a static file hosting service using a public repository. GitHub Actions is a service to automate the software workflow.
Before you start, you need to install and configure the tools:
git
Node.js and npm
Angular CLI
IDE (e.g. Visual Studio Code)
1. Let's create the account. Access the site https://github.com/ and click on the button Sign up.

2. Fill in the fields Username, Email address, Password, click on the button Verify to solve the challenge and click on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Kamada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Interface Loopback (TAP) on Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-install-interface-loopback-tap-on-ubuntu-57dh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/danielcristho/how-to-install-interface-loopback-tap-on-ubuntu-57dh"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T02:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The loopback interface is a virtual interface on Linux, which allows us to connect to the GNS3 network simulator.
In the following I will explain how to install and configure the TAP Interface on the Linux operating system.
First you should install uml-utilities by typing the command sudo apt install uml-utilities.
Next step create a virtual interface by typing the command sudo tunctl -t tap10, then assign an IP Address to the interface by typing the command sudo ifconfig tap10 192.168.0.1 netmask 255.255.255.0 up.
The last check whether the IP address has been successfully added using the ifconfig tap10 command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danielpepuho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Move you angular cli app to Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/move-you-angular-cli-app-to-nx-3ej4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/move-you-angular-cli-app-to-nx-3ej4"/>
        <updated>2021-09-25T00:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Help me improve these updates by giving suggestions.
https://github.com/ajitsinghkaler/devto-clone
Deployed on Firebase - https://dev-toclone.firebaseapp.com/
Last week I was sick so there was no updates last week.
This week I mostly focused on my moving my clone to Nx monorepo. While converting it here are some of my findings on how to convert an Angular cli app to Nx monorepo
To convert an angular cli app to nx follow the steps below:-
Run the automatic nx generator in you app whoch will convert the angular cli project to an nx workspace




ng add @nrwl/workspace --preserveAngularCLILayout

After that remember project should never be imported into the library. Environments, common models, common components, common services move to an entirely different lib.
Example of moving 
Environmen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajit Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systems for z-index]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352287</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/systems-for-z-index/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T21:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Say you have a z-index bug. Something is being covered up by something else. In my experience, a typical solution is to put position: relative on the thing so z-index works in the first place, and maybe rejigger the z-index…
The post Systems for z-index appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Self Provisioning Runtime]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352533</id>
        <link href="https://www.swyx.io/self-provisioning-runtime/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T18:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big thoughts on where the industry is headed from Shawn Wang:
Advancements in two fields — programming languages and cloud infrastructure — will converge in a single paradigm: where all resources required by a program will be automatically provisioned, and 
…
The post The Self Provisioning Runtime appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Button Type – How to Add Buttons to your Website]]></title>
        <id>614df185ccc97307eb2bc079</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-button-type-how-to-add-buttons-to-your-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T18:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buttons are an essential part of websites. You need them for various functionalities, from submitting information and getting access to more content to linking to different parts of the web page and other websites.  HTML gives you several ways to add buttons to your website – with the button tag, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Insert a Text Box in Google Docs – Add Textbox Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>614b428f9456b407b871068a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-insert-a-text-box-in-google-docs-add-textbox-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T17:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Docs is one of the most popular text processors.  It has many features available to help you visually enhance your writing and make specific parts stand out more.  One of the ways you can add more functionality to your documents is by adding a textbox.  A textbox helps make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching to Pipewire-Opensuse[GUIDE]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/drunckj/switching-to-pipewire-opensuse-guide-1cop</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/drunckj/switching-to-pipewire-opensuse-guide-1cop"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T15:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently switched to pipewire on my Opensuse build and I'm loving it so far. I switched over to pipewire because it fixes a lot of pulseaudio issues which I've faced in the past. Pipewire is really new and still in the works and its more upto date for recent hardwares and bluetooth peripherals.
I've made a script which has does other stuff but has an option for switching to pipewire without much hassle. Clone it and run it and enter the correct option.
git clone https://github.com/drunckj/Asus-ESS
cd Asus-ESS/
./setupscript.sh

First we need to install all the necessary files
sudo zypper install pipewire pipewire-pulseaudio pipewire-alsa

It will show and errors about conflicts you should select option 1 to fix the issue which reads de-installation.
systemctl --user enable --now pipewire.{service,socket}
systemctl --user enable --now pipewire-pulse.{service,socket}

After running the above commands, you should reboot.
pactl info

Look for server name in output. If it shows 
Server Name: PulseAudio (on PipeWire)
Sometimes pipewire doesn't generate config files so we have to move them to the right location. This can cause the bluetooth to not work too. Follow the below steps for fixing it.
If your having errors check if the below directory exists
/etc/pipewire
~/.config/pipewire

If they don't exist, do the following and reboot and check again by running pactl info again.
sudo cp -r /usr/share/pipewire /etc/

The above command will move the config files to their default locations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swastik Dwivedi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Methods for Appending and Inserting With JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352342</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/comparing-methods-for-appending-and-inserting-with-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say we want to add something to a webpage after the initial load. JavaScript gives us a variety of tools. Perhaps you’ve used some of them, like append, appendChild, insertAdjacentHTML, or innerHTML.
The difficult thing …
The post Comparing Methods for Appending and Inserting With JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Markfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Learning Partner: Frontend Masters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351975</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/our-learning-partner-frontend-masters-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend Masters has been our learning partner for a couple of years now. I love it. If you need structured learning to up your web development skills, Frontend Masters is the place. It works so well because we don’t offer …
The post Our Learning Partner: Frontend Masters appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image Creation, Management, and Registry(Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dporwal/image-creation-management-and-registry-part-2-514n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dporwal/image-creation-management-and-registry-part-2-514n"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T12:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tagging Docker Images


Docker tags convey useful information about a specific image version/variant.
They are aliases to the ID of your image which often look like this: 8f5487c8b942
Assigning tag while building image
docker build -t demo:v1 .


Assigning tag if no tag default
Lets build a image without tag.
docker build .


Now lets assign tag to the existing image without tag.
docker tag adc07a47930e demo:v2


tag for existing tag of the image
This will create another image with the same IMAGE ID.
docker tag demo:v2 demo2:v3


Whenever you make changes inside the container, it can be useful to commit a container’s file changes or settings into a new image.
By default, the container being committed and its processes will be paused while the image is committed.
Syntax:
docker container co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Porwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding A Large E-Commerce Website With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/lessons-learned-ecommerce-nextjs-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We made the switch from a more traditional integrated e-commerce platform to a headless platform with Next.js. Here are the most important lessons learned while rebuilding a large e-commerce site with Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jonne Kats)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[80+ Linux Alternatives to Windows Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mochamadboval/80-linux-alternatives-to-windows-apps-3eia</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mochamadboval/80-linux-alternatives-to-windows-apps-3eia"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T09:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When decided to switch from Windows to Linux, the next thing you need to think about is how to find alternative apps that you usually use on Windows. You need to do this because not all apps that available on Windows are also available for Linux, especially apps from developers like Adobe and Microsoft itself. But don't worry, in this article I will share with you some of the alternative apps that I know.
Here is the list:



Category
Apps





2D Animation (alt. Adobe Animate, Toon Boom Harmony)


OpenToonz, Pencil2D, Synfig Studio




3D Animation (alt. Autodesk 3ds Max, Autodesk Maya)


Bforartists, Blender



Academic & Research Management

Mendeley, Zotero



All-in-One Messaging App

Ferdi, Franz, Rambox




Archive Manager (alt. WinRAR)

PeaZip



Audio Editing & Recording (alt. Ado…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mochamad Boval</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configura AutoFirma con el DNIe en Ubuntu Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sinhouse/configura-autofirma-con-el-dnie-en-ubuntu-linux-34gh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sinhouse/configura-autofirma-con-el-dnie-en-ubuntu-linux-34gh"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T07:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nota: este post es la continuación de 
.
AutoFirma es el sistema de firma electrónica desarrollado por la administración pública en España.
Con este software podemos aprovechar el certificado digital de nuestro DNIe para firmar cualquier documento generando un fichero nuevo con el sufijo _signed.csig.
firmado por nosotros y que no ha sufrido ninguna modificación.
AutoFirma está desarrollado en Java por lo que vamos a instalar el soporte JRE por defecto en Ubuntu:
sudo apt install default-jre

A continuación descargamos el fichero comprimido de AutoFirma para sistemas Linux desde la web oficial y lo instalamos:
mkdir -p /tmp/AutoFirma
wget -P /tmp/AutoFirma https://estaticos.redsara.es/comunes/autofirma/1/6/5/AutoFirma_Linux.zip
unzip /tmp/AutoFirma_Linux.zip -d /tmp/AutoFirma
sudo dpkg -i …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J. Mulet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side Navigation - Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/karthikeyans21/side-navigation-angular-265a</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/karthikeyans21/side-navigation-angular-265a"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I hope you're doing good. Here as an angular UI developers we would have used many frameworks and libraries for minimizing our works or some of us are new to angular UI stream we would have been searching for side navigation with a well-defined style or animation effects but most of us won't get one. So I'm going to spend some time showing how to do that without depending on frameworks and libraries, it is quite simple. Let's jump into creation.
First, create a new project or just create a module in your existing project. To create a module, use the below command, or whatever you use all the time it will make no difference. I've named it side-nav you can use your own.
ng g m side-nav --route side-nav --module app.module

After this, we should be seeing these files created in a folder a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>karthikeyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Online Workshop: Frustrating Design Patterns And How To Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/smashing-workshop-frustrating-design-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve seen them before. Confusing and frustrating design patterns that seem to be chasing you everywhere you go, from one website to another. It’s time to fix them for good in a [free Smashing online workshop](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/workshops/vitaly-friedman-frustrating-patterns/) next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Install Ubuntu 20.04 LTS (For Beginners)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/devtonight/how-to-install-ubuntu-20-04-lts-for-beginners-2a9e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/devtonight/how-to-install-ubuntu-20-04-lts-for-beginners-2a9e"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T04:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The installation process of Ubuntu 20.04 LTS (Focal Fossa) can be a bit challenging, especially for people who are not much familiar with Linux environments. Among worst cases, it can cause data deletions, file corruptions or even complete system boot failures. This guide is focused on beginners and previous Ubuntu or any other Linux experience is not necessary. After following this guide, you will be able to install Ubuntu 20.04 LTS on your desktop computer or laptop by yourself.
As mentioned earlier, this process can be critical. So make sure to keep following things in your mind.
This guide is mainly focused on fresh Ubuntu 20.04 LTS installations. That means your computer should not have any OS (Operating System) or otherwise if exist it can be unusable anymore.
All partitions, files, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devtonight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Your Page Title on a Google Search Engine Results Page?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-is-your-page-title-on-a-google-search-engine-results-page/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T18:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever Google wants it to be. I always thought it was exactly what your <title> element was. Perhaps in lieu of that, what the first <h1> on the page is. But recently I noticed some pages on this site that …
The post What is Your Page Title on a Google Search Engine Results Page? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working With GraphQL Caching]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352381</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/working-with-graphql-caching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve recently started working with GraphQL, or reviewed its pros and cons, you’ve no doubt heard things like “GraphQL doesn’t support caching” or “GraphQL doesn’t care about caching.” And for most, that is a big deal.
The official …
The post Working With GraphQL Caching appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Barton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Build True Edge Apps With Cloudflare Workers and Fauna]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352487</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/learn-how-to-build-true-edge-apps-with-cloudflare-workers-and-fauna/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
There is a lot of buzz around apps running on the edge instead of on a centralized server in web development. Running your app on the edge allows your code to be closer to …
The post Learn How to Build True Edge Apps With Cloudflare Workers and Fauna appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Form Styles With `accent-color`]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/simplifying-form-styles-accent-color/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new CSS `accent-color` property makes it quick and easy to roll out our brand colors to certain form inputs by leveraging user agent styles. In this article we’ll take a look at what it does and how to use it alongside `color-scheme` for simple, accessible checkboxes and radio buttons — and imagine how we might use it in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Units Should Be Pretty Handy]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352210</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/container-units-should-be-pretty-handy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T23:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container queries are going to solve this long-standing issue in web design where we want to make design choices based on the size of an element (the container) rather than the size of the entire page. So, if a container …
The post Container Units Should Be Pretty Handy appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter’s div Soup and Uglyfied CSS, Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352388</id>
        <link href="https://giuseppegurgone.com/twitter-html/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T21:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I came up in web development (2005-2010 were formative years for me), one of the first lessons I learned was to have a clean foundation of HTML. “What Beautiful HTML Code Looks Like” is actually one of the most …
The post Twitter’s div Soup and Uglyfied CSS, Explained appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Your `head` Straight: A New CSS Performance Diagnostics Snippet]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/css-head-tag/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love little useful tools and techniques to help folks get their work done better and faster. Today, we’d love to shine the spotlights on a little helper that helps spot common performance bottlenecks easily: [ct.css](https://csswizardry.com/ct/).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Logging in a Node.js Application With Pino-logger]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352074</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-implement-logging-in-a-node-js-application-with-pino-logger/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging, on its own, is a key aspect of any application. Logging helps developers comprehend what it is that their code is doing. It also helps save developers hours of debugging work. This tutorial is about implementing logging in a …
The post How to Implement Logging in a Node.js Application With Pino-logger appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarthak Duggal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposal for CSS @when]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352328</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/proposal-for-css-when/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T22:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is on a tear lately. Again, I’ve heard of a brand new thing I’ve never seen before, and again it’s via Miriam: CSS Conditionals. 
🎉 CSSWG just resolved to adopt @tabatkins when/else proposal into the next level of CSS 
…
The post Proposal for CSS @when appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cascade Layers?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=352140</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cascade-layers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T19:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a new thing coming in CSS: @layer. As with all new things, it takes time to really wrap your head around it. And despite me tapping at my keyboard about it, full disclosure, I’m not sure my …
The post Cascade Layers? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Practical Uses for the ::before and ::after Pseudo-Elements in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=351992</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/7-practical-uses-for-the-before-and-after-pseudo-elements-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T14:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS ::before and ::after pseudo-elements allow you to insert “content” before and after any non-replaced element (e.g. they work on a <div> but not an <input>). This effectively allows you to show something on a web page that might …
The post 7 Practical Uses for the ::before and ::after Pseudo-Elements in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Your Own Mouseless Development Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/mouseless-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a development environment with the shell as a keystone offers multiple benefits. You can customize everything depending on your own needs, and the biggest of all, you can control your entire development environment with your keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthieu Cneude)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Web Development Tools Are Helping Users Keep Pace With Rapid Change]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-development-tools-users-keep-pace-rapid-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last 18 months have been a time of unprecedented turbulence. As the people of the world have flooded online, businesses have joined them, using web development tools to adapt in real-time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Imposter Domains Re-Publishing Your Website?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/imposter-domains-republishing-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content scraping is a fact of life on the Internet. When you think of web scraping, you probably do not think about the scrapers turning around and immediately serving your entire, whole page content on another website. But what if your site content is being re-published?  It might be already happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ken Harker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetize Open-Source Software With Gatsby Functions And Stripe]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/monetize-open-source-software-gatsby-functions-stripe/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby Functions provide front-end developers a way to write and use server-side code without the hassle of maintaining a server. If making money from open-source is of interest to you and your site isn’t built using Gatsby, this approach may well be the answer you were looking for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Quality Assurance: From User Requirements To Web Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/journey-into-web-quality-assurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty years ago, Elie Sloïm chose to dedicate his professional life to web quality assurance. He started asking, ”What does quality mean for a web user?” Well, this article explains everything he has learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Elie Sloïm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons To Build A CRM-Powered Website For Your Business]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reasons-build-crm-powered-website-business/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a CRM with your business website has numerous benefits. In this article, Zara Cooper explains what these benefits are and why websites should be integrated with a CRM platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Zara Cooper)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.1"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Unexpected nested element in author field crashes the parser
Thank you @ad-m]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Need For Pseudo-Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-need-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pseudo-elements have faithfully helped front-end developers implement creative designs. While they still have an important place, we can now leave pseudo-elements behind in some scenarios, thanks to newer CSS properties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moreau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Pen And Paper Sketching]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/power-pen-paper-sketching/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When designing for digital spaces, it’s natural to default to digital mockup tools, but doing so cuts out a world of possibilities. Analog drawing can unleash your imagination and allow you to focus on what’s most important at the start: the ideas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tracy Osborn)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating Complexity With Web Animations API]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/orchestrating-complexity-web-animations-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are way too many options in Web Animations API to pick them up that easily. Learning how timing works and how to control the playback of several animations at once makes for a solid foundation on which to base your projects on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kirill Myshkin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Excellent Editorial]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/web-design-done-well-excellent-editorial/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say content is king, and they’re right. The web has unlocked untold possibilities for storytellers — provided the story is right, of course. Here are some of our favorite examples of editorial content thriving in the digital realm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SWR React Hooks With Next.js’ Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/useswr-react-hook-library-incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When paired with ISR and Next.js’ API routes, SWR can be used to create a responsive user experience. In this article, Sam Poder explains what SWR is, where to use it (and where not), and how to build a website by using Incremental Static Regeneration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Decisions For Building Flexible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/developer-decisions-building-flexible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll walk through the process of taking a seemingly simple design for a text-and-media component and deciding how best to translate it into code, keeping in mind the needs of both users and content authors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Smashing Online Workshops on Front-End & UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/new-smashing-online-workshops-sep-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the state of HTML Email, Vue.js and Next.js? What are new, smart interface design patterns we could use? Let’s figure it out. With our brand new online workshops on front-end & design. Now with **free workshops** for you to test the waters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New With DevTools: Cross-Browser Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/devtools-cross-browser-edition/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what’s new with developer tools in Firefox, Edge, Chrome and Safari. Discover new and powerful features that will help you be more comfortable and productive when testing and debugging across browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTTP/3: Practical Deployment Options (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/http3-practical-deployment-options-part3/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost five years in development, the new HTTP/3 protocol is nearing its final form. Let’s take a close look at the challenges involved in deploying and testing HTTP/3, and how and if you should change your websites and resources as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robin Marx)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Carbon Emissions On The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/reducing-carbon-emissions-on-web/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Websites, unfortunately, aren’t as environmentally friendly as we might like them to be. This article contains some thoughts and experiences from trying to clean them up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Berwyn Powell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive Learning Tools For Front-End Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/interactive-learning-tools-front-end-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive coding tools to help you learn CSS, JavaScript, SQL, React, Vim, regular expressions and Jamstack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into The Wonderful World Of SVG Displacement Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/09/deep-dive-wonderful-world-svg-displacement-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly is a displacement filter? In this article, Dirk Weber explains the SVG `feDisplacementMap` filter primitive with a good number of examples to demonstrate the concept of animated displacement maps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dirk Weber)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Management In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/state-management-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By combining some React APIs, we can accurately manage “simple” states. With Next.js though, we can quickly find situations where we need to accommodate many other requirements. Let’s have a look at some patterns to accomplish all that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stories Of September (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New month, new wallpapers! In this post, you’ll find inspiring wallpaper designs for September 2021. They were created with love by artists and designers from across the globe and are available with and without a calendar. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring CSS: Optimizing Size And Performance (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-optimizing-size-performance-part3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/08/refactoring-css-optimizing-size-performance-part3/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many CSS optimization techniques to tackle potential file size and performance issues. Let’s take a look at some of them. After all, if deploying the refactored codebase causes loading or performance issues, it will result in less traffic and revenue, which might leave the management and project managers dissatisfied.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>