<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-11-01T01:05:25.972Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-01T01:05:25.972Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Hacktoberfest2021 Journey]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kwing25/my-hacktoberfest2021-journey-4cc5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kwing25/my-hacktoberfest2021-journey-4cc5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T00:49:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest 2021 ~ Women In Tech App/API creation ~ A Web Dev's Reflection


Hacktoberfest2021
 / 
        Women-Who-ve-Changed-Tech
      
    
‣The Project ‣The Beginning ‣The Future ‣Being a Maintainer ‣Women In Tech ‣Thanks ‣See more
This was my 1st time being a Contrbutor & Maintainer in Hactoberfest. I'm a new Bootcamp Grad & Developer and this event was a great opportunity to contribute to Open Source Projects.   
Looking at the many open source projects I decided I wanted to do more than just contribute. For a while, I've wanted to do a Female Tech Pioneers Web API/React App after noticing that there aren't many sources online of just Females in Tech. I decided to start a project that would build the foundation of an all-Women Tech & STEM Pioneer API and Website. I wanted to have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kendra Wing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/angular-environment-mbp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/angular-environment-mbp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T00:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As variáveis de ambiente permitem que nós possamos incluir no nosso código condições, parâmetros e valores diferentes de acordo com nosso ambiente. 
Imagine que você utilize uma API Rest de um serviço qualquer, seja ele criado internamente na empresa que você trabalha, seja ele de terceiros e que esse serviço ofereça um endpoint para homologação e outro para produção.
Uma abordagem inicial seria trocar os valores dessa api todas as vezes que quisermos publicar nossa aplicação em produção.
Uma abordagem muito mais elegante é configurar as variáveis de ambiente para que você não tenha que lembrar de trocar o conteúdo de nenhuma variável.
Aqui mostro como fazer isso utilizando o recurso de configuração de ambiente do Angular.
Projetos criados com Angular CLI possuem por padrão um arquivo de configuração chamado environment.ts disponível na pasta environments da sua aplicação.

environment.ts:
export const environment = {
  production: false
};

environment.prod.ts
export const environment = {
  production: true
};

Veja um exemplo de como usar o environment.
import { environment } from '../environments/environment';

environment = environment;

<div class="row justify-content-center" *ngIf="!environment.production">    
    <div class="auth-box text-center">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <button type="button" (click)="LimparTudo()" class="btn btn-danger btn-md btn-block waves-effect text-center m-b-20">Limpar Memória</button>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/angular-environment-mbp</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/angular-environment-mbp"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T00:40:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As variáveis de ambiente permitem que nós possamos incluir no nosso código condições, parâmetros e valores diferentes de acordo com nosso ambiente. 
Imagine que você utilize uma API Rest de um serviço qualquer, seja ele criado internamente na empresa que você trabalha, seja ele de terceiros e que esse serviço ofereça um endpoint para homologação e outro para produção.
Uma abordagem inicial seria trocar os valores dessa api todas as vezes que quisermos publicar nossa aplicação em produção.
Uma abordagem muito mais elegante é configurar as variáveis de ambiente para que você não tenha que lembrar de trocar o conteúdo de nenhuma variável.
Aqui mostro como fazer isso utilizando o recurso de configuração de ambiente do Angular.
Projetos criados com Angular CLI possuem por padrão um arquivo de configuração chamado environment.ts disponível na pasta environments da sua aplicação.

environment.ts:
export const environment = {
  production: false
};

environment.prod.ts
export const environment = {
  production: true
};

Veja um exemplo de como usar o environment.
import { environment } from '../environments/environment';

environment = environment;

<div class="row justify-content-center" *ngIf="!environment.production">    
    <div class="auth-box text-center">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-md-12">
                <button type="button" (click)="LimparTudo()" class="btn btn-danger btn-md btn-block waves-effect text-center m-b-20">Limpar Memória</button>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publicação automática de um app flutter na PlayStore com Github Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/publicacao-automatica-de-um-app-flutter-na-playstore-com-github-actions-i4b</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/publicacao-automatica-de-um-app-flutter-na-playstore-com-github-actions-i4b"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T00:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O objetivo desse post é detalhar o passo a passo para publicar uma aplicação Flutter na Play Store.
A primeira publicação deve ser feita manualmente e só depois de aprovado pela PlayStore que será possível fazer o deploy totalmente automatizado.
Abra o Android Studio, acesse Build/Generate Signed Bundle or Apk, na próxima tela escolha Android App Bundle e clique em Next. Clique em Create new... para criar uma key store nova.
Lembre-se de guardar o conteúdo que for utilizado nos campos de senha e no campo Alias. Você vai precisar deles depois.

Após concluir a geração da chave, abra o terminal do seu SO e execute os comandos abaixo. Obs: Se estiver no Windows, talvez precise instalar o openssl antes. Talvez esse link do StackOverflow possa te ajudar.
Uma vez que você esteja com o arquivo my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of AWS : Containers,
Database,
Developer Tools Services| AWS WhitePaper Summary]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/overview-of-aws-containersdatabasedeveloper-tools-services-aws-whitepaper-summary-398e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/awsmenacommunity/overview-of-aws-containersdatabasedeveloper-tools-services-aws-whitepaper-summary-398e"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T22:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers


Amazon Elastic Container Registry (ECR) is a fully-managed Docker container registry that makes it easy for developers to store, manage, and deploy Docker container images.
Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) is a highly scalable, high-performance container orchestration service that supports Docker containers and allows you to easily run and scale containerized applications on AWS. 
Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) makes it easy to deploy, manage, and scale containerized applications using Kubernetes on AWS.
AWS App2Container (A2C) is a command-line tool for modernizing .NET and Java applications into containerized applications. A2C analyzes and builds an inventory of all applications running in virtual machines, on-premises, or in the cloud.
Red Hat O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>‪Karim Negm‬‏</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest: Final Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/belokond/hacktoberfest-final-challenge-42d</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/belokond/hacktoberfest-final-challenge-42d"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T22:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking For an Issue


The last issue for the #Hacktoberfest challenge was really difficult to find.
After a long time of trying to find an issue with no luck, I decided to cheat a little and see what repos my classmates were contributing to. Funnily enough, I noticed that 3 of my classmates contributed to the same repo - usTaxes. This made me wonder what was so special about that repo, like why would my classmates care about US Taxes in Canada?? Or even generally care about taxes 😵 So I decided to take a look at that repo and see what's going on. I still don't know why they would choose it but I noticed that it had quite a few issues that were manageable and straightforward. So I decided to try and see how it goes, even though I'm not interested in taxes 😅
The issue I chose was related …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbelokon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dyslexic DEV? No problem!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/realvorl/dyslexic-dev-no-problem-1nfc</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/realvorl/dyslexic-dev-no-problem-1nfc"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T22:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given


that I am dyslexic and also suffer from aphantasia, which is a fascinating quirk of the brain, one  can imagine I have sort of a love / hate relationship with reading. 
On the one hand, I must keep up with the news and trends of the software engineering industry but the serious and useful information I require, is in written form and that always drains my reading battery because of the above average amount of concentration I have to put forward.
daylight saving Weekend rolled around, I decided to do something useful with the "additional" hour, so I set out to improve this situation for people like me. 
I decided to build something that allows us to take the text from any article in any language (English, German, Romanian in my case) and convert it to an mp3 file so that we can "lis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viorel PETCU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest: Challenge #3]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/belokond/hacktoberfest-challenge-3-1482</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/belokond/hacktoberfest-challenge-3-1482"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T21:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Experience Looking for Issues


This time it took me quite a while to find another issue to work on. There were so many repos that I found that weren't active, didn't have any open issues, or the issues were too complicated/already assigned to someone else. I didn't expect that finding issues would be that hard!🥵🙈 
Eventually, I remembered one of the repos that I've used before to contribute to one of the Hacktoberfest issues, I thought that it would be nice to give back (hint hint😉😉😉 something to think about when looking for an issue... hint😉) to that repo. I quickly gave up everything I was doing and went to check it out to see if it is even active and if it has any open issues I could work on. To my surprise, no one except the author has ever contributed to that before, so I am…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbelokon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy containerized functions on AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mubbashir10/deploy-container-images-on-aws-lambda-functions-254h</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mubbashir10/deploy-container-images-on-aws-lambda-functions-254h"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T19:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS lambda lets you deploy containerized functions by packaging your AWS lambda function code and dependencies using Docker upto a size of 10gb. Here's a tutorial to demonstrate how you can containerize and deploy nodejs based lambda function.
If you prefer you can clone the repo, otherwise follow along.
Create a file called functions.js inside your node project and add the following sample function to it.
// A sample function to demo containers deployment on aws lambda
exports.helloLambda = async (event) => {
  const response = {
    isBase64Encoded: false,
    statusCode: 200,
    headers: {
      "Content-Type": "application/json",
    },
    body: JSON.stringify({
      message: "Containers on lambda!🐳",
    }),
  };
  return response;
};

Create a Dockerfile with the following conten…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mubbashir Mustafa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DPS909 - Release 0.2 W4]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/romanrezinkin/dps909-release-02-w4-55k9</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/romanrezinkin/dps909-release-02-w4-55k9"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T17:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week 4 Hacktoberfest


For this week, I have chosen to work on this repository: link. The issue that was asked from the creator was to implement jwt tokens that should be returned when a user authenticates themselves into the program.
The issue could be found here: issue link
I have made a PR with my changes, which could be found here:
PR Link
Here is my commit link:commit
Currently, I am waiting for the owner to add the Hacktoberfest label to the issue, as well as review my PR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roman Rezinkin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 1 - Building Projects to impress 🤯🤯 Employers or Hiring Managers [VoteSub]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kiranbansode/week-1-building-projects-to-impress-employers-or-hiring-managers-votesub-4e9n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kiranbansode/week-1-building-projects-to-impress-employers-or-hiring-managers-votesub-4e9n"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T17:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone, My name is Kiran A. Bansode. I'm a self-taught Full-Stack web developer.
This is 2nd blog of Building Projects to impress 🤯🤯 Employers or Hiring Managers[VoteSub] series.
So as from 1st blog you already know, Why I'm buiding this project ?
In this blog I'm going to share you, What I did in last 3 days ?
No matter what if your project is small or big,  SDLC(Software Development Life-Cycle) methodology will provide clearly defined processes for creating high-quality software.
Requirement(Research)
Design
Coding
Testing
Production 
Maintenance
On Day - 1, I did some research for my project like, Which will be most common input fields ? What data will be required for firebase to create a new user ? ... and much more.
On the basis of that research, I designed two pages using Fig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kiranbansode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LERN GQL WITH ME: Schema Definition Language]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/darshanbajeja/lern-gql-with-me-schema-definition-language-24h1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/darshanbajeja/lern-gql-with-me-schema-definition-language-24h1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T16:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Examples taken from howtographql)
Welcome to the second part of Learn GraphQL With Me. In this post we will be learning about some core concepts related to GraphQL. These concepts are language independent, so it means that you do not need to know any particular language to understand these, as these are GraphQL specific, and once understood can be implemented in any language.
One thing to keep in mind here is that as GraphQL is different from REST and SOAP, you need to try to understand this little differently as GraphQL has its own specific concepts, which are independent of any other type of API.
So let's finally begin learning GraphQL.
GraphQL has its own type system for defining schemas, like we do for modelling the database tables (for SQL) and documents (for NoSQL). This is called the SDL or the Schema Definition Language. 
So this is how you define schemas or types in GraphQL:
type Person {
    name: String!
    age: Int!
}

Notice how we have ! after the data types String and Int. This tells that 'name' and 'age' are compulsory. If we just wrote name as name: String, this would have meant that it is not compulsory that Person has a name.
Let's also add a Post type to our schema:
type Post {
    title: String!
}

Now what if we want to have relations between the Post and the Person type. We can now use Person and Post as a data type, like we use String, Int. So let's define an author field, which is of type Person.
type Post {
    title: String!
    author: Person!
}

This tells that a Post will have an author who will be a Person. But we also want to say that a Person can write many posts, so how do we do that. Let's add a posts field to Person type which will be an array of type Post.
type Person {
    name: String!
    age: Int!
    posts: [Post!]!
}

Notice how we have ! after Post as well as after ], this tells that the array is compulsory as well as there has to be some data of type Post inside it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darshan-Bajeja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple App with session-based authentication in Express.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dejansdev/simple-app-with-session-based-authentication-in-expressjs-2mog</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dejansdev/simple-app-with-session-based-authentication-in-expressjs-2mog"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T15:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DISCLAIMER: This is not "the best way" or "should do" blog post, instead I will just try to share my experience and what I find to work out.
The goal is to create an application that will implement session-based authentication in Node.js using the Express.js framework. 
The application is available on the following link Authentication App, and the complete code is available on the GitHub repository.
Authentication
Basic application setup
Database
Register and login functionality
Session-based authentication
Logout functionality 
Protecting routes and checking the current user
It is important to distinguish between authentication and authorization. Authentication is the process of verifying the identity of the user 401 Unauthorized and authorization dictates what the user can see and do whe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dejan Samardzija</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install Gromacs, PyMOL, AutoDock Vina, VMD, MGLTools, Avogadro2, Open Babel in Ubuntu 20.04]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/abdnahid/how-to-install-gromacs-pymol-autodock-vina-vmd-mgltools-avogadro-open-babel-in-ubuntu-2004-1867</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/abdnahid/how-to-install-gromacs-pymol-autodock-vina-vmd-mgltools-avogadro-open-babel-in-ubuntu-2004-1867"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T14:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most time-consuming and frustrating aspects of computational tasks has always been properly installing software and getting it up and running in no time. In the case of bioinformatics tools, this is notoriously difficult in some cases, particularly in Linux-based operating systems such as Ubuntu, where one-click installer files, unlike Windows, are not an option. Although much of the popular software in the bioinformatics world is easy to install in Ubuntu if one is familiar with the ecosystem, a beginner will certainly have a difficult time circling the internet trying to find a proper installation method, at least, that’s what I had to go through when I first started out.
Here in this article, I compiled out the installation methods of some of the most commonly used bioinformatics and simulation tools, as well as how to run these tools after installing them on an Ubuntu 20.04 machine. Feel free to let me know which software should be added next.



  
  
  Before running any of the commands below, run this command once:





sudo apt-get -y update

sudo apt-get install -y avogadro

Avogadro2





avogadro2

sudo apt-get install -y pymol

pymol





pymol

sudo apt-get install -y gromacs

Gromacs





gmx

cd ~

curl -k https://www.ks.uiuc.edu/Research/vmd/vmd-1.9.3/files/final/vmd-1.9.3.bin.LINUXAMD64-CUDA8-OptiX4-OSPRay111p1.opengl.tar.gz --output vmd.tar.gz

mkdir -p vmd

tar -xvzf vmd.tar.gz -C vmd --strip-components=1

cd vmd

./configure

cd src

sudo make install

VMD





vmd

sudo apt-get install -y autodock-vina

AutoDock Vina





vina

cd ~

curl -k https://ccsb.scripps.edu/download/532/ --output mgltools.tar.gz

mkdir -p mgltools

tar -xvzf mgltools.tar.gz -C mgltools --strip-components=1

cd mgltools

bash install.sh

source ./initMGLtools.sh 


Python Molecule Viewer (PMV)





pmv

AutoDockTools (ADT)





adt

Vision





vision

sudo apt-get install -y openbabel

openbabel





obabel

sudo apt-get install -y openbabel-gui

openbabel gui





obgui]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdullah Al Nahid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hawk Open Source Project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/medpaf/hawk-open-source-project-4okk</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/medpaf/hawk-open-source-project-4okk"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T13:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hawk is a network and pentest utility that I developed so that I could perform different kinds of task using the same suite, instead of jumping from one tool to another.
ifconfig, 
ping, 
traceroute, 
port scans (including SYN, TCP, UDP, ACK, comprehensive scan), 
host discovery (scan for up devices on a local network), 
MAC address detection (get MAC address of a host IP on a local network), 
banner grabbing, 
DNS checks (with geolocation information), 
WHOIS, 
subdomain enumeration, 
vulnerability reconnaissance, - 
packet sniffing, 
MAC spoofing, 
IP spoofing, 
SYN flooding, 
deauth attack, 
brute-force attack (beta).
Other features are still being implemented. Future implementations may include WAF detection, DNS enumeration, traffic analysis, XSS vulnerability scanner, ARP cache poisoning, DNS cache poisoning, MAC flooding, ping of death, network disassociation attack (not deauth attack), OSINT, exploits, some automated tasks and others.
Link to the repository: 
https://github.com/medpaf/hawk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulo Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bazeng/installing-docker-217g</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bazeng/installing-docker-217g"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T13:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker has different versions:
Community 
Enterprise
We will be working with the community edition.
If you are using:
Windows Visit Windows Docker Installation Notes


Mac Os Visit Mac Docker Installation Notes


Linux Visit Linux Docker Installation Notes



If you have trouble installing ,reach out to me on Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel K.M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notificação no Telegram pelo Github Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/felipemsfg/telegram-github-actions-26nj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/felipemsfg/telegram-github-actions-26nj"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T12:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Para receber notificações no Telegram sempre que seu script executar no Github Actions, use o script abaixo:
    - name: Send Telegram Message Ok
        uses: appleboy/telegram-action@master
        env:
          GITHUB_CONTEXT: ${{ toJSON(github) }}
        with:
          to: ${{ secrets.TELEGRAM_ID }}
          token: ${{ secrets.TELEGRAM_TOKEN }}
          format: markdown
          message: |
            *1ª linha da mensagem*
            *2ª linha da mensagem*
            Applicação: *Preencha como quiser e com quantas linhas quiser* os asteriscos são apenas para deixar o conteúdo em negrito. As linhas abaixo também fazem parte da mensagem e foram escritas para o exemplo.          
            Branch: *${{ github.ref }}*
            Repository: *${{ github.repository }}*
          …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe Marques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction To Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bazeng/docker-tutorial-series-4d97</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bazeng/docker-tutorial-series-4d97"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T12:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is an open platform for developing, shipping, and running applications.
In lay mans language i would define docker as a platform that enables you build once and deploy everywhere.Docker enables you to separate your applications from your infrastructure, therefore you wont have to set up all the dependencies your apps need all over again and again as you migrate between different environments
Before proceeding further it is important to highlight some important concepts that you will commonly hear of in the docker world .This are:
A Docker image is a lightweight, standalone, executable package of software .For example we have a mysql image which includes everything needed to run mysql: code, runtime, system tools, system libraries and settings
The hub is a repository where container images are stored. You can get public images as well as store your own private images.
Docker Container is a layer of images .

Docker images become containers when they run on Docker Engine.

Docker Engine is the runtime environment for all containers. Docker engine can be used in both linux and windows based infrastructure. A docker application can easily be run in any environment as long as there is a docker engine.
This solves the “dependency hell” for developers and operations teams, and eliminating the “it works on my laptop!” problem.

Before understanding the difference between Docker and Virtual machines its important to understand Operating systems. Operating systems have an application and kernel layer

Docker virtualizes the application layer and use the kernel of the host while a virtual machines virtualizes both application & kernel layer.
Docker size is small a couple of megabytes while a virtual machine size is large a couple of gigabytes .
Docker is faster while a virtual machines size is slower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel K.M</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/nicm42/linux-2ofa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/nicm42/linux-2ofa"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T10:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like a lot of people on here who use Linux like to talk about Linux. I am not an exception, so here's my journey/opinions on Linux.
My first exposure to Linux was in a virtual machine and it was OpenSUSE. Which I remember very little about now, except that I thought it was quite fun. I mostly just looked at it a bit, but I liked it.
When Netbooks came out, you could get a 9 inch one with Linux on it. I don't remember which distro was on it, but it wasn't a common one. I don't think it said when it was sold, I googled to find out. It was more of a useful little computer to have on your lap on the sofa for odd little bits, so the OS didn't make a great deal of difference. But the computer not being very powerful meant Linux was better on it than Windows.
I don't remember what it was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide To Express Middlewares]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ps173/guide-to-express-middlewares-i7f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ps173/guide-to-express-middlewares-i7f"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T09:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A basic definition


Express middlewares are the functions that have access to the request, response and next function in applications request response cycle. The next function calls the next middleware that is succeding the current middleware.
Let's simplify the above statement a bit. So a express middleware is basically a function that has req,res and next as a parameters. For example,
const express = require('express')
const app = express()

function logger(req, res, next) {
  console.log("I am a middleware and I log the text");
  next();
}
app.use(logger)
app.get('/', (req,res)=>{
 res.send("Hellow World!!")
})
app.listen(3000)

Now here I have a logger function which is a middleware. Yup that's how simple a middleware can be. Here the logger function has one thing which other function…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pratham Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevent Heroku Server from Sleeping for FREE]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/j471n/prevent-heroku-server-from-sleeping-for-free-1ib1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/j471n/prevent-heroku-server-from-sleeping-for-free-1ib1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T09:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I am gonna tell you about how you can run the Heroku server free for a lifetime. So let's get into it.
As you may have known that Heroku does not allow your app to run for more than 1 hour. When an app on Heroku has only one web dyno and that dyno doesn't receive any traffic in 1 hour, the dyno goes to sleep.
When someone accesses the app, the dyno manager automatically wakes up the web dyno to run the web process type. This causes a short delay for this first request, but subsequent requests perform normally.
So now how can we run it forever without sleep? so that web process or API request doesn't have any kind of delay.
Heroku


Firstly you need to have a Heroku app which can be a new or old one. if you don't have a Heroku app Click Here

Now the next part is the domain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jatin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefits Of Using Pipe Over Function In Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/stackblogger/benefits-of-using-pipe-over-function-in-angular-2mgj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/stackblogger/benefits-of-using-pipe-over-function-in-angular-2mgj"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T09:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article is originally published at my blog here: Benefits Of Using Pipe Over Function In Angular
Do you use functions / methods to implement various conditions and DOM manipulations in Angular ? If yes, trust me it will worsen your website performance. In this tutorial I will explain how pipes increase your angular website performance and what are the various benefits of using Pipe over Functions based on a case study.
Before diving straight into tutorial, let’s start with some basic questions.
The first question comes in mind- What is Pipe? A simple definition of pipe- it is a decorative function in Angular used to manipulate DOM. It takes an untransformed value as input and returns a transformed value as output.
Various built-in pipes are provided by Angular- AsyncPipe, CurrencyPipe,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jameer Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Splash Of Color For Misty Days (November 2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November is just around the corner, and with it, a new collection of desktop wallpapers to celebrate the beginning of the month. Designed by creatives from all across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar. Let’s make November colorful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving deep into JavaScript functions]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/diving-deep-into-javascript-functions-276f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rawas_aditya/diving-deep-into-javascript-functions-276f"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@codewithaditya]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aditya Rawas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetching Query and Route Parameters in Express.js]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/davidamunga/fetching-query-and-route-parameters-in-expressjs-1d92</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/davidamunga/fetching-query-and-route-parameters-in-expressjs-1d92"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T08:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Oskar Yildiz on Unsplash
Express.js is a popular backend web application framework for Node.js. While setting up your routes you might encounter scenarios where you need to fetch the parameters specified in the URL path to retrieve a particular set of data. This article will take you through how to extract values from URL route and query parameters. 
We recommend you have some basic experience with Javascript and NodeJS and have setup simple routes using Express.js before you go on with this guide.
A Query String is the part that comes after the Question mark ? in a URL. Let's take an example URL.
https://example.com/api/users?type=admin&status=active

The URL above fetches a list of users with a type of admin and status is active .To fetch these values in Express you can access t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Amunga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The "DeRxJSViewModel Pattern": The E=mc^2 of State Management [Part 2]]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/zackderose/the-derxjsviewmodel-pattern-the-emc2-of-state-management-part-2-2i73</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/zackderose/the-derxjsviewmodel-pattern-the-emc2-of-state-management-part-2-2i73"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T07:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[👋 hi all - this article is a continuation of a previous article that explains the goals of the DeRxJS pattern:
entirely de-couple state management code from presentational code (to the point where your state management code could be re-used across frameworks)
maximize the benefits of RxJS, while minimizing the negatives
next-level testing [and potential to hand over all our state-management code to AI at some point]
In that article, we did most of the heavy lifting - developing our state-management code and fully testing out every edge case with "timeline testing" (allowing us to assert not only "what" state looks like, but "when" it should look that way as well).
In this article, we'll bring that state management code and show how we can use this across 3 front-end "frameworks": React, A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zack DeRose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feathers.js Request Id Middleware]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/berviantoleo/feathersjs-request-id-middleware-5co0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/berviantoleo/feathersjs-request-id-middleware-5co0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T06:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare your project




Generate the app (if you don't have existing app), please see here. Basically you need to install the generator with: npm install @feathersjs/cli -g


You can follow the step-by-step in the generate app page. Some notes: I use Typescript for the codebase.




  
  
  Generate and write the Middleware



Use feathers generate middleware. You can see how I generate the middleware here.

I want to use uuidv4 as my request id. So please install the uuid use: npm install uuid @types/uuid or yarn install uuid @types/uuid (if you use yarn).


Write the middleware. We put the requestId at feathers object. You can found the file at src/middleware/request-id.ts.




import { v4 as uuidv4 } from 'uuid';
import { Request, Response, NextFunction } from 'express';

export defaul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bervianto Leo Pratama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging the Query Function Context]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tkdodo/leveraging-the-query-function-context-3i72</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tkdodo/leveraging-the-query-function-context-3i72"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T06:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all strive to improve as engineers, and as time goes by, we hopefully succeed in that endeavour. Maybe we learn new things that invalidate or challenge our previous thinking. Or we realise that patterns that we thought ideal would not scale to the level we now need them to.
Quite some time has passed since I first started to use React Query. I think I learned a great deal on that journey, and I've also "seen" a lot. I want my blog to be as up-to-date as possible, so that you can come back here and re-read it, knowing that the concepts are still valid. This is now more relevant than ever since Tanner Linsley agreed to link to my blog from the official React Query documentation.
That's why I've decided to write this addendum to my Effective React Query Keys article. Please make sure to re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominik D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to auto shutdown when you are not using the EC2 instance?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kpldvnpne/how-to-auto-shutdown-when-you-are-not-using-the-ec2-instance-5g5e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kpldvnpne/how-to-auto-shutdown-when-you-are-not-using-the-ec2-instance-5g5e"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T06:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background


I always forget to turn off the EC2 instance when I am not using the computer. Because of this, I always end up paying tons for forgetting to turn it off. The cost of these EC2 instances are usually $1 per hour. Hence, if I forget to turn it off for a whole day, I would incur $24.
This feels like something the machine should do itself and not burden me for remembering. Hence, I have gathered information from all over the web to make this short, simple and easy to follow guide.
First, we need a script that checks if there is a user connecting through SSH and turn off the EC2 instance if there are none for a set interval of time. The following script does exactly that:
#!/bin/bash
#
# Reference: https://serverfault.com/a/1061792
# Shuts down the host on inactivity.
#
# Designed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kapildev Neupane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposed Infrastructure Setup on AWS for a Microservices Architecture (3)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/proposed-infrastructure-setup-on-aws-for-a-microservices-architecture-1-5c1n</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/proposed-infrastructure-setup-on-aws-for-a-microservices-architecture-1-5c1n"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T06:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 3: Deployment Strategy for Microservices.


Chapter 2 provided an overview of the proposed infrastructure, and explained the different components used, along with its advantages. However, the aforementioned infrastructure is only as robust as the environment hosting the microservices. In fact, an improper deployment of microservices may lead to numerous problems, namely, bottlenecks, single point of failure, increased downtimes, and many more.
This chapter promotes one way of deploying microservices, along with some best practices, in order to achieve security, scalability, and availability.

To further illustrate the proposed solution, the diagram above represents a Virtual Private Cluster (VPC) located in the region Ireland (eu-west-1) (The details of creating a VPC and its under…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas El Khoury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to practice more hands on AWS and partner services ?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/leewalter/how-to-practice-more-hands-on-aws-and-partner-services--44j4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/leewalter/how-to-practice-more-hands-on-aws-and-partner-services--44j4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T05:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I hear and I forget. I see and I remember. I do and I understand."
I always like to do more hands on practices which help me remember and understand better. Below has many good and easy to follow workshops for many AWS and partner services:
https://workshops.aws/ (100 workshops and growing)
https://awsworkshop.io/ (many partners here) 
https://awesome-aws-workshops.com/ (Unofficial Curated list of awesome workshops found around in the internet.)
Just remember to do the last CLEAN UP step to delete those resources you do not need AFTER the workshops. I did a workshop a few months ago with Sysdig and EKS but forgot to delete IGW (which was to ship the EKS metrics, data to Sysdig monitoring), so a few more dollars till my billing budget alerts showed up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walter Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Query in Apache CouchDB: Mango Query]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-mango-query-lfd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-mango-query-lfd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T03:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles, we talked about design documents and how to use views to query in CouchDB. Besides Javascript query server, CouchDB also has a built-in Mango query server for us to query documents. Therefore in this article, I will talk about what is Mango Query, and when to use Mango Query?
Mango is a MongoDB inspired query language interface for Apache CouchDB.
Mango provides a single HTTP API endpoint that accepts JSON bodies via HTTP POST. These bodies provide a set of instructions that will be handled with the results being returned to the client in the same order as they were specified. The general principle of this API is to be simple to implement on the client side while providing users a more natural conversion to Apache CouchDB than would otherwise exist using the standard …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Soo Yen Yih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 console.log() alternatives]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/siddharthshyniben/7-consolelog-alternatives-377k</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/siddharthshyniben/7-consolelog-alternatives-377k"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T03:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes while debugging you may use console.log or maybe console.warn too. But there are a lot more methods which can help you debug your code even better. Let's take a look at some of them:
console.table()


The handiest method on this list. Can be used to log any object or array in table form.
console.table([
  {
    "userId": 1,
    "id": 1,
    "title": "delectus aut autem",
    "completed": false
  },
  {
    "userId": 1,
    "id": 2,
    "title": "quis ut nam facilis et officia qui",
    "completed": false
  },
  {
    "userId": 1,
    "id": 3,
    "title": "fugiat veniam minus",
    "completed": false
  },
  {
    "userId": 1,
    "id": 4,
    "title": "et porro tempora",
    "completed": true
  },
  {
    "userId": 1,
    "id": 5,
    "title": "laboriosam mollitia et enim quasi a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddharth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktoberfest PR 2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jli/hacktoberfest-pr-2-ji3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jli/hacktoberfest-pr-2-ji3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T03:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the Hacktoberfest I had been slowly working on finding issues and completing some PRs from the open source community. Similar to my first PR I did I found another fairly simple typescript issue to help contribute to for the toynet-react repo. This issue was a pretty simple one, I just needed to fix the header of a component to be the proper sizing. While working on this one I got the chance to learn about the component library chakra. Chakra is a really cool component library for React applications that provides a whole bunch of building block components to easily make a React application. It makes creating different components really easy and looks very clean as well. There are a bunch of easy to use customizations for each component and seems pretty flexible as well. This library is definitely something I wanna remember to try out when I am working with React. So thanks to chakra my solution was very simple, I just needed to use chakra's Heading component to fix the header for the component. You can checkout the PR here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JLi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running JS physics in a webworker - part 1 - proof of concept]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/jerzakm/running-js-physics-in-a-webworker-part-1-proof-of-concept-ibj</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/jerzakm/running-js-physics-in-a-webworker-part-1-proof-of-concept-ibj"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T01:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web workers are a great way of offloading compute intensive tasks from the main thread. I have been interested in using them for quite a while, but none of the projects I worked on really justified using them. Until now! In this short series I'm going to explore using webworkers, physics, pixi.js and others to create interactive web experiences and games.
Live
Github

scripts that run in background threads
they communicate with the main thread by sending and receiving messages
In depth info, better than I could ever explain:
Using web workers for safe, concurrent JavaScript - Bruce Wilson, Logrocket
MDN entry
The benefits of using webworkers are undeniable. Most importantly it keeps main thread responsive. Frozen webpages and slow UI make for terrible user experience. In my case, even if t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy .NET 6 API to AWS App Runner using AWS Copilot CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploy-net-6-api-to-aws-app-runner-using-aws-copilot-cli-4hnl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/aws-builders/deploy-net-6-api-to-aws-app-runner-using-aws-copilot-cli-4hnl"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T23:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial blog post, we are going to see how to deploy .NET 6 API to AWS App Runner using AWS Copilot CLI. 
AWS App Runner is a fully managed service that makes it easy for developers to quickly deploy containerized web applications and APIs at scale and with no prior infrastructure experience required. Start with your source code or a container image. App Runner automatically builds and deploys the web application, and load balances traffic with encryption. App Runner also scales up or down automatically to meet your traffic needs. With App Runner, you have more time to focus on your applications rather than thinking about servers or scaling. 

The features of App Runner are
Autoscaling: starting and stopping as demand changes, between configurable min and max limits.
Load balancin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sivamuthu Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[📁Elasticsearch TypeScript template]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/andrew_dev/elasticsearch-typescript-template-5d1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/andrew_dev/elasticsearch-typescript-template-5d1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T22:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! I've recently created an Elasticsearch Typescript template so you can get started using TS & Elasticsearch. 
Elasticsearch is a open-source search engine built on Apache Lucene and developed in Java. Elasticsearch allows you to store & search huge volumes of data very quickly in near real-time and give back responses in milliseconds. Yes you heard that right milliseconds... It's able to achieve these fast search speeds/responses because instead of searching the text directly, it searches through an index. It uses a structure based on documents instead of tables and schemas.
I created this template because I haven't seen many templates for Elasticsearch & Typescript and even tutorials covering this so I decided to create one to make peoples lives easier.
You can get started here!, Just follow the README on how to setup your environment variables, and setting up the server.
⭐s are much appreciated! :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andrew_dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Angular testbed setup by converting to synchronous test hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/this-is-angular/simplifying-angular-testbed-setup-by-converting-to-synchronous-test-hooks-19cl</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/this-is-angular/simplifying-angular-testbed-setup-by-converting-to-synchronous-test-hooks-19cl"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T22:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we use Angular's schematics to generate components, unnecessary asynchronous code is added to the test setup hook for its test suite.
The following test setup is generated by Angular's component generation schematic:
beforeEach(async () => {
  await TestBed.configureTestingModule({
    declarations: [MyComponent],
  }).compileComponents();
});

component schematic.





Alternatively, we might be using Angular's waitForAsync test function wrapper (formerly named async) as seen in the following code snippet:
beforeEach(waitForAsync(() => {
  TestBed.configureTestingModule({
    declarations: [MyComponent],
  }).compileComponents();
}));

waitForAsync.





Here's the deal: It's only necessary to call the static TestBed.compileComponents method if we're not using the Angular CLI to run our tests (who would do such a thing, Google? 👈😏).
The Angular CLI compiles our application and tests before the tests are run so no asynchronous action is needed for setting up the declarables.
Let's simplify the common test setup by leaving out async-await, waitForAsync, and even the TestBed.createComponent invocation as seen in this code snippet:
beforeEach(() => {
  TestBed.configureTestingModule({
    declarations: [MyComponent],
  });
});

The following points are true for common Angular testbed setup for tests covering all types of Angular declarables:
No need to use async-await
No need to use waitForAsync (formerly named async)
No need to call TestBed.compileComponents



Of course, there might be other reasons for introducing asynchronicity to our test setup but compiling and linking declarables is not one of them.
Enjoy a little less boilerplate in your Angular tests 🌞]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Gyrup Brink Nielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JWTs explained with code examples]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/propelauth/jwts-explained-with-code-examples-3k29</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/propelauth/jwts-explained-with-code-examples-3k29"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T21:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wikipedia description of a JSON Web Token (JWT) is:
JSON Web Token is a proposed Internet standard for creating data with optional signature and/or optional encryption 
However, this definition says a lot without really saying a lot. When I'm trying to understand a concept, I like to play around with relevant libraries. We'll try this out with JWTs using the popular javascript library jsonwebtoken.
The first thing the docs mention is that the sign function returns a 
secret.
const jwtLibrary = require('jsonwebtoken');

// The only arguments we need are a secret value and some JSON
const json = {"key": "value", "key2": "value2"}
const secret = "shhhhh";

// Ignore the options for now, we'll check them later
const jwt = jwtLibrary.sign(json, secret);

console.log("JWT:", jwt);
// JWT: ey…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>propelauthblog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[TypeScript][Express] Search and load local files]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/masanori_msl/typescriptexpress-search-and-load-local-files-4koa</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/masanori_msl/typescriptexpress-search-and-load-local-files-4koa"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T20:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro


This time, I will try searching local files and returning them for getting requests.
Node.js ver.17.0.1
TypeScript ver.4.4.4
Express ver.4.17.1
ts-node ver.10.4.0
I want to get files from these directories.
sample_files
    L type1
        L subFolder
            L こんにちは.txt
        L webrtc_image.pptx
    L type2
        L sub folder
            L こんにちは.txt
    L Hello world!.txt

I can get directory and file informations by "fs.promises.readdir".
import fs from "fs";

async function getFilePath(): Promise<void> {
    const directory = "C:/Users/example/OneDrive/Documents/workspace/express-sample/sample_files";    

    // get directory or file informations as fs.Dirent[]
    const paths = await fs.promises.readdir(directory, { withFileTypes: true});

    // get only file names as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Masui Masanori</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any ready-made internal user messaging solution ? (not real-time 😡)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bacloud14/any-ready-made-internal-user-messaging-solution-not-real-time--1o7p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bacloud14/any-ready-made-internal-user-messaging-solution-not-real-time--1o7p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T19:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello there !
Simply, I want that very ancient one to one messaging based on logged users (not bound to any SMTP servers or APIs, even If I use users oAuth and I have emails).
Whatever keywords I search with, I find sockets and real-time messaging everywhere. No one mentions internal and private users messaging nowhere. Unbelievable 😡.
You could suggest any real-time many-to-many solution and assume theoretically we can limit messaging to one-to-one, private, but no, 
The only scenario possible: A user is interested in one listing, he/she sends a message to the author of the thread, then they can chat about that in a small time window (2 days or something). This is important as I don't want my site to be a chatting platform.
So to sum up, I'm looking for an open-source NodeJS solution even some part of a NodeJS project that I can pick. Ready made to not reinvent the wheel, and because I'm tired of this project ;(
Many thanks !!!! and no open source solutions like Slack 😡😡 you now know why 😂
You can snitch on my profile on a French website and what I'm selling 😂]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bacloud14</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of Hacktoberfest]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tuenguyen2911_67/the-end-of-hacktoberfest-3d40</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tuenguyen2911_67/the-end-of-hacktoberfest-3d40"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T18:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, I've got my 4th pull request merged. 
I was looking some good issues in repos that I have starred and I found the issue Update CreateEvent to deal with repository creation. 
This is the live feed of the website and it failed to display the message whenever someone would create a new repo in the organization. 

Let's take a look at how the front-end component deals with the REST endpoint
    case 'CreateEvent':
    case 'DeleteEvent': {
      const target = payload?.ref;
      const targetType = payload?.ref_type;
      const action = type === 'CreateEvent'? 'created' : 'deleted';
      if (!targetType || !target) {
        return unknown;
      }
      return <span>{action} {targetType} <code>{target}</code> in</span>;
    }

and the data returned by the api
{
    "id": "18549674018",
    "type": "CreateEvent",
    "actor": {
      "id": 65370631,
      "login": "matthewcn56",
      "display_login": "matthewcn56",
      "gravatar_id": "",
      "url": "https://api.github.com/users/matthewcn56",
      "avatar_url": "https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/65370631?"
    },
    "repo": {
      "id": 419984626,
      "name": "uclaacm/status-check",
      "url": "https://api.github.com/repos/uclaacm/status-check"
    },
    "payload": {
      "ref": null,
      "ref_type": "repository",
      "master_branch": "main",
      "description": "Check the health/status of ACM's various websites/deployments!",
      "pusher_type": "user"
    },

Since ref is null when a user creates a new repo, the code returns the default message unknown. Therefore, adding a condition should fix it.
      if (!target) {
        return <span>{action} the {targetType} </span>;
      }
      if (!targetType) {
        return unknown;
      }

Though the issue wasn't hard to solve, I found it more valuable getting to know the project's workflow. I got to learn about husky, pre-commit hooks and how to make sure code linting has no error before passing the PR tests as well as GitHub API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TueNguyen2911</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Um Guia sobre Gerenciadores de Senhas]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/raissaccorreia/um-guia-sobre-gerenciadores-de-senhas-3a1p</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/raissaccorreia/um-guia-sobre-gerenciadores-de-senhas-3a1p"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T17:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introdução a essa série — Segurança Digital
Atualmente temos muitas coisas valiosas em bens digitais, por exemplo: Mensalidades de serviços de streaming, e-books comprados pela Loja do Kindle, jogos comprados na Steams, cursos comprados na Udemy ou no Coursera, a mensalidade do office ligado a sua conta de Microsoft, uma imagem pessoal ou uma carreira que é sustentada pela presença no Youtube, ou no Instagram, ou uma página do Facebook.
Não faltam exemplos de bens digitais muito valiosos, mas ainda assim, a maioria das pessoas deixa tudo escancarado sem nem mesmo uma cerca, e o motivo é simples: as pessoas não sabem construir essas proteções virtuais, e esse é o primeiro de MUITOS guias. Então me siga no Medium, ou no Twitter ou no Instagram que ainda falarei de VPN, Antivirus, Privacidade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raissa Correia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Query in Apache CouchDB: Views]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-views-4hlh</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/yenyih/query-in-apache-couchdb-views-4hlh"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T17:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this articles, I will talk about how to query documents in Apache CouchDB via Views.
A short introduce about CouchDB first for those who don't know. Apache CouchDB is an open-source document-oriented NoSQL database, implemented in Erlang. It is very easy to use as CouchDB makes use of the ubiquitous HTTP protocol and JSON data format. Do check out their Official Website for more detail. 😉
Alright, back to our main topic today.✌
First of all, before we talk about what is view, I need to introduce 2 important things in CouchDB.
The first thing to introduce is CouchDB Query Server. What is Query Server? Based on the official documentation:
The Query server is an external process that communicates with CouchDB by JSON protocol through stdio interface and processes all design functions call…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Soo Yen Yih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing my everyday errors!!]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/deek9399/fixing-my-everyday-errors-1bol</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/deek9399/fixing-my-everyday-errors-1bol"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T16:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. How do I kill a process currently using a port on localhost?


npx kill-port 8001
Inside package.json add

"type": "module",


run npm install or yarn add
stack-overflow 
// Set config defaults when creating the instance
const instance = axios.create({
  baseURL: 'https://api.example.com'
});

error code = H10


Heroku dynamically sets the PORT, which can be accessed with process.env.PORT
const port = process.env.PORT || 8001;

yarn add eslint-config-react-app
dev.to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deeksha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to stop docker containers from auto starting]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/faizanarif121/how-to-stop-docker-containers-from-auto-starting-202l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/faizanarif121/how-to-stop-docker-containers-from-auto-starting-202l"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T15:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem


As a developer, We work on different projects. Some of the projects (having oAuth or constant ports) work on only specific ports. For example, I've a project which always run on 8080. If any other process is using this port, I've to stop that process and then restart the project. 
docker containers from other projects run 
We can stop specific container by going to the specific directory and then running the following command



docker-compose down // this will shut down all the containers running in that docker environment

Additionally, to prevent a specific container from auto starting when a system is powered on (started), we can run following command
docker update --restart=no [container id] //without square brackets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Faizan Arif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a node.js app to digital ocean using Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lukeecart/how-to-deploy-a-nodejs-app-to-digital-ocean-using-docker-al6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lukeecart/how-to-deploy-a-nodejs-app-to-digital-ocean-using-docker-al6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T12:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to assume you have a working Node js app locally. In a terminal you type in npm start and whoosh we have a working node app locally. However how do you deploy it to the internet? 
You could use Platforms as a Service (PAAS) sites like Heroku and you can link your github repo to Heroku and deploy from there. At the time of writing that costs $7/month (roughly £5/month)
But there is a more Devops pro like way which may be more customisable. 
Digital Ocean (the lowest version is $5/month or £3.65 /month) which also offers a PAAS or Infrastructure as a service (IAAS). 
Sign up here
You can pay per month to run your code on one of their private virtual servers which they call 'Droplets'. Hence the digital ocean... 
Now to get started, let's set up a Docker Hub account …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Cartwright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a node.js app to digital ocean using Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/lukeecart/how-to-deploy-a-nodejs-app-to-digital-ocean-using-docker-al6</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/lukeecart/how-to-deploy-a-nodejs-app-to-digital-ocean-using-docker-al6"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T12:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article I'm going to assume you have a working Node js app locally. In a terminal you type in npm start and whoosh we have a working node app locally. However how do you deploy it to the internet? 
You could use Platforms as a Service (PAAS) sites like Heroku and you can link your github repo to Heroku and deploy from there. At the time of writing that costs $7/month (roughly £5/month)
But there is a more Devops pro like way which may be more customisable. 
Digital Ocean (the lowest version is $5/month or £3.65 /month) which also offers a PAAS or Infrastructure as a service (IAAS). 
Sign up here
You can pay per month to run your code on one of their private virtual servers which they call 'Droplets'. Hence the digital ocean... 
Now to get started, let's set up a Docker Hub account …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Cartwright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS + Express partie 4 : Créer un CRUD API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/nodejs-express-partie-4-creer-un-crud-api-4mn5</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericlecodeur/nodejs-express-partie-4-creer-un-crud-api-4mn5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T11:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voici une série d'articles qui vous permettra créer des applications backend avec NodeJS + Express.
Cette série est la suite de ma série sur les bases de NodeJS. Si vous n'avez pas les connaissances de bases en NodeJS lisez cette série d'abord : Introduction à NodeJS
Node.js est aujourd'hui un incontournable, il est donc essentiel pour un développeur de le maitriser.
Je vais donc publier un nouvel article environ au deux jours et petit à petit vous apprendrez tout ce qu'il y a à savoir sur Node.js + Espress
Pour ne rien manquer suivez moi sur twitter : https://twitter.com/EricLeCodeur
Maintenant que nous connaissons les concepts de base, il est temps de construire une véritable API CRUD (créer, lire, mettre à jour, supprimer)
Nous allons construire toutes ces routes CRUD :
Create: POST /ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Le Codeur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NodeJS + Express part 4: CRUD API]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ericchapman/nodejs-express-part-4-crud-api-37ef</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ericchapman/nodejs-express-part-4-crud-api-37ef"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T11:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a series of articles that will allow you to create backend applications with NodeJS + Express.
This series is the continuation of my series on the basics of NodeJS. If you don't have basic knowledge of NodeJS read this series first: Introduction to NodeJS
Node.js is today a must, so it is essential for a developer to master it.
So I will publish a new article about every two days and little by little you will learn everything there is to know about Node.js + Espress
To not miss anything follow me on twitter: https://twitter.com/EricTheCoder_
Now that we know the basics concept, it's time to build real CRUD API (create, read, update, delete)
We will build all those CRUD routes:
Create: POST /api/products
Read all: GET /api/products
Read: GET /api/product/1
Update: PUT /api/products/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric The Coder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can this makeshift vertical case keep the Pi cool?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bearlike/can-this-makeshift-vertical-case-keep-the-pi-cool-22ek</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bearlike/can-this-makeshift-vertical-case-keep-the-pi-cool-22ek"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T11:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published at thekrishna.in
The Raspberry Pi 4 offers an excellent upgrade to the preceding Pi 3B+, but keeping the new model from overheating can be a challenge. Users have tried many techniques to tackle this issue, from running the Pi in the open air to utilizing cooling rigs with fans attached. But as vertical cases are gaining popularity, can my DIY vertical case keep the Broadcom BCM2711B0 quad-core A72 SOC (system on chip)—cool? Spoiler alert: Surprisingly, yes.
First of all, why subject your Raspberry Pi to this level of stress? In the case of Raspberry Pi 4, the A72 CPU is so powerful that it can overheat if it doesn't have enough cooling. This results in the CPU being thermal throttled (governed) to reduce the power consumption and in turn reducing heat generation. The …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krishnakanth Alagiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount a Linux image on Windows and access to it from File Explorer with WSL2]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/sgtino/mount-a-linux-image-on-windows-and-access-to-it-from-file-explorer-with-wsl2-pkm</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/sgtino/mount-a-linux-image-on-windows-and-access-to-it-from-file-explorer-with-wsl2-pkm"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T10:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Requisites


A Windows system with WSL2 and an installed distro.
wget __linux_image_url

$ wsl

$ partx --show __linux_image_filepath__
NR  START     END SECTORS SIZE NAME UUID
 1   8192  532479  524288 256M      9730496b-01
 2 532480 3661823 3129344 1.5G      9730496b-02

$ bc
bc 1.07.1
Copyright 1991-1994, 1997, 1998, 2000, 2004, 2006, 2008, 2012-2017 Free Software Foundation, Inc.
This is free software with ABSOLUTELY NO WARRANTY.
For details type `warranty'.
> 532480 * 512
> 272629760
> quit

Create mounting point
$ sudo mkdir /mnt/other

Mount image
$ sudo mount -v -o offset=272629760 -t ext4 /_path_to_file_image/__filename__.img /mnt/other
mount: /dev/loop0 mounted on /mnt/other.

Check mounted image
$ ls /mnt/other

Open File Explorer
Type \\wsl$ in the address bar
Installed distros will be shown up. Click on it and navigate in the file system into the mounted path.
Access Linux filesystems in Windows and WSL 2
Access WSL2/Ubuntu Drive from File Explorer
How to mount Linux file system using WSL on Windows 11
Mounting a Raspberry Pi disk image under WSL 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefano Giraldi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure KDE Plasma with EndeavourOS in Laptops with dedicated GPU]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/mage1k99/how-to-configure-kde-plasma-with-endeavouros-in-laptops-with-dedicated-gpu-36m7</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/mage1k99/how-to-configure-kde-plasma-with-endeavouros-in-laptops-with-dedicated-gpu-36m7"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T08:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the issues faced by me when configuring KDE Plasma
Scaled Icons, Text, Stuffs in Display
Unable to use Function Keys in keyboard
Dual Booting
Installing deb files in arch
Enabling Bluetooth in KDE
Connecting to bluetooth audio device




mysql_install_db --user=mysql --ldata=/var/lib/mysql/

https://starbeamrainbowlabs.com/blog/article.php?article=posts/436-running-application-on-nvidia.html

I have to enable the bluetooth service by running sudo systemctl enable bluetooth.service

Start the service
sudo systemctl start bluetooth.service




  
  
  Connecting to Bluetooth





sudo pacman -S pulseaudio-bluetooth

Edit main.conf file




sudo vim /etc/bluetooth/main.conf

add these lines Enable=Source,Sink,Media,Socket under [general]


And reboot to see changes




fullscreen option under desktop effects in system settings seems to mess with it


VSCode git push fails to open ssh-askpass
yay -S x11-ssh-askpass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Magesh Babu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard Domains For Bug Bounties]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/wildcard-domains-for-bug-bounties-li0</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/therealdarkmage/wildcard-domains-for-bug-bounties-li0"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T07:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A private bug bounty program I am on had a scope increase recently.
*target.com

amass does not seem to have a feature that handles this sort of search, so I generated that list in bash/zsh:
for i in $(cat mylist.txt); do 
    echo $itarget.com >> potential-targets; 
done

This is for only one target. If your list containing multiple targets is in targets.txt, do:
for i in $(cat targets.txt); do 
    for j in $(cat mylist.txt); do
        echo $j$i >> potential-targets.txt; 
    done
done

This can yield a big file. To compress it after creation:
gzip -9 potential-targets.txt

To zip them during creation:
for i in $(cat targets.txt); do 
    for j in $(cat mylist.txt); do
        echo $j$i | gzip -9 >> potential-targets.txt.gz; 
    done
done

Once you've created the list of targets and zipped them, lets say we want to find all of the potentials yielding actual pages with content. Fire up httpx:
zcat potential-targets.txt.gz | \
httpx -no-fallback -o httpx.txt

Because this can take a long time, you might consider lowering the timeout, or using more or less threads:
zcat potential-targets.txt.gz | \
httpx -no-fallback -o httpx.txt -threads 200 -timeout 1

Lets say you didn't zip potential-targets. That's ok. httpx has an option to read directly from file. Everyone online is so obsessed with piping output because they think it is cool, but encouraging people to merely copy/paste data results in bad thinking and approach.
httpx -l potential-targets.txt -no-fallback \
-o httpx.txt -threads 200 -timeout 1

This will run for a long time. I was running it with default timeout and 8 threads on 300,000+ possible names and it had not completed after several hours. I'm running it now on a much larger namespace and even though it is taking a long time, I am already yielding new names that did not show up in amass. 
If this helps you at all, or you want to lurk for other content or whatever, here is my twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>darkmage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Ansible? A Tool to Automate Parts of Your Job]]></title>
        <id>61353325d6679a07b7d4318c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-ansible/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T20:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone, today we will talk about Ansible, a fantastic software tool that allows you to automate cross-platform computer support in a simple but effective way.  Table of Contents What is Ansible? How Does Ansible Work? Ansible's Architecture Plugins Modules Inventories Playbook Benefits of Using Ansible Why is Ansible so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Things to Keep in Mind about Auth]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alisaduncan/the-things-to-keep-in-mind-about-auth-25eg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alisaduncan/the-things-to-keep-in-mind-about-auth-25eg"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T18:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's National Cat day and Cybersecurity awareness month so I'm celebrating by reposting a blog post I wrote with permission from Okta Dev blog.
There's a lot of information out there about adding authentication to your app, which is helpful! But also overwhelming. It can be hard to find relevant and up-to-date information. Security best practices and technologies change, so refreshing your understanding and keeping up with current best practices is a good thing. Here are some notes I took while I reviewed my knowledge and applied my experience implementing auth.

If you're implementing authentication to a new application, the best practice is to use OAuth 2.0 with OpenID Connect (OIDC). The combination of OAuth 2.0 with OIDC provides consistency across many integration providers, standardi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alisa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular: The power of Async Pipe + Observables.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/saulodias/angular-the-power-of-async-pipe-observables-97m</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/saulodias/angular-the-power-of-async-pipe-observables-97m"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T18:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful features when creating Angular components is the Async Pipe. The greatest thing about it is that it allows you to take advantage of asynchronous rendering in your templates, but without having to worry about subscribing and unsubscribing from Observables.
import { Component, OnInit, OnDestroy } from '@angular/core';
import { of, Subject } from 'rxjs';
import { delay, startWith, takeUntil } from 'rxjs/operators';

@Component({
  selector: 'my-app',
  template: `
    <h1>Async example</h1> 
    <h2>Items</h2> 
    <ul>
      <li *ngFor="let item of items | async">{{item}}</li>
    </ul>
    <h2>Other Items</h2> 
    <ul>
      <li *ngFor="let other of otherItems">{{other}}</li>
    </ul>
  `,
  styleUrls: [ './app.component.css' ]
})
export class AppComponent implements OnInit, OnDestroy  {

  items = of([1, 2, 3])
    .pipe(
      delay(2000), 
      startWith(['...'])
    );

  // vs 

  otherItems: any[];
  private destroy$ = new Subject();
  ngOnInit() {
    of([1, 2, 3])
      .pipe(
        delay(2000),
        startWith(['...']),
        takeUntil(this.destroy$)
      )
      .subscribe(other  => this.otherItems = other)
  }
  ngOnDestroy() {
    this.destroy$.next();
    this.destroy$.complete();
  }
}


Check it out on Stackblitz.
As you can see, in the first example, we are rendering a list (items) using the async pipe in the HTML template. There is no need for the additional handling after the component is destroyed, which you can see is not the case for the other list otherItems.   That is simply because the async pipe is going to take care of that for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saulo Dias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Articles About Accessibility I’ve Saved Recently IV]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354581</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-articles-about-accessibility-ive-saved-recently-iv/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T18:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to designing accessible, WCAG-compliant focus indicators — Sara Soueidan says you can make more accessible focus outlines by doing your own, rather than leaving it to the browser — as long as you do it right. Deep dive! 
…
The post Some Articles About Accessibility I’ve Saved Recently IV appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security news weekly round-up - 29th October 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-29th-october-2021-2757</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/ziizium/security-news-weekly-round-up-29th-october-2021-2757"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T15:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


Hello, and welcome!
It's another Friday. Let's get down to business.
Most of the news that we'll review this week is about vulnerabilities and bugs.
Popular NPM Package Hijacked to Publish Crypto-mining Malware


As a developer, reading articles like this makes me think twice before downloading a package from NPM, but sometimes, you might need that package so bad, you'll forget about "security".
Excerpt from the article:
The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency on Friday warned of crypto-mining and password-stealing malware embedded in "UAParser.js," a popular JavaScript NPM library with over 6 million weekly downloads, days after the NPM repository moved to get rid of three rogue packages that were found to mimic the same library
Researcher Earns $2 Million…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Habdul Hazeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few simple ways to protect your digital privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/alexwilsonjr/a-few-simple-ways-to-protect-your-digital-privacy-5e3e</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/alexwilsonjr/a-few-simple-ways-to-protect-your-digital-privacy-5e3e"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T15:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people are concerned about how much personal information is stored on the internet and could be stolen or misused in today's reality. You're not the only one who feels this way. The issue of online privacy is crucial.
You can improve your online security against unwanted access to your data and privacy by taking several simple actions.
1 
Browse in private mode or use a browser, which doesn't store and send your data.
Browsing in private mode can let you avoid your browser's history from tracing. However, these private modes aren't entirely private. Your ISP can observe your surfing behavior even if you're using an incognito or private mode.
e.g.
https://www.brave.com/
https://www.beakerbrowser.com/
2 
Be cautious about where you click.
Phishing attempts are one of the ways how hackers can compromise your online privacy. They frequently accomplish this by sending fake emails that look like from banks, credit card companies, etc. 
3 
Change your search engine.
If you're like most web users, you use Google as your primary search engine.
e.g.
https://www.duckduckgo.com/
https://www.startpage.com/
4
Use dedicated proxy servers. 
A dedicated proxy server acts as a private and secure connection point between users and the internet. It's a server that acts as an "intermediary" between end-users and the web pages they browse on the internet. An IP address is used when a computer connects to the internet.
You can compare it to your home's street address. It directs data to the appropriate destination while also providing a return address for other devices.
A dedicated proxy server is a machine connected to the internet that has its unique IP address and serves as a disguise for your computer.
There are plenty of companies that provide such services, here is my personal top of the most reliable ones:
https://www.dslrentals.com/
https://www.proxy-hub.com/
Stay safe=)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexWilsonJr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vscode freezing on linux mint]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tomasszz/vscode-freezing-on-linux-mint-3o0j</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tomasszz/vscode-freezing-on-linux-mint-3o0j"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T15:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone. I've been fighting with VSCode for almost two weeks now.
VSC keeps freezing my whole system randomly while working.
FiveServer
Pretier
Aura Theme
Tabnine (free)
I've tried working with and without extensions, with the same result.
I've even tried to run VSC from console with --disable-gpu attr.
Freezing is random. Sometimes while typing, sometimes when switching windows between VSC and FF.
First thought there is a problem with FF but then it froze wit only VSC lunched :/
Does anyone had the same problem?
I really liked working with VSC.
I've tried Atom as a replacement, but not like it so much.
WEBSTORM is cool but it's overkill for me for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tomasszz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Social Login with OAuth to Make Your Apps More Secure]]></title>
        <id>6178555333422e07df364ee9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-social-login-with-oauth-for-more-secure-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many developers have written a demo login application at some point in time. We all start with the simple user defined ID and password. We then try to implement something like a social login with, say, Google or Twitter. There is, of course, a more complex process involved in setting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Your Own Automated Social Images With Resoc]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354296</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/create-your-own-automated-social-images-with-resoc/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T14:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a lot of talk about automated social images lately. GitHub has created its own. A WordPress plugin has been acquired by Jetpack. There is definitely interest! People like Ryan Filler and Zach Leatherman have implemented …
The post Create Your Own Automated Social Images With Resoc appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Bernard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Features of Angular Version 12 To Simplify Development Process]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rlogical/latest-features-of-angular-version-12-to-simplify-development-process-3f34</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rlogical/latest-features-of-angular-version-12-to-simplify-development-process-3f34"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T11:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's know here Top 10 Angular Version 12 Features for Streamlining Development Process
1. Ivy Everywhere
In Angular 12, View Engine is deprecated, and the community is working on ongoing delivery towards the goal of amalgamating the ecosystem of Angular on Ivy. Current libraries still use View Engine. But the library authors want to shift to Ivy. AngularJS development services become easy with Ivy as developers can compile all components independently and enhances development times.
2. Adios Protractor
The Angular team is working to decide Protractor’s future. They are currently exploring the given feedbacks in RFC. The team decided to remove it in further new tasks and more furnished alternatives along with third-party solutions. They are working with webdriverIO, TestCafe, and Cypress t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rlogical Techsoft Pvt Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🐧 Linux - Porque usar?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/tonybsilvadev/linux-porque-usar-1mc3</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/tonybsilvadev/linux-porque-usar-1mc3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T11:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[O Linux é um dos avanços tecnológicos mais importantes do século 21.
O Google roda milhares de servidores Linux para fornecer sua tecnologia de busca.
A adoção do Linux em todo o mundo criou uma demanda enorme pelo seu conhecimento, quase mandatório!
Basicamente, o Linux é um sistema operacional de um computador. 
Um sistema operacional é um software que gerencia o computador e permite que você execute aplicativos nele.
Eles devem ser capazes de:
1. Detectar e preparar o Hardware
2. Gerenciar processos
3. Gerenciar memória
4. Fornecer interfaces de usuário (nem sempre necessário)
5. Controlar sistema de arquivos
6. Acesso e autenticação de usuário
7. Oferecer utilitários administrativos
8. Iniciar serviços
9. Ferramentas de programação
Recursos avançados de Linux, frequentemente usados em …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Resources And Tools To Turbocharge Your Copywriting Skills]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/resources-tools-turbocharge-copywriting-skills/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop wasting time and effort writing copy that falls flat. Raise your copywriting game and boost your powers of persuasion with these rich and informative online resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Freya Giles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireplumber and pipewire in conflict (Arch linux)]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/_jhohannes/wireplumber-and-pipewire-in-conflict-arch-linux-1cif</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/_jhohannes/wireplumber-and-pipewire-in-conflict-arch-linux-1cif"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T09:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever try an update and run into this error in your terminal that 

This is all you have to do.
sudo pacman -S pipewire-media-session
then after that
sudo pacman -Syyu and try updating.
If questions are being asked, just be careful if you have to delete or replace any file.
You're welcome]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhohannes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular : BehaviorSubject]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/dipteekhd/angular-behaviorsubject-p1</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/dipteekhd/angular-behaviorsubject-p1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T07:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we know multiple components share the common data and always need updated shared data. In such scenarios most of the time BehaviorSubject is used which acts as a single store to hold updated shared data.
BehaviorSubject is both observer and type of observable.
BehaviorSubject always need an initial/default value.
Every observer on subscribe gets current value.
Current value is either latest value emitted by source observable using next() method or initial/default value.
Let’s implement BehaviorSubject to understand a concept better!
For e.g In order tracking app, display total items in cart and total items in wish list on UI in header and dashboard section based on user action.
Now we have three components -

Run Live
When user add items in the cart/wishList, total count needs to be updated in the header and dashboard component.
1.First create a BehaviorSubject in order service which holds the initial state of order count ,so that it can be used by any component.




3.When a user performs any action, call the next() method of BehaviorSubject. When the next() method gets called it will update current count with new count and notifies updated count to all observers(3 Components) who subscribed to source observable.

This way BehaviorSubject makes components communication more effective.
Thanks for reading! If you found this helpful please share!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>diptee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Tips to Find the Best Mobile App Development Company]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/vrinsoftaustralia/top-10-tips-to-find-the-best-mobile-app-development-company-53bg</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/vrinsoftaustralia/top-10-tips-to-find-the-best-mobile-app-development-company-53bg"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T07:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deciding to have a mobile App designed for your business is easy; the difficult part is how to settle on the best company to handle the task. There are many App development firms out there, but not all of them can build an App to your satisfaction. Owing to the weight of the impact that your mobile will have on your business, it’s essential to follow these guidelines when looking for a developer for your App.
Top 10 tips for choosing a Mobile App Development company
Do your homework thoroughly
Consider the expertise and skills of the developer
Consider the relevance to your niche
Hire a developer with expertise in device optimization
Price vs. Quality analysis
Go for the best App Development Company Strategy
Hire a future-focused App developer
Communication is key
Remember to get the Source Code
Vrinsoft is one of the leading mobile app developers in Sydney. You can rely on Vrinsoft to develop a stunning iOS and Android mobile application. This is an award-winning development company that works closely with many types of businesses including start-ups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vrinsoft Pty Ltd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing Data Through Angular Router State.]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/passing-data-through-angular-router-state-4add</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/bacancy_technology/passing-data-through-angular-router-state-4add"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T04:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might be aware of the Router State in Angular 7. The application developed by the angular will be divided into different parts. Those separate components help to understand the business login easily. 
Today we here share a tutorial about the Router State in Angular 7. And in the tutorial we get to know how to pass data from the Categories component to the Blog by Categories component. Our demo video will help you to understand it better.
After the demo video of the tutorial, we share some technical details that help you to understand and implement the technical parts of the tutorial at your projects.
We discussed the following points to understand Passing data through Angular router state.
Configure Angular Project
Angular Project Structure
Angular Generate Components
Configure Routes
Basic User Interface
Passing Data
Receiving Data
If you want to know more about how to Passing data through Angular routerstate, Read our article now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bacancy Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read Certificate from Key Vault from Azure App Service by using Managed Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kenakamu/read-certificate-from-key-vault-from-azure-app-service-by-using-managed-identity-afd</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kenakamu/read-certificate-from-key-vault-from-azure-app-service-by-using-managed-identity-afd"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T01:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often use Azure Web App and Key Vault together to protect keys/secrets/certificates.
To read certificates from Key Vault by using system assigned managed identity of App Service, there are several things to do.
From WebApp, enable managed identity.

From Key Vault access policy, assign certificate get permission (or any other additional required permissions) for the managed id.
From WebApp configurations menu, add WEBSITE_LOAD_USER_PROFILE application setting and set value to 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenichiro Nakamura</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Secure Your React.js Application]]></title>
        <id>617a55f533422e07df366544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-practices-for-security-of-your-react-js-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T23:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React.js is a scalable open-source JavaScript library and is one of the most commonly used front-end frameworks out there today.  It's dynamic and is easy to get started with if you want to create interactive web applications with reusable components. There are lots of reasons to use React.js]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Simplify Kubernetes Troubleshooting]]></title>
        <id>615c49eb0d91c9077974ca38</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-simplify-kubernetes-troubleshooting/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T22:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diagnosing and resolving issues in Kubernetes can be quite challenging. Kubernetes, after all, is a complex system.  Resolving problems even in small K8s clusters, nodes, and containers can be tricky, and it's often hard to identify and address issues. And an issue isn't even always easy to trace – it might]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okhsv and Okhsl]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354922</id>
        <link href="https://bottosson.github.io/posts/colorpicker/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T20:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an old Russian fable where Okhsv and Okhsl are on a rowboat and Okhsv says to Okhsl, “What are the known shortcomings of HSL and HSV color pickers in design applications?” I kid, I kid. But really, what …
The post Okhsv and Okhsl appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentest/networking project]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/medpaf/pentestnetworking-project-22ha</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/medpaf/pentestnetworking-project-22ha"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T19:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MedSec is a network and pentest utility that I developed so that I could perform different kinds of task using the same suite, instead of jumping from one tool to another.
Currently, this script can perform a good variety of tasks such as ifconfig, ping, traceroute, port scans (including SYN, TCP, UDP, ACK, comprehensive scan, host discovery (scan for up devices on a local network), MAC address detection (get MAC address of a host IP on a local network), banner grabbing, DNS checks (with geolocation information), WHOIS, subdomain enumeration, vulnerability reconnaissance, packet sniffing, MAC spoofing, IP spoofing, SYN flooding, deauth attack and brute-force attack (beta).
Other features are still being implemented. Future implementations may include WAF detection, DNS enumeration, traffic analysis, XSS vulnerability scanner, ARP cache poisoning, DNS cache poisoning, MAC flooding, ping of death, network disassociation attack (not deauth attack), OSINT, exploits, some automated tasks and others.
If you want to become a contributor, make a pull request or issue.
Waiting for your feedback. Kudos
Link to the repository: https://github.com/medpaf/medsec]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paulo Medeiros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decimal Place Value – Hundreds, Thousandths, and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>617a63cf33422e07df366730</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/decimal-place-value-hundreds-thousandths-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is a decimal place value? What is the difference between whole and decimal numbers?  In this quick guide, you'll learn the basics of the decimal place value and how it works.  Let's get started!  How number systems work Numbers are used for performing mathematical operations and for representing data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Sets – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>61795dda33422e07df365779</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-set-operations-explained-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner to Python, chances are you've come across lists. But have you heard about sets in Python? In this tutorial, we'll explore what sets are, how to create them, and the different operations you can use on them. What are sets in Python?In Python, sets are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vite + _____]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=355166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/vite-plus-blank/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vite, “Next Generation Frontend Tooling” from Evan You, has been capturing a lot of attention. I’ve heard rave reviews from developers, even in private chats (you gotta try this!). Being from Evan, Vite works great with Vue, …
The post Vite + _____ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Postgres Docker Container on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>6178541d33422e07df364eba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-a-postgres-docker-container-on-oracle-cloud-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will show you how I quickly set up and ran a Docker container for free on Oracle Cloud Infrastructure.  In short, I used a VM in the Always Free Tier of OCI, and for a side project I set up a dockerised Postgres database. Let's get]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn HTML and CSS in Spanish – Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>61784ef033422e07df364e34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-html-and-css-in-spanish-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T15:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! If you speak Spanish and you want you learn HTML and CSS, you're in the right place. In this article, you will find a brief introduction to the basics of HTML and CSS. Then you will find a free 5-hour course on HTML and CSS on our Spanish YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ES6 Features in React]]></title>
        <id>61728f9ed48e1707b6d79b46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-es6-javascript-features-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many JavaScript frameworks use ES6 features. So to help you learn these handy features, I'll introduce you to them and then show you how to apply them in React.js.  Here are the ES6 features we'll cover in this guide: ModulesDestructuringSpread OperatorArrow functionsTemplate LiteralsAll the examples we'll see here are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merge Conflicts: What They Are and How to Deal with Them​]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354389</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/merge-conflicts-what-they-are-and-how-to-deal-with-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T14:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merge conflicts... Nobody likes them. Some of us even fear them. But they are a fact of life when you're working with Git, especially when you're teaming up with other developers. In most cases, merge conflicts aren't as scary as you might think. In this fourth part of our “Advanced Git” series we'll talk about when they can happen, what they actually are, and how to solve them.
The post Merge Conflicts: What They Are and How to Deal with Them​ appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tobias Günther</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an Angular Data Grid With Filtering]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354782</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/building-an-angular-data-grid-with-filtering/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T14:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Kendo UI makes it possible to go from a basic idea to a full-fledged app, thanks to a massive component library. We’re talking well over 100 components that are ready for you to drop …
The post Building an Angular Data Grid With Filtering appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Project: Create a PuzzleCam Game]]></title>
        <id>61797e0833422e07df365c36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-project-create-a-puzzlecam-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T13:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a game is a great way to improve your JavaScript skills. We just published a JavaScript tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a puzzle game that gets an image for the puzzle from your computer's camera. Radu Mariescu-Istodor developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS in Angular: from beginner to advanced beginner]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/kamilbugnokrk/rxjs-in-angular-from-beginner-to-advanced-beginner-78c</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/kamilbugnokrk/rxjs-in-angular-from-beginner-to-advanced-beginner-78c"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T12:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RxJS in Angular: from beginner to advanced beginner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamil Bugno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Amazon Product Scraper With Node.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-amazon-product-scraper-nodejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealth of data that Amazon holds can make a huge difference when you’re designing a product or hunting for a bargain. But, how can a developer get that data? Simple, by using a web scraper. Here’s how to build your data extraction bot with Node.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Robert Sfichi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Alarm System using a Bipolar Junction Transistor Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/eyuelberga/security-alarm-system-using-a-bipolar-junction-transistor-switch-2eb4</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/eyuelberga/security-alarm-system-using-a-bipolar-junction-transistor-switch-2eb4"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T06:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction


The security alarm system will use a bipolar junction transistor switch to detect security problems. Theft attempt and other security threats can be controlled by using this simple circuit.
For the purpose of this application, we will design a security system for one room in a house. The sensor used for each opening can be either a mechanical switch, a magnetically operated switch, or an optical sensor. Detection of an intrusion can be used to initiate an audible alarm signal. 
We will be using a mechanical switch as our sensor and use a transistor as a NOT gate, so that when there is an open switch in our room a transistor will show a signal that an intruder has entered.
Resistor
Transistor
Buzzer
Voltage source

Room sensor is normally in a closed position and it is connected to a DC voltage source. When a door is open it creates an open circuit.


Transistor switches are used for high power devices such as
The areas of operation for Transistor switch are known as the Saturation Region and the Cut-Off Region.
Cut-off Region: here there is a large depletion layer


Saturation Region: here the depletion layer is as




  
  
  NOT Gate Transistor


A NOT gate simply inverts its input. If the input is high, the output is low, and if the input is low, the output is high

The operation of this circuit is simple. The input is connected through resistor R2 to the transistor’s
When voltage is present at the input, the transistor turns on, allowing current to flow through the collector-emitter circuit directly to ground. This ground path creates a shortcut that bypasses the output, which causes the output to go low.
We run our simulation with a voltmeter connected to the output, in place of the buzzer .

In the normal state, the switch will be closed.

When intrusion happens, the switch will open and the alarm (buzzer) will go off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eyuel Berga Woldemichael</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky Definition Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354777</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sticky-definition-lists/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T23:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ran across this 30 seconds of code website the other day, and they have a CSS section which is really good! The first example snippet I looked at was this “floating section headers” example, reminding me yet again how …
The post Sticky Definition Lists appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement and Style the Dialog Element]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354857</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-implement-and-style-the-dialog-element/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T20:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look from Christian Kozalla on the <dialog> HTML element and using it to create a nice-looking and accessible modal. 
CodePen Embed Fallback
I’m attracted to the <dialog> element as it’s one of those “you get a lot for free” …
The post How to Implement and Style the Dialog Element appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encrypt/decrypt data with .NET 6 and Azure Key Vault]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/425show/encryptdecrypt-data-with-net-6-and-azure-key-vault-oak</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/425show/encryptdecrypt-data-with-net-6-and-azure-key-vault-oak"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T18:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security is hard. It's hard because there are so many things that can go wrong along the way. Attackers only need to find one small gap to make it through whereas developers and IT Pros have to think about all the possible attack permutations and potential security vulnerabilities every step of the way. That's why we talk about "security in layers" when it comes to building systems that handle sensitive data. And unless you're creating static marketing pages, it's very likely that your solution will need to work with some data.
If you're running on Azure (or other cloud providers) there are tools to help you keep your data secure both at rest and in transit. This is great document that can help you get a high level overview of Azure data security and encryption. And there are many more too…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christos Matskas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Salesforce Using a Client Written In Angular]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/johnjvester/leveraging-salesforce-using-a-client-written-in-angular-4l66</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/johnjvester/leveraging-salesforce-using-a-client-written-in-angular-4l66"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T16:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the “Leveraging Salesforce Using Spring Boot” article, I navigated the course for introducing a Spring Boot service that would leverage the well-established Salesforce RESTful API. The goal of this service was to act as a middleware layer; that way, clients not written in Salesforce could retrieve and update contact data stored in Salesforce. This backend service implemented its own caching layer to provide a faster response time and also cut down on the number of times Salesforce needed to be called.
In “Leveraging Salesforce Using a Client Written In Svelte,” I introduced a simple client written in Svelte, which made it possible to update the Salesforce data using an inline editor—again, without actually using the Salesforce client.
The “Leveraging Salesforce Using a Client Written In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Vester</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A solution to rEFInd unable to load using shim when Secure Boot is enabled]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/hollowman6/a-solution-to-refind-unable-to-load-using-shim-when-secure-boot-is-enabled-1e8l</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/hollowman6/a-solution-to-refind-unable-to-load-using-shim-when-secure-boot-is-enabled-1e8l"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T15:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background


Ubuntu 21.10 can load on my computer through secure boot, and the shim version is 15.4. Then refer to the official tutorial, I installed rEFInd v0.13.2 (the latest version when I posted this blog) via PPA in Ubuntu 21.10. However, when I restart the system and load rEFInd, it always fails with the message Verification failed:(0x1A)Security Violation. I'm sure that both refind_local.cer and refind.cer under the EFI/refind/keys/ have been enrolled through MokManager (Although only refind_local.cer is needed through PPA installation).
From this post, I got that rEFInd currently (v0.13.2) lacks the .sbat section. For shim 15.3 and later versions, SBAT is mandatory, resulting in failure to start rEFInd.
The post also indicates that the author of rEFInd is currently studying how to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hollow Man</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Vue Components With Cypress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353842</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/testing-vue-components-with-cypress/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T14:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cypress is an automated test runner for browser-based applications and pages. I’ve used it for years to write end-to-end tests for web projects, and was happy to see recently that individual component testing had come to Cypress. I work on …
The post Testing Vue Components With Cypress appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Noonan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Manage Encryption at Scale?]]></title>
        <id>https://dev.to/rohitjmathew/how-to-manage-encryption-at-scale-c1f</id>
        <link href="https://dev.to/rohitjmathew/how-to-manage-encryption-at-scale-c1f"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T11:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently at work, I came across an interesting method to handle encryption at scale called envelope encryption. 
First of all, it increases security and helps you ease out the management of encryption keys. But it's also a highly recommended pattern by PCI-DSS (Security Standard for Credit Card Processing) and results in much stronger data privacy and data protection of Personally Identifiable Information (PII). 
When we think of data there are 3 places we can think of encrypting data:
At Rest - On hardware storage devices like on a disk or in your devices 
In Transit - In moving data between different locations like server to server through API calls
In Use - While it's being used by a server (New concept and still being researched)
We will be dealing primarily with encryption at rest and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Jacob Mathew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking In Mobile UX Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/eye-tracking-mobile-ux-research/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to technology, eye-tracking has become more accessible to UX research as it allows researchers to get insights about users ’visual attention. This article explores the latest trends in the eye-tracking market and how the methodology can be included in the UX researcher’s toolbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mariana Macedo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Browser-Specific URL Schemes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354365</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-browser-specific-url-schemes/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T20:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve covered URL schemes: 
A URL Scheme is like “http://…” or “ftp://…”. Those seem like a very low-level concept that you don’t have much control over, but actually, you do!
I’d call it non-trivial, but developers can register new …
The post On Browser-Specific URL Schemes appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-Page Filtered Search With Vanilla JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353747</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/in-page-filtered-search-with-vanilla-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T14:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a page that includes a lot of information, it’s a good idea to let users search for what they might be looking for. I’m not talking about searching a database or even searching JSON data — I’m …
The post In-Page Filtered Search With Vanilla JavaScript appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hilman Ramadhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Userwell is for Managing Customer Feedback]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353621</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/userwell-is-for-managing-customer-feedback/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T14:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Building products for users is a balance between your vision of what your product can do for them, and refining that vision based on their feedback. If you’re really a customer-focused company, you’re listening. …
The post Userwell is for Managing Customer Feedback appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Next.js Applications With Nx]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/optimizing-nextjs-applications-nx/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nx is a build framework that facilitates optimization, efficient scaling of applications, and other features such as shared libraries and components. In this article, we will be looking at how we can effectively scale Next.js applications by using Nx.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Melvin Kosisochukwu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Greatest CSS Tricks Vol. I eBook (PDF and EPUB)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353728</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-greatest-css-tricks-vol-i-ebook-pdf-and-epub/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T19:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I wrote the “book” The Greatest CSS Tricks Vol. I, I put “book” in quotes because there wasn’t anything terribly book-like about it. The only way you could read it was online, logged into this website, with an …
The post The Greatest CSS Tricks Vol. I eBook (PDF and EPUB) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Semantics of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=353496</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-semantics-of-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T14:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past year has seen a healthy debate around the term ‘Jamstack’ as the definition gets stretched to include new use cases. I recently posted my take on a Jamstack definition in “Static vs. Dynamic vs. Jamstack: Where’s The Line?”…
The post The Semantics of Jamstack appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Neumegen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep Dive Into object-fit And background-size In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/object-fit-background-size-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will go through how `object-fit` and `background-size` work, when we can use them, and why, along with some practical use cases and recommendations. Let’s dive in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To Quasar Framework: Building Cross-Platform Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/introduction-quasar-framework-cross-platform-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quasar is an open-source Vue.js-based cross-platform framework that allows you, as a developer, to easily build apps for both desktop and mobile using technologies such as Cordova and Electron and writing your code once. The app we’ll build will store and get its data from Firebase, meaning that we will also be seeing how to use Firebase in Quasar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joel Olawanle)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Include (a Certain HTML element within another Certain HTML Element)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=354567</id>
        <link href="https://caninclude.glitch.me/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T17:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A single-serving website from Alexander Vishnyakov for testing if it’s valid to put any particular HTML element within another type of HTML element. Kinda neat to have a quick reference for this.
Some combinations feel fairly obvious: can you put …
The post Can Include (a Certain HTML element within another Certain HTML Element) appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Real-Time Multi-User Game From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/real-time-multi-user-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article highlights the process, technical decisions and lessons learned behind building the real-time game Autowuzzler. Learn how to share game state across multiple clients in real-time with Colyseus, do physics calculations with Matter.js, store data in Supabase.io and build the front-end with SvelteKit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Martin Grubinger)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Respecting Users’ Motion Preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/respecting-users-motion-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The `prefers-reduced-motion` media query has excellent support in all modern browsers going back a couple of years. In this article, Michelle Barker explains why there’s no reason not to use it today to make your sites more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The SSG I’ve Always Wanted: An 11ty, Vite And JAM Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-ssg-11ty-vite-jam-sandwich/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, Ben Holmes set out to do what just about every web developer does each year: rebuild his personal site. In this article, he shares his story of how he set out to build his own build pipeline from absolute ground zero and created “Slinkity”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ben Holmes)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building An API With Gatsby Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/building-api-gatsby-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Paul Scanlon explains how to build an API by using Gatsby Functions and what you need to keep in mind when deploying it to Gatsby Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Scanlon)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 42 With Jeff Smith: What Is DevOps?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/smashing-podcast-episode-42/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about DevOps. What is it, and is it a string to add to your web development bow? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeff Smith to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving CLS Issues In A Next.js-Powered E-Commerce Website (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/nextjs-ecommerce-cls-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cumulative Layout Shift is one of the hardest core web vital to debug. In this article, we go through different tools to investigate CLS, when to use them(and when not), and solutions to some of the CLS issues we faced in our Next.js-based e-commerce website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Arijit Mondal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple But Effective Mental Health Routine For Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/effective-mental-health-routine-programmers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look at why taking care of our work-life balance is important, how to develop a simple and effective mental health routine, and the most common and efficient techniques you can use to make your custom routine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dave Oscar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.11.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.11.3"/>
        <updated>2021-10-16T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: broken links in documentation
Chore: Dependency updates
Thank you: @hirdot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips And Tricks For Evaluating UX/UI Designers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/tips-tricks-evaluating-ux-ui-designers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers may start using your app because you offer a unique product, but user experience is what makes them stay. For that, you need excellent UX designers, and the know-how to spot them when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nataliya Sambir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart CSS Solutions For Common UI Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/modern-css-solutions-for-common-problems/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-14T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing CSS has probably never been more fun and exciting than it is today. In this post we’ll take a look at common problems and use cases we all have to face in our work and how to solve them with modern CSS. If you’re interested, we’ve also just recently covered [CSS auditing tools](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-auditing-tools/), [CSS generators](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/03/css-generators/), [front-end boilerplates](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/) and [VS code extensions](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/useful-vs-code-extensions-web-developers/) — you might find them useful, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Live Workshops On Front-End & UX (Oct 2021&ndash;Jan 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/new-smashing-online-workshops-oct-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like a good interface design challenge? What about accessibility testing and design systems? Or maybe Next.js and advanced CSS? With our new online workshops on front-end & design, we cover all of it. Ah, and [here's what our workshops are like](https://vimeo.com/616485526).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful React APIs For Building Flexible Components With TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/react-apis-building-flexible-components-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[React with JSX is a fantastic tool for making easy-to-use components. Typescript components make it an absolute pleasure for developers to integrate your components into their apps and explore your APIs. Learn about three lesser-known React APIs that can take your components to the next level, and help you build even better React Components in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gaurav Khanna)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bridging The Gap Between Designers And Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/bridging-gap-between-designers-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UXPin has recently launched a new feature called “Merge”. This tool aims to break through the chasms of design and development, all while improving the agility and quality our teams expect. This new technology may cause some rethink on how the whole design team and engineering team collaborates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matthew Talebi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Autofill Dark Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/autofill-dark-pattern/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A “dark pattern” is a deceptive UX pattern that tricks users into doing things they may not really want to do. In this article, Alvaro Montoro does a little experiment to find out how much privacy is taken away from users across three different browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Montoro)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable CSS Animation In Vue With AnimXYZ]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/composable-css-animation-vue-animxyz/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most animation libraries like GSAP and Framer Motion are built purely with JavaScript or TypeScript, unlike AnimXYZ, which is labelled “the first composable CSS animation toolkit”, built mainly with SCSS While a simple library, it can be used to achieve a lot of awesome animation on the web in a short amount of time and little code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ejiro Asiuwhu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Static-First MadLib Generator With Portable Text And Netlify On-Demand Builder Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/static-first-madlib-generator-portable-text-netlify-builder-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be building an interactive fiction experience in which a user can insert words that match parts of speech given by the content creator. Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: COVID-19 Icon Set (56 Icons, AI, EPS, SVG, PNG)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/freebie-coronavirus-icon-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies/) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, every designer will be able to find their own use case and contribute to saving lives. Free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To CSS Debugging]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/guide-debugging-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging in CSS means figuring out what might be the problem when you have unexpected layout results. We’ll look at a few categories bugs often fit into, see how we can evaluate the situation, and explore techniques that help prevent these bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Testing A Serverless API (API Gateway And Lambda)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/local-testing-serverless-api-gateway-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-05T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever struggled with testing cloud services locally? Specifically, have you ever struggled with locally testing an API that uses API Gateway and Lambda, with the Serverless framework, on AWS? In this article, Tom Hudson shares a quick overview of how easy it is to quickly set up your project to test locally before deploying to AWS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hudson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build An Expandable Accessible Gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/10/build-expandable-accessible-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be looking at how to set up a gallery that is expandable as well as accessible with a few tips and tricks along the way. Let’s get started!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Silvestar Bistrović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>